<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-06-20T20:14:02.215Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Years of Innovation: Student developers solving real-world problems using Google tech]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:13:57.904Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Developer Student Clubs globally are tackling the United Nations' Sustainable Development Goals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tor Browser 13.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979177/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979177/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
13.5 of the privacy-focused Tor browser has been released.


	Regular readers of our release posts will know that for the past
	two years we've been gradually increasing our capacity to not only
	maintain, but bring tangible improvements to Tor Browser for
	Android. In that respect, Tor Browser 13.5 feels like a milestone:
	in addition to the dozens of bug fixes and minor improvements noted
	in the changelog below, this release features major changes to
	Android's connection experience in preparation for the future
	addition of Connection Assist, including full access to Settings
	before connecting and a new, permanent home for Tor logs.


The release also features desktop user-interface improvements and enhanced
fingerprinting protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A capability set for user namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978846/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978846/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User namespaces in Linux create an
environment in which all privileges are granted, but their effect is
contained within the namespace; they have become an important tool for the
implementation of containers.  They have also become a significant source
of worries for people who do not like the increased attack surface they
create for the kernel.  Various attempts have been made to restrict that
attack surface over the years; the latest is user namespace
capabilities, posted by Jonathan Calmels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Updates to pahole]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978727/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978727/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arnaldo Carvalho de Melo spoke at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit
about his work on

Poke-a-hole (pahole),
a program that has expanded greatly over the years, but which was relevant to the
BPF track because it produces BPF Type Format (BTF) information from DWARF
debugging information. He covered some small changes to the program, and then
went into detail about the new support for data-type profiling. His
slides include
several examples.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Naptime: Evaluating Offensive Security Capabilities of Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/project-naptime.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/project-naptime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=DFQxm4rd7fRHgM9OTejWVT5Vho6BE7M80rHXEVKqXWckOnM5xqt2DUw2f5lNcrroidEvLLi3H0BPvcL7ypcd6c76ZZ8PqJ7WOKqynLI9-xo);.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-8>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}ol.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}li.li-bullet-0:before{margin-left:-18pt;white-space:nowrap;display:inline-block;min-width:18pt}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}ol.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0 0}ul.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-7{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979153/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979153/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (ghostscript and thunderbird), Debian (chromium, composer, libndp, and sendmail), Fedora (composer), Mageia (flatpak and python-scikit-learn), Red Hat (curl, ghostscript, and thunderbird), SUSE (hdf5 and opencc), and Ubuntu (gdb and php7.4, php8.1, php8.2, php8.3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stateful and reactive stream processing applications with Apache Kafka, Quarkus, and Angular on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>c4289561-6575-449d-8709-a47336231e6a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/20/stateful-and-reactive-stream-processing-applications-apache-kafka-quarkus-and"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this in-depth article, you're going to learn how to build an end-to-end reactive stream processing application using Apache Kafka as an event streaming platform, Quarkus for your backend, and a frontend written in Angular. In the end, you'll deploy all three containerized applications on the Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift.
A first look at the final result—a colorful live dashboard tracking the usage of emojis in public 🐘 Mastodon 🐘 posts (a.k.a., toots)—should give you a rough idea of what you may expect throughout this article. See Figure 1.



  
        


        Fig. 1 - Emoji Tracker Live Dashboard
  

Figure 1: Emoji tracker live dashboard.

Let's dive right in.
Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift
All applications which are part of the complete demo scenario are su…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hans-Peter Grahsl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to find vulnerabilities across millions of Quay.io images]]></title>
        <id>81b44d70-0b3f-40d6-8083-d64f28ab4fb9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/20/how-find-vulnerabilities-across-millions-quayio-images"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Quay.io was the first private container registry on the internet and began serving images back in 2013. Today, it hosts millions of images for hundreds of thousands of critical customer workloads, including Red Hat’s own product catalog.
One of the marquee features of Quay.io is free security scanning for any image that we host. This happens automatically as soon as you push an image to Quay.io. Not only does it scan your image at upload time, it also provides an up-to-date view of your vulnerabilities, no matter how long ago you pushed it. There is no need to ask Quay.io to rescan your image—that information is available whenever you request it. 
This is critical, as container images typically only gather more and more vulnerabilities as they age. An old container image isn’t alwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Dettelback</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[성심당 코레일 월세 4억 원의 비밀.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110519</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110519"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T06:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대전하면 성심당 떠올리는 사람들 많다. 오늘은 두 가지 이야기를 해보자. 코레일이 성심당 대전역사점 임대료를 현재 1억 원에서 4억 원으로 올려 받겠다고 해서 논란이다. 코레일 임대사업자 입찰, 지금까지 5차 유찰. 성심당 대전역에서 나갈까? 지금도 월 1억씩 내는데, 왜 이렇게 임대료 올랐나. 원칙이라고 해도… 돈 벌수록 버티기 어렵다. 부산역 입점했던 삼진어묵도 방 뺐다. 매출과 월세가 비례: 다른...
The post 성심당 코레일 월세 4억 원의 비밀. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 20, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978238/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978238/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T03:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 20, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블로그 안내]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/2024-06-19/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/2024-06-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T23:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이런저런 글을 올리는 공간입니다.

RSS 피드
사는...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “숨 쉬는 건 범죄가 아니다”…노숙도 마찬가지? 간단치 않은 사정들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79247</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/19/npsbs_scotushomeless/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsbs_scotushomeless"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 1일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 미국 연방 대법원은 6월 말이면 회기를 마치고 여름 휴지기에 들어갑니다. 지난주가 이번 회기에 예정된 구두변론을 진행하는 마지막 주였습니다. 5월은 대법관들이 진정인과 피진정인 또는 원고와 피고의 주장을 추가로 듣는 일 없이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[출구전략 없는 갈등, 이것은 민주주의가 아니다: 슬로우레터 6월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110486</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110486"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[북한과 러시아의 밀착, “침략당하면 상호 지원.” ‘지각 대장’ 푸틴. 쟁점과 현안. “인구 비상사태.” 복지가 부족해서 애 안 낳을까. 무기한 휴진? “처음 듣는 이야기.” 대통령 거부권 포기할 수 있나. 더 깊게 읽기. 한국이 가장 먹고 살기 힘들다. 쿠팡의 네 가지 거짓말. 다르게 읽기. 김건희가 변수다. 선을 넘는 이복현. 당원 중심 정당의 함정. 해법과 대안. 지역 대도시에...
The post 출구전략 없는 갈등, 이것은 민주주의가 아니다: 슬로우레터 6월20일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] How free software hijacked Philip Hazel's life]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978463/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978463/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T18:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philip Hazel was 51 when he began the Exim message transfer agent (MTA)
project in 1995, which
led to the Perl-Compatible Regular
Expressions (PRCE) project in 1998. At 80,
he's maintained PCRE, and its successor PCRE2, for more than 27
years. For those doing the math, that's a year longer than LWN has
been in publication. Exim maintenance was handed off around the time
of his retirement in 2007. Now, he is ready to hand off PCRE2 as well,
if a successor can be found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mate 1.28 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978946/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978946/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.28 of the MATE Desktop
has been released.
See the announcement for a full list of improvements and bug fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Libgcrypt 1.11.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978939/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978939/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 1.11.0 of Libgcrypt, a general-purpose library of
cryptographic building blocks, has been released by the GnuPG project:


This release starts a new stable branch of Libgcrypt with full API and
ABI compatibility to the 1.10 series.  Over the last years Jussi
Kivilinna put again a lot of work into speeding up the algorithms for
many commonly used CPUs.  Niibe-san implemented new APIs and algorithms
and also integrated quantum-resistant encryption algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Capturing stack traces asynchronously with BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978736/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978736/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T14:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrii Nakryiko led a session at
the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit giving
a look into the APIs for capturing stack traces
using BPF, and how the APIs could be made more useful. BPF programs can capture the
current stack trace of a running process, including the portion in the kernel
during execution of a system call, which can be useful for diagnosing
performance problems, among other things. But there are substantial problems with
the existing API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] How kernel CVE numbers are assigned]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978711/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978711/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T13:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been four months since Greg
Kroah-Hartman and MITRE
announced that the Linux kernel project had become its own CVE Numbering
Authority (CNA).  Since then, the Linux CNA Team has developed workflows
and mechanisms to help manage the various tasks associated with this
challenge.  There does however, appear to be a lack of understanding among
community members of the processes and rules the team have been working
within.  The principal aim of this article, written by a member of the
Linux kernel CNA team, is to clarify how the team works and how kernel CVE
numbers are assigned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978907/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978907/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T13:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (container-tools, firefox, and flatpak), Debian (composer, roundcube, and thunderbird), Fedora (kitty and webkitgtk), Oracle (container-tools and flatpak), Red Hat (flatpak and java-1.8.0-ibm), SUSE (gdcm, gdk-pixbuf, libarchive, libzypp, zypper, ntfs-3g_ntfsprogs, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, podman, python-Werkzeug, and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (git, linux-hwe-6.5, mariadb, mariadb-10.6, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing sensor capabilities: test characterization and linearization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482525</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/optimizing-sensor-capabilities-test-characterization-and-linearization/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The benefits of optimizing sensors are enormous and include improving their accuracy, range, and sensitivity. Characterizing and linearizing sensors can help integrate them into larger...
The post Optimizing sensor capabilities: test characterization and linearization appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernard Ang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡의 거짓말]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110411</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110411"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T08:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[0. 극단적 요약 (1분) “쿠팡은 모험가의 도전과 성공을 훔친다” (권호현) 온라인플랫폼공정화법(온플법) 제정이 필요한 이유다. 1. PB상품으로 물가 안정에 기여? 쿠팡이 PB 상품으로 물가 안정에 기여했다고요? 거짓말입니다. 쿠팡은 내부 보고 문건에서 자체 분석하고 있습니다. (쿠팡이 랭킹 조작이나 리뷰 조작 등을 중단할 경우) “1) 소비자 1인당 지출 2) 입점업체 평균 판매가 3) 쿠팡 PB 등 자체 상품...
The post 쿠팡의 거짓말 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>권호현</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/19, 엔비디아 시총 1위 등극을 보며]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595087</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595087/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%9c%ec%b4%9d-1%ec%9c%84-%eb%93%b1%ea%b7%b9"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T08:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation topology considerations]]></title>
        <id>823cacac-3fd9-41b3-977d-11eb58000cb0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/19/red-hat-openshift-data-foundation-topology-considerations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many different factors to consider when using Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation to set up a storage cluster. This article dives into some specifics to consider when building a production-grade resilient scalable deployment of OpenShift Data Foundation. We'll need to dig into the following points to design and build out a suitable deployment architecture:

What does the underlying platform environment look like in terms of architecture/topology/design?
What underlying storage is available and how is that presented?
Replication options.

To start, if you're new to OpenShift Data Foundation, please see the architecture documentation to get a high level understanding of what the operator provides and is doing. Under the covers, OpenShift Data Foundation uses Rook and Ceph. If you are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Force, Travis Nielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/19, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595078</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595078/6-19-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T01:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“얻다 대고 애완견인가”, 언론의 반발: 슬로우레터 6월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110374</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110374"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[의료 대란, 해결 의지가 없다. 쟁점과 현안. 방송3법과 방통위법 과방위 통과. “언론 스스로 증명하라.” 저널리즘의 개(犬) 사분면. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명 일극 체제가 완성됐다. 민주당의 속도전. 과반 의석으로 못할 게 뭐냐는 질문에 대한 답변. 국민의힘 전당대회는 반윤 vs 비윤. 다르게 읽기. 창의력은 2위, 자신감은 49위. 김만배 인터뷰 배후가 김만배? 내년 집값? 해법과 대안. 엑스포 외교...
The post “얻다 대고 애완견인가”, 언론의 반발: 슬로우레터 6월19일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I _____ hate arrays in C++!]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1134/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1134/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or why I think developers need to know about them but should not use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Rust: Hello World!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482510</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-rust-hello-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series on Embedded Rust, we will look at Rust syntax, resources, and design methodologies that can be applied to embedded systems. It’s a...
The post Embedded Rust: Hello World! appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How It’s Made: AI Roadtrip, a Pixel Campaign Powered by Generative AI and Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-ai-roadtrip-a-pixel-campaign-powered-by-generative-ai-and-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-ai-roadtrip-a-pixel-campaign-powered-by-generative-ai-and-fans/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:14:31.967Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Phones Forever: AI Roadtrip is our first experiment in using generative AI to put fans in the driver's seat and bring characters to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software-defined radar enables hardware to be customized for ADAS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482512</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/software-defined-radar-enables-hardware-to-be-customized-for-adas/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbe SDR architecture is said to offer OEMs and Tier 1s full control over key radar parameters and operation modes, enabling customized performance and optimized operations in various driving scenarios.
The post Software-defined radar enables hardware to be customized for ADAS appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Adding a JIT compiler to CPython]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977855/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977855/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the big-ticket items for the upcoming Python 3.13 release is an experimental just-in-time (JIT) compiler for the language;
the other is, of course, the removal of the 
global interpreter lock (GIL), which is also an experiment.  Brandt
Bucher is a member of the Faster CPython project, which is
working on making the reference implementation of the language faster via a
variety of techniques.  Last year at PyCon, he gave a talk about the specializing adaptive
interpreter; at PyCon 2024 in Pittsburgh, he described the work he and others have been doing
to add a copy-and-patch JIT compiler to CPython.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] BPF tracing performance]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978335/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978335/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the final day of the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, the BPF track
opened with a series of sessions on improving the performance and
flexibility of probes and other performance-monitoring tools, in the kernel and in
user space. Jiri Olsa led two sessions about different aspects of probes:
making the API for BPF programs attached to a probe more flexible, and making
user-space probes more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma 6.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978806/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978806/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.1 of
the Plasma desktop environment has been released.


	Plasma 6 hits its stride with version 6.1. While Plasma 6.0 was all
	about getting the migration to the underlying Qt 6 frameworks
	correct (and what a massive job that was), 6.1 is where developers
	start implementing the features that will take you desktop to a new
	level.


Enhancements include better remote-desktop support, improved customization,
persistent apps, smoother animation under Wayland, and more; see the
changelog for the full list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978804/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978804/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (php7.3), Fedora (galera, ghostscript, and mariadb), Mageia (cups, iperf, and libndp), Oracle (firefox and flatpak), Red Hat (container-tools:rhel8, Firefox, firefox, and flatpak), SUSE (booth, bouncycastle, firefox, ghostscript, less, libaom, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, podman, python-Authlib, python-requests, python-Werkzeug, webkit2gtk3, and xdg-desktop-portal), and Ubuntu (ghostscript, ruby-rack, ruby2.7, ruby3.0, ruby3.1, ruby3.2, and sssd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering motor control: functional safety]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482507</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mastering-motor-control-functional-safety/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T11:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By integrating robust safety measures and compliance with established safety standards, we can ensure that motor control systems not only perform efficiently but also uphold...
The post Mastering motor control: functional safety appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Radonic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat UBI container images]]></title>
        <id>a42ea76d-fc6e-4a7b-b799-779a62bed8de</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/18/build-applications-paketo-buildpacks-and-red-hat-ubi-container-images"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the growth in the use of containers, the need to bundle your application into a container has never been stronger. Many Red Hat customers will be familiar with Source-to-Image (S2I) as an easy way to build container images from application source code. While S2I is a convenient way to build images on Red Hat OpenShift, Red Hat works to support our customers when using a variety of approaches, and we’ve recently seen an increasing interest in building applications using Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) Buildpacks.  
This is the first in a 5-part series of articles on building your applications with C and UBI. The series will include:

Building applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat UBI container images (this post)
Running applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson, Ozzy Osborne, Costas Papastathis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding support for s390x in LLD, the LLVM linker]]></title>
        <id>0dbb476d-69f9-44cf-b4a6-9481dff86734</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/18/adding-support-s390x-lld-llvm-linker"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLD is a linker developed by the LLVM project. It is a drop-in replacement for the system linker and aims to consume less resources than them.
LLD provides production-quality support for the following architectures:

AArch64 and ARM
LoongArch
MIPS
PowerPC and PowerPC64
RISC-V
x86-32 and x86-64

Despite this list, there is still one architecture supported by Fedora that was missing: s390x. This absence impacts how Fedora packages are built on s390x, either by prohibiting packages that require LLD or by requiring that the s390x package is linked with a different linker than other architectures. This difference is known to increase the maintenance burden because different linkers can behave differently.
The support for s390x was added to LLD 18.1. In this article, we explore the work involved…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tulio Magno Quites Machado Filho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 커피 프랜차이즈 매출 및 영업이익 비교]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595064</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595064/23%eb%85%84-%ec%bb%a4%ed%94%bc-%ed%94%84%eb%9e%9c%ec%b0%a8%eb%8b%88%ec%a6%88-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c-%eb%b0%91-%ec%98%81%ec%97%85%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T06:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/18, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595047</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595047/6-18-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T01:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[일론 머스크의 관심 값이 64조 원… 인류의 희망을 거는 대가, 맞나요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79531</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/17/npsp_muskpaypackage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_muskpaypackage"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T01:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 주주들이 창업자이자 CEO 일론 머스크에게 스톡 옵션으로 3억 주를 (할인된 가격에) 지급하는 전례를 찾기 힘든 대형 급여안을 승인했습니다. 첫 번째도 아니고 6년 전에 이미 한 번 승인했던 걸 법원이 무효로 하자 마치 법원에 시위라도 하듯 그대로 다시 승인한 겁니다. 테슬라의 주가에 따라 정확한 가치가 달라지겠지만, 460억 달러, 우리돈 64조 원에 이르는 전례 없는 급여입니다. 이번 급여안을 둘러싼 논란의 배경과 맥락을 분석했습니다. 전문 번역: ‘어그로꾼’이 된 머스크, 그의 급여 460억 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대왕고래 20% 확률, 공개 검증해야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110322</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110322"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[푸틴-김정은 만난다. 환자들 분통? 예상보다 적었다? 쟁점과 현안. 다시 등장한 언론 징벌적 손배 카드. 대왕고래 20% 확률, 공개 검증하자. 더 깊게 읽기. 420억 원 상속받는 상위 0.27% 세금 깎아주기. 최태원 판결문 오류. 다르게 읽기. 민주주의에 대한 세 가지 오해. 한국은 왜 징역 100년 안 되나. 해법과 대안. 소득대체율 인상이 개혁 맞나. 종부세 없앨 수 있나....
The post 대왕고래 20% 확률, 공개 검증해야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월18일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.31: new C++ analyzer features, enhanced user annotations, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1133/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1133/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.31 has been released. We have so much news to share with you! We've enhanced the user annotation system, the mode to analyze individual files, and much more! Learn more release details...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Static keys for BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977993/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977993/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T19:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel has a lot of code paths that are normally disabled: debugging print
statements, tracepoints, etc. To support these efficiently, there
is a common mechanism called

static keys that provides a way to enable or disable a
code path at run time, with effectively no overhead for disabled
branches. BPF programs have not been able to take advantage of static keys so far,
because they aren't compiled into the kernel.
Now, it looks like BPF may be getting support for a similar mechanism —
and the design could also provide one of the components needed to support

jump tables, another missing feature.
Anton Protopovov presented his plans to add static keys to BPF at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostmarketOS v24.06 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978733/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978733/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostmarketOS is an Alpine Linux
derivative distribution aimed at mobile devices; the v24.06
release claims support for over 250 devices, though the level of that
support varies widely.  "This release is geared mainly towards Linux
enthusiasts. We are working hard on stability improvements and automated
testing, but if you expect Android or iOS levels of polish, then this is
not for you yet."  Changes include an upgrade to Alpine Linux 3.20,
newer GNOME and KDE versions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Nested bottom-half locking for realtime kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978189/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978189/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software-interrupt handlers (also called "bottom halves") have a long
history in the Linux kernel; for much of that history, developers have
wished that they could go away.  One of their unfortunate characteristics
is that they can add unexpected latency to the execution of unrelated
processes; this problem is felt especially acutely in the
realtime-preemption community.  The solution adopted there has created
problems of its own, though; in response Sebastian Andrzej Siewior is proposing
a new locking mechanism for realtime builds of the kernel that may have
benefits for non-realtime users as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978709/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978709/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (389-ds-base, buildah, c-ares, cockpit, containernetworking-plugins, fence-agents, gdk-pixbuf2, gvisor-tap-vsock, libreoffice, podman, python-idna, rpm-ostree, and ruby), Debian (atril, chromium, ffmpeg, libndp, libvpx, nano, plasma-workspace, pymongo, roundcube, sendmail, and thunderbird), Fedora (booth and thunderbird), Mageia (aom, atril, libvpx, nano, nss, firefox, and vte), Red Hat (linux-firmware), SUSE (bind, booth, mariadb, openssl-1_1, php7, php8, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (linux-azure, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure, linux-gke, and linux-nvidia-6.5).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[컴포즈커피 사례, 컴포즈커피의 놀라운 영입이익률 비결은?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595035</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595035/%ec%bb%b4%ed%8f%ac%ec%a6%88%ec%bb%a4%ed%94%bc-%ec%98%81%ec%9e%85%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5%eb%a5%a0-%eb%b9%84%ea%b2%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T11:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[밥 먹여주는 정치: 경제를 알아야 선동에 흔들리지 않는다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110290</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110290"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T10:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[낙수효과의 유래 낙수효과. 이 단어는 어느 무능한 대통령을 비판할 때 처음 등장했다. 92년 전 미국 대공황 시절 코미디언이자 사회평론가 윌 로저스가 원조다. 물과 달리 돈은 오히려 아래에서 위로 흐르는 사실을 모른다며, 허버트 후버 대통령을 풍자했다. 낙수효과 따위 없다는 얘기다. 그런데 낙수효과는 1980년대 이후 신자유주의 핵심 키워드가 됐다. [경제신문이 말하지 않는 경제 이야기], 1장의 에피소드다. 경제...
The post 밥 먹여주는 정치: 경제를 알아야 선동에 흔들리지 않는다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experiment and test AI models with Podman AI Lab]]></title>
        <id>291150c5-b1a4-454e-b94c-727611e85178</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/17/experiment-and-test-ai-models-podman-ai-lab"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experimenting with AI models and testing different prompts is a key part of developing AI-enabled applications. However, setting up the right environment and managing model dependencies can be challenging. Podman AI Lab's Playground feature solves this by providing an intuitive, containerized environment for exploring open-source machine learning models locally. Let’s explore the Playground feature in-depth and show how it can accelerate your application development workflow when working with generative AI.
What is Podman AI Lab?
Podman AI Lab is an extension for Podman Desktop, the graphical tool for managing containers and Kubernetes, and enables developers to work with large language models (LLMs) and other AI models locally on their machine. It provides an intuitive interface to discov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Clyburn, Legare Kerrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect apps with Red Hat build of Keycloak and Active Directory Federation Services]]></title>
        <id>d4d4d891-84f4-467b-b90d-81c8dd8a1d5d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/17/protect-apps-red-hat-build-keycloak-and-active-directory-federation-services"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Active Directory Federation Services (AD FS) terminology, Red Hat build of Keycloak will be set up as a Resource Federation Server and AD FS as an Account Federation Server. This means that users will reside in Active Directory (AD) on Windows Server, while the protected web app will reside within the realm protected by Red Hat build of Keycloak on Red Hat OpenShift. With this, we want AD FS to authenticate users to give them access to web apps on OpenShift. Hence, when a user with an account in AD tries to access a web app on OpenShift, the user will be redirected to Red Hat build of Keycloak where they can choose to authenticate with AD FS. The user doesn't need to have an account in Red Hat build of Keycloak or in OpenShift for this to work.
In Red Hat build of Keycloak terminology, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Torbjorn Dahlen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Displaying File Time in C++: Finally fixed in C++20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/file-time-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/file-time-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll examine the potentially simple task of getting and displaying file time. Usually, we can depend on some library or OS-specific code to get that file property. Fortunately, since C++20, we have a reliable and simple technique from the std::filesystem and std::chrono components.
Let’s jump in.



     
    


In C++, working with files was usually reserved for OS APIs and third-party libraries. Here are two examples of such an approach:



     
    


In Linux or any POSIX-compliant system, you can use the stat function to get file times.
#include <iostream>
#include <fstream>
#include <sys/stat.h>
#include <ctime>

int main() {
    const char* file_path = "example.txt";
    std::ofstream(file_path) << "Hello, World!";

    struct stat file_stat;

    if (stat(file_…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 기후변화로 인한 ‘변화’가 이 정도였어? 뜻밖의 결과들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79227</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/16/npsp_climatechangeimpact/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_climatechangeimpact"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 29일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 주말 내내 세계 각지의 이상기후 소식이 전해졌습니다. 에콰도르에서는 극심한 가뭄으로 에너지 비상사태가 선포되었고, 파키스탄과 두바이, 카자흐스탄에서는 이례적인 폭우가 쏟아졌습니다. 하지만 해수면 상승으로 삶의 터전이 눈앞에서 사라지는 바닷가나 폭우로 매년 여름 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978629/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978629/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.10-rc4 for testing.
"Apart from a rather unusual spike in the diffstat due to a parisc fix,
things look normal and pretty small."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[장인어른]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/father-in-law/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/father-in-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[올해 초 장인어른께서 야속하게도 소천하셨다.
장인어른은 정말 평생 일만 하셨다. 차량정비를 하셨는데, 주6일 출근하시고도 주말...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“언론은 검찰의 애완견”, 이재명이 화난 이유는?: 슬로우레터 6월17일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110251</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110251"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“언론은 검찰의 애완견.” 안부수와 이화영 판결 달랐다. 쟁점과 현안. 동해 유전 탐사는 이미 1월에 결정됐다. 한 다리 건너 모두 아는 사람들. 오늘부터 서울대병원 휴진. 더 깊게 읽기. 용산발 감세 드라이브. 지금 이 시점에 부자 감세 맞나. 윤석열의 남은 3년. 다르게 읽기. 권익위가 김영란법을 모르나. 검사 시절과 입장이 달라진 건가. 독일의 한국 정치사 수업. 해법과 대안....
The post “언론은 검찰의 애완견”, 이재명이 화난 이유는?: 슬로우레터 6월17일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distribution of program sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8866</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/06/16/distribution-of-program-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T21:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Program size, in lines of code (LOC), used to be a topic of conversation among developers and managers. Program size is an issue when computer memory is measured in kilobytes. Large programs would be organized into overlays such that only small subsets needed to be held in memory at any time, i.e., programmer defined memory […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How template method can ruin your Java code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1132/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1132/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OOP is wonderful. Programmers usually criticize those who don't follow this paradigm, while the knowledge of patterns is often a must. However, even the right approach doesn't completely protect from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome India to the Google Wallet API]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T20:13:20.573Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To all developers in India: Welcome to the Google Wallet API! Now you can create digital assets like boarding passes, event tickets, gift cards, loyalty cards, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about Google Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T20:13:20.573Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the new features and enhancements Google Wallet announced at I/O this year, focused on security, wearables, push notifications, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some weekend stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978591/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978591/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T19:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.9.5,
6.6.34,
6.1.94,
5.15.161,
5.10.219,
5.4.278, and
4.19.316
stable kernels have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블름버그인텔리전스, 미국인 전기차 선호는 여전하나 내연기관 대체는 어렵다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595028</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595028/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad%ec%9d%b8-%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%84%a0%ed%98%b8"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T01:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘인구소멸’ 한국을 위해 할 수 있는 일]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79516</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/15/npsp_aging/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aging"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이미 고령화 사회를 지나 초고령화 사회를 향해 빠르게 나아가는 한국 사회에서 나타나는 문제의 많은 부분을 풀 수 있는 열쇠는 나이 든 기성세대가 쥐고 있다고 할 수 있습니다. 노화를 우아하게 수용하는 법에 관해 찰스 블로우가 쓴 글을 번역하고, 해설을 썼습니다. 기성세대가 세상이 바뀌었다는 걸 이해하고, 바뀐 세상에서 살아가야 할 다음 세대의 어려움을 함부로 재단하지 않는 모습을 보여줬으면 좋겠습니다. 전문 번역: 눈가 주름이 지혜와 우아함의 대가라니! – 우아하게 노화를 수용한다는 것 해설: “라떼는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of discussions on AI bias]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/ai-bias/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/ai-bias/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There've been regular viral stories about ML/AI bias with LLMs and generative AI for the past couple years. One thing I find interesting about discussions of bias is how different the reaction is in the LLM and generative AI case when compared to "classical" bugs in cases where there's a clear bug. In particular, if you look at forums or other discussions with lay people, people frequently deny that a model which produces output that's sort of the opposite of what the user asked for is even a bug. For example, a year ago, an Asian MIT grad student asked Playground AI (PAI) to "Give the girl from the original photo a professional linkedin profile photo" and PAI converted her face to a white face with blue eyes.
The top "there's no bias" response on the front-page reddit story, and one of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constant Integer Type Declarations Initialized With Constant Expressions Should Be Constants]]></title>
        <id>https://thephd.dev/constant-integers-are-actually-constant-wow-finally-someones-writing-the-goddamn-paper-%F0%9F%99%84</id>
        <link href="https://thephd.dev/constant-integers-are-actually-constant-wow-finally-someones-writing-the-goddamn-paper-%F0%9F%99%84"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Constant integer-typed (including enumeration-typed) object declarations in C that are immediately initialized with an integer constant expression should just be constant expressions. That’s it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Pasture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2024 recap: Making AI accessible and helpful for every developer]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-io-2024-recap-making-ai-accessible-and-helpful-for-every-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-io-2024-recap-making-ai-accessible-and-helpful-for-every-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for joining us at this year's Google I/O. Check out all of the Google I/O announcements and updates with 150+ sessions and learning content available on demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch: High Performance Inference of PyTorch Models on Mobile Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-high-performance-inference-of-pytorch-models-on-mobile-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-high-performance-inference-of-pytorch-models-on-mobile-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Released today, AI Edge Torch enables support for PyTorch, JAX, Keras, and TensorFlow with TFLite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of Checks is now available to all Android and iOS Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/checks-now-available-to-all-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/checks-now-available-to-all-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checks identifies potential privacy issues, provides recommendations, monitors app compliance, and provides results in an intuitive dashboard or directly in your CI/CD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Firebase at  I/O '24]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-firebase-io-24/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-firebase-io-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase, is evolving to enable you to rapidly build and run AI-powered experiences in your apps across platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build for Tomorrow in the Gemini API Developer Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-for-tomorrow-in-the-gemini-api-developer-competition/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-for-tomorrow-in-the-gemini-api-developer-competition/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build a new app with the Gemini API or integrate our Gemini API into an existing application for a chance to win some really cool prizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Building with Project IDX Today]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-project-idx-today/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-project-idx-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.417Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve removed the waitlist for Project IDX. Now, anyone can sign up to start building with AI-assistance, collaboration capabilities, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Firebase Genkit helped add AI to our Compass app]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.415Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We used Firebase Genkit – Firebase’s open source framework for building powerful AI features into your apps with familiar patterns and paradigms – to add AI to an existing application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google AR at I/O 2024: New Geospatial AR features and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-ar-at-io-2024-new-geospatial-ar-features-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-ar-at-io-2024-new-geospatial-ar-features-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.415Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've been exploring new ways to create engaging, easy to use, and shareable experiences and connect your Geospatial AR creations with more users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home APIs: Enabling all developers to build for the home]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/home-apis-enabling-all-developers-to-build-for-the-home/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/home-apis-enabling-all-developers-to-build-for-the-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.415Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've re-envisioned Google Home as a platform for all developers – not just those that build smart home devices – to create innovative experiences for the home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reports from the Python Language Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978541/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978541/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Software Foundation has published a
set of reports from the 2024 Python Language summit.  Topics covered
include version numbering, the limited C API, a new default read-eval-print
loop, and Python's security model in light of the XZ backdoor:


	For multiple reasons like being able to fix bugs and
	single-maintainer modules, CPython doesn't require reviewers on the
	pull requests of core developers. This can lead to "unilateral
	action", meaning that a change is introduced into CPython without
	the review of someone besides the author. Other situations like
	release managers backporting fixes to other branches without review
	are common.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/15, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595019</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595019/6-15-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T09:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[너무 늦었던 양평 용문사 은행나무 출사기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594547</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594547/%eb%84%88%eb%ac%b4-%eb%8a%a6%ec%97%88%eb%8d%98-%ec%96%91%ed%8f%89-%ec%9a%a9%eb%ac%b8%ec%82%ac-%ec%9d%80%ed%96%89%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4-%ec%b6%9c%ec%82%ac%ea%b8%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T08:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 데이트 상대로 ‘심리 상담’ 받는 사람을 선호한다고? 운동만 자기 관리가 아니다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79211</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/14/npsp_mindsos/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_mindsos"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T22:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 24일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 저는 한국에서 의과대학 교육을 받고, 미국에서 일하고 있는 정신과 의사입니다. 미국에서는 정신질환 및 정신건강 서비스를 향한 낙인이 많이 사라졌습니다. 제가 처음 태평양을 건너온 10년 전과 비교하면 피부로 느껴질 정도입니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rukahs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making development across platforms easier for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/making-development-across-platforms-easier-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/making-development-across-platforms-easier-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:14:08.594Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do what works best for your business; whether you’re sharing both UI and business logic across multiple platforms with Flutter or development with Kotlin Multiplatform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing PaliGemma, Gemma 2, and an Upgraded Responsible AI Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-and-toolkit-expansion-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-and-toolkit-expansion-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:14:08.593Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gemma family expands further with the introduction of PaliGemma, and a sneak peek into the near future with the announcement of Gemma 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schaller: Fedora Workstation development update – AI edition]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978470/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978470/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christian Schaller writes about AI and GPU-related features that are in flight and planned for Fedora 41.
streamlined user experience in GNOME Software to let you install the binary NVIDIA driver and provide you with an integrated graphical user interface help to sign the kernel module for use with secure boot. This is a bit different than what we for instance are doing in RHEL, where we are working with NVIDIA to provide pre-signed kernel modules, but that is a lot harder to do in Fedora due to the rapidly updating kernel versions and which most Fedora users appreciate as a big plus. So instead what we are for opting in Fedora is as I said to make it simple for you to self-sign the kernel module for use with secure boot. We are currently looking at when we can make this feature available, but no later than Fedora Workstation 41 for sure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Human Interface Guidelines for KDE]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978465/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978465/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T17:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KDE developer Nate Graham has announced
a new set of KDE Human
Interface Guidelines (HIG) for the KDE project. Graham says that the goals
for the new HIGs were to reflect how KDE designs software today, make
the content 100% actionable, improve navigation, and to improve the
guidelines so people feel comfortable contributing:
contributing!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Aeon: openSUSE for lazy developers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977987/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977987/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T14:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE project recently announced
the second release candidate (RC2) of its Aeon Desktop, formerly known
as MicroOS Desktop GNOME. Aside from the new coat of naming paint,
Aeon breaks ground in a few other ways by dabbling with technologies not found in other openSUSE releases. The goal for Aeon is to provide
automated system updates using snapshots that can be applied
atomically, removing the burden of system maintenance for
"lazy developers" who want to focus on their work rather than desktop
administration. System-tinkerers need not apply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving forward in Android drivers (Project Zero)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978441/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978441/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T14:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
Project Zero article looks at the exploitation of a few Android driver
bugs in great detail.


	As it becomes more difficult to find 0-days in core Android,
	third-party Linux kernel drivers continue to become a more and more
	attractive target for attackers. While the bulk of present-day
	detected ITW [in-the-wild] Android exploitation targets GPU
	drivers, it's equally important that other third-party drivers are
	encouraged towards the same security standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978418/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978418/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (389-ds-base, bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, and dhcp, firefox, glibc, ipa, less, libreoffice, and thunderbird), Debian (cups), Fedora (chromium and cyrus-imapd), Mageia (golang and poppler), Oracle (bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, and dhcp, gvisor-tap-vsock, python-idna, and ruby), Red Hat (dnsmasq and expat), SUSE (libaom, php8, podman, python-pymongo, python-scikit-learn, and tiff), and Ubuntu (h2database and vte2.91).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPC라고 왜 말을 못하나: 우리는 피에 젖은 빵을 먹고 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110180</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110180"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T09:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] SPC 사망 사고 그 이후. 제빵 원료를 만드는 공장에서 일하던 노동자가 소스 배합기에 끼어 숨지는 사고가 있었다. 사람이 죽어나간 그 자리에서 동료 노동자들은 계속 공장을 돌렸다. 다음날 빈소에 찾아온 회사 직원들은 크림빵과 단팥빵을 두 상자 내려놓고 갔다. 한국 최대 규모 제빵 프랜차이즈를 거느린 SPC 그룹 계열사 SPL에서 벌어진 일이다. 유족들은 울부짖었다. “우리 아이가 이...
The post SPC라고 왜 말을 못하나: 우리는 피에 젖은 빵을 먹고 있다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[석열바라기 KBS: 순방 중에도 “지진 피해 신속 파악” 개별 보도]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110169</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110169"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T04:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[전북 부안에서 6월 12일 오전 8시 26분경 규모 4.8의 지진이 발생했습니다. 2016년 경북 경주의 규모 5.8 지진을 시작으로 경북 포항, 충북 괴산에 이어 전북 부안에서 올해 들어 최대 규모의 지진이 일어난 것입니다. 수도권 등에서도 감지될 만큼 강진이었는데요. 지진 규모와 더불어 한반도가 더 이상 지진 안전지대가 아니라는 위기감에 언론도 긴급히 보도했습니다. 그러나 KBS는 해외순방 중인 대통령의...
The post 석열바라기 KBS: 순방 중에도 “지진 피해 신속 파악” 개별 보도 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/14, 테슬라 주총과 이론 머스크 보상 패키지 승인을 보는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595001</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595001/%ec%9d%bc%eb%a1%a0-%eb%a8%b8%ec%8a%a4%ed%81%ac-%eb%b3%b4%ec%83%81-%ed%8c%a8%ed%82%a4%ec%a7%80"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T03:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using NXP i.MX RT685 with pyOCD: Device Support and Debugging Configuration]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40717</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/06/14/using-nxp-i-mx-rt685-with-pyocd-device-support-and-debugging-configuration/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T23:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NXP i.MX RT685 features an ARM Cortex M33 with a Cadence Xtensa audio DSP. To use the NXP EVK board with pyOCD, additional device support is required. By installing the RT685 packs, it becomes easy to debug with pyOCD using Eclipse/MCUXpresso for the NXP i.MX RT685 target board. Happy debugging! Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[탄핵 훨씬 어려워졌다 Vs. 더 큰 불행 막아야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110142</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110142"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[존재감 없는 국민의힘. 쟁점과 현안. 이화영 재판 판사, 이재명 재판도 맡는다. “나도 ‘배우자’더러 받으라고 해야겠네.” 나쁜 풍선인지 좋은 풍선인지 까봐야 안다? 더 깊게 읽기. 탄핵은 훨씬 더 어려워졌다. 탄핵이 불행인가. “언론이 없으면 얼마나 좋겠나.” 당심과 민심 8:2. 더 깊게 읽기. 경찰 판 ‘스포트라이트’. 우리 PB 상품을 맨 위에. 오늘의 TMI. 요즘 개인택시 수입 월 700만...
The post 탄핵 훨씬 어려워졌다 Vs. 더 큰 불행 막아야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월14일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smile while drowning in bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1131/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1131/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many times, we've written about bugs in games, in space flight software, etc. Now we'd like to honor the tradition. This time, we'll take a look at the bugs that have crept into some of the biggest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving forward in Android drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/driving-forward-in-android-drivers.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/driving-forward-in-android-drivers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=MXVwpSGzOOhqOc5hUWJbBLizfYjsfH9XaeDpmRKYJN5bV0WvE1cEyAoIq5yYZlSc);.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-7>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-7,lower-latin) ". "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-2>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-6>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-6,decimal) ". "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-8>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-8,lower-roman) ". "}.lst-kix_kbd3zqh16g9u-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_kbd3zqh16g9u-4}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-1>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}ol.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-3.start{co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Simplifying the BPF verifier]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977815/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977815/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T17:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BPF verifier is a complex program. This has the unfortunate effect of making
it simultaneously more difficult for contributors to work on, and more likely
to harbor unknown bugs. Shung-Hsi Yu had two concrete proposals for how to
simplify the verifier to make it easier to maintain that he presented at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit. Yu proposed changing how the
verifier tracks partially known values and cleaning up the interface to
hide the details of the value-tracker's internal representation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Improving control-flow integrity for Linux on RISC-V]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977720/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977720/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redirecting execution flow is a common malware
technique that can be used to compromise operating systems. To protect from such attacks,
the chip makers of leading architectures like x86 and arm64 have implemented
control-flow-integrity (CFI) extensions, though they need system
software support to function. At the Linux
Security Summit North America,  RISC-V kernel developer Deepak Gupta described the CFI
protections for that architecture and  invited community input on the
kernel support for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.79.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978323/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978323/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.79.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Changes this time
include inline const expressions, the "associated item bounds
syntax", and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978291/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978291/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr), Fedora (nginx-mod-modsecurity, php, and tomcat), Mageia (strongswan), Oracle (389-ds-base, buildah, c-ares, cockpit, containernetworking-plugins, fence-agents, firefox, gdk-pixbuf2, idm:DL1, ipa, kernel, libreoffice, podman, rpm-ostree, and thunderbird), Red Hat (dnsmasq and nghttp2), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (curl, firefox, kernel, kernel-firmware-nvidia-gspx-G06, nvidia-open- driver-G06-signed, openssl-3, and python-Pillow), and Ubuntu (libmatio, libndp, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp,
 linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4,
 linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4,
 linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux-oem-6.5, and virtuoso-opensource).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying the role of an automation developer (it's not what you think)]]></title>
        <id>7bcfd2ee-c9d8-4c8e-91d0-d0178b32e01a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/13/demystifying-role-automation-developer-its-not-what-you-think"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving field of IT, new roles, titles, and frameworks often emerge, leading to varying terminology across organizations. One such role is the automation developer.
Despite what the title might suggest, an automation developer is not a traditional software developer. In fact, most automation developers (or automation engineers or platform engineers) don’t have extensive development skills or backgrounds in coding, yet they are creating Ansible content every day and are contributing to the successful adoption of automation within their organization.
Traditional developers vs. the automation developers
When we think of a traditional software developer, we imagine someone who writes code to build applications. Their work involves designing, coding, testing, and maintaining sof…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A practical guide to linker section ordering]]></title>
        <id>02af4efc-1a6a-41e2-a47d-88c451288c05</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/13/practical-guide-linker-section-ordering"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The location of code and data in memory can have a big effect on a program's performance. Placing functions that reference each other frequently in the same area of memory can help reduce the need to load and unload pages of memory. Similarly, pieces of data that are used a lot at the same time benefit from being located in the same region of memory.
Alternatively, sometimes it is better not to group code and data based upon its use, but rather upon its similarity to each other. Placing similar code and data in adjacent memory regions means that the binary image can be compressed to a greater degree, a feature which is often important for mobile applications.
Compilers attempt to address these needs via the use of profile directed optimizations as well as supporting language features like …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Clifton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to manage and preserve Kafka Connect offsets smoothly]]></title>
        <id>d1be7b84-24e7-42cc-9252-14a96657c986</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/13/how-manage-and-preserve-kafka-connect-offsets-smoothly"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever faced the challenge of needing to recreate a Kafka Connector while preserving its offset position? If so, we have fantastic news for you!
Picture this: your Kafka Connect cluster is perfectly set up, your connectors are finely tuned, and everything is running smoothly. Suddenly, you need to recreate one of your connectors. The thought of losing all the offset information is daunting—nobody wants to risk data duplication or loss.
But worry no more, because Red Hat AMQ Streams 2.6 on Red Hat OpenShift (based on Apache Kafka 3.6.0 and Strimzi 0.38.x) has introduced a revolutionary feature: first-class offsets support with KIP-875. This new feature includes REST API endpoints specifically designed for managing connector offsets, making it seamless to preserve your offset position…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdellatif Bouchama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5인 미만 사업장은 언제나 시기상조]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109384</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109384"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T05:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)의 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기 강약약강 국회가 5인 미만 사업장에 대한 근로기준법 전면 적용 논의를 본격적으로 시작한다. 1989년 최저임금, 주휴수당, 퇴직금 등 일부 조항만 예외적으로 적용하기로 개정한 지 32년 만이다. 김윤나영(경향신문), 노동권 사각지대 ‘5인 미만 사업장’ 근로기준법 적용, 이번엔 될까?, 2021.12.15. 중대재해처벌법은 2022년 1월부터 50명 이상 사업장을 대상으로 시행됐다....
The post 5인 미만 사업장은 언제나 시기상조 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing up Kimos]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/06/13/kimos.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/06/13/kimos.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever had one of those problems where you were stuck for weeks?
It’s not supposed to happen, but … it does.
Let me tell you about the Kimos story so far.
What is Kimos?
Kimos is the name of one of the current open source
projects I’m working on.  The project is
officially named the “Kintex-7 Memory controller, Open Source toolchain”, but
the team shortened that to “KiMOS” and I’ve gotten to the point where I just
call it “Kimos” (pronounced KEE-mos).  The goals of the project are twofold.
Test an Open Source DDR3 SDRAM memory
controller.
This includes both performance testing, and performance comparisons against
Xilinx’s MIG controller.
Just as a note, Angelo’s
controller has a couple of
differences with Xilinx’s controller.  One of them is a simpler
“native” interface: Wishbone, with an op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/12, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594989</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594989/6-12-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T03:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 13, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977365/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977365/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T01:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 13, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“외국인에게 받은 디올 백이라”… 권익위의 상상초월 답변: 슬로우레터 6월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110089</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110089"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T22:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이재명 다섯번째 기소. 핵심은 ‘보고 받았나’. 일주일에 사흘은 법원에서. 쟁점과 현안. 재판 속도에 달렸다. ‘이재명 대통령’이라는 코끼리. “디올 백 준 게 외국인이라.” 더 깊게 읽기. 고용률은 역대 최고, 청년 취업은 하락 전환. 8표 이탈, 김건희 특검법이 가능성 높다. 다르게 읽기. “심판도 선출해야.” 어머니의 편지와 사단장의 탄원서. 헌재는 대북 전단 방관하라고 한 적 없다. 해법과 대안....
The post “외국인에게 받은 디올 백이라”… 권익위의 상상초월 답변: 슬로우레터 6월13일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT Innovations: Qualcomm debuts new technologies at Embedded World 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482500</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/iot-innovations-qualcomm-debuts-new-technologies-at-embedded-world-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T19:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a discussion on Qualcomm Technologies’ IoT strategy in Europe, Enrico Salvatori, SVP & President of Qualcomm Europe, highlighted the introduction of innovative product offerings...
The post IoT Innovations: Qualcomm debuts new technologies at Embedded World 2024 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Qualcomm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cockpit project releases Cockpit Files plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978156/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978156/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cockpit project has
announced
the first release of Cockpit
Files, a plugin for Cockpit that allows file management on your server
via a web browser:
Mahmoud Hamdy
and is now under active development by the Cockpit team. The goal is
to replace the functionality of the cockpit-navigator
plugin from 45Drives and include automated testing per commit, a
standard PatternFly-based interface, and consistency with the rest of
Cockpit.


Development builds for Fedora are available via a
Copr repository, and packages are expected for Arch, Debian, and
Fedora. LWN covered the
Cockpit project in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국가에서 배운 혐오: 조선인 마을을 불태운 증오는 어디에서 왔는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110066</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110066"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[특별 기고] 우토로 마을 방화 사건(2021) 피해자 재일조선인 변호인 도요후쿠 세이지를 비언론인 최초로 안종필 언론상을 받은 김보라미 변호사가 인터뷰했습니다. 왜 재일 한국·조선인에 대한 증오가 눈에 띄는 걸까요. 정부가, 헤이트를 뒤에서 지지하고 있는, 말하자면 ‘정부가 승인한다’라고 하는, ‘위로부터의 헤이트’, ‘관제 헤이트’라고 하는 현상이 있다고 생각합니다. 조선학교만 고교 무상화에서 제외된 사례가 전형적인 예입니다. 왜 국가는 재일조선인 차별에...
The post 국가에서 배운 혐오: 조선인 마을을 불태운 증오는 어디에서 왔는가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Elevating CentOS 7 to a new life]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977762/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977762/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CentOS Linux 7 was first
released in July 2014, and is due to go end-of-life (EOL) on June 30.
By now, anyone who pays attention to such things is aware that Red Hat pulled the plug on
CentOS Linux in late 2020 to be replaced by CentOS Stream
instead. CentOS Linux 8
support was wound
down at the end of 2021 rather than in 2029 as originally stated.
CentOS Linux 7 was allowed to serve out its
full lifespan—but that EOL is approaching rapidly and
there's no direct upgrade path. Users and organizations looking for a lifeline might want to consider
AlmaLinux's ELevate
utility, which allows CentOS users to migrate to alternate enterprise
Linux (EL) operating systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nominations are open for the PSF Board election]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978149/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978149/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Software
Foundation (PSF) has announced
that nominations are open for the PSF Board election through June
25:
The PSF has a video about
serving on the board for those who might be interested. PSF members
can nominate themselves or another member. Candidates
will be announced on June 27. Voting begins on July 2 and will end on
July 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Memory sealing for the GNU C Library]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978010/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978010/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mseal() system call allows a
process to prevent any future changes to portions of its address space
(thus "sealing" them); it was patterned after the mimmutable() system call in OpenBSD.
mseal() generated a lot of discussion, but it was finally merged
for the upcoming 6.10 kernel release.  While mseal() was initially
aimed at securing the Chrome browser, the hope was that it would be useful
elsewhere; as a step toward realizing that hope, Adhemerval Zanella has
posted a
patch series adding support for — and use of — mseal() to the
GNU C library (glibc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[systemd 256 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978151/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978151/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 256 has been released.  As usual, the list of changes is long; see
this article for an overview, or the
announcement for all the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three mid-week stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978139/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978139/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced another round of stable kernel
updates: 6.9.4, 6.6.33, and 6.1.93 have been released. Each contains
another set of important fixes, users of these kernels are advised to
upgrade right away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSUSE Leap 15.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978137/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978137/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE
Leap 15.6 release is available; this is intended to be the last
Leap 15.x release before Leap 16 comes out.
"Leap 15.6 is projected to receive maintenance and security updates
until the end of 2025 to ensure sufficient overlap with the next
release".  Changes include the addition of the Cockpit server-management tool, a
6.4 kernel, GNOME 45, and many other upgrades.  This release also
removes a long list of unmaintained Python packages.  See the
release notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978136/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978136/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (booth), Debian (cyrus-imapd and vlc), Fedora (firefox, libarchive, php, and singularity-ce), Oracle (ipa and ruby:3.3), Red Hat (389-ds-base, buildah, c-ares, cockpit, containernetworking-plugins, fence-agents, gdk-pixbuf2, gvisor-tap-vsock, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, libreoffice, podman, protobuf-c, python-idna, rpm-ostree, ruby, and tomcat), Slackware (cups and mozilla), SUSE (bind, cups, iperf, kernel, nano, and poppler), and Ubuntu (libapache-mod-jk, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-aws, linux-oracle, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-nvidia, and mysql-8.0).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can AI and developers work in harmony?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482495</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/can-ai-and-developers-work-in-harmony/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T10:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI becomes more intelligent, it can code faster than developers. That puts developers in a quandary; we love to write code, but if AI...
The post Can AI and developers work in harmony? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[애플 세계개발자회의(WWDC24)를 보는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594983</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594983/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84%ea%b0%9c%eb%b0%9c%ec%9e%90%ed%9a%8c%ec%9d%98"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Red Hat Connectivity Link on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>8387d247-7986-4f79-879a-3e47528f344e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/12/getting-started-red-hat-connectivity-link-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Connectivity Link is a new offering from Red Hat, which brings a Kubernetes/Red Hat OpenShift native solution for complex application connectivity and API management in hybrid and multi-cloud environments. Connectivity Link is based on the upstream Kuadrant project and was released as a Developer Preview at Red Hat Summit 2024, with the goal of going GA in the fall of 2024.
In this article, I will demonstrate how to get started with Connectivity Link on Red Hat OpenShift. Connectivity Link is not limited to OpenShift, and can be installed and used on other Kubernetes distributions like EKS. However, the installation is much simpler on OpenShift as the required operators can be installed and managed through the Operator Lifecycle Manager (OLM).
Prerequisites
The first prerequisite i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernard Tison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 ways to deploy Quarkus applications in OpenShift Container Platform 4]]></title>
        <id>2ca1d9ab-00cd-4a03-8063-b22f41707281</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/12/4-ways-deploy-quarkus-applications-openshift-container-platform-4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As explained in Deploying your Quarkus applications to OpenShift, there are several approaches for deploying in Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform (RHOCP) 4. Each situation might require different a approach from the ones listed in this article given different (project) requirements.
When doing Quarkus builds for OpenShift, there are several approaches. One of the simplest is the Quarkus Maven plug-in, meaning that the usage of quarkus-openshift extension considerably facilitates the deployment.
Either via pom.xml setting the following dependency:
<dependency>
    <groupId>io.quarkus</groupId>
    <artifactId>quarkus-openshift</artifactId>
</dependency>
Or by adding the extension manually via the command line interface (CLI command) using the Maven Wrapper: 
<-- Below has the latest Quar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior, Alexander Barbosa Ayala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[밀양 사건 폭로전: 사이버렉카의 거짓말 돈벌이, 언론의 잔인한 받아쓰기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110050</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110050"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T06:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[※ 민주언론시민연합은 2차 가해에 해당하는 선정적이고 자극적인 보도에는 바로보기 링크를 걸지 않습니다. 한국성폭력상담소는 6월 5일 ‘2004년 밀양에서 발생한 여자 중학생 집단 성폭행 사건 가해자 신상 공개’에 나선 A유튜브가 피해자(가족) 측 동의를 구했다는 것은 사실이 아니라는 입장을 밝혔습니다. 한국성폭력상담소는 다음과 같은 사실을 알렸습니다. 피해자 의사존중과는 거리가 먼 일방적 영상에 우려를 표하며, 언론 역시 자극적 보도행태를 자제해달라고...
The post 밀양 사건 폭로전: 사이버렉카의 거짓말 돈벌이, 언론의 잔인한 받아쓰기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving into JTAG — Usage Scenarios (Part 5)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-5</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-5"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous articles, we have considered the primary uses of JTAG, including
debugging and testing boards in production. For firmware developers, the first -
debugging - is the most common. In this article, I want to look at two uses of
JTAG Boundary Scan, which are also common tasks for a firmware developer: board
bring-up and reverse engineering.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9개월 동안 거짓말, 윤석열이 감추려는 진짜 비밀이 뭘까: 슬로우레터 6월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110018</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110018"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개원 6일 만에 국회의장 사퇴 결의안. 쟁점과 현안. 조민의 장학금과 김건희의 디올 백. “배우자에 금품, 권익위가 괜찮답니다.” 종결 8표, 송부 7표였다. 더 깊게 읽기. 모든 뉴스는 연결돼 있다. “문제는 속도다.” 경향신문과 한겨레의 논조가 미묘하게 다르다. 다르게 읽기. “800만 달러는 주가 조작 자금.” 다시 등장한 방송 3법. 판사 선출제. 박정훈 변호인이 던진 두 가지 질문. 해법과...
The post 9개월 동안 거짓말, 윤석열이 감추려는 진짜 비밀이 뭘까: 슬로우레터 6월12일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extensible scheduler class to be merged for 6.11]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978007/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978007/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The extensible scheduler class
("sched_ext") framework allows the writing of CPU schedulers as a set of
BPF programs.  It has been somewhat
controversial, and its merging into the kernel has been blocked despite
a clear level of interest from users.

Linus Torvalds has now let
it be known that he has made a decision and, overriding the scheduler
maintainer, will merge sched_ext for the 6.11 release.


	I honestly see no reason to delay this any more. This whole
	patchset was the major (private) discussion at last year's kernel
	maintainer summit, and I don't find any value in having the same
	discussion (whether off-list or as an actual event) at the upcoming
	maintainer summit one year later, so to make any kind of sane
	progress, my current plan is to merge this for 6.11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How it's Made: GenType Alphabet Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:13:56.413Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of our newest experiments in the series is GenTypeGenType. This tool uses generative AI to create an alphabet out of anything you want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Securing BPF programs before and after verification]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977394/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977394/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BPF is in a unique position in terms of security. It runs in a privileged
context, within the kernel, and can have access to many sensitive details of the
kernel's operation. At the same time, unlike kernel modules, BPF programs aren't signed.
Additionally, the mechanisms behind BPF present challenges to implementing
signing or other security features. Three nearly back-to-back sessions at the
2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit
addressed some of the potential security problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancing memory performance with DDR5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482488</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/advancing-memory-performance-with-ddr5/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access to sufficient memory bandwidth will be crucial for engineers and system designers as companies invest further in data centers to meet demand. This article looks at the advances in DDR5 memory that help meet this demand.
The post Advancing memory performance with DDR5 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Eble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 127.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977973/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977973/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
127.0 of the Firefox browser is out.  Changes include support for DNS
prefetching and the ability to close duplicate tabs in a window.  The
browser will now try to upgrade images and videos with HTTP URLs that are
found in an HTTPS page to HTTPS as well; if that fails, the non-HTTPS
resources will simply fail to load.

Update: this
Mozilla Secuirty Blog post describes the HTTPS-related changes in
detail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Dropping the page cache for filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977486/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977486/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VFS maintainer Christian Brauner led a discussion about the possibility of
selectively dropping the contents of the page cache for a filesystem in a
session at the
2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  As he described in his
topic
proposal, the use case that started him down this path comes from
GNOME, which wants to be able to safely suspend access to an encrypted home
directory.  While it is known to kernel
developers, it is surprising to others that reads from encrypted
filesystems that have been suspended will succeed if the data to be read
still exists in the 
page cache.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANCS and HID: Controlling Your iPhone From Zephyr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1669.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1669.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
In a previous blog post (https://embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1630.php), we learned how we can configure our nRF52840 development kit (https://www.nordicsemi.com/Products/Development-ha...) as a Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) device using The Zephyr Project. Similarly, we learned how to advertise standard and custom capabilities. 

In this blog post, we will take...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977939/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977939/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (ruby:3.3), Fedora (efifs, libvirt, podman-tui, prometheus-podman-exporter, and strongswan), Red Hat (firefox, idm:DL1, ipa, nghttp2, and thunderbird), SUSE (aws-nitro-enclaves-cli, cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, containerized-data-importer, frr, glibc, go1.21, go1.22, gstreamer-plugins-base, kernel, kernel-firmware-nvidia-gspx-G06, nvidia-open- driver-G06-signed, libxml2, mariadb, poppler, python-Brotli, python-docker, python-idna, rmt-server, skopeo, sssd, unbound, unrar, util-linux, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (giflib, libphp-adodb, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-laptop, linux-oem-6.8, nodejs, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How developers can leverage RTOS functional safety certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482483</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-developers-can-leverage-rtos-functional-safety-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T12:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RTOS functional safety certification benefits not only safety-critical devices but all embedded devices as a means to improve time-to-market, improve product quality, and reduce product...
The post How developers can leverage RTOS functional safety certification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Lamie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get system-wide profiles of binaries without frame pointers]]></title>
        <id>c9890276-935c-42b8-aae6-8c44a9326f08</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/11/get-system-wide-profiles-binaries-without-frame-pointers"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many profiling tools on Linux have previously been limited by their reliance on stack unwinding algorithms that require commonly-used frame pointer optimizations to be disabled. This article introduces eu-stacktrace, a prototype tool that uses the elfutils toolkit’s unwinding libraries to support a sampling profiler to unwind frame pointer-less stack sample data.
Background
Developers and customers find benefit in profiling the performance of their applications in both development and production environments. A typical requirement for useful profile data is an accurate stack trace listing the active functions at every sample in the profile. Commonly used profiling tools try to fulfill this requirement with basic unwinder implementations that assume programs to have been compiled with a sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serhei Makarov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동의도 영장도 없는 방역 만능주의? 절차와 사생활 보호도 중요하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109996</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109996"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[동의도, 영장도 없이 국가가 내 위치를 추적한다면? 나의 중요한 권리인 사생활의 비밀과 자유는 침해될 수밖에 없습니다. 2020년 5월, 코로나19 팬데믹 당시 정부는 이태원 일대에 있었던 약 1만 명의 위치 정보를 동의 없이 수집했습니다. 수집의 근거가 된 감염병예방법 제76조의2에는 누구를 감염의심자로 볼지, 어떤 정보까지 추적할지, 과도한 사생활 침해는 없는지 제어할 수 있는 보호장치조차 없었습니다. 이에 시민사회단체들은...
The post 동의도 영장도 없는 방역 만능주의? 절차와 사생활 보호도 중요하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세월호 10년: 세 번의 조사, 가려진 진실, 책임 없는 정부]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109989</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109989"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T03:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[민언련 이달의 좋은 보도상 인터뷰] 한국일보 세월호 10주기 ‘산 자들의 10년’ 특별기획팀 (2024년 5월 수상자) 2014년 4월 16일. 우리 모두의 아픔으로 남은 세월호 참사가 일어났다. 그러나 정부, 언론, 수사기관 등은 제 역할을 하지 못했다. 가려진 진실, 정부의 책임 회피, 미흡한 책임자 처벌, 유족과 생존자를 향한 왜곡된 비난 속에 온전한 진상규명은 지금도 현재진행형이다. 세 번의 공적...
The post 세월호 10년: 세 번의 조사, 가려진 진실, 책임 없는 정부 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘사이다 발언’에 박수 갈채? 그에 앞서 생각해 볼 두 가지 용기]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79168</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/10/npsp_openletters/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_openletters"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 22일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 하마스가 이스라엘을 상대로 테러 공격을 벌인 뒤 그에 대한 반격으로 시작된 이스라엘의 가자지구 군사 작전 혹은 이스라엘과 팔레스타인의 전쟁이 벌써 반년이 더 지났습니다. 평화적인 해결은커녕 잠시 총을 내려놓고 민간인들의 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[디올 백 대신 에코백, 김건희의 발걸음이 가벼웠던 이유: 슬로우레터 6월11일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109953</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109953"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘배우자’는 받아도 되나. 권익위는 왜 그랬을까. 에코백을 들었다. 쟁점과 현안. 국민의힘이 깔아준 판, 민주당이 상임위 싹쓸이. “법사위만 달라”, 국민의힘 마지막 제안도 거부. 이재명 맞춤형 당헌 개정. 더 깊게 읽기. 대북 전단 왜 안 막나. 대북 확성기 일단 중지. 바이든-트럼프 초박빙 판세. 유럽에서는 극우의 약진. 다르게 읽기. 헌법 84조 논란, 현직 대통령을 법정에 세울 수 있나....
The post 디올 백 대신 에코백, 김건희의 발걸음이 가벼웠던 이유: 슬로우레터 6월11일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much UB is in my compiler?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1130/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1130/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C and C++ developers have two bug-related headaches: memory leaks and undefined behavior. As you can guess, I'll talk about undefined behavior—and about "my" compiler. To be more precise, I'll talk...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microcontroller operations in an OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482477</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/microcontroller-operations-in-an-ocp-orv3-smart-battery-backup-unit/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a smart battery backup unit, the microcontroller’s software is responsible for guaranteeing the smooth functioning of processes, hence ensuring the unit’s high efficiency and...
The post Microcontroller operations in an OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Cruz and Marvin Neil Cabueñas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computex 2024: a video roundup from Taiwan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482473</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/computex-2024-a-video-roundup-from-taiwan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a taste of the happenings at Computex 2024 in Taiwan covered through my daily video roundups at the show – summarized here.
The post Computex 2024: a video roundup from Taiwan appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computex 2024 keynotes focus on data centers and AI PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482457</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/computex-2024-keynotes-focus-on-data-centers-and-ai-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the announcements in the keynotes at Computex 2024 in Taiwan from Nvidia, AMD, Intel and Qualcomm Technologies.
The post Computex 2024 keynotes focus on data centers and AI PCs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] P4TC hits a brick wall]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977310/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977310/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[P4, short for "Programming
Protocol-independent Packet Processors", is a programming language aimed at
networking devices; it is useful for the configuration of firewalls and
complicated routing architectures.  Since a lot of advanced networking is
done with Linux systems, it stands to reason that there would be value in
supporting P4 and, indeed, an
implementation of P4 in the kernel's traffic-control subsystem was
first posted by Jamal Hadi Salim at the beginning of 2023.  After nearly
18 months, though, this feature has not been merged, and the chances
of that happening would appear to be getting worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[perl v5.40.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977765/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977765/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 5.40.0 of the Perl language has been released.  "Perl 5.40.0
represents approximately 11 months of development since Perl 5.38.0 and
contains approximately 160,000 lines of changes across 1,500 files from 75
authors".  Significant changes include a new __CLASS__
keyword, a :reader: attribute for field variables, a new
"^^" logical-XOR operator (because two of those were not enough),
moving "try/catch" out of the experimental category, and more; see
this
page for lots of details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977789/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977789/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (galera and mariadb10.11), Mageia (0-plugins-base and plasma-workspace), Oracle (ruby:3.1 and ruby:3.3), Red Hat (bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, and dhcp), SUSE (apache2, glib2, libvirt, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, opera, python-Jinja2, python-requests, and squid), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-6.5, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-raspi, linux, linux-ibm, linux-lowlatency, linux-raspi, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-azure, linux-azure-6.5, linux-starfive, linux-starfive-6.5, and linux-gke, linux-ibm, linux-intel-iotg, linux-oracle).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synthara gets $11m to bring in-memory computing to embedded AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482448</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/synthara-gets-11m-to-bring-in-memory-computing-to-embedded-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T11:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless integration of in-memory computing into existing chip designs is a game-changer, particularly for AI applications, says Hermann Hauser.
The post Synthara gets $11m to bring in-memory computing to embedded AI appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A platform for building developer portals]]></title>
        <id>690d5adc-605a-45d3-8381-b91ac5f83968</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/10/platform-building-developer-portals"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an excerpt from Developer Portals: Prepare to Perform with Red Hat Developer Hub. Download the full e-book.
As a cultural initiative, DevOps has probably made software more reliable and its creation more rapid. Its best understood practices have benefited their progenitors, publicizers, and most successful adopters. Developer engagement with deployment concerns engenders a systems thinking that improves application architecture, but DevOps declares for developers an unbounded array of new concepts, terms, and concerns.
This increase in cognitive load can make it feel like the early returns from DevOps practices such as automation and “infrastructure as code” and its progression toward GitOps are diminishing and progress slowing. More than 80% of developers say they have some kind o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hans-Peter Grahsl, Joshua Wood, Ryan Jarvinen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite webhook and Insights automation for efficient RHEL operations]]></title>
        <id>4d91736c-7cb0-4f30-9ecf-de26ef6c4141</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/10/satellite-webhook-and-insights-automation-efficient-rhel-operations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Satellite is an infrastructure management tool designed for the management and operations of Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) environments. It allows system administrators to scale the management of their datacenters to thousands of hosts at ease, while implementing and enforcing secure and compliant standard operating environments (SOE).
In this article, we investigate the use of Satellite webhooks and automation to interact with third-party tooling and react to events occurring within Satellite. This is traditionally used to improve the overall operational efficiency by either forwarding events to third-party auditing and monitoring tools (e.g., Splunk), or using events as triggers for automation (e.g., Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, ServiceNow). To this point, we explore ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerome Marc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국이 자칫하면 ‘한국 꼴’ 될 수 있다고? 달갑지 않은 최신 ‘K-트렌드’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79498</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/10/npsp_birthrategendernorm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_birthrategendernorm"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T04:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한류를 시작으로 대한민국의 국가 브랜드를 뜻하는 “K-시리즈”는 많은 이들에게 긍지를 안겨줬습니다. 그러나 전례를 찾아보기 힘든 저출생 문제와 그 원인의 하나로 꼽히는 젠더 규범을 둘러싼 갈등 문제에 있어서는 우리나라가 소위 “안 좋은 일로 세계에서 1등”을 달리고 있습니다. 미국의 젊은 세대도 연애도, 섹스도, 결혼도 덜한다는 통계가 꾸준히 나오는데, 이에 관한 우려를 담은 글에서 반면교사로 삼아야 할 사례로 한국이 등장하곤 합니다. 닉 크리스토프의 칼럼을 번역하고, 해설을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 결혼도, 섹스도 덜 하는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977725/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977725/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T03:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10-rc3 kernel prepatch is out.
"So things look good, the water is warm, please jump right in and keep
testing,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++17 in Detail: Filesystem in The Standard Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2017/08/cpp17-details-filesystem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2017/08/cpp17-details-filesystem/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although C++ is an old programming language, its Standard Library misses a few basic things. Features that Java or .NET had for years were/are not available in STL. With C++17 there’s a nice improvement: for example, we now have the standard filesystem!
Traversing a path, even recursively, is so simple now!



     
    


For the last five episodes/articles, I’ve covered most of the language features. Now it’s time for the Standard Library. I’ve planned three posts on that: Filesystem, Parallel STL and Concurrency, Utils.
Maybe I was a bit harsh in the introduction. Although the Standard Library lacks some important features, you could always use Boost with its thousands of sub-libraries and do the work. The C++ Committee and the Community decided that the Boost libraries are so important…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이화영 유죄 변수로 보는 이재명 재판의 경우의 수: 슬로우레터 6월10일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109903</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109903"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T22:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[풍선 전쟁에 확성기, 그다음은? 1조 원 풀었는데, 의료 대란 최악의 상황. 쟁점과 현안. 3자 뇌물 혐의, 이재명의 네 번째 리스크. 이화영 미스터리. 대북 송금 특검법 갈 수 있을까. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명의 네 가지 재판. 이재명 재판의 경우의 수. “형사상 소추를 받지 않는다.” 정청래와 최민희 등 선수들 전면 배치. 다르게 읽기. 20% 가능성의 근거는? 설명...
The post 이화영 유죄 변수로 보는 이재명 재판의 경우의 수: 슬로우레터 6월10일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantity of source in a given language]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8852</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/06/09/quantity-of-source-in-a-given-language/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T22:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much source code exists in a particular language? Traditionally, indicators of the quantity of source in a language is the number of people making a living working on software written in the language. Job adverts are a proxy for the number of people employed to write/support programs implemented in a language (i.e., number of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alphawave Semi develops Arm-based compute chiplet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482444</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/alphawave-semi-develops-arm-based-compute-chiplet/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T10:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Neoverse CSS-based CPU chiplet  delivers features ultra-high-speed interfaces and advanced packaging to help deliver scalable performance for AI, HPC and networking infrastructure.
The post Alphawave Semi develops Arm-based compute chiplet appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[신호와 소음을 구분하는 방법: 슬로우뉴스의 새로운 제안.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109833</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109833"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[슬로우레터 구독자 여러분, 안녕하세요. 슬로우뉴스 재창간 1년을 맞아 보내려던 인사가 벌써 몇 달이 지났습니다.슬로우레터는 벌써 300회를 앞두고 있습니다. 오늘은 지난 1년을 돌아보고 슬로우뉴스의 새로운 계획을 말씀드리려고 합니다. 이 글은 세 가지를 담고 있습니다. 슬로우레터의 1년, Q&A으로 풀어볼까요? 아침에 몇 시에 일어나세요? 뉴스를 잘 읽는 방법이 있나요? 좀 더 의견이 들어가도 좋을 것 같습니다. 편향적이라고 비판하는...
The post 신호와 소음을 구분하는 방법: 슬로우뉴스의 새로운 제안. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 엔비디아 액면분할 후 엔비디아 주가 상승 랠리는 지속될 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594975</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594975/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%95%a1%eb%a9%b4%eb%b6%84%ed%95%a0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T14:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[은퇴자 건강을 위한 건강 걸음수 가이드]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594968</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594968/%ea%b1%b4%ea%b0%95%ea%b4%80%eb%a6%ac-%ea%b1%b8%ec%9d%8c%ec%88%98"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T13:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 아마존은 시가총액 3조 달러 클럽에 가입할 수 있을까요? 어떻게 가능할까요?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594962</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594962/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%88%ec%95%a1-3%ec%a1%b0%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac-%ea%b0%80%eb%8a%a5%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T08:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[버닝썬 게이트, 우리가 놓치고 있었던 이야기들.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109811</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109811"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T04:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 한류 스타들의 일탈? 자본과 권력의 구조적 유착을 봐야 한다. 영국의 공영 방송 BBC가 한국 K-팝의 그늘을 조명했다. ‘버닝썬: K팝 스타들의 비밀 대화방을 폭로한 여성들’이라는 다큐멘터리다. 5년 전 사건을 다룬 영상에 페이지뷰가 1000만 뷰에 육박한다는 건 세상의 관심이 살아있다는 이야기다. 우리가 이미 충분히 잘 알고 있다고 생각했던 사건을 외부의 시선으로 들여다 보니 우리가 놓치고 있는...
The post 버닝썬 게이트, 우리가 놓치고 있었던 이야기들. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/8, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594906</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594906/6-8-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T03:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting a high speed parallel ADC to SAM E70]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-06-08:/parallel-adc-and-sam-e70.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/parallel-adc-and-sam-e70.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADCs come in all shapes and sizes. Converters built into MCUs made great progress across the years
but sometimes you need a dedicated discrete ADC. At the extremes of the "speed spectrum"
there are "slow but precise" ADCs (that tend to use SPI or I2C),
and absolute monsters with SerDes outputs that can only be consumed by an FPGA.
My application needed an ADC from the middle ground but with multiple channels and simultaneous sampling.
Interfacing a medium-speed multichannel ADC to an SAM E70 MCU turned out more interesting than I wished for. 😊]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 선거제 허점 악용해도 견제할 방법, 저기도 없네?!]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79147</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/07/npsp_electoralcollege/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_electoralcollege"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T22:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 17일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 미국 대선에 관해 이야기할 때마다 반드시 언급되는 단골 소재가 바로 선거인단(electoral college)입니다. 우리나라처럼 대통령제를 채택한 나라에서도 쉽게 찾아볼 수 없는 독특한 제도라서 더욱 그렇습니다. 투표권이 있는 유권자들의 표를 더해 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Ladybird browser spreads its wings]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976822/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976822/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T18:27:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ladybird is an open-source
project aimed at building an independent web browser, rather than
yet another browser based on Chrome. It is written in C++ and licensed under a
two-clause BSD license. The effort 
began as part of the SerenityOS project, but
developer Andreas Kling announced
on June 3 that he was "forking" Ladybird as a separate project and stepping away from
SerenityOS to focus his attention on the browser completely. Ladybird
is not ready to replace Firefox or Chrome for regular use, but it is showing
great promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux nftables vulnerability exploited in the wild (CrowdStrike)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977583/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977583/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to CrowdStrike, a

vulnerability in the Linux kernel's nftables code
that was  discovered earlier this
year is being actively exploited in the wild. The vulnerability allows for
local privilege escalation. Most distributions have already released a fix.



As noted by the exploit developer, leveraging this POC is dependent on the
kernel's unprivileged user namespaces feature accessing nf_tables. This access
is enabled by default on Debian, Ubuntu and kernel capture-the-flag (CTF)
distributions. An attacker can then trigger the double-free vulnerability, scan
the physical memory for the kernel base address, bypass kernel address-space
layout randomization (KASLR) and access the modprobe_path kernel variable with
read/write privileges. After overwriting the modprobe_path, the exploit drops a
root shell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[The Motley Fool]엔비디아 액면분할은 엔비디아 매수 이유가 될 수 없다. 엔비디아 주가에서 주목할 3가지 요인]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594904</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594904/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Modernizing BPF for the next 10 years]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977013/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977013/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BPF was first

generalized beyond packet filtering more than a decade ago. In that time, it
has changed a lot, becoming much more capable.
Alexei Starovoitov kicked off the second day of the BPF track at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit by leading a session
discussing which changes to BPF are going to come in the next ten years as it
continues evolving. He proposed several ideas, including expanding the number of
registers available to BPF programs, dynamic deadlock detection, and relaxing
some existing limits of the verifier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977555/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977555/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (libtiff), Oracle (cockpit, glibc, kernel, less, libxml2, linux-kernel, and tomcat), Red Hat (java-1.8.0-ibm, nghttp2, and ruby:3.3), Slackware (php), SUSE (go1.21, go1.22, and python-docker), and Ubuntu (aom and libvpx).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[The Motley Fool] 월스트리트 최초 시가총액 5조 달러 기업이 될 아마존]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594897</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594897/%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%9d%ec%95%a1-5%ec%a1%b0-%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac-%ea%b8%b0%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T08:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[The Motley Fool]시총 2조달러 클럽 후보, 3년내 메타 시가총액 2조달러 가능성]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594893</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594893/%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%9d%ec%95%a1-2%ec%a1%b0%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac-%ea%b0%80%eb%8a%a5%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA, 엔비디아는 향후 10년간 컴퓨팅 시장을 지배할 것이며, 엔비디아 목표주가 1,500달러 제시]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594886</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594886/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-1500%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3124-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3124-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T01:50:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.12.4:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3124/
 
This is the third maintenance release of Python 3.12
Python 3.12 is the newest major release of the Python programming 
language, and it contains many new features and optimizations. 3.12.4 is
 the latest maintenance release, containing more than 250 bugfixes, 
build improvements and documentation changes since 3.12.3.
 
Major new features of the 3.12 series, compared to 3.11
 
New features
More flexible f-string parsing, allowing many things previously disallowed (PEP 701).
Support for the buffer protocol in Python code (PEP 688).
A new debugging/profiling API (PEP 669).
Support for isolated subinterpreters with separate Global Interpreter Locks (PEP 684).
Even more improved error…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 beta 2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3130-beta-2-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3130-beta-2-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T01:46:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.13 beta 2.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130b2/
 
This is a beta preview of Python 3.13
Python 3.13 is still in development. This release, 3.13.0b2, is the second of four beta release previews of 3.13.
Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the 
opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their 
projects to support the new feature release.
We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects to test with 3.13 during the beta phase and report issues found to the Python bug tracker 
 as soon as possible. While the release is planned to be feature 
complete entering the beta phase, it is possible that features may be 
modified or, in rare cases, deleted up until the start o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/7, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594877</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594877/6-7-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T00:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이재명의 우향우? “민주당이 무섭다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 6월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109773</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109773"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T22:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“평화는 힘으로 지킨다.” 오늘 액트지오 기자회견. 영일만 브리핑, 산업부 패싱 논란. 쟁점과 현안. 17일부터 서울대병원 전면 휴진. 방통위원장 탄핵 간다. 다시 나온 언론보도 징벌적 손배 법안. ‘어대한’? 힘 빠진 국민의힘 전당대회. 더 깊게 읽기. 원조 친명과 신친명의 갈등. 44명의 가해자, 누구도 처벌받지 않았다. 사이버 자경단의 사적 제재. 다르게 읽기. “최태원은 일부일처제를 깬 게 아니다.” 저출산과...
The post 이재명의 우향우? “민주당이 무섭다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 6월7일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ programmer's guide to undefined behavior: part 1 of 11]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1129/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1129/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your attention is invited to the first part of an e-book on undefined behavior. This is not a textbook, as it's intended for those who are already familiar with C++ programming. It's a kind of C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A generic ring buffer for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976836/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976836/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T16:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's user-space ABI does not lack for ring buffers; they have been
defined for subsystems like BPF, io_uring, perf,
and tracing, for
example.  Naturally, each of those ring buffers is unique, with no common
interface between them.  The natural response to this ABI proliferation is,
of course, to add yet another ring buffer as the generic option; that is
the intent of this
patch series from Kent Overstreet adding a new set of system calls for
ring buffers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977442/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977442/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T16:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (cockpit, kernel, kernel-rt, libxml2, ruby:3.1, and tomcat), Debian (libarchive, pillow, and tinyproxy), Fedora (apptainer), Mageia (amavisd-new and libxml2), Oracle (edk2), Red Hat (booth, cockpit, kernel-rt, less, libxml2, nghttp2, ruby:3.1, ruby:3.3, and tomcat), Slackware (kernel), and Ubuntu (atril, bluez, frr, gdk-pixbuf, openjdk-17, openjdk-21, openjdk-8, openjdk-lts, qemu, and unixodbc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to integrate and use RStudio Server on OpenShift AI]]></title>
        <id>3bed29c8-4504-4367-8f96-46bc979c418c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/06/how-integrate-and-use-rstudio-server-openshift-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RStudio Server is a powerful open source integrated development environment (IDE) that offers a graphical interface for the R programming language, significantly enhancing data analysis and visualization capabilities. With the rise of data-driven decision-making, having a robust tool like RStudio Server becomes crucial for data scientists and analysts. This guide will walk you through the process of setting up RStudio Server on Red Hat OpenShift AI and getting started with its extensive features.
Setting Up RStudio Server on OpenShift AI
The integration of RStudio Server with OpenShift AI provides a scalable and secure environment for data analysis.
Here’s a step-by-step guide to get you started.

Log in to the cluster. First, access your OpenShift cluster by logging in through the termina…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andriana Theodorakopoulou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance Kubernetes deployment efficiency with Argo CD and ApplicationSet]]></title>
        <id>a7dfda04-861d-4593-b806-f4945c3ab857</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/06/enhance-kubernetes-deployment-efficiency-argo-cd-and-applicationset"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Argo CD to manage your Kubernetes ecosystem is an excellent GitOps approach to continuous deployment (CD). However, it can pose challenges when trying to manage multiple Kubernetes manifests for deployments, services, secrets, configurations, and other files within your Git repository.
Unlike an Argo CD Application resource that deploys resources from a single Git repository in a single cluster or namespace, ApplicationSet expands upon this use case. An ApplicationSet utilizes template-based automation to create, modify, and manage multiple Argo CD applications simultaneously, targeting multiple clusters and namespaces.
In what situations is it more convenient to use an ApplicationSet?



It is convenient to use an ApplicationSet when a user or team has too many applications to manag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Falero Otiniano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[크라우드스트라이크 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594863</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594863/%ed%81%ac%eb%9d%bc%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T06:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/6, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594859</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594859/6-6-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T06:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[홍윤희 스토리 1. 이제 회사 가서 좀 쉬어]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109322</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109322"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[홍윤희 스토리] 잘 다니던 회사 그만두고 지금은 장애인 이동권을 위한 사단법인 ‘무의’ 이사장. 지민이 엄마로, 활동가로, 자유기고가에서 이사장까지. 대체로 바쁘고 힘겹고 지겹지만 가끔씩 찬란한 ‘홍윤희의 그 길’에 관한 이야기. 홍윤희? 근데 누구세요? 장애가 ‘무의미’해지는 세상을 꿈꾸는, 아니 계획하고 실행하며 그걸 알리는 ‘무의’라는 단체가 있습니다. 처음에는 ‘진짜’ 직업 따로인 자원봉사 1인 활동가 단체였지만, 협동조합의 테두리를 갖추고,...
The post 홍윤희 스토리 1. 이제 회사 가서 좀 쉬어 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 6, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975974/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975974/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T01:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 6, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“내가 해봐서 아는데”, 백종원과 윤석열의 차이: 슬로우레터 6월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109706</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109706"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“더 이상 가망이 없다고 생각한다.” S&P도 “희망과 꿈일 뿐.” 쟁점과 현안. 헌정사상 첫 야당 단독 국회 개원. 국민의힘이 법사위에 목매는 이유. 법사위 기피증. 더 깊게 읽기. “다른 국정 운영도 이렇게 하는 것 같아 걱정.” 국가채무 비율 딜레마. “이런 사건은 범인 못 잡아요.” 언더커버를 합법 수사로. 다르게 읽기. 종부세와 재산세 통합하자는 주장 따져보니. 한국 사람들이 돈을...
The post “내가 해봐서 아는데”, 백종원과 윤석열의 차이: 슬로우레터 6월6일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘억만장자들만의 세상’, 이제는 대놓고 펼쳐진다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79483</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/05/npsp_buylongerlife/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_buylongerlife"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[불로초를 찾으려 했던 진시황의 이야기는 다들 잘 아실 겁니다. 굳이 진시황이 아니라도 인류 역사에 이름을 남긴 권력자 가운데는 다시 젊어지려고 애쓴 사람이 많습니다. 오늘날 우리는 돈이 곧 권력의 중요한 원천이 되거나 아예 그 자체로 권력이 되는 자본주의 사회를 살고 있습니다. 자본주의의 첨단을 달린다는 미국의 부자들은 불로초와 비슷한 효과를 내는 비법을 독점적으로 터득했습니다. 비결이 뭘까요? 이번에도 역시 돈입니다. 전문 번역: 젊어지려고 아들 피 수혈한 백만장자…돈으로 ‘불로장생’을 사다 해설: ‘억만장자들만의 세상’, 이제는 대놓고 펼쳐진다]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Measuring and improving buffered I/O]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976856/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976856/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T20:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two types of file I/O on Linux, buffered I/O, which goes through
the page cache, and direct I/O, which goes directly to the storage device.
The performance of buffered I/O was reported to be a lot worse than direct
I/O, especially for one specific test, in Luis Chamberlain's 
topic
proposal for a session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.
The proposal resulted in a lengthy mailing-list discussion, 
which also came up in Paul McKenney's RCU session the next
day; Chamberlain led a 
combined storage and filesystem session to discuss those results with an
eye toward improving buffered I/O performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kali Linux 2024.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977303/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977303/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T19:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2024.2 of the Kali Linux penetration testing distribution
has been released. This
release includes an update to GNOME
46, a high-resolution (HiDPI) mode for Xfce, as well as a number
of new packages such as the AutoRecon network
reconnaissance tool, pspy command-line utility for
snooping on Linux processes, and SploitScan tool for
fetching and displaying CVE information. Kali Linux is based on Debian
testing, and 2024.2 incorporates Debian's work to transition to 64-bit
time_t to avoid year 2038 problems. Users with existing Kali
systems should be sure to follow the documentation
when upgrading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD 14.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977285/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977285/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 14.1 of FreeBSD has
been released. This
is the second release of the 14.x stable branch. Highlights of this
release include upgrades to OpenZFS 2.2.4, Clang/LLVM 18.1.5, and
OpenSSH 9.7p1. FreeBSD 14.1 also features cloud-init support,
sound subsystem improvements, and more. See the
what's
new blog post from the FreeBSD Foundation, 
release
notes, and errata for
more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rethinking the PostgreSQL CommitFest model]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976793/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976793/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T16:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many years ago, the PostgreSQL project started holding regular CommitFests to
help tackle the work of reviewing and committing patches in a more
organized fashion. That has served the project well, but some in
the project are concerned that CommitFests are no longer meeting
the needs of PostgreSQL or its contributors. A lengthy discussion on the
pgsql-hackers mailing list turned up a number of complaints, a few
suggestions for improvement, but little consensus or momentum toward
a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Removing GFP_NOFS]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976355/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976355/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GFP_NOFS flag is meant for kernel memory allocations that
should not cause a call into the filesystems to reclaim memory because there are
already locks held that can potentially cause a deadlock.  The "scoped
allocation" API is a better choice for filesystems to indicate that they
are holding a lock, so GFP_NOFS has long been on the chopping block, though
progress has been slow.  In a filesystem-track session at
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Matthew Wilcox wanted to
discuss how to move kernel filesystems away from the flag with the eventual
goal of removing it completely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The state of SourceHut]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977174/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977174/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew DeVault has published
an update about the state of the SourceHut software development
platform and its plans for the coming months. This is the first update
since the January post-mortem
following a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that resulted
in a prolonged
outage:
As you can imagine, it has been a stressful time for us. However, I
wish to stress that everything we've been dealing with is planned for
in our models, both technical and financial. There is no existential
threat to SourceHut. Nevertheless, we are grateful for your patience
and support.
[...] We have been focusing on two things this year: provisioning
and managing our infrastructure and getting as much rest as
possible. Our situation has calmed down, and while we still have a lot
of loose ends to attend to I'm happy to say that we're resuming a
sense of normalcy here and preparing to resume our work on the
features you need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Comparing BPF performance between implementations]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976317/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976317/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Jowett returned for a second remote presentation at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit to compare the performance of
different BPF runtimes. He showed the results of the MIT-licensed BPF

microbenchmark suite he has been working on.
The benchmark suite does not yet provide a good direct comparison between all
platforms, so the results should be
taken with a grain of salt. They do
seem to indicate that there is some significant variation between
implementations, especially for different types of BPF maps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977233/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977233/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (deepin-qt5integration, deepin-qt5platform-plugins, dotnet8.0, dwayland, fcitx-qt5, fcitx5-qt, gammaray, kddockwidgets, keepassxc, kf5-akonadi-server, kf5-frameworkintegration, kf5-kwayland, plasma-integration, python-qt5, qadwaitadecorations, qgnomeplatform, qt5, qt5-qt3d, qt5-qtbase, qt5-qtcharts, qt5-qtconnectivity, qt5-qtdatavis3d, qt5-qtdeclarative, qt5-qtdoc, qt5-qtgamepad, qt5-qtgraphicaleffects, qt5-qtimageformats, qt5-qtlocation, qt5-qtmultimedia, qt5-qtnetworkauth, qt5-qtquickcontrols, qt5-qtquickcontrols2, qt5-qtremoteobjects, qt5-qtscript, qt5-qtscxml, qt5-qtsensors, qt5-qtserialbus, qt5-qtserialport, and qt5-qtspeech), Oracle (389-ds-base and ruby:3.1), Red Hat (389-ds-base, glibc, and kernel), SUSE (python-PyMySQL), and Ubuntu (libarchive).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing server calls in generated HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Round-tripToTheServer</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Round-tripToTheServer"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Vaccari completes his article on testing
         template-generated HTML, by looking at how to use TDD with pages that make
         calls to the server.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 best practices for writing interrupt service routines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482438</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-best-practices-for-writing-interrupt-service-routines/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T11:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poorly written ISRs can result in systems with race conditions, poor responsiveness, and even excessive CPU use. Nearly every embedded system uses interrupt service routines...
The post 5 best practices for writing interrupt service routines appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encryption at rest for Apache Kafka]]></title>
        <id>a7bd3f0f-f8f9-4b69-a4e7-b575cbcd0921</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/05/encryption-rest-apache-kafka"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past decade Apache Kafka has become a commonly deployed piece of data infrastructure. It is considered by many to be the de facto standard for low latency, high throughput, scale out message processing, and data streaming. Kafka is also a data store and therefore subject to many of the same security and compliance obligations as databases, such as encryption at rest.
Encrypting Kafka data at rest 
Apache Kafka does not provide a facility for encrypting sensitive data at rest. Infrastructure providers usually compensate for this by deploying file system or volume encryption. However, encrypting at this level has drawbacks. First, operations personnel and services with file system permissions may view data content. Secondly, file system and volume encryption is not differentiated wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Bentley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multicluster replication in Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation S3]]></title>
        <id>660179fe-5725-4644-a799-c3783fcc6225</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/05/multicluster-replication-red-hat-openshift-data-foundation-s3"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial is designed for developers and who are managing cloud-native applications on Red Hat OpenShift. If you're looking to enhance data availability and resilience across multiple clusters, this guide will walk you through the process of setting up S3-compatible multi-cluster replication using OpenShift Data Foundation's NooBaa. By following these steps, you'll be able to ensure data is replicated across clusters, improving redundancy and fault tolerance in your infrastructure.
Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation is a comprehensive storage solution that integrates with OpenShift to provide persistent storage for containerized applications. It supports a variety of storage types, including block, file, and object storage, and is designed to be highly scalable and resilient. OpenShift …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Filice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why your errno value isn't printing in GDB—and what to do about it]]></title>
        <id>1d7b25df-8a39-4351-bb45-47d9f9dbb91b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/05/why-your-errno-value-isnt-printing-gdb-and-what-do-about-it"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When debugging a program using the GNU Project Debugger (GDB), printing the value of errno should be easy, but sometimes it isn't. This article explains why printing errno might not work and what to do when it doesn't.
This article will focus on systems with runtime environments which use the GNU C Library (glibc) as the C library; printing errno on other modern multi-threaded systems which use a different C library implementation should be similar, though some of the details for accessing errno (when it doesn't just work) might be different. This article with be most applicable to GNU/Linux systems running either the Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) or Fedora distributions. Much of the article should be applicable to other popular Linux distributions too, but be aware that package names ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Buettner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[라인야후 사태, 국가주의 프레임을 넘어서]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109641</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109641"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T02:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[기고] 라인야후 사태를 공공성과 인권 관점에서 살펴봅니다. 오병일(진보네트워크센터 대표)은 국가주의 프레임에 빠져 라인야후 사태를 보면 타국의 보호주의를 비난하면서 자국의 보호주의를 요구하는 모순에 빠질 수 있다고 지적합니다. 라인야후 대주주인 A홀딩스의 네이버 지분을 매각하라는 일본 정부의 요구를 둘러싸고 논란이 뜨겁다. 한국의 기업과 기술을 강탈하려는 일본과 이를 수수방관하는 듯한 한국 정부에 대한 비난의 목소리가 높다. 급기야 일본 정부의...
The post 라인야후 사태, 국가주의 프레임을 넘어서 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오병일</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사이먼 오웬스, 유튜브가 헐리우드를 계속 압도할 수 있는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594849</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594849/%ec%9c%a0%ed%8a%9c%eb%b8%8c%ea%b0%80-%ed%97%90%eb%a6%ac%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c-%ec%95%95%eb%8f%84-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T01:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/5, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594836</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594836/6-4-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T00:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in May (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/may-2024-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/may-2024-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this May.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 주가조작, “탈탈 털었는데 안 나온 것” 아니었다: 슬로우레터 6월5일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109617</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109617"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 서면 진술서, 소명 부족했다. 탈탈 털지 않았다. 쟁점과 현안. 산유국의 꿈? 반응이 미지근한 이유. 구멍가게 수준? 세계적인 시추 전문가? 전공의 복귀 출구 전략. 더 깊게 읽기. 국가채무 비율 줄여서 발표했나. 민주당의 감세 드라이브, “상속세 부담 줄인다.” 다르게 읽기. 쌀값이 오르는 이유. 물가 2.7%라는데 농산물은 19% 급등. 해법과 대안. 의대 증원 이후가 문제다. 4대 개혁...
The post 김건희 주가조작, “탈탈 털었는데 안 나온 것” 아니었다: 슬로우레터 6월5일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volatile, DCL, and synchronization pitfalls in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1128/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1128/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if common knowledge is actually more nuanced, and old familiar things like Double-checked locking are quite controversial? Examining the code of real projects gives this kind of thought. In this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Google Developer Program: Unlock New Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-the-google-developer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-the-google-developer-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:13:44.216Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Developer Program gives developers access to a range of new tools and benefits,  to allow them to discover and explore all the Google sponsored communities we already offer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Karels has passed away]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977070/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977070/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have just received the
sad news that longtime core BSD developer Mike Karels has died; he will
certainly be missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incus 6.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977059/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977059/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T19:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.2 of the Incus container-management system is out.  "This
release contains the second wave of changes contributed by students of the
University of Texas at Austin and a few other features and
improvements."  The features include a new incus top
command, a new API for system load information, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hardware security underlies AI progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482434</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/why-hardware-security-underlies-ai-progress/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T18:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The security of AI chips must be ironclad so models behave as expected and end users are protected from harm. Semiconductors in AI have been...
The post Why hardware security underlies AI progress appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Oberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New site feature: comment subthread hiding]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977033/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977033/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T18:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the recent discussion on commenting at
LWN, several readers asked for the ability to hide subthreads of a long
comment stream.  That feature has just been added; it is also integrated
with the three comment-display modes and with comment filtering, removing
the need for JavaScript for filtering.  Hiding is not persistent; no extra
data is stored at either end.

Give it a try; if you have comments on the new mechanism, this is the place
to put them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Handling the NFS change attribute]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975863/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975863/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T15:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The saga of the i_version field for inodes, which tracks the
occurrence of changes
to the data or metadata of a file, continued in a discussion at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  In a session led by
Jeff Layton, who has been doing a lot the work on changing the semantics and functioning of
i_version over the years, he updated attendees on the status of the effort since a session at last year's summit.  His summary
was that things are
"pretty much where we started last year", but the discussion this time
pointed to some possible ways forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying robot operating system drivers for motor controllers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482430</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/applying-robot-operating-system-drivers-for-motor-controllers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T14:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will give an overview on how to use and integrate ROS drivers in applications, products, and systems, enabling faster technology evaluation and avoiding...
The post Applying robot operating system drivers for motor controllers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krizelle Paulene Apostol, Jamila Macagba, and Maggie Maralit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] An instruction-level BPF memory model]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976071/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976071/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T13:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few topics as arcane as memory models, so it was a pleasant surprise
when the double-length session on the BPF memory model at the
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit turned out to be
understandable. Paul McKenney led the session, although he was clear that the
work he was presenting was also due to Puranjay Mohan, who unfortunately could
not attend the summit.
BPF does not actually have a formalized memory model yet;
instead it has relied on a history of talks like this one and a general informal understanding.
Unfortunately, ignoring memory models does not make them go away, and this has
already caused at least one BPF-related bug on weakly-ordered architectures.
Figuring out what a formal memory model for BPF should define was the focus of
McKenney's talk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976977/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976977/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T13:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, git, libreoffice, microcode, python-requests, webkit2, and wireshark), Oracle (container-tools:ol8, glibc, go-toolset:ol8, idm:DL1 and idm:client, less, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9, ruby:3.0, and virt:ol and virt-devel:rhel), Red Hat (nodejs, nodejs:18, python-idna, and ruby:3.1), and SUSE (389-ds, ffmpeg, ffmpeg-4, gnutls, gstreamer-plugins-base, libhtp, mariadb104, poppler, python-python-jose, squid, and unbound).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[환자는 없었다: 정부 vs. 의료계 보도 22,224건 분석]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109592</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109592"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사직서를 내고 진료현장을 이탈한 전공의 대부분은 전문의 자격취득을 위한 복귀 시한인 5월 20일에도 돌아오지 않았습니다. 의사 수를 늘려 의료공백을 개선하겠다는 정부 정책이 무색하게 당장 내년부터 의료인력 부족이 예고된 것이나 다름없는데요. 의료계 이탈은 정부가 2월 6일 지방의료 붕괴와 필수의료 강화 등을 위해 2025년 대입부터 의대 정원을 대폭 늘리겠다고 선포하면서 시작됐습니다. 의료계는 정부 정책에 항의하며 의료현장을 떠났고,...
The post 환자는 없었다: 정부 vs. 의료계 보도 22,224건 분석 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA 마이클 하트넷, 금리 인하 후 행동강령 : 채권 매수와 주식 매도]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594834</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594834/%ea%b8%88%eb%a6%ac%ec%9d%b8%ed%95%98-%ed%9b%84-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%eb%a7%a4%eb%8f%84"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T23:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 계속 심각하니 어느새 간과하는 걸까, 저출생 문제]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79136</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/03/npsp_birthdearth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_birthdearth"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 15일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 로스 더우댓(Ross Douthat)은 지난해 말 대한민국은 사라지고 있는가?라는 칼럼을 쓴 뉴욕타임스 칼럼니스트입니다. 제목만으로도 당연히 한국에서 큰 관심을 받을 수밖에 없던 글인데, 많은 선진국에서 공통으로 나타나는 저출생 경향이 유난히 두드러지는 나라가 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[140억 배럴 산유국의 꿈? 어느 신문이 가장 흥분했나: 슬로우레터 6월4일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109542</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109542"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[산유국의 꿈, 어느 신문이 가장 흥분했나. 삼성전자 시가총액 5배라고? 동해 가스전의 씁쓸한 추억. 7광구는? 천공의 예언? 쟁점과 현안. VIP 격노설, 해명을 내놨는데. 9.19합의 효력 정지, 완충 구역이 사라졌다. 더 깊게 읽기. 이원석이 “성역은 없다”고 한 이유. “은밀하게 전달만 해드리고 싶어요.” 오늘 전공의 사표 받는다. 다르게 읽기. 탄핵을 정치적 반전 카드로? 1일1특검, 어제는 대북송금 수사 특검....
The post 140억 배럴 산유국의 꿈? 어느 신문이 가장 흥분했나: 슬로우레터 6월4일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LyX 2.4.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976826/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976826/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T20:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.4.0 of the LyX
document processor has been released. LyX is a "What You See Is What You
Mean" (WYSIWYM) application that offers GUI editing of LaTeX
documents with import and export to PDF, HTML, OpenDocument, Word, and
other formats. LyX 2.4.0 is the first major release in six years, and
brings support for EPUB, DocBook 5, improved
table styles, and now uses Unicode (utf8) as its default encoding. See
the full list of new
features on the LyX wiki, and release
notes for information on known issues and caveats for those
upgrading from earlier versions of LyX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don't Need an RTOS (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1653.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1653.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T17:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least, probably not as often as you think you do. Using a preemptive RTOS can help make a system schedulable (i.e. help all of its tasks meet their deadlines) but it comes at a cost: "concurrently" running tasks can interact in unforeseen ways that cause system failures, that dreaded class of errors known as "race conditions". In part, this is because humans have difficulty thinking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Debian's /tmpest in a teapot]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975565/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975565/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T16:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debian had a major discussion
about mounting /tmp as a RAM-based tmpfs in 2012 but inertia
won out in the end. Debian systems have continued to
store temporary files on disk by default. Until now. A mere 
12 years later, the project will be switching to a RAM-based /tmp in the Debian
13 ("Trixie") release. Additionally, starting with Trixie, the
default will be to periodically clean up temporary files automatically in
/tmp and /var/tmp. Naturally, it involved a lengthy discussion first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976782/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976782/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T14:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9 and ruby:3.0), Debian (chromium, gst-plugins-base1.0, and kernel), Fedora (chromium, glances, glycin-loaders, gnome-tour, helix, helvum, kitty, libarchive, libipuz, librsvg2, loupe, maturin, ntpd-rs, plasma-workspace, and a huge list of Rust-based packages due to a "mini-mass-rebuild" that updated the toolchain to Rust 1.78 and picked up fixes for various pieces), Mageia (gifsicle, netatalk, openssl, python-jinja2, and unbound), Red Hat (kernel and kernel-rt), SUSE (bind, glibc, gstreamer-plugins-base, squid, and tiff), and Ubuntu (glibc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling Backstage: A developer's guide to the CNCF project]]></title>
        <id>51e55c52-4926-439d-bb73-cefd398926b5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/03/backstage-cncf-project"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of software development is constantly evolving. The Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), a non-profit organization fostering open source technologies, plays a crucial role in this evolution. The CNCF acts as a hub, bringing together developers and companies to create and refine technologies specifically designed for building and running applications in the cloud. These "cloud-native" technologies emphasize scalability, resilience, and agility–essential qualities for modern software that needs to adapt to ever-changing demands.
However, the very features that make cloud-native development powerful also introduce layers of complexity. As software development teams leverage a growing ecosystem of services, APIs, and tools, developers can find themselves overwhelmed. Jugglin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Eisele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load testing 3scale API Management with Hyperfoil and Ansible]]></title>
        <id>9cc090d8-704b-4940-aa3c-0a4e5a30dedd</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/03/load-testing-3scale-api-management-hyperfoil-and-ansible"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was interested in doing some load testing against Red Hat 3scale API Management. After a bit of digging around, I discovered perftest-toolkit, an open source load testing toolkit.
Figure 1 depicts an infrastructure diagram from the perftest-toolkit repository.



  
        



  

Figure 1: Infrastructure diagram showing how the the load testing tooling relates to 3scale API Management and OpenShift.

At first look I was unsure what this gave me or what it required. But after playing around with it for a while, I eventually figured it out along with a few pain points.
What do we need?
Prerequisites:

A Red Hat OpenShift Kubernetes cluster.
An instance of 3scale API Management on this cluster.
An Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instance that can connect a route on your cluster, and al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사회연대임금: 탐욕의 풍선]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108616</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108616"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T06:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)의 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기 인트로 & 요약 (2분) 1.스웨덴 모델인지 여부가 왜 중요한가? 스웨덴 모델인지 아닌지, 스웨덴에서 성공했는지 실패했는지는 중요하지 않다(스웨덴에서 실패했다는 지적은 대체로 사실이 아니다). 중요한 건 이제 한국은 외국 모델을 수입할 수준은 이미 넘어섰다. 우리 제도에서 어떻게 적용될 수 있을지에 관한 논의가 중요하다. 2.노조와 메커니즘의 문제....
The post 사회연대임금: 탐욕의 풍선 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/3, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594827</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594827/6-3-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI와 같이 살아도 ‘외로움’을 느낄 수밖에 없는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79462</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/02/npsp_aillmloneliness/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aillmloneliness"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T00:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인공지능이 나날이 발달하면서 인간의 외로움도 AI 챗봇이 해결해주는 날이 머지않아 오리라는 기대 섞인 말도 많이 나옵니다. 그러나 인공지능 기술이 아무리 좋아져도 다른 사람과 관계에서 오는 연결감을 해소해주는 데는 한계가 있을 수 있다는 지적도 있습니다. 제시카 그로스의 칼럼을 번역하고, 연결감과 ‘나를 필요로 하는 경험’에 대해 예일대학교 정신의학과 나종호 교수에게 해설을 청했습니다. 전문 번역: ‘그녀’라면 여친보다 나을 것이라고?… AI가 외로움까지 해결할 수 있을까 해설: AI와 같이 살아도 ‘외로움’을 느낄 수밖에 없는 이유는 이렇다]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976498/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976498/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T23:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second 6.10 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Nothing feels particularly odd, but rc2 is usually fairly small and
people are only starting to find regressions.

So please go test some more."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지지율 21% 윤석열, 그날 꼭 술을 마셨어야 했나: 슬로우레터 6월3일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109475</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109475"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T22:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 지지율 21%. 쟁점과 현안. 종합부동산세 “개편” 꺼냈더니 “폐지”. 가뜩이나 세수 줄어드는데. 종부세와 재산세를 합친다면? 한국판 ‘하우스 오브 카드’, 복수가 시작된다. 다르게 읽기. 최태원-노소영 재산 분할의 세 가지 관점. 노태우 비자금 팩트체크. “버립니다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 김정숙 특검법? 여당이 검찰 못 믿나. “이재명이 대통령처럼 보이기 시작한다.” 어떤 중산층을 말하나. 오물 풍선과 대북 확성기. 오늘의 TMI....
The post 지지율 21% 윤석열, 그날 꼭 술을 마셨어야 했나: 슬로우레터 6월3일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obtaining source code for training LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8824</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/06/02/obtaining-source-code-for-training-llms/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T21:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Training a large language model to be a coding assistant requires huge amounts of source code. Github is a very well known publicly available repository of code, and various sites have created substantial collections of GitHub repos, e.g., GitTorrent, and Google’s BigQuery. Since 2017 the Software Heritage has been amassing the world’s source code, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Linux 40 election results]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976447/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976447/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T18:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fedora Project has announced
the results of the Fedora Linux 40 election cycle. Four seats were
open on the Fedora
Engineering Steering Committee (FESCo), and the winners are Stephen
Gallagher, Neal Gompa, Michel Lind, and Fabio Valentini. The Fedora
Council had two seats open, and the winners
are Aleksandra Fedorova and Adam Samalik. One seat was open on the
Fedora Mindshare
Committee, and the winner
is Sumantro Mukherjee. Four seats were open for the first election to select
members of the EPEL
Steering Committee, which went to Troy
Dawson, Kevin Fenzi, Carl George, and Jonathan Wright.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘대파 게이트’의 악몽, 물가가 모든 걸 삼킨다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109404</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109404"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T04:03:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우데이터] 누적 물가 상승률 역대 2위… 인플레이션의 의미가 달라졌다. 조 바이든(미국 대통령)이 재선에 실패한다면 물가 때문일 가능성이 크다. 경제는 좋은데 물가가 엉망이라는 비판이 많다. 그런데!! 한국은 경제 성장률은 더 낮고 물가는 더 높다. 오늘은 정치와 물가의 상관관계를 살펴본다. 대파 875원 논란. 총선에 얼마나 영향을 미쳤을까. 대파 원가가 1000원이 넘는다고 하지 않았나. 문재인 정부 때 더...
The post ‘대파 게이트’의 악몽, 물가가 모든 걸 삼킨다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[번역] 프로그래머를 위한 카테고리 이론 - 10. 자연 변환]]></title>
        <id>20240601-category-theory-for-programmers-10-natural-transformations</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/06/01/category-theory-for-programmers-10-natural-transformations/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[필자는 지금까지 카테고리 사이의 구조를 보존하는 사상으로써의 펑터에 대해 이야기하였다. 펑터는 한 카테고리를 다른 카테고리에 포함(Embeds)한다. 이는 결국 펑터가 여러 대상을 하나로 합칠 수는 있지만, 절대 구조를 변형하지는 않는다는 것을 의미한다. 펑터에 대해 이해하는 방법 중 하나는 함자를 사용하여 하나의 카테고리를 다른 카테고리 내부에서 모델링해보는 것이다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reading Google Sheets from a Go program]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/reading-google-sheets-from-a-go-program/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/reading-google-sheets-from-a-go-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T01:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I recently needed to process some data from a Google Sheet in a Go program, and
was looking for the most straightforward way to do so on my local machine. Using
<tt class="docutils literal">gcloud</tt>'s ADC didn't work for me because it typically doesn't have access to
sheets or docs.</p>
<p>The simplest …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 선거 패자도 ‘정치 보복’ 걱정 안 해도 되는 미국]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79102</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/31/npsp_democracyelection/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_democracyelection"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T22:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 10일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 올해는 전 세계 수많은 나라에서 다양한 층위의 선거가 치러지는 해입니다. 우리나라도 총선을 치르고, 스브스프리미엄을 통해 자주 관련 소식을 전해드린 미국 대선도 오는 11월입니다. 오늘날 여러 민주주의 국가에서 찾아볼 수 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opt Green: KDE Eco's New Sustainable Software Project]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976176/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976176/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T19:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Eco, a KDE project focused
on reducing software's environmental impact, has announced its Opt
Green campaign to reduce e-waste:
Over the next two years, the "Opt Green" initiative will bring what
KDE Eco has been doing for sustainable software directly to end
users. A particular target group for the project is those whose
consumer behavior is driven by principles related to the environment,
and not just price or convenience: the "eco-consumers".
Through online and offline campaigns as well as installation
workshops, we will demonstrate the power of Free Software to drive
down resource and energy consumption, and keep devices in use for the
lifespan of the hardware, not the software.
Our motto: The most environmentally-friendly device is the
one you already own.
See the KDE Eco Get
Involved page for more information on how to participate.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] One more pidfdfs surprise]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976125/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976125/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T18:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "pidfdfs" virtual filesystem was added to the 6.9 kernel release as a
way to export better information about running processes to user space.  It
replaced a previous implementation in a way that was, on its surface, fully
compatible while adding a number of new capabilities.  This transition,
which was intended to be entirely invisible to existing applications,
already ran into trouble in March, when a
misunderstanding with SELinux caused systems with pidfdfs to fail to boot
properly.  That problem was quickly fixed, but it turns out that there was
one more surprise in store, showing just how hard ABI compatibility can be
at times.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CFP: the 2024 Kernel Maintainers Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976319/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976319/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T15:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Kernel Maintainers Summit will happen on September 17 in
Vienna, Austria; it is an invitation-only event for a small group to
discuss important kernel-development problems.  The call for
proposals for this gathering has now been posted.  One of the best ways
to be invited to the event is to propose a topic that needs discussion in
that forum.  The deadline for proposals is June 18.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25 Years of Krita]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976211/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976211/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developers of the Krita painting
application are celebrating
25 years of development with a detailed history of the project.


	A quarter century. That's how long we've been working on
	Krita. Well, what would become Krita. It started out as KImageShop,
	but that name was nuked by a now long-dead German lawyer. Then it
	was renamed to Krayon, and that name was also nuked. Then it was
	renamed to Krita, and that name stuck.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976209/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976209/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:05:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, 389-ds:1.4, ansible-core bug fix, enhancement, and, bind and dhcp, container-tools:rhel8, edk2, exempi, fence-agents, freeglut, frr, gdk-pixbuf2, ghostscript, git-lfs, glibc, gmp, go-toolset:rhel8, grafana, grub2, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, gstreamer1-plugins-base, gstreamer1-plugins-good, harfbuzz, httpd:2.4, Image builder components bug fix, enhancement and, kernel, kernel-rt, krb5, less, LibRaw, libsndfile, libssh, libtiff, libX11, libXpm, linux-firmware, motif, mutt, nghttp2, openssh, pam, pcp, pcs, perl-Convert-ASN1, perl-CPAN, perl:5.32, pki-core:10.6 and pki-deps:10.6, pmix, poppler, python-dns, python-jinja2, python-pillow, python27:2.7, python3, python3.11, python3.11-cryptography, python3.11-urllib3, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9, qt5-qtbase, resource-agents, squashfs-tools, sssd, systemd, tigervnc, traceroute, vorbis-tools, webkit2gtk3, xorg-x11-server, xorg-x11-server-Xwayland, and zziplib), Debian (gst-plugins-base1.0), Fedora (cacti, cacti-spine, roundcubemail, and wireshark), Oracle (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, bind and dhcp, gdk-pixbuf2, git-lfs, glibc, grafana, krb5, pcp, python-dns, python3, sssd, tigervnc, xorg-x11-server, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Red Hat (edk2, less, nghttp2, and ruby:3.0), SUSE (gstreamer-plugins-base, Java, kernel, and python-requests), and Ubuntu (ffmpeg, node-browserify-sign, postgresql-14, postgresql-15, postgresql-16, and python-pymysql).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이슬람 사원 앞 바베큐 파티, 누가 이들을 극단으로 내모는가.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109388</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109388"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T08:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[토론회 지상 중계] 혐오와 차별을 넘어: 대구 이슬람 사원 논란이 드러낸 한국의 갈등 구조. 대구 이슬람 사원은 아직도 공사를 시작하지 못하고 있다. 대한변호사협회가 조사단을 꾸려서 무슬림 학생들과 지역 주민, 대구 북구청 관계자 등을 면담하고 보고서를 냈다. 다음은 5월31일 대한변협 주최 토론회 내용을 정리한 것이다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 생각해 볼 부분. 조사단 보고서의 핵심 제안. 주민들은...
The post 이슬람 사원 앞 바베큐 파티, 누가 이들을 극단으로 내모는가. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify Tenant as a Service with the Multi Tenant Operator]]></title>
        <id>00c73331-0dfc-460c-8020-a23d38867975</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/31/simplify-tenant-service-multi-tenant-operator"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing environments efficiently has become a significant challenge for DevOps engineers, platform engineers, and developers. The concept of Environment as a Service (EaaS) promises agility and scalability but is often challenged with the complexities of provisioning, de-provisioning, applying consistent configurations across namespaces, and managing Day 2 operations. Some of the challenges include ensuring isolation between teams, managing access controls and automating the environment life cycles to support CI/CD (continuous integration/continuous deployment). As organizations strive to streamline these processes, the need for a product that can offer simple, efficient, flexible and expandable solutions is very important. 
In this article, we will explore how the Multi Tenant Operator b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>asherman@redhat.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware of Bioware]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/bioware/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/bioware/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an archive of some posts in a forum thread titled "Beware of Bioware" in a now defunct forum, with comments from that forum as well as blog comments from a now defunct blog that archived that made the first attempt to archive this content. The original posts were deleted shortly after being posted, replaced with "big scary company vs. li'l ol' me."

Milez5858
EA gets a lot of the grief for their employment history.
For anyone considering work at Bioware, beware of them as well.
They use seriously cult like tactics to keep their employees towing the company line, but don't be fooled. The second you don't tow that line you'll be walked out the doors.
They love out of country workers because they don't understand the Canadian labour laws. They continually fire people with out warning.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민희진의 반전, “배신 맞지만 배임 아니다”: 슬로우레터 5월31일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109356</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109356"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T22:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[성 추문 은폐, 트럼프 34건 유죄. 최태원 노소영에게 1조3808억 원 분할. SK 경영권 위협에 주가는 폭등. 노태우 비자금 300억 원. 배신 맞지만 배임 아니다, 민희진 해임 금지. 쟁점과 현안. 민주당 1호 법안은 채 상병 특검법. 이재명 대권 맞춤당 된다. “뼈가 빠지게 뛰겠다.” 다르게 읽기. 대통령 개인 폰 괜찮나. 1분기 성장률 1.3%의 비밀. ‘즉강끝’의 한계. 더...
The post 민희진의 반전, “배신 맞지만 배임 아니다”: 슬로우레터 5월31일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Standardizing the BPF ISA]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975830/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975830/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:19:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While BPF may be most famous for its use in the Linux kernel, there is actually
a growing effort to standardize BPF for use on other systems. These include

eBPF for Windows, but also

uBPF,

rBPF,

hBPF,

bpftime, and
others. Some hardware manufacturers are even
considering integrating BPF directly into networking hardware. Dave Thaler
led two sessions about all of the problems that cross-platform use inevitably
brings and the current status of the standardization work at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro and 1.5 Flash GA, 1.5 Flash tuning support, higher rate limits, and more API updates]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T20:15:11.266Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re incredibly excited to see what you build with these new models. Get started with Gemini 1.5 Flash and 1.5 Pro free of charge in Google AI Studio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] New APIs for filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975444/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975444/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T13:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of extensions to the statx()
system call comes up frequently at the Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit; this year's edition was
no exception.  Kent Overstreet led the first filesystem-only session at the
summit on querying information about filesystems that have subvolumes and
snapshots. While it was billed as a discussion on statx()
additions, it ranged more widely over new APIs needed for modern filesystems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 6.9.3 and 6.8.12]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976007/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976007/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.9.3 and 6.8.12 stable kernels.  As usual, they contain
lots of important fixes throughout the tree.  Note that 6.8.12 is the end
of the line for the 6.8.x stable kernel series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976006/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976006/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:47:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (python-pymysql), Fedora (chromium, mingw-python-requests, and thunderbird), Mageia (perl-Email-MIME and qtnetworkauth5 & qtnetworkauth6), Red Hat (gdisk and python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9 modules), SUSE (freerdp, gdk-pixbuf, gifsicle, glib2, java-1_8_0-ibm, kernel, libfastjson, libredwg, nodejs16, python, python3, python36, rpm, warewulf4, and xdg-desktop-portal), and Ubuntu (gst-plugins-base1.0, python-werkzeug, and tpm2-tss).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing the behavior of generated HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Level3TestingHtmlBehaviour</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Level3TestingHtmlBehaviour"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the story so far, Matteo Vaccari has shown how
         to test the behaviour of the HTML templates,
         by checking the structure of the generated HTML. That's good, but what
         if we want to test the behavior of the HTML itself, plus any CSS and
         JavaScript it may use?
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensure a scalable and performant environment for ROSA with hosted control planes]]></title>
        <id>66991237-1821-4b2c-bf71-14788227dcdf</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/30/ensure-scalable-and-performant-environment-rosa-hosted-control-planes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Service on AWS (ROSA) is a turn-key and performant solution to run managed Red Hat OpenShift on Amazon Web Services (AWS). It lets users to focus more on their applications and less on the infrastructure or platform it runs on, helping drive developer innovation. 
Ensuring that OpenShift is performant and scalable is a core tenant of the OpenShift Performance and Scale team at Red Hat. Prior to its release (and still to this day), ROSA undergoes a vast array of performance and scale testing to ensure that it delivers industry leading performance. These tests run the gamut from control plane and data path focus, to upgrades, to network performance. These tests have been used to help measure and better the performance of “classic” ROSA, but what happens when we move to host…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Russell Zaleski</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 30, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974709/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974709/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T02:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 30, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/30, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594816</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594816/5-30-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T02:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[식물 정권의 세 가지 무기, ‘레임덕’ 막으려다 ‘데드덕’ 간다: 슬로우레터 5월30일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109330</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109330"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T22:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[거부, 거부, 거부, 거부. 22대 국회 첫날 1호 법안은 채 상병 특검법. 윤석열-이종섭 통화기록, 탄핵 태블릿될까. 공수처의 고민. 군 사망 사고의 구멍. 쟁점과 현안. 김건희 수사 검사들 모두 남았다. 북한에서 넘어온 ‘오물 풍선’. 더 깊게 읽기. 지난해보다 더 적다. 지역은 솔로 지옥. 다르게 읽기. 충주 사과 미국에서 반값에 팔리는 이유. 호미로 막을 걸 가래로 막아야...
The post 식물 정권의 세 가지 무기, ‘레임덕’ 막으려다 ‘데드덕’ 간다: 슬로우레터 5월30일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Error on verge of extinction, or why I put if (x = 42) in Red List of C & C++ bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1127/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1127/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we ask a programmer what bugs are the most common in C and C++ code, they'll name a null pointer dereference, undefined behavior, array overrun, and other typical error patterns. They may name an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Google Pay at I/O 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T20:14:29.081Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re adding new features to Google Pay so you can offer richer and more accessible payment experiences for your customers, and improved APIs to simplify your payments integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API for Custom LLMs on Device]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T20:14:29.078Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API enables developers to bring powerful new capabilities on-device, such as summarization, content generation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fedora approves shipping pre-built macOS binaries]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975445/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975445/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T18:15:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Asahi Linux project works
to support Linux on Apple Silicon hardware. The
project's flagship
distribution is the Fedora
Asahi Remix, which has its own installer (rather than Anaconda) to
accommodate the unique requirements of installing on Apple's
hardware. Previously the installer was built by the Asahi project, but it has asked for (and received) an exception
from the Fedora
Engineering Steering Committee (FESCo) to include two binaries
from upstream open-source projects so that the installer can be built on Fedora
infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Results from the 2024 FreeBSD Community Survey Report]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975807/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975807/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T17:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FreeBSD Foundation has announced
the 2024
FreeBSD Community Survey Report. The report provides a summary of
1,446 responses to an anonymous online survey of FreeBSD users. It
provides insights into user profiles, typical usage, how the FreeBSD
project is viewed, as well as recommendations for expanding the
FreeBSD community and contributor base:
The raw
data for the survey is available as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A plea for more thoughtful comments]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975597/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975597/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T16:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When redesigning the LWN site in 2002, we thought long and hard about
whether the ability to post comments should be part of it; LWN had not
offered that feature for the first four years of its existence.  There were
already plenty of examples of how comments can go bad by then, but we
decided to trust our readers to keep things under control.  Much of the
time, that trust has proved justified, but there have been times where
things have not gone so well.  This time is quickly becoming one of those
others.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero Tolerance for Bias]]></title>
        <id>3664645</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664645"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T15:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Structuring Success]]></title>
        <id>3664276</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664276"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T15:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parameterizing HTML template tests]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#MakeItEasyToAddNewTests</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#MakeItEasyToAddNewTests"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing templates for generating HTML leads to tests that are very
        similar. Matteo Vaccari wisely likes to separate the
        common elements of tests from those that vary. He continues
        his article to show how he does this by
        parameterizing the tests. The resulting tests are
        easier to write, and more importantly, faster to understand and modify.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prefetching in Single-Page Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#prefetching</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#prefetching"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juntao Qiu's completes his set of data fetching
      patterns for single-page applications. Prefetching involves fetching data
      before it's called for in the application flow. Although this can mean
      data is fetched unnecessarily, it reduces latency should the data be needed.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timing alternatives for critical applications in GNSS-denied environments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482404</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/timing-alternatives-for-critical-applications-in-gnss-denied-environments/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T13:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a menu of options and technologies available to provide timing services in GNSS/GPS-denied environments for extended periods of wide-area outages. Critical infrastructure and...
The post Timing alternatives for critical applications in GNSS-denied environments appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Olsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975737/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975737/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T13:20:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (glibc and tomcat), Fedora (chromium, fcitx5-qt, python-pyqt6, qadwaitadecorations, qgnomeplatform, qt6, qt6-qt3d, qt6-qt5compat, qt6-qtbase, qt6-qtcharts, qt6-qtcoap, qt6-qtconnectivity, qt6-qtdatavis3d, qt6-qtdeclarative, qt6-qtgraphs, qt6-qtgrpc, qt6-qthttpserver, qt6-qtimageformats, qt6-qtlanguageserver, qt6-qtlocation, qt6-qtlottie, qt6-qtmqtt, qt6-qtmultimedia, qt6-qtnetworkauth, qt6-qtopcua, qt6-qtpositioning, qt6-qtquick3d, qt6-qtquick3dphysics, qt6-qtquicktimeline, qt6-qtremoteobjects, qt6-qtscxml, qt6-qtsensors, qt6-qtserialbus, qt6-qtserialport, qt6-qtshadertools, qt6-qtspeech, qt6-qtsvg, qt6-qttools, qt6-qttranslations, qt6-qtvirtualkeyboard, qt6-qtwayland, qt6-qtwebchannel, qt6-qtwebengine, qt6-qtwebsockets, qt6-qtwebview, and zeal), Red Hat (glibc, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, linux-firmware, mod_http2, pcp, pcs, protobuf, python3, rpm-ostree, and rust), SUSE (git, glibc-livepatches, kernel, libxml2, openssl-1_1, SUSE Manager Client Tools, SUSE Manager Client Tools, salt, and xdg-desktop-portal), and Ubuntu (amavisd-new, firefox, flask-security, frr, git, intel-microcode, jinja2, libreoffice, linux-intel-iotg, unbound, and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 tips for using CMake with embedded software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482399</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3-tips-for-using-cmake-with-embedded-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T12:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vendor-supplied IDEs will generate makefiles for you, but if you want to leverage modern development practices, you need a tool that can help simplify your...
The post 3 tips for using CMake with embedded software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A 13-step compliance checklist for IoMT regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482396</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/a-13-step-compliance-checklist-for-iomt-regulations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T12:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost all Internet of Medical Things (IoMT) devices are subject to some government regulation and require a compliance effort by manufacturers. The Internet of Medical...
The post A 13-step compliance checklist for IoMT regulations appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilad David Maayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UBS, S&P 500 전망치를 5,600으로 상향 조정]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594811</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594811/ubs-sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d%ec%b9%98"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T01:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 만년 2등이었던 AMD, AMD 주가는 승자가 될 수 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594808</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594808/amd-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T01:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/29, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594799</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594799/5-29-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T01:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전례 없는 흥행 돌풍의 벌써 ‘레전드’…그런데 프로 되니까 수익 증발했다?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79434</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/28/npsp_caitlinclark/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_caitlinclark"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T23:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 미국 스포츠의 아이콘으로 떠오른 인물 가운데 대학을 갓 졸업한 프로 1년차 농구 선수 케이틀린 클락(Caitlin Clark)이 있습니다. NCAA 통산 득점 3,951점으로 역대 1위, 각종 기록은 물론 엄청난 인기로 흥행 측면에서도 전대미문이라 할 만한 기록을 세운 살아 있는 레전드지만, 그의 프로 첫 시즌 연봉은 76,535달러. 우리돈 약 1억 원입니다. 이름에서 추측할 수 있는 그는 여자 농구선수이기 때문입니다. 명시적인 차별이 있다기보다는 여자 프로농구리그(WNBA) 시장이 미국을 넘어 전 세계적으로 인기를 구가하는 NBA에 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use I2C devices in (Apache) NuttX: Adding support for an I2C device in your board]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1668.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1668.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T22:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously in this EmbeddedRelated article,
 we saw how to
find an I2C device connected to your board using the i2ctool that is very familiar for people with previous experience with embedded Linux. 
Today we will see how to add support to an I2C device (i.e. BMP280 sensor) in your board. So, lets to get started!
NuttX uses a very simple approach to interface with devices connected to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[일찍 찾아온 조중동의 ‘헤어질 결심’, 손절 타이밍은 언제일까: 슬로우레터 5월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109284</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109284"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T22:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[특검법 부결, 여기서 끝이 아니다. 22대 국회에서 다시 간다. 쟁점과 현안. 윤석열-이종섭 통화 기록도 나왔다. 또 거부권? “민생 법안 날렸다.” 다르게 읽기. 윤석열을 지킬 수 있을까. 더 깊게 읽기. 30년 뒤 서울 중위 연령은 56세. 생성형 AI는 ‘돈 먹는 하마’. “뭉개면서 가겠죠.” 오늘의 TMI. 수도권 거주자, 서울 출근에 평균 71분. 성심당, “임대료 1억 넘으면 대전역점...
The post 일찍 찾아온 조중동의 ‘헤어질 결심’, 손절 타이밍은 언제일까: 슬로우레터 5월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What errors are lurking in LLVM code?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1126/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1126/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM is an open-source project with a pretty large code base. The acme in terms of code quality, considering its size and open-source nature. After all, it's the developers of compiler tools who know...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Supporting BPF in GCC]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975412/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975412/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T19:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GCC project has been working to support compiling to BPF
for some time. José Marchesi and David Faust spoke in an extended session at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit
about how that work has been going, and what is left for GCC to be on-par with
LLVM with regard to BPF support. They also related tentative plans for how
GCC BPF support would be maintained in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Filesystems and iomap]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974958/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974958/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iomap
block-mapping abstraction is being used by more filesystems, in part
because of its support for large folios.  But there are some challenges in
adopting iomap, which was the topic of a discussion led by Ritesh Harjani
in a combined storage and filesystem session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  One of the main trouble
spots is how to handle metadata, which is not an area that iomap has been aimed
at.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Measuring memory fragmentation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974943/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974943/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:29:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the final session in the memory-management track of the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, the exhausted group of
developers looked one more time at the use of huge pages and the associated
problem of memory fragmentation.  At its worst, this problem can make huge
pages harder (and more expensive) to allocate.  Luis Chamberlain, who ran
the session, felt that people were worried about this problem, but that
there was little data on how severe it truly is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The state of the memory-management community in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974939/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974939/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:28:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A longstanding tradition in the memory-management track of the Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit is a session with
maintainer Andrew Morton to discuss the overall state of the community and
the development process.  The 2024 gathering upheld that tradition toward
the end of the final day of the event.  It seems that Morton and the
assembled developers were all happy with how memory-management work is
going, but there is always room for improvement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975529/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975529/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T13:19:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (less), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable), SUSE (apache2, java-1_8_0-openj9, kernel, libqt5-qtnetworkauth, and openssl-3), and Ubuntu (netatalk and python-cryptography).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary deployment strategy with Argo Rollouts and OpenShift Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>05ca9844-4e44-40f2-9528-e2bc24daff78</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/28/canary-deployment-strategy-argo-rollouts-and-openshift-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous articles, I explained how to implement a canary deployment strategy with OpenShift Service Mesh and another article with Argo Rollouts. In this article, we will walk through the same example, this time using both technologies: Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh and Argo Rollouts.
Argo Rollouts is a Kubernetes controller and set of CRDs that provide advanced deployment capabilities such as blue/green, canary, canary analysis, experimentation, and progressive delivery features to Kubernetes. In this demo, we are going to use canary capabilities. 
You can also check this other article for a blue/green deployment strategy with Argo Rollouts.
In the next sections, we will see a real example of how to install, deploy, and manage the life cycle of cloud-native applications doing canary…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Severiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A beginner's guide to the Shenandoah garbage collector]]></title>
        <id>76116a09-d358-4b72-a338-0e642225226f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/28/beginners-guide-shenandoah-garbage-collector"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a quick introduction to Red Hat's Shenandoah, a high-performance low-pause-time garbage collector. It covers Shenandoah's basic features, use cases, garbage collection (GC) logging, and basic troubleshooting.
This post is meant to be a straightforward overview. For a deeper dive, I recommend going straight to the upstream documentation page. The upstream email list is shenandoah-dev@openjdk.org.
About Shenandoah GC
Here is a very quick summary of Shenandoah's key characteristics:

Concurrent: This means the application runs together with the garbage collection.
Location-based GC: Forwarding pointers enable Shenandoah to collect each region independently without remembered sets.
Not generational-based: This means the log does not have Young, Tenure, or Old divisions; Therefo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 인간보다 로봇에 더 혜택이 많은 미국, 우리는?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79082</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/27/npsp_aijobs/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aijobs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T22:59:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 8일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 인공지능(AI), 범용 인공지능(AGI) 같은 단어가 더는 낯설지 않은 용어가 된 요즘입니다. 인류의 삶을 근본적으로 바꿔놓을 수 있는 잠재력을 지닌 강력하고 새로운 기술인 만큼 인공지능 시대를 맞아 논의하고 대비해야 할 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“대통령이 격노한 게 죄냐”, 국민의힘 이탈표 17표에 윤석열의 운명이 걸렸다: 슬로우레터 5월28일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109254</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109254"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T22:05:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[채 상병 특검법 이탈표 최소 5명. “대통령이 격노한 게 죄냐.” 간단한 복습. 쟁점과 현안. 한일 vs 중 대화. 북한 정찰 위성은 실패. ‘비윤’ 나경원의 질주, “개헌 논의도 가능.” 연금 개혁 불발. 언론은 압도적으로 이재명 편이다. 더 깊게 읽기. 법안 63%가 버려졌다. 대통령은 해결사, 장관은 희생양. 민정수석은 대통령 뒤 봐주는 자리가 아니다. 다르게 읽기. 윤석열이 기시다에게...
The post “대통령이 격노한 게 죄냐”, 국민의힘 이탈표 17표에 윤석열의 운명이 걸렸다: 슬로우레터 5월28일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huston: Calling Time on DNSSEC?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975454/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975454/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T21:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff Huston suggests
that it is time to give up on DNSSEC and look for a better way to secure
the Internet namespace.


	What appears to be very clear (to me at any rate!) is that DNSSEC
	as we know it today is just not going anywhere. It's too complex,
	too fragile and just too slow to use for the majority of services
	and their users. Some value its benefits highly enough that they
	are prepared to live with its shortcomings, but that's not the case
	for the overall majority of name holders and for the majority of
	users, and no amount of passionate exhortations about DNSSEC will
	change this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/27, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594796</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594796/5-27-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T17:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LLVM improvements for BPF verification]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974945/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974945/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T17:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Jowett gave a remote presentation at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit about what features could be
added to LLVM to make writing BPF programs easier. While there is nothing specific
to LLVM about BPF code (and the next session in the track was led by GCC
developer José Marchesi about better support for that compiler), LLVM is currently the most
common way to turn C code into BPF bytecode. That translation, however, runs
into problems when the BPF verifier cannot understand the code LLVM's
optimizations produce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fleshing out memory descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974937/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974937/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the long-term goals of the folio conversion in the kernel's
memory-management subsystem is the replacement of the page
structure, which describes a page of physical memory, with an eight-byte
"memory descriptor".  This change would reduce the overhead of tracking
physical memory, increase type safety, and make memory management more
flexible.  Thus far, though, details on what the memory-descriptor future
will look like have been relatively scarce.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Matthew Wilcox led a
discussion to try to fill in the picture somewhat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975399/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975399/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache2, bluez, chromium, fossil, libreoffice, python-pymysql, redmine, and ruby-rack), Fedora (buildah, crosswords, dotnet7.0, glycin-loaders, gnome-tour, helix, helvum, libipuz, loupe, maturin, mingw-libxml2, ntpd-rs, perl-Email-MIME, and a huge list of Rust-based packages due to a "mini-mass-rebuild" that updated the toolchain to Rust 1.78 and picked up fixes for various pieces), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, mariadb, and roundcubemail), Oracle (kernel, libreoffice, nodejs, and tomcat), and SUSE (cJSON, libfastjson, opera, postgresql15, python3, and qt6-networkauth).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.10 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974869/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974869/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released 6.10-rc1 and closed
the 6.10 merge window on May 26.  By that time, 11,534 non-merge
changesets had been pulled into the mainline for the next release; nearly
5,000 of those came in after "The first half of
the 6.10 merge window" was written.  While the latter half of the merge
window tends to focus more on fixes, there was also a lot of new
functionality that landed during this time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The next steps for the maple tree]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974860/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974860/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T12:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maple tree data structure was added
during the 6.1 development cycle; since then, it has taken its
place at the core of the kernel's memory-management subsystem.
Unsurprisingly, work on maple trees is not yet done.  Maple-tree maintainer
Liam Howlett ran a session in the memory-management track of the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit to discuss the current
state of the maple tree and which features can be expected next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세계화의 딜레마, 탈출을 꿈꾸는 청년]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105879</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105879"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T10:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)의 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기. 인트로 & 요약 (약 3분) 지난 인터뷰들 오늘은 세계화 인터뷰, 그 네 번째 마지막 편이다. 그동안 이상헌 박사와 함께 폴 콜리어의 책 [자본주의의 미래] (2018, 한글 2020)을 매개로 ‘세계화’의 문제에 관해 이야기했다. 국제적 관계: 라인야후 사태와 호혜성 오늘 주제는 국제 관계다. 여러 국제기구를 이야기하고,...
The post 세계화의 딜레마, 탈출을 꿈꾸는 청년 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Core competencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1666.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1666.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T07:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a good, albeit rather general, rule that applies to the management of a successful business: focus on what you do well, then do it better than everyone else. There are numerous examples of how companies have been very successful by following this approach.
But the world of embedded software is commonly an exception …
To start with, I can cite some examples of good practice:
Have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공익소송의 가치, 돈으로 막아서도 괜찮은가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109234</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109234"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T04:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[호주제 폐지, 낙태죄 헌법소원 등 ‘공익소송’은 우리 사회에 전향적인 변화를 일으켜 왔습니다. 소송에서의 승패를 넘어서서, 국가기관이나 대기업 등을 향한 소송 제기 자체가 사회의 변화를 촉구하는 공익적 목적을 가지는데요. 하지만 패소한다면 막대한 소송비용을 오롯이 떠맡아야 합니다. 현행 민사소송법이 예외 없이 소송비용은 무조건 패소한 측이 부담한다고 규정하고 있기 때문입니다(패소자부담주의). 이에 공익소송 당사자들이 헌법소원을 제기했지만, 헌법재판소는 해당 법조항이...
The post 공익소송의 가치, 돈으로 막아서도 괜찮은가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Function Composition and the Pipe Operator in C++23 – With std::expected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/pipe-operator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/pipe-operator/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll show how to implement a custom pipe operator and apply it to a data processing example. Thanks to C++23 and std::expectedwe can write a rather efficient framework that easily handles unexpected outcomes.
This is a collaborative guest post by prof. Bogusław Cyganek:
        
        

        
Prof. Cyganek is a researcher and lecturer at the Department of Electronics, AGH University of Science and Technology in Cracow, Poland. He has worked as a software engineer for a number of companies such as Nisus Writer USA, Compression Techniques USA, Manta Corp. USA, Visual Atoms UK, Wroclaw University in Poland, and Diagnostyka Inc. Poland. His research interests include computer vision and pattern recognition, as well as the development of embedded systems. See his recent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975145/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975145/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T22:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released
6.10-rc1 and closed the merge window for this release.  For reasons
that have not been spelled out, the codename for the release has been
changed to "Baby Opossum Posse".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“정의 구현” 대 “마녀사냥”, 프레임 전쟁의 승자와 패자는]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79414</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/26/npsp_trumptrialelection/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_trumptrialelection"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T22:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이달 초 뉴욕타임스가 공개한 대선 여론조사 결과를 보면, 바이든 대통령이 트럼프 전 대통령에게 계속 뒤처지는 거로 나왔습니다. 여러 가지 원인이 지목되는 가운데, 지난달 맨해튼 법정에서 시작된 트럼프 전 대통령의 소위 “입막음용 뒷돈” 재판은 트럼프에게 오히려 득이 되고 있다는 주장이 설득력을 얻고 있습니다. 로스 더우댓이 그런 주장을 담은 칼럼을 썼습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 여론조사 결과를 해설로 덧붙였습니다. 전문 번역: 야당 대통령 후보 향한 이런 식의 법정 공세, 정치 과잉의 부조리 아닌가: 이것은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열의 계란말이 파티, 기자들은 아무것도 묻지 않았다: 슬로우레터 5월27일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109185</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109185"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T22:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[술은 없었지만 화기애애했다. “국민 분노 비웃나.” 쟁점과 현안. 윤석열 지지율은 여전히 24%. 특검법 이탈표 4명으로 늘었다. “라인 사태 외교 사안 아니다.” 더 깊게 읽기. “44% 받겠다” 이재명 제안에 국민의힘 ‘움찔’. “연금 개혁은 코끼리 옮기기 같은 것.” 모수 개혁과 구조 개혁. 다르게 읽기. 대북 송금 사건? 쌍방울 주가조작 사건이다. 엥겔 지수의 함정. 시진핑은 왜 안 왔을까....
The post 윤석열의 계란말이 파티, 기자들은 아무것도 묻지 않았다: 슬로우레터 5월27일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sampling error in software engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8811</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/05/26/sampling-error-in-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T21:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the physical sciences, measurement error occurs because of accuracy limits on the device used to make the measurement and the interpretation of the data by the person doing the measurement. In software engineering, some measurements appear to be error free. For instance, lines of code is a discrete value that is easily counted. While […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한미반도체 HBM 기술 관련 삼성전자 기술탈취 소송을 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594788</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594788/%ec%83%81%ec%a0%84%ec%a0%84%ec%9e%90-%ea%b8%b0%ec%88%a0%ed%83%88%ec%b7%a8"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T13:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모처럼 조선일보가 이재명을 칭찬하는 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109158</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109158"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T07:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 국민연금 막판 협상, 누가 거짓말을 하나: 더 내고 더 받는 개혁, 이것이 최선일까. 이재명(민주당 대표)이 승부수를 던졌다. 국회에서 기자간담회를 열고 “여당이 제시한 소득대체율 44%를 전적으로 수용하겠다”고 말했다. “꼭 해야 할 일인데 시간은 없으니 불가피하게 민주당이 다 양보하겠다”면서 “1%포인트 차이 때문에 연금 개혁안을 무산시킬 수는 없다”고 강조했다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 핵심 쟁점. 충돌하는 지점. 말이...
The post 모처럼 조선일보가 이재명을 칭찬하는 이유. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight weekend stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975072/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975072/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T00:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9.2, 6.8.11, 6.6.32, 6.1.92, 5.15.160, 5.10.218, 5.4.277, and 4.19.315
stable kernel updates have all been released. Each contains an
important set of fixes. Users of those kernels should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comments on the FTC antitrust investigation of Google]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/ftc-google-antitrust/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/ftc-google-antitrust/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[html {
  max-width: 170ch;
  padding: 0.5em 0.5em;
  margin: auto;
  line-height: 1.5;
  font-size: 1.15em;
}


This is a summary of the publicly available documents on the 2011-2012 FTC investigation of Google's allegedly antitcompetive actions in search and ads, followed by a tech-focused analysis of the decision from someone who's worked at the two companies that are discussed in the most detail in the memos (Google and Microsoft), worked in search, and worked closely with ads teams on optimizing ads ranking algorithms. I've seen a number of law-focused and economics-focused analyses, but I haven't seen a tech-focused analysis in a level of detail I find satisfying. In particular, a number of key arguments in the memos rely on evidence and inferences that would've seen implausible to so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Two talks on multi-size transparent huge page performance]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974826/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974826/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T16:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using huge pages has been known for years to improve the performance of
many workloads.  But traditional huge pages, often sized by the CPU at 2MB,
can be difficult to allocate and can waste memory due to internal
fragmentation.  Driven by both the folio transition and hardware
improvements, attention to smaller, multi-size transparent huge pages
(mTHPs) has been on the rise.  In two memory-management-track sessions at
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, developers discussed the
kernel's ability to reliably allocate mTHPs and the performance gains that
result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arenas and the almighty concatenation operator]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/25/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/25/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I continue to streamline an arena-based paradigm, and stumbled
upon a concise technique for dynamic growth — an efficient, generic
“concatenate anything to anything” within an arena built atop a core of
9-ish lines of code. The key insight originated from a reader suggestion
about dynamic arrays. The subject of concatenation can be a string,
dynamic array, or even something else. The “system” is extensible, and
especially useful for path handling.
Continuing from last time, the examples are in light, C-style C++.
I chose it because templates and function overloading express the concepts
succinctly. It uses no standard library functionality, so converting to C,
or similar, should be straightforward. The core concatenation “operator”:

template<typename T>
T concat(arena *a, T head, T tail)
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guidelines for computing sizes and subscripts]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/24/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/24/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T22:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Occasionally we need to compute the size of an object that does not yet
exist, or a subscript that may fall out of bounds. It’s easy to miss
the edge cases where results overflow, creating a nasty, subtle bug, even
in the presence of type safety. Ideally such computations happen in
specialized code, such as inside an allocator (calloc, reallocarray)
and not outside by the allocatee (i.e. malloc). Mitigations exist with
different trade-offs: arbitrary precision, or using a wider fixed integer
— i.e. 128-bit integers on 64-bit hosts. In the typical case, working only
with fixed size-type integers, I’ve come up with a set of guidelines to
avoid overflows in the edge cases.
Range check before computing a result. No exceptions.
Do not cast unless you know a priori the operand is in range.
Never…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Atomic writes without tears]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974578/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974578/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T21:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Garry and Ted Ts'o led a discussion about supporting atomic writes for buffered
I/O, without any torn (or partial) writes to the device, at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  It is something of a
continuation of a discussion at last year's
summit. The goal is to help PostgreSQL, which writes its data using
16KB buffered I/O; it currently has to do a lot of extra work to ensure
that its data is safe on disk.  A promise of non-torn, 16KB buffered writes
would allow the database 
to avoid doing double writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Allocator optimizations for transparent huge pages]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974636/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974636/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T20:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Linux kernel, posted in 1991, ran on a system with a 4KB page
size.  Over 30 years later, most of us are still running on systems
with 4KB pages, even though the amount of installed memory has grown by a
few orders of magnitude.  It is generally accepted that using large page
sizes results in better performance for most applications, but allocating
larger pages is often difficult.  During a memory-management session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Yu Zhao presented his
ideas on improving the allocation of huge pages in the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google @ KotlinConf 2024: A Look Inside Multiplatform Development with KMP and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T20:13:52.290Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following our recent Google I/O announcement recommending Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) for sharing business logic across mobile, web, server, and desktop platforms, and our move to use KMP in Google Workspace, KotlinConf 2024 was the next moment to share the highlights and connect with the Kotlin community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Recent improvements to BPF's struct_ops mechanism]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974848/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974848/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T19:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kui-Feng Lee spoke early in the BPF track at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit about some of the
recent improvements to BPF. These changes were largely driven by the
sched_ext work that David Vernet had covered in
the previous talk. Lee focused on changes relevant to struct_ops
programs, but several of those changes apply to all BPF programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Readying DNF5 for Fedora 41]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/969640/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/969640/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of Fedora 40 it's time to
start looking ahead to what Fedora 41 has in store. One of the largest
changes planned for the next release is a switch to
DNF5, a C++ rewrite of the DNF
package manager. A previous attempt to make the switch, during the Fedora 39 cycle, was called off, and
deferred to Fedora 41. The developers have had nearly a year to address
compatibility problems and bring DNF5 to a state suitable to replace DNF4. Signs point to a successful switch in
the upcoming release, though there may be a few surprises lurking for Fedora users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: a look at the implications of the Cyber Resilience Act (CRA)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482387</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/podcast-a-look-at-the-implications-of-the-cyber-resilience-act-cra/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Parliament approved the CRA in March 2024, which means companies will now need to step up their preparations or be prepared to pay fines for non-compliance.
The post Podcast: a look at the implications of the Cyber Resilience Act (CRA) appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFC I2C bridge tag enables secure contactless IoT device authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482382</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nfc-i2c-bridge-tag-enables-secure-contactless-iot-device-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T15:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infineon Technologies has launched a high-performance NFC I2C bridge tag for single-tap authentication and secured configuration of IoT devices. 
The post NFC I2C bridge tag enables secure contactless IoT device authentication appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated parking replaces ultrasonic with vision cameras]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482377</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/automated-parking-replaces-ultrasonic-with-vision-cameras/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nodar said its solution is able to combine different independently mounted stereo pairs of cameras around the vehicle to generate high-resolution 3D point clouds.
The post Automated parking replaces ultrasonic with vision cameras appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Large-folio support for shmem and tmpfs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974630/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974630/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel contains a pair of related filesystems that, among other things,
can be used for shared-memory applications; shmem is an internal mechanism
used within the kernel, while the tmpfs filesystem is mounted and
accessible from user space.  As is the case elsewhere in the kernel, these
subsystems would benefit from the addition of large-folio support.  During
a joint storage, filesystem, and memory-management session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Daniel Gomez talked about
the work he is doing to add that support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitKeeper, Linux, and licensing disputes: How Linus wrote Git in 14 days 
(Graphite blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974914/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974914/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
Graphite blog post retells the history of the BitKeeper fiasco and the
dawn of the Git era.


	When we think of history, we often romanticize it as being born of
	a sudden stroke of inspiration. But the creation of git shows the
	far harsher reality of invention: a slowly escalating disagreement
	over a license; the need for a scrappy backup solution to unblock
	work; and then continued polishing and iteration through years and
	years, led not by the inventor, but rather a community.


For those who weren't around in those days, a perusal of the LWN coverage
from the time might be of interest too, including:


 Our first mention of BitKeeper
     in October 1998
 Not quite open source,
     1999
 Linus tries out BitKeeper, 2002
 The free software community and proprietary
     packages, 2002
 The kernel and BitKeeper part ways,
     2005
 How Tridge reverse engineered
     BitKeeper, 2005
 The guts of Git, 2005


...and a lot more for those who care to search for it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974913/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974913/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium, libreoffice, and thunderbird), Red Hat (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, gdk-pixbuf2, git-lfs, glibc, python3, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), SUSE (firefox, opensc, and ucode-intel), and Ubuntu (cjson and gnome-remote-desktop).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trustworthy AI using Confidential Federated Learning]]></title>
        <id>3665220</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3665220"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T12:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[스노우플레이크 실적을 읽는월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594786</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594786/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%8a%a4%eb%85%b8%ec%9a%b0%ed%94%8c%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/24, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594784</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594784/5-24-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement AI-driven edge to core data pipelines]]></title>
        <id>0e750f45-625d-460e-8591-9f922c1b562e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/24/implement-ai-driven-edge-core-data-pipelines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The interaction of AI/ML and edge computing occurs in a variety of businesses. For example, in the retail industry, customer behavior and patterns can be used to determine promotions. In a manufacturing facility, likewise, data inference can help improve processes where machines are failing, products are not up to standard, and so on. The basic premise is that you might collect data and then infer from it in order to make decisions based on it.
In the context of this retail use case example, a superstore company has branches spread across the country. Each branch decides the products it wants to sell and can customize an AI/ML intelligent app for customers to use.
This article presents a video demonstration illustrating an opinionated solution capable of automating a continuous cycle for r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno Meseguer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run OpenShift sandboxed containers with hosted control planes]]></title>
        <id>d8d96b3f-e3b0-47e1-977f-c50b0810079b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/24/run-openshift-sandboxed-containers-hosted-control-planes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosted control planes, available via the multi-cluster engine, has been generally available since Red Hat OpenShift 4.14. Hosted control planes reduce costs and improve productivity for organizations adopting a multi-cluster approach.
OpenShift sandboxed containers, based on Kata Containers, and generally available since OpenShift 4.8, is a native Kubernetes CRI runtime that provides an additional layer of isolation for workloads through hardware virtualization.
When used together, hosted control planes and OpenShift sandboxed containers offer several benefits, such as speed, separation of concerns, and the necessary hardening to run multi-tenant workloads with stringent security constraints. 
This article provides a detailed guide on how to configure and run sandboxed workloads for OpenSh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camilla Conte, Adel Zaalouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MBTI? 30점짜리 심리테스트, 100점짜리 예능 소품]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108188</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108188"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T06:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 분석합니다. 이번 케이스는 MBTI(두둥!). “MBTI의 핵심은 내 성격을 내가 안다는 게 아니에요. 내가 세상 모든 사람을 MBTI 하나로 다 알 수 있다고 생각(착각)하는 거죠.” (캡콜드) MBTI, 더 말이 필요한가. 그 열풍에 관해 캡콜드(김낙호 펜실베이니아주립대학교 커뮤니케이션학과 교수)에게 물었다. MBTI 개요 MBTI 누가 만들었나. MBTI는 ‘마이어스-브리그스 유형 지표'(Myers-Briggs...
The post MBTI? 30점짜리 심리테스트, 100점짜리 예능 소품 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 이보다 더 좋을 순 없다, 목표주가 1400$까지 상향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594776</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594776/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T00:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 환율도 제각각, 음식값도 매일 달라지는 ‘메시의 나라’, “다시 위대”해질 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79059</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/23/npsp_javiermilei/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_javiermilei"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T22:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 3일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난 3월 초, 엿새간 아르헨티나에 다녀왔습니다. 다소 촉박하게 일정이 잡혀서 처음 가보는 나라, 지역임에도 미리 충분히 공부하고 준비하지 못한 채 비행기에 몸을 실었습니다. 사실 열정적인 축구팬인 저는 “현재 월드컵 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 ‘격노’ 담긴 녹음 파일, ‘스모킹 건’이 될까: 슬로우레터 5월24일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109076</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109076"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T22:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김계환 녹취 파일, ‘스모킹 건’이 될까. ‘격노’ 이후 모든 게 달라졌다. 김계환의 양심선언이 필요할 때다. 쟁점과 현안. 연금 개혁은 다음 국회로. 반도체 산업에 26조 원 투입. 물가 때문에… 기준 금리 동결. 가계 실질 소득, 7년 만에 최대폭 감소. 더 깊게 읽기. 4년 중임제 개헌, 해볼 만하다. “외롭습니다.” 다르게 읽기. 이종섭 출국 금지는 공수처 작품이었다. ‘버닝썬’이...
The post 윤석열 ‘격노’ 담긴 녹음 파일, ‘스모킹 건’이 될까: 슬로우레터 5월24일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A new swap abstraction layer for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974587/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974587/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T19:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swapping may be a memory-management technique at its core, but its
implementation also involves the kernel's filesystem and storage layers.
So it is not surprising that a session on the kernel's swap abstraction
layer, led by Chris Li at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, was held jointly by all
three of those tracks.  Li has some ambitious ideas for an improved
subsystem, but getting to a workable implementation may not be easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What's scheduled for sched_ext]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974387/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974387/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T17:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Vernet's second talk at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit was a summary of the state of
sched_ext, the extensible BPF scheduler that LWN
covered a in early May. In short, sched_ext is intended as a platform for
rapid experimentation with schedulers, and a tool to let performance-minded
administrators customize the scheduler to their workload. The patch set has seen
several revisions, becoming more generic and powerful over time.
Vernet spoke about what has been done in the past year,
and what is still missing before sched_ext can be considered pretty much
complete.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Splitting in Single-Page Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#IntroducingUserdetailcardComponent</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#IntroducingUserdetailcardComponent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Single-Page Applications often require a lot of code to be downloaded
       to the browser, which can delay a page's initial
       appearance. Juntao Qiu's next pattern, Code Splitting,
       describes how this code can be divided up, so that modules are only
       loaded if they are going to be needed, and the dangers of doing so.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Gear 24.05.0]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974708/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974708/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The KDE Project has announced the
release of KDE Gear 24.05.0, with new features and updates for the
more than 200 applications that
are part of the project. In addition to new versions of the Dolphin
file manager, Kdenlive video
editor, and Elisa music player, this
release includes five applications new to KDE Gear: the Audex CD-ripper application,
an application Accessibility
Inspector, the Francis
Pomodoro timer, Kalm to teach breathing techniques, and a Sokoban-like game
called Skladnik. See the
full
changelog for a complete list of changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The twilight of the version-1 memory controller]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974575/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974575/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost immediately after the merging of control
groups, kernel developers set their sights on reimplementing them
properly.  The second version of the control-group API started trickling
into the kernel around the 3.16 release in 2014 and users have long since
been encouraged to migrate, but support for (and users of) the initial API
remain.  At the 2024
Linux Storage, Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit,
memory-management developers discussed whether (and when) it might be
possible to remove the version-1 memory controller.  The session was led by
Shakeel Butt and (participating remotely) Roman Gushchin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974824/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974824/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T13:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (chromium, libxml2, pgadmin4, and python-libgravatar), Mageia (ghostscript), Red Hat (389-ds:1.4, ansible-core, bind and dhcp, container-tools:rhel8, edk2, exempi, fence-agents, freeglut, frr, ghostscript, glibc, gmp, go-toolset:rhel8, grafana, grub2, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, gstreamer1-plugins-base, gstreamer1-plugins-good, harfbuzz, httpd:2.4, idm:DL1, idm:DL1 and idm:client modules, kernel, kernel-rt, krb5, LibRaw, libreoffice, libsndfile, libssh, libtiff, libX11, libxml2, libXpm, linux-firmware, motif, mutt, openssh, osbuild and osbuild-composer, pam, pcp, pcs, perl-Convert-ASN1, perl-CPAN, perl:5.32, pki-core:10.6 and pki-deps:10.6 modules, pmix, poppler, postgresql-jdbc, python-dns, python-jinja2, python-pillow, python27:2.7, python3.11, python3.11-cryptography, python3.11-urllib3, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9 modules, qt5-qtbase, resource-agents, squashfs-tools, sssd, systemd, tigervnc, tomcat, traceroute, varnish:6, virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel modules, vorbis-tools, webkit2gtk3, xorg-x11-server, xorg-x11-server-Xwayland, and zziplib), SUSE (chromium, perl, postgresql14, and python-sqlparse), and Ubuntu (klibc, linux-aws-hwe, openssl, and vlc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidential Computing or Cryptographic Computing?]]></title>
        <id>3664295</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664295"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T12:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[네이버의 진짜 위기는 라인이 아니다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109022</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109022"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 최대 실적 내고도 주가가 안 오르는 이유: 검색 광고 시장 위축에 한 발 늦은 AI 전략, 새로운 성장 엔진이 필요한 시점. 누구나 잘 아는 것 같지만 의외로 잘 모르는 기업. 오늘 슬로우리포트에서는 네이버의 위기를 살펴봅니다. 국민주 네이버는 왜 사상 최대의 실적을 기록하고도 주가가 지지부진할까요? 라인야후 사태도 심각하지만 근본적으로 전망이 안 보인다는 관측이 많습니다. 한동안...
The post 네이버의 진짜 위기는 라인이 아니다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 1: Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) Introduction]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:65dfa3dd-b3dd-42ee-930d-1301a6ee028b</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/arm-scalable-matrix-extension-introduction"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog series provides an introduction to the Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) including SVE and SVE2.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zenon Xiu (修志龙）</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift Virtualization for VMware vSphere admins: Disaster and site recovery]]></title>
        <id>c724ccd6-3b6b-4679-8c6a-3541dd2bf6e7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/24/virtualization-vsphere-disaster-recovery"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes to think about disasters. Surely that won’t happen to you. Often the mantra is to hope for the best and plan for the worst. In today’s IT world, downtime, no matter how small, can have a disastrous effect on a business’ ability to compete in the marketplace. 
What is disaster recovery?
There are many options to consider when it comes to the concepts of business continuity and disaster recovery. Primarily we find ourselves concerned with two major metrics: the recovery point objective (RPO) and the recovery time objective (RTO). 
The RPO is what amount of data is considered an acceptable loss in the event of a disaster. If you lose data due to an unforeseen event, and your last successful backup and restore point is three days old, is that an acceptable loss of data? 
The RTO i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Cowles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing frameworks for images built via Insights image builder]]></title>
        <id>55dd06bd-950c-41d2-888a-fef10af36296</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/23/testing-frameworks-images-built-insights-image-builder"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building images for cloud deployments or on-premises servers provides a number of challenges. These include reducing the attack surface, ensuring the images are hardened, and monitoring their compliance on an ongoing basis. We will explore how Red Hat Insights can achieve what no other service can by leveraging Red Hat’s open hybrid cloud strategy. You can use Red Hat Insights image builder to deploy pre-hardened images then monitor the systems with our compliance tool, compared to using custom-built testing frameworks leveraging tools such as AWS Security Hub.
Building images
Insights image builder makes the process of hardening images much simpler because it leverages OpenSCAP remediations at build time before the image has even been launched. This is desirable since some options, such a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gianluca Zuccarelli, Obinna Ezeakachi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install and migrate to Red Hat build of Keycloak]]></title>
        <id>e8fa57ec-4e86-49e9-b732-e8ac2fd534f5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/23/migrate-sso-red-hat-build-keycloak"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat's single sign-on tool has long been a trusted solution for securing web applications and providing centralized identity management. However, with the introduction of the Red Hat build of Keycloak, a next-generation option has emerged. This article will guide you through how to migrate from Red Hat's single sign-on to Red Hat build of Keycloak, highlighting the benefits and considerations involved in this strategic move.
We'll delve into the key advantages of Red Hat build of Keycloak, such as its cloud-native architecture, enhanced performance, and streamlined configuration. Additionally, we'll provide a step-by-step approach to the migration process, ensuring a smooth transition with minimal disruption to your existing infrastructure. Whether you're seeking improved scalability, c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo Castelo, Ignacio Lago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘희생양 이론’으로 보는 학생인권조례 폐지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109000</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109000"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T06:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[심리학 및 사회학 연구에 뿌리를 둔 ‘희생양 이론’은 개인이나 집단이 자신의 문제나 실패에 관해 부당하게 다른 사람이나 집단을 비난하는 현상을 말한다. 희생양 메커니즘의 본질은 한 개인이나 단체·사회가 서로의 이해관계가 충돌했을 때 또는 그저 그들의 욕망이 충돌해서 문제가 드러날 때 힘없는 또는 상대적으로 미약한 희생양에게 책임을 전가함으로써 진짜 문제의 원인인 가해자가 자신의 죄책감, 좌절감 또는 무능함을...
The post ‘희생양 이론’으로 보는 학생인권조례 폐지 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤지명</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 실적 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594774</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594774/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-2"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T03:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 23, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973888/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973888/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T01:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 23, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“검사 위에 여사, 이게 나라냐”, 동아일보 김순덕의 분노: 슬로우레터 5월23일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108962</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108962"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T22:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘VIP 격노’ 들은 사람이 또 있다. “이탈 표 10명은 나올 것.” “박정훈 기소 취소하자” 보고서 뭉갰다. 쟁점과 현안. “공매도 재개는 이복현 개인 의견.” 카드 연체율 9년 만에 최고. “전통과 권위의 정론지, 조선일보.” 더 깊게 읽기. 정권 말 복지부동이 벌써 시작됐다. 윤석열에게는 ‘레드팀’이 필요하다. 다르게 읽기. 나이 들면 운전 제한? 하루 만에 말 바꾼 이유. 안보동맹이...
The post “검사 위에 여사, 이게 나라냐”, 동아일보 김순덕의 분노: 슬로우레터 5월23일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++: freeing resources in destructors using helper functions]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1125/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1125/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll look at how to correctly destroy objects in the OOP-based C++ program without redundant operations. This is the final article in the series about the bugs in qdEngine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Supporting larger block sizes in filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974219/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974219/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T20:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a 
combined storage and filesystem session at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Luis Chamberlain led a
discussion on filesystem support for block sizes larger than the usual 4KB
page size, 
which followed up on  discussion from last year.  While the
session was meant to look at the intersection of larger block sizes
with atomic block writes  that avoid torn
(partial) writes (which was also discussed last year), it mostly focused on the
filesystem side.  Over time, the
block sizes offered by storage devices have risen from the original
512 bytes; Chamberlain
wanted to discuss filesystem support for block sizes larger than 4KB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The path to deprecating SPARSEMEM]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974517/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974517/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T18:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term "memory model" is used in a couple of ways within the kernel.
Perhaps the more obscure meaning is the memory-management subsystem's view
of how physical memory is organized on a given system.  A proper
representation of physical memory will be more efficient in terms of memory
and CPU use.  Since hardware comes in numerous variations, the kernel
supports a number of memory models to match; see this article for details.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Oscar Salvador,
presenting remotely, made the case for removing one of those models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Two sessions on CXL memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974518/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974518/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T18:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compute
Express Link (CXL) is a data-center-oriented memory solution that,
according to some in the industry, will yield large cost savings and
performance improvements.  Others are more skeptical.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, two sessions covered CXL
and how it will be supported in future kernels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A short note on how I use and render footnotes]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-footnote-rendering.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-footnote-rendering.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week I added a small feature to this website, changing the way it
       renders footnotes. That prompted me to write this quick note about how I
       use footnotes, and how that influences the best way to render them.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Documenting page flags by committee]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974515/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974515/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T17:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For every page of memory in the system, the kernel maintains a set of page
flags describing how the page is used and various aspects of its current
state.  Space for page flags has been in chronic short supply, leading to a desire to
eliminate or consolidate them whenever possible.  That objective, though,
is hampered by the fact that the purpose of many page flags is not well
understood.  In a memory-management-track session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Matthew Wilcox set out to
cooperatively update the page-flag documentation to improve that situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Merging msharefs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974512/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974512/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T17:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem of sharing page tables across processes has been discussed
numerous times over the years, Khaled Aziz said at the beginning of his 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit session on the topic.  He
was there to, once again, talk about the proposed mshare() system call (which, in its
current form, is no longer actually a system call but the feature still
goes by that name) and to see what can be done to finally get it into the
mainline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 실적에서 살펴볼 5가지 요소]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594772</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594772/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Toward the unification of hugetlbfs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974491/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974491/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's hugetlbfs
subsystem was the first mechanism by which the kernel made huge pages
available to user space; it was added to the 2.5.46 development kernel in
2002.  While hugetlbfs remains useful, it is also viewed as a sort of
second memory-management subsystem that would be best unified with the rest
of the kernel.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Peter Xu raised the
question of what that unification would involve and what the first steps
might be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The KeePassXC kerfuffle]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973782/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973782/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KeePassXC is an open-source (GPLv3),
cross-platform password manager with local-only data storage. The
project comes with a number of build
options that can be used to toggle optional features, such as browser
integration and password
database sharing. However, controversy ensued when Debian Developer Julian Klode decided to
make use of these compile flags to disable these features to improve security in the
keepassxc package uploaded to Debian unstable for the
upcoming Debian 13 ("Trixie") release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidential Container Groups]]></title>
        <id>3664293</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664293"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The interaction between memory reclaim and RCU]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974487/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974487/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit was a development
conference, where discussion was prioritized and presentations with a lot
of slides were discouraged.  Paul McKenney seemingly flouted this
convention in a joint session of the storage, filesystem, and
memory-management tracks where he presented about 50 slides — in five
minutes, twice.  The subject was the use of the read-copy-update (RCU)
mechanism in the memory-reclaim process, and whether changes to RCU would
be needed for that purpose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux 3.20.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974576/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974576/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
3.20.0 of the Alpine Linux
distribution has been released with initial support for 64-bit
RISC-V. Other important changes include updates to GNOME 46, 
KDE Plasma 6, and replacing Redis with Valkey due to Redis's
adoption of a non-free
license model. See the release
notes for more on this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing the contents of generated HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Level2TestingHtmlStructure</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Level2TestingHtmlStructure"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Vaccari continues his testing of
       template-generated HTML by describing tests for the contents of that
       HTML. He shows how to gradually build up the template, using Test-Driven
       Development in Go and Java. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Faster page faults with RCU-protected VMA walks]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974392/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974392/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking up a virtual memory area (VMA) in a process's address space, for
the handling of page faults or any of a number of other tasks, in
multi-threaded processes has long been bedeviled by lock contention in the
kernel.  As a result, developer gatherings have been subjected to many
sessions on how to improve the situation.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, developers in the
memory-management track met, in a session led by Liam Howlett, to talk
about a situation that has improved considerably in recent times, but which
still offers opportunities for optimization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974572/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974572/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (webkit2gtk), Fedora (kernel), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, djvulibre, gdk-pixbuf2.0, nss & firefox, postgresql15 & postgresql13, python-pymongo, python-sqlparse, stb, thunderbird, and vim), Red Hat (go-toolset:rhel8, nodejs, and varnish:6), SUSE (gitui, glibc, and kernel), and Ubuntu (libspreadsheet-parseexcel-perl, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gcp, python-idna, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Virtual machine scheduling with BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974363/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974363/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vineeth Pillai gave a remote talk at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit explaining how BPF could be
used to improve the performance of virtual machines (VMs). Pillai has

a patch
set designed to let guest and host machines share scheduling information in
order to eliminate some of the overhead of running in a VM. The assembled
developers had several comments on the design, but seemed overall to approve of
the prospect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FSM - Let 'em talk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1665.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1665.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T12:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the fourth part of my two-part article on state machines (1). This post topic has been suggested by
	Miro Samek, who, in a comment to my first post, wrote: "The biggest issues are not so much with the state machine implementations [...]. Instead, the biggest issues are with the code surrounding state machines.".

Indeed Miro is right, many
problems come from outside state...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>