<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2021-12-06T20:20:16.546Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A reference-count tracking infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877603/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877603/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T18:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reference counts are a commonly used mechanism for tracking the life cycle
of objects in a computing system.  As long as every user of an object
correctly maintains its references by incrementing and decrementing the
reference count, that object will persist for as long as it
is needed
and will be properly destroyed once the last user is done.  The "correctly"
in that sentence is important, though; things do not work
as well in the presence of reference-counting errors.  Networking
developer Eric Dumazet is working on a
reference-count tracking system that could prove useful for finding
these errors in the networking subsystem and, someday, throughout the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877821/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877821/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (isync, lib32-nss, nss, opera, and vivaldi), Debian (gerbv and xen), Fedora (autotrace, chafa, converseen, digikam, dmtx-utils, dvdauthor, eom, kxstitch, libsndfile, nss, pfstools, php-pecl-imagick, psiconv, q, R-magick, rss-glx, rubygem-rmagick, seamonkey, skopeo, synfig, synfigstudio, vdr-scraper2vdr, vdr-skinelchihd, vdr-skinnopacity, vdr-tvguide, vim, vips, and WindowMaker), Mageia (golang, kernel, kernel-linus, mariadb, and vim), openSUSE (aaa_base, python-Pygments, singularity, and tor), Red Hat (nss), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (aaa_base, kernel, openssh, php74, and xen), and Ubuntu (libmodbus, lrzip, samba, and uriparser).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon tries to sell distributed-not-decentralized computing]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9428</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/amazon-tries-to-sell-distributed-not-decentralized-computing/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T14:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I initially thought that my overview of the AWS re:Invent conference would focus on the details of a bunch of new features and services. But on Thursday morning, Amazon CTO Werner Vogels took the stage and proceeded to outline a future of computing that’s utterly distributed and tailor-made for the internet of things, yet still […]
The post Amazon tries to sell distributed-not-decentralized computing appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a DevSecOps approach improved security in iris recognition systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471756</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-a-devsecops-approach-improved-security-in-iris-recognition-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T14:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at DevSecOps best practice and use of static application security testing (SAST) as part of the software development lifecycle at Iris ID, who provide iris recognition for state-of-the-art access control and sensitive biometric authentication applications. 
The post How a DevSecOps approach improved security in iris recognition systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jun Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trends in embedded development: a Mouser perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471746</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/trends-in-embedded-development-a-mouser-perspective/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T13:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the trends in embedded systems design, including greater system integration , connected devices, and the 'virtual' revolution.
The post Trends in embedded development: a Mouser perspective appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Patrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous integration with Go and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/ci-with-go-and-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/ci-with-go-and-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T09:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we're going to walk through how to use GitHub Actions to create a continuous integration (CI) pipeline that automatically tests, vets and lints your Go code.
For solo projects I usually create a pre-commit Git hook to carry out these kinds of checks, but for team projects or open-source work — where you don't have control over everyone's development environment — using a CI workflow is a great way to flag up potential problems and help catch bugs before they make it into production or a versioned release.
And if you're already using GitHub to host your repository, it's nice and easy to use their built-in functionality to do this without any need for additional third-party tools or services.
To demonstrate how it works, let's run through a step-by-step example.
If you'd like to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[필터 버블과 팬덤 정치: 대선 후를 더 우려하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82917</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82917"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T09:23:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 대통령선거를 앞둔 현재 상황은 여러 측면에서 예외적인 모습을 띤다. 치열하게 각축하고 있는 양대 정당의 후보들은 중앙정치 경험이 없고, 당직 경험이 없는 ‘아웃사이더’로서 정당 내부보다는 외부의 지지에 힘입어 소속 정당의 경선을 통과했다.(1) 또한, 양대 정당 이외의 제3의 후보들이 존재하지만, 과거와 달리 그 영향력은 미미하다.(2) 더불어 자신에 대한 낮은 호감도가 자신이 유권자에게 그다지 매력적인 대안으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Links #6: C++23 Progress, Command Line, Containers, and more!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cplinksdec/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cplinksdec/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 6th episode of C++ Links available for C++ Stories subscribers.
See the best C++ stories from the past month.
Here’s the plan for today:
C++23 progress
Parsing Command Line Arguments
3 New articles at C++stories in November
+ 8 Hot C++ News
How to write a custom iterator in C++20
Read till the end to see an additional bonus :)
Let’s start!
🚧 C++23 ISO Progress
At the end of October, there was a cool episode at C++ Cast with Bryce Adelstein Lelbach about the progress of C++23.
Notes:
Everything is moving to Clang - is that good? It’s now lagging with the latest C++ features, probably because of its growth. In GCC, they started using  C++ for the compiler, so it looks like it speeds up things.
Networking has no consensus - TS is probably not worth putting into the Standard  w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some latency measurement pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/latency-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/latency-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a pseudo-transcript (actual words modified to be more readable than a 100% faithful transcription) of a short lightning talk I did at Twitter a year or two ago, on pitfalls of how we use latency metrics (with the actual service names anonymized per a comms request). Since this presentation, significant progress has been made on this on the infra side, so the situation is much improved over what was presented, but I think this is still relevant since, from talking to folks at peer companies, many folks are facing similar issues.
We frequently use tail latency metrics here at Twitter. Most frequently, service owners want to get cluster-wide or Twitter-wide latency numbers for their services. Unfortunately, the numbers that service owners tend to use differ from what we'd like to meas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877724/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877724/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-05T23:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth 5.16 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Nothing looks all that scary, although I certainly hope
the kvm side will calm down".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AP 특파원의 ‘소름 끼치는 임무’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82896</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82896"/>
        <updated>2021-12-05T23:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AP 특파원은 전투 결과를 정확하게 전달하기 위해 현장에 직접 들어가 시체를 하나씩 센다. 아마도 AP 특파원이 수행하는 가장 기본적이면서도 위험한 임무일 것이다. 정부가 발표하는 정보에는 왜곡이 많기 때문에 기자는 직접 현장에 가서 사실을 확인하고 기사의 신빙성을 높여야 한다. 물론 이러한 경험은 상당한 트라우마를 남긴다. 1980년 광주, 테리 앤더슨   테리 앤더슨(Terry Anderson)은 이런 일을 두 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advent Calendar for 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=34006</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/12/05/advent-calendar-for-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-05T20:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Switzerland got a snow cover, part of it melted away again. But with more snow coming the next days. December started, and so did the Advent season. Similar to last year, we wanted to create a special advent calendar, which … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가능성과 불가능성의 이중성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222587108307</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222587108307"/>
        <updated>2021-12-04T23:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[재현 관계, 혹은 표상 관계는 이항 관계이다. 그러나 재현 관계는 그것이 어떻게 가능할 수 있는지 스스로 묻지 못한다. 이것이 재현적 혹은 표상적 사유의 한계이다. 재현적 사유를 가능하게 하는 것이 무엇인가? 그것을 가능하게 하는 제3항이 무엇인가? 그것을 타자의 욕망이라고 주장한다. 그러나 타자의 욕망이, 혹은 대타자의 욕망이 재현이나 표상 관계를 가능하게 하는가? 오히려 내 욕망과 내 욕망 대상의 관계를 가능하게 만든다고 주장해야 한다. 욕망은 어떻게 가능한가? 타자의 욕망 때문에 가능하다. 그러나 이것은 순환적이다. 욕망의 가능성을 설명하는데 이미 타자의 ‘욕망’을 전제하고 있다. 내 욕망은 어떻게 가능한가? 그.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast CSV processing with SIMD]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/04/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/04/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-04T01:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was discussed on Hacker News.
I recently learned of csvquote, a tool that encodes troublesome
CSV characters such that unix tools can correctly process them. It
reverses the encoding at the end of the pipeline, recovering the original
input. The original implementation handles CSV quotes using the
straightforward, naive method. However, there’s a better approach that is
not only simpler, but around 3x faster on modern hardware. Even more,
there’s yet another approach using SIMD intrinsics, plus some bit
twiddling tricks, which increases the processing speed by an order of
magnitude. My csvquote implementation includes both
approaches.
Background
Records in CSV data are separated by line feeds, and fields are separated
by commas. Fields may be quoted.

aaa,bbb,ccc
xxx,"yyy",zzz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Minutes: Inside the GameStop Drama; U.S. Constitution, Auctioned]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2662</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/16-minutes-inside-the-gamestop-drama-u-s-constitution-auctioned/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T20:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to 16 Minutes, our show on the a16z podcast network where we talk about tech trends that are dominating news headlines, industry buzz, and where we are on the long arc of innovation.  Today’s episode actually features a look back at the GameStop saga — the stock market drama that some headlines described as... Read More
The post 16 Minutes: Inside the GameStop Drama; U.S. Constitution, Auctioned appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Andreessen and Ken Griffin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Dec. 3, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9418</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-dec-3-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T18:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some things I just learned about Matter: During a recent pre-CES chat with the folks from Eve, I learned that the company is planning to upgrade most of its devices either via firmware or, in the case of Eve’s light switch and motion sensor, through new devices to Matter. But because a firmware update is so complicated, once […]
The post IoT news of the week for Dec. 3, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#BazelCon 2021 Wrap Up]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/bazelcon-2021-wrap-up.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/bazelcon-2021-wrap-up.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joe Hicks, Product Manager, Core Developer
   

          
The apps, platforms, and systems that the Bazel community builds with Bazel touch the lives of people around the world in ways we couldn’t have imagined. Through BazelCon, we aim to connect Bazel enthusiasts, the Bazel team, maintainers, contributors, users, and friends in an inclusive and welcoming environment. At BazelCon, the community demonstrates the global user impact of the community—with some quirky and carefully crafted talks, a readout on the State-of-Bazel, an upfront discussion on “Implicit Bias Mitigation,” and community sharing events that remind us that we are not alone in our efforts to build a better world, one line of code at a time.  
     

   
At BazelCon, the community shared over 24 technical sessio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CentOS Stream 9]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877599/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877599/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T15:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CentOS blog has announced the release of CentOS Stream 9:

CentOS Stream is a continuous-delivery distribution providing each point-release of Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL). Before a package is formally introduced to CentOS Stream, it undergoes a battery of tests and checks—both automated and manual—to ensure it meets the stringent standards for inclusion in RHEL. Updates posted to Stream are identical to those posted to the unreleased minor version of RHEL. The aim? For CentOS Stream to be as fundamentally stable as RHEL itself.

To achieve this stability, each major release of Stream starts from a stable release of Fedora Linux—In CentOS Stream 9, this begins with Fedora 34, which is the same code base from which RHEL 9 is built. As updated packages pass testing and meet standards for stability, they are pushed into CentOS Stream as well as the nightly build of RHEL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A filesystem for namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877308/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877308/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T14:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is natural, when looking at the kernel development process, to focus on
patches that find their way to acceptance and become a part of future
kernels.  But there can be value in looking at work that doesn't clear the
bar; in failing, these patches often reveal things about the kernel and the
community that creates it.  Such is the case with the proof-of-concept
namespacefs
patch series recently posted by Yordan Karadzhov.  One should not
expect to see namespacefs in a future kernel but, in failing, this work
showed a real use case and why it is hard to satisfy that use case in the
kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877582/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877582/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (krb5 and mailman), Debian (gmp and librecad), Fedora (php-symfony4 and wireshark), Mageia (bluez, busybox, docker-containerd, gfbgraph, hivex, nss, perl/perl-Encode, and udisks2/libblockdev), openSUSE (permissions), Oracle (mailman and mailman:2.1), Red Hat (mailman, mailman:2.1, and nss), Scientific Linux (mailman and nss), and SUSE (nodejs14).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[검찰의 ‘보복기소’를 ‘공소권 남용’으로 처음 막아내다 (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82884</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82884"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T08:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 대법원은 소위 ‘서울시 공무원 간첩’ 사건으로 무죄가 선고된 피고인에게, 이미 수년 전에 조사가 마무리됐던 다른 사건을 추가로 기소한 검사의 공소제기가 위법하다는 판결을 확정하였다. 그가 구속(2013.2.~2013.10.)되고 법정에 선 지 약 8년 6개월만의 일이다. 대법원 판결의 의의   위 판결은 오랫동안 고통받아 온 피고인을 위해 너무나도 다행스러운 결과이고, ‘교과서’에 있던 “검사가 자의적으로 공소권을 행사하여 피고인에게 실질적인 불이익을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언어는 존재의 집이다.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222585519094</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222585519094"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T21:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[하이데거가 <이정표>에 있는 <휴머니즘 서간>에서 다음처럼 말한다. <언어는 존재의 집이다. 언어라는 가옥 안에 인간은 거주한다. 사유가와 시인은 이러한 가옥의 파수꾼이다. 그들의 파수 행위는 그들이 존재의 개방 가능성을 그들의 말행위를 통해 언어로 가져오고 언어 안에 보존하는 한, 존재의 개방 가능성을 완성하는 것이다. 사유로부터 하나의 결과가 비롯됨에 의해, 혹은 사유가 응용됨에 의해, 사유가 비로소 작용케 되는 것이 아니다. 사유는 사유하는 동안, 이미 행위하고 있는 것이다. 아마도 이러한 행위는 가장 단순 소박한 것이면서도 또한 동시에 가장 지고한 것인데, 그 까닭은 이러한 행위는 존재와 인간의 관.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even small projects have bugs, or how PVS-Studio checked Blend2D]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0894/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0894/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often check large projects because it's easier to find bugs there. What if we try PVS-Studio on a small project? In this article we analyze Blend2D — a library for vector 2D graphics. Let's look at what we found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Detecting missing memory barriers with KCSAN]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877200/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877200/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T19:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing (correct) concurrent code that uses locking to avoid race
conditions is difficult enough.  When the objective is to use lockless algorithms, relying on memory
barriers instead of locks to eliminate locking overhead, the problem
becomes harder 
still.  Bugs are easy to create and hard to find in this type of code.
There may be some help on the way, though, in the form of this
patch set from Marco Elver that enhances the Kernel
Concurrency 
Sanitizer (KCSAN) with  the ability to detect some types of missing
memory barriers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.57.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877422/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877422/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T15:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.57.0 of the Rust language is out.  "Rust 1.57 brings panic! to
const contexts, adds support for custom profiles to Cargo, and stabilizes
fallible reservation APIs."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This shouldn't have happened: A vulnerability postmortem (Project Zero blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877420/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877420/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Project Zero blog, Tavis Ormandy has a lengthy postmortem on a vulnerability that he found in the Network Security Services (NSS) cryptography library.  The vulnerability is a bog-standard buffer overflow that has existed in the library since 2012 despite various kinds of static analysis, testing, and fuzzing that Mozilla and others have applied to it over the years.  He found it with a new fuzzing technique:

To solve this problem, I’ve been experimenting with monitoring the call stack during execution.

The naive implementation is too slow to be practical, but after a lot of optimization I had come up with a library that was fast enough to be integrated into coverage-guided fuzzing, and was testing how it performed with NSS and other libraries.

[...] The fuzzer I was using is able to isolate and extract interesting new ASN.1 OIDs, SEQUENCEs, INTEGERs, and so on. Once extracted, it can then randomly combine or insert them into template data. This isn’t really a new idea, but is a new implementation. I'm planning to open source this code in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: AWS overload and Libelium embraces the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9414</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-aws-overload-and-libelium-embraces-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show kicks off with a bunch of IoT-related news from Amazon’s re:Invent conference happening this week in Las Vegas. We cover the launch of a fleet management service, a digital twin service, an easy way to securely connect hardware to Amazon’s cloud, a way to manage massive robot deployments, and the launch of […]
The post Podcast: AWS overload and Libelium embraces the cloud appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877410/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877410/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T13:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (kernel, openssh, and rpm), Debian (nss), Fedora (seamonkey), Mageia (glibc), openSUSE (go1.16, go1.17, kernel, mariadb, netcdf, openexr, poppler, python-Pygments, python-sqlparse, ruby2.5, speex, and webkit2gtk3), Oracle (nss), Red Hat (nss), SUSE (clamav, glibc, gmp, go1.16, go1.17, kernel, mariadb, netcdf, OpenEXR, openexr, openssh, poppler, python-Pygments, python-sqlparse, ruby2.1, ruby2.5, speex, webkit2gtk3, and xen), and Ubuntu (nss and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 2, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876363/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876363/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T00:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 2, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동아·TV조선, 국정원 간첩 조작 편승 사건 (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82862</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82862"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T22:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2013년 국가정보원 간첩 조작 사건은 군사독재 시절에나 있을 법한 일이라고 생각했던 용공 조작 사건이 얼마든지 다시 벌어질 수 있음을 보여준 대표적인 사건입니다. 국가정보원은 한 개인을 간첩으로 몰기 위해 탈북민 출신 서울시 공무원 유 모 씨 동생을 잡아 폭행과 고문 위협을 가하며 허위 자백을 받아냈고, 중국 공문서를 위조해 외교 마찰까지 불렀습니다. 결국, 탈북민 출신 서울시 공무원 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fedora revisits the Git-forge debate]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877240/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877240/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T22:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A seemingly straightforward question aimed at candidates for the in-progress
Fedora
elections led to a discussion on the Fedora devel mailing list that
branched into a few different directions.  The question was related to a
struggle that the distribution has had before: whether using non-free Git
forges is appropriate.  One of the
differences this time, though, is that the focus is on where source-git (or src-git)
repositories will be hosted, which is a separate question from where the dist-git repository
lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFC: First Update on the Vizio lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877294/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877294/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T17:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Software Freedom Conservancy provides
an update on its suit against Vizio for
copyleft license violations.  Vizio's response was not to release the
source code:

Instead, Vizio filed
a request to "remove" the case from California State Court (into US federal
court), which indicates Vizio's belief that consumers have no
third-party beneficiary rights under copyleft! In other words, Vizio’s
answer to this complaint is not to comply with the copyleft licenses, but instead imply that Software Freedom Conservancy — and all other purchasers of the devices who might want to assert their right under GPL and LGPL to complete, corresponding source — have no right to even ask for that source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[November 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d75a402cb216</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/november-2021-d75a402cb216?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/38ccf1d60bcd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-38ccf1d60bcd?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matter is an initiative of the Connectivity Standards Alliance, and developed through collaboration amongst all the leaders of the IoT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877285/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877285/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.15.6, 5.10.83, 5.4.163, and 4.19.219 have been released. They all contain
important fixes throughout the tree.  Users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877284/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877284/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (rsync, rsyslog, and uriparser), Fedora (containerd, freeipa, golang-github-containerd-ttrpc, libdxfrw, libldb, librecad, mingw-speex, moby-engine, samba, and xen), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, and samba), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.11, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.11, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.11, linux-hwe-5.11, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.11, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-kvm, linux-oem-5.13, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, and linux-oem-5.14).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A thinking and recording tool: Decision Records]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#1.AThinkingAndRecordingToolDecisionRecords</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#1.AThinkingAndRecordingToolDecisionRecords"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Advice Process works when supported by four elements. Andrew
      describes the first of these, Decision Records, which act as a tool for
      thinking about and recording the decision process.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put most of your energy into building clean interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#PutMostOfYourEnergyIntoBuildingCleanInterfaces</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#PutMostOfYourEnergyIntoBuildingCleanInterfaces"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we have historically drawn up our project plans and costs around
      the boxes—the digital products we are introducing—the lines are the
      hidden and often primary driver of organizational tech debt. They are the
      reason that things just take longer now than they used to. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allegion Ventures creates $100 million fund]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9405</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/allegion-ventures-creates-100-million-fund/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Allegion has created a second venture fund with $100 million in capital to invest in IoT-related startups. The company, which is the parent of Schlage branded locks, plans to continue investing in software startups that provide cybersecurity and privacy services. The corporate venture fund will also look for investments in construction and property and asset […]
The post Allegion Ventures creates $100 million fund appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the future of embedded software lies in containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471731</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/why-the-future-of-embedded-software-lies-in-containers/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are becoming increasingly important in IoT, industrial, and automation applications, which often require regular refreshes of many different components over long time periods. In...
The post Why the future of embedded software lies in containers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Till Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julia 1.7 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877242/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877242/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.7 of the Julia programming language has been released.  The list of
new features is long; see the release announcement and this LWN article for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter: Clusters, Attributes, Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/82b8ec1640a0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-clusters-attributes-commands-82b8ec1640a0?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T09:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Sovani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genetics of a Modern IoT Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21401</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/genetics-of-a-modern-iot-attack/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T09:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to IoT attacks and malware, there is a perceptible pattern in which most intrusions manifest. It is good practice to study such patterns and draw conclusions so that we may extrapolate to future attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[영국 정부의 디지털 콘트롤 타워 ‘GDS’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82841</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82841"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T08:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[세 차례 칼럼을 통해 ‘플랫폼으로서의 정부'(GaaP: Government as a Platform) 개념 및 속성, 그리고 실행전략을 소개했다. 앞서 소개한 내용은 완전히 새로운 개념이라기보다는 지난 수십 년 동안 정부가 디지털 기술을 도입하는 과정에서 터득한 바람직한 디지털 정부의 모습을 체계적으로 정의한 것이다. 공공 디지털 서비스 분야에서 자주 인용되는 사례 중 하나가 영국 정부의 디지털 전환 거버넌스 체계다. 이 중심에는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python identifiers, PEP 8, and consistency]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877115/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877115/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T22:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are few rules on the names of variables, classes, functions,
and so on (i.e. identifiers) in the Python language, there are some
guidelines on how those things should be named.   But, of course, those
guidelines were not always followed in 
the standard library, especially in the early years of the project.  A
suggestion to add aliases to the standard library for
identifiers that do not follow the guidelines seems highly unlikely to go
anywhere, but it led to an interesting 
discussion on the python-ideas mailing list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checking Chromium after three years. How's it going?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0893/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0893/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We dust off the irregular series of articles about the Chromium project check. Let's look at the code quality in the latest Chromium release and check the new features of the PVS-Studio analyzer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personalize user journeys by Pushing Dynamic Shortcuts to Assistant]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/personalize-user-journeys-by-pushing-dynamic-shortcuts.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/personalize-user-journeys-by-pushing-dynamic-shortcuts.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T17:57:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jessica Dene Earley-Cha, Developer Relations Engineer
 Like many other people who use their smartphone to make their lives easier, I’m way more likely to use an app that adapts to my behavior and is customized to fit me. Android apps already can support some personalization like the ability to long touch an app and a list of common user journeys are listed. When I long press my Audible app (an online audiobook and podcast service), it gives me a shortcut to the book I’m currently listening to; right now that is Daring Greatly by Brené Brown.  
Now, imagine if these shortcuts could also be triggered by a voice command –    and, when relevant to the user, show up in Google Assistant for easy use. 
 Wouldn't that be lovely? 
  
Dynamic shortcuts on a mobile device
 Well, now you can…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Machine Learning for COVID-19 helpline with Krupal Modi #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/Iamagde-krupal-modi.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/Iamagde-krupal-modi.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T17:03:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
In college, Krupal Modi programmed a robot to catch a ball based on the ball’s color, and he enjoyed it enough that he became a developer. Now, he leads machine learning initiatives at Haptik, a conversational AI platform. He is a Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning and recently built the MyGov Corona Helpdesk module for the Indian government, to help Indians around the country schedule COVID-19 vaccinations. He lives in Gujarat, India. 
Meet Krupal Modi, Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning.
   
GDE Krupal Modi
    
The early days
Krupal Modi didn’t set out to become a developer, but when he …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877186/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877186/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T16:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (samba), Fedora (kernel), openSUSE (netcdf and tor), SUSE (netcdf and python-Pygments), and Ubuntu (imagemagick).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How will the IoT be used to prevent drunken driving?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9399</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-will-the-iot-be-used-to-prevent-drunken-driving/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T15:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Brian called into our voicemail hotline with a question about the Build Back Better legislation recently passed in the U.S. House of Representatives. There’s a provision in the current bill that requires new vehicles to prevent drunken driving. Specifically, Brian wants to know how this might be implemented. […]
The post How will the IoT be used to prevent drunken driving? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can't Buy Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Build versus buy” decisions are everywhere today, and rightly so.
      Building software is risky and expensive, and software product companies
      can spread that risk and expense across multiple customers. But my
      colleague Brandon Byars argues that the kinds
      of tools that are available to buy for systems integration are not
      products that directly solve a business problem. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling the Practice of Architecture, Conversationally]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many modern software architects, Andrew Harmel-Law struggles with
      the need to scale architectural thinking to larger organizations while
      allowing teams to be as autonomous as possible. The approach he's
      currently using is the "Advice Process", that encourages and supports
      these teams to be engaged in broader architectural decision making. In
      this first installment, Andrew describes this advice process, later
      installments will dig into four supporting elements that help make it work.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경마 중계식 ‘대선 지지율’ 보도, 이제 좀 작작 해라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82834</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82834"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T07:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지금까지 한국 대선 보도에서 찾아볼 수 없었지만 이번 선거부터라도 새로운 판세 조사를 할 수는 없을까? 선거 때만 되면 늘 봐오던 지지율 조사와 보도가 올해도 여전히 정당이나 후보자 중심으로 이뤄지고 있다. 지지하는 후보와 선호하는 정당 조사는 물론이고 후보 간 대결구도를 가상으로 설정해서 누구를 지지하는지를 묻고 있다. 심지어는 누가 될 것 같은지도 질문하여 결과를 발표하고 있다. 언론은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[ 책 소개 ] 기하급수적인 기술 발전과 급변하는 세상을 다루는 두 권의 책]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73847</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/11/29/two-new-books-explore-the-impact-of-accelerating-technology/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-new-books-explore-the-impact-of-accelerating-technology"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T22:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자율주행차, 메타버스, NFT 등 최근 유튜브를 달구는 영상들을 보고 있자면 현기증 나는 속도로 변하는 세상의 흐름에 멀미가 날 정도입니다. 불과 10년 전과 비교해도 우리가 사는 세상이 얼마나 변했는지 깜짝 놀랄 때가 많습니다. 기술과 산업이 발전하는 속도와 급변하는 세상을 다루는 책 3권을 소개합니다. 기하급수적으로 성장하는 기술이 사회와 경제를 뒤흔들고 있으며, 격변기의 승리자들은 엄청난 과실을 누리고 있습니다. 과연 인류는 엄청난 속도로 발전하는 기술을 발판으로 벽을 깰 수 있을까요? 답을 찾아봅시다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A different approach to BPF loops]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877062/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877062/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T22:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the key features of the extended BPF virtual machine is the verifier
built into the kernel that ensures that all BPF programs are safe to run.
BPF developers often see the verifier as a bit of a mixed blessing, though;
while it can catch a lot of problems before they happen, it can also be
hard to please.  Comparisons with a well-meaning but rule-bound and picky
bureaucracy would not be entirely misplaced.  The bpf_loop()
proposal from Joanne Koong is an attempt to make pleasing the BPF
bureaucrats a bit easier for one type of loop construct.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인의 사적 언어]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222582453332</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222582453332"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T21:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(A) 우리는 자기 자신을 격려하고, 명령하고, 복종하고, 비난하고, 자기 자신을 벌줄 수 있다. 그는 자기에게 질문을 던지고 그것에 대답할 수 있다. 우리는 오직 독백으로 이야기하는 인간을 상상할 수 있다. 그는 그의 활동에 혼잣말을 덧붙인다. - 이런 사람을 보고 그들이 말하는 것을 듣는 관찰자는 그들의 언어를 자기 언어로 번역할 수 있을 것이다. (따라서 그는 그렇게 독백으로 말하는 사람의 행동을 올바르게 예측할 수 있다. 그는 그들이 결단하고 결심하는 것도 들을 수 있다.) 그러나 우리는 마찬가지로 그의 사적 사용을 위해 그의 내적 경험에, 즉 그의 감정, 기분 등에 언어적 표현을 주는 그런 언어를 상상할 수 있는가? - 우.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPOs and Beyond: A Guide to Exit Options for Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2625</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/ipos-and-beyond-a-guide-to-exit-options-for-companies/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T18:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exit options for startups, and their investors, were relatively straightforward for years — the companies could either go public or be acquired. Now the menu of possible options has significantly expanded, as Direct Listings and SPACs have also become tested-and-proven pathways to the public markets. All these choices add complexity for founders and investors, and... Read More
The post IPOs and Beyond: A Guide to Exit Options for Companies appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blake Kim and Quinten Burgunder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Computer Architecture Through a Game]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=16911</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/11/29/learning-computer-architecture-through-a-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[29 November 2021 by Phillip JohnstonLearning and meta-learning have been lifelong passions of mine. I find it endlessly fascinating to think about how we learn, to improve my own ability to learn, and to rethink the ways that we try to teach in our society. One nagging thread I’ve been thinking about is what’s next for learning, … 
Continue reading "Learning Computer Architecture Through a Game"
The post Learning Computer Architecture Through a Game appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Fest in Spain: Exploring the Potential of Artificial Intelligence in Careers, Communities, and Commerce]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdg-ai-fest-spain.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdg-ai-fest-spain.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alessandro Palmieri, Regional Lead for Spain Developer Communities
 Google Developer Groups (GDGs) around the world are in a unique position to organize events on technology topics that community members are passionate about.  That’s what happened in Spain in July 2021, where two GDG chapters decided to put on an event called AI Fest after noticing a lack of conferences dedicated exclusively to artificial intelligence. “Artificial intelligence is everywhere, although many people do not know it,” says Irene Ruiz Pozo, the organizer of GDG Murcia and GDG Cartagena. While AI has the potential to transform industries from retail to real estate with products like Dialogflow and Lending DocAI, “there are still companies falling behind,” she notes. 
   
  
Irene and her GDG team members…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877105/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877105/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T16:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bluez, icu, libntlm, libvorbis, libvpx, opensc, roundcube, and tar), Fedora (kernel, kernel-headers, kernel-tools, puppet, slurm, stargz-snapshotter, and suricata), openSUSE (netcdf), Oracle (bluez, kernel, kernel-container, krb5, mailman:2.1, openssh, python3, and rpm), Red Hat (samba), and SUSE (xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve and track your home’s air quality]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9393</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-improve-and-track-your-homes-air-quality/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T14:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the pandemic was the big story of 2020, then climate change was the big story of 2021, with prolonged freezes in Texas, raging wildfires in California, and devastating floods in Europe. Yet even as more and more people wake up to the reality of a hotter world, we’re apparently still not ready to pull […]
The post How to improve and track your home’s air quality appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[단지 그대가 ‘용역’이라는 이유만으로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82775</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82775"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T08:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2020년 7월 서울청년유니온 조합원이 직장 내 괴롭힘 문제로 상담을 요청했습니다. 해당 조합원은 서울시 사업을 수행하는 서울바이오허브와 용역계약을 맺은 시설관리업체 소속 근로자로, 시설관리 용역업체가 변경됨에 따라 고용승계 후 3개월 단기 계약을 맺었으며, 직장 내 괴롭힘 신고 후 계약만료로 이어진 상황이었습니다. 서울청년유니온은 해당 사건을 계약· 만료가 아닌 직장 내 괴롭힘 신고로 인한 부당해고 건으로 파악하고 이에 대응했습니다.  입사에서 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>청년유니온</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877031/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877031/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T04:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc3 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "So rc3 is usually a bit larger than rc2 just because people had some
time to start finding things.

So too this time, although it's not like this is a particularly big
rc3."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP 8.1.0 and a new foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877024/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877024/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T22:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
8.1.0 of the PHP language has been released.  This release includes a
number of new features, including enumerations,
read-only
properties,
fibers, and more.

Meanwhile, a
new foundation has been created to support development of PHP:


	The initial purpose of the PHP Foundation is to support the
	development of PHP by contracting developers to work on php-src
	either part-time or full-time. If that sounds interesting to you,
	be sure to apply!

	The foundation does not have any decision-making power on language
	changes: these remain within the sole purview of the internals
	mailing list and the RFC process. The fact that some work has been
	funded by the foundation does not imply that it will be accepted
	into PHP.


More information can be found in this
blog entry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An article for those who, like me, do not understand the purpose of std::common_type]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0892/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0892/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article investigates why the standard library needs a way to deduce a common type, how it is implemented and how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick tip: Change URL query params in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/change-url-query-params-in-go</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/change-url-query-params-in-go"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this short post we're going to discuss how to add, modify or delete URL query string parameters in Go. To illustrate, we'll look at how to change this URL:



To this:



If you want to change the URL query string in place:

  

Running this will print out:



If you want to create a clone of the URL but with a different query string, while leaving the original URL unchanged, you need to create a copy of the original url.URL struct first. 
There are a couple of ways to do this. You can either re-parse the URL, or you can dereference the original url.URL and make a copy, like so:



When you do this, you create a new newURL variable of type url.URL which is initialized to the (dereferenced) value of *originalURL. This means that newURL has a different address in memory to originalURL.
Putting this together, the pattern for creating a new URL with different parameters is:



Running this will print out:



As a side note, you can use this technique any time you want to 'clone' a URL and make changes to it. For example to create a clone of a URL with a different path, you can do this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space War]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/11/28/Spacewar.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/11/28/Spacewar.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last month I've been spending a lot of time working on Space War.  I know, I know, I should have been working on Clean Code Episode 67: Legacy Code, and Euler 5, and Countest and Curmugeon 3.  I should have been working on a blog, or a new book, or...  But I couldn't let go of Space War.  It kept calling me.
The first time I wrote Space War was in 1978.  I wrote it in Alcom, which was a simple derivative of Focal, which was an analog of Basic for the PDP-8.  The computer was an M365 which was an augmented version of a PDP-8 and was proprietery to Teradyne, my employer at the time.
The UI was screen based, using character graphics, similar to curses.  Screen updates took on the order of a second.  All input was through the keyboard.
We used to play it on one machine while waiting fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Clean Code Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주관적 의미와 의미 회의주의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222580676689</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222580676689"/>
        <updated>2021-11-27T21:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인은 <철학적 탐구> §201에서 하나의 역설을 말한다. 우리의 역설은 이것이었다. 모든 행위 방식을 하나의 규칙과 일치하게 만들 수 있기 때문에, 규칙은 어떠한 행위 방식도 규정할 수 있다. 규칙은 하나의, 특정한 행위 방식을 규정한다. 그런데 모든 행위 방식을 그 규칙에 일치하게 만들 수 있다. 따라서 규칙은 결국 하나의 특정한 행위 방식을 규정할 수 없다. 즉 규칙은 규칙으로서 기능할 수 없다. 이것이 규칙 회의주의이다. 규칙은 규칙으로서 그 역할을 하지만, 우리는 그것을 정당화할 수 없다. 규칙이 의미를 규정한다. 의미는 사용 규칙에 의해 규정된다. 그런데 사용 규칙이 정당화되지 않기 때문에 결국 의미도.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: HPC, BMS, & network sharing podcast, plus CAD tool goes from cloud to desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471718</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-hpc-bms-network-sharing-podcast-plus-cad-tool-goes-from-cloud-to-desktop/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T19:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes a new embedded edge with Nitin podcast, a look at hardware for the metaverse, new desktop app integration for a popular online component design library plus news of products, people and events.
The post embedded news: HPC, BMS, & network sharing podcast, plus CAD tool goes from cloud to desktop appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SnapEDA launches on desktop as users seek bridge with existing CAD tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471709</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/snapeda-launches-on-desktop-as-users-seek-bridge-with-existing-cad-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many designers wanted a better integration with their existing desktop CAD tools, so SnapEDA, an online design library for CAD models of electronic parts, launched a desktop app.
The post SnapEDA launches on desktop as users seek bridge with existing CAD tools appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 26, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9385</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-26-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GM is simplifying its chip supply chain: I think this is a smart move on GM’s part and also an indication that as we put computers into more places, we need to consolidate platforms and simplify the underlying hardware and software. GM will co-develop chips with its suppliers as well as shrink the number of chip families […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 26, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codasip adopts Imperas for RISC-V processor verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471703</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/codasip-adopts-imperas-for-risc-v-processor-verification/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T16:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Codasip has included Imperas golden reference models in its DV testbenches to ensure an efficient verification flow that accommodates a wide range of flexible features and options while scaling across the entire roadmap of future cores.
The post Codasip adopts Imperas for RISC-V processor verification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrossSync PHY interposer supports PCIe 5.0 in CEM form factor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471696</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/crosssync-phy-interposer-supports-pcie-5-0-in-cem-form-factor/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T15:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New interposer brings CrossSync PHY capability to the CEM specification form factor at the full PCIe 5.0 rate of 32 GT/s. It includes probing points for reference clock, sideband signal, and power rail voltage and current monitoring, in addition to data signals for the protocol analyzer.
The post CrossSync PHY interposer supports PCIe 5.0 in CEM form factor appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ShieldIoT raises $7.4m to deploy coreset-AI for IoT cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471691</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/shieldiot-raises-7-4m-to-deploy-coreset-ai-for-iot-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As IoT networks become larger using conventional anomaly detection algorithms on large datasets can take hours or days, which increases vulnerability to IoT cyber-attacks. ShieldIoT’s coreset-AI helps cut that time down to minutes.
The post ShieldIoT raises $7.4m to deploy coreset-AI for IoT cybersecurity appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six more stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876923/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876923/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of six new stable kernels: 5.10.82, 5.4.162, 4.19.218, 4.14.256, 4.9.291, and 4.4.293.  These kernels contain lots of
important fixes throughout the tree; users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876922/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876922/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (freerdp, gnome-boxes, gnome-connections, gnome-remote-desktop, guacamole-server, hydra, java-1.8.0-openjdk-aarch32, medusa, mingw-gstreamer1, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-base, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-good, php, pidgin-sipe, remmina, vinagre, and weston), openSUSE (kernel and netcdf), and SUSE (kernel and netcdf).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microchip adds edge compute dev tool for smart vision in IIoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471687</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/microchip-adds-edge-compute-dev-tool-for-smart-vision-in-iiot/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T13:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Second development tool in its smart embedded vision initiative for designers using its PolarFire RISC-V SoC FPGA simplifies edge-compute design in thermally challenging IIoT and factory automation environments.
The post Microchip adds edge compute dev tool for smart vision in IIoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling the hardware for the metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471678</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/enabling-the-hardware-for-the-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T12:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How far are we in creating the hardware and software for enabling the metaverse that leading tech firms seem to want us to live in? Analyst firm IDTechEx provides a view of the key technologies and companies involved.
The post Enabling the hardware for the metaverse appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sensor fusion algorithm uses raw data for automotive models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471672</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/sensor-fusion-algorithm-uses-raw-data-for-automotive-models/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T10:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BASELABS’ new Dynamic Grid algorithm takes high-resolution raw sensor data to provide a consistent, detailed environment model, and includes dynamic and static objects as well as free space estimation.
The post Sensor fusion algorithm uses raw data for automotive models appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논증이냐 아니냐: 고등학교와 대학 글쓰기의 차이]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82794</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82794"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T08:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대학에 입학하고 첫 작문 과제를 제출했을 때 받은 피드백을 기억하는가? 상당히 많은 이들이 당황스러운 경험을 한다. 공 들인 과제에 낮은 점수를 받은 것은 차치하고라도, 과제물에 적힌 교수의 코멘트는 대개 충격적이다. 대학에서 요구하는 글쓰기는 고등학교에서 요구하는 글쓰기와 완전히 다르기 때문이다. 그 차이의 핵심은 바로 ‘논증’에 있다. 고등학교 글쓰기: 요약과 의견  고등학교에서 요구하는 글쓰기란 대개 어떤 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사적 언어와 주관적 정당화]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222579383082</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222579383082"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T06:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<비트겐슈타인은 “내가 어떤 것을 ‘S’라고 부른 다음에 내가 그것이 진짜 S인지 어떻게 아는가?”하는 것을 논의하고 있는 것이 아니다. 오히려 “내가 무엇을 ‘S’라고 부른 다음에 ‘S’에 의해서 의미하는 것을 내가 어떻게 아는가?” 하는 것을 논의하고 있다. 어떤 것을 S라고 잘못 생각하는 경우조차 나는 ‘S’의 의미를 알고 있어야만 한다. 이것이 비트겐슈타인이 사적 언어에서 불가능하다고 주장하는 것이다. 비트겐슈타인은 다음처럼 말한다. <오로지 우리 상상 속에 존재하는 어떤 일람표, 사전과 같은 것을 생각해 보자. 가령, 우리들은 사전에 의해서 낱말 X를 낱말 Y로 번역하는 것을 정당화할 수 있다. 그러나 이 일.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전두환 사망, "어두웠던 역사의 기억도 함께 떠나보내"자는 어느 언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82780</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82780"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T23:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11월 23일 오전 제12대·13대 대통령을 지낸 전두환 씨가 사망했습니다. 전 씨는 12·12군사쿠데타를 일으켜 권력을 탈취한 뒤, 5.18민주화운동을 무자비하게 진압해 수많은 이들을 희생시켰으며 집권기간 내내 독재로 일관하며 시민들의 민주화 열망을 짓밟았습니다. 하지만 권력에서 물러나 죽음에 이르기까지 단 한 번도 과오를 사죄하지 않았습니다. 이처럼 역사 속에서 학살자이자 독재자로 평가받는 전 씨가 사망하자 언론은 관련 보도를 쏟아냈는데요. 민주언론시민연합은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Tips for Optimizing GUIs in Industrial Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=13734</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/5-tips-for-optimizing-guis-in-industrial-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T22:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial applications have traditionally involved analog buttons, switches, and dials to interact with a user. As you are aware, times are changing, and industrial application users now need rich graphical user interfaces. Many interfaces are built on top of embedded systems, which are quite powerful, but they are still resource-constrained systems. They may be resource-constrained … Continue reading 5 Tips for Optimizing GUIs in Industrial Applications
5 Tips for Optimizing GUIs in Industrial Applications first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 5.15.5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876861/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876861/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T21:52:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.15.5 stable kernel has been
released.  As usual, it contains lots of important fixes throughout the
kernel tree.  Users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual function calls in constructors and destructors (C++)]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0891/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0891/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In different programming languages, the behavior of virtual functions differs when it comes to constructors and destructors. Incorrect use of virtual functions is a classic mistake. Developers often use virtual functions incorrectly. In this article, we discuss this classic mistake. I suppose the reader is familiar with virtual functions in C++. Let's get straight to the point. When we call a virtual function in a constructor, the function is overridden only within a base class or a currently created class. Constructors in the derived classes have not yet been called. Therefore, the virtual functions implemented in them will not be called. Let me illustrate this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEC- Embedded Software Development Tools and Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=13741</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/cec-embedded-software-development-tools-and-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T17:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tools and techniques developers use to design and build their systems can make the difference between success and failure. Tools and techniques are constantly evolving and to stay relevant and beat out the competition, it’s critical to be up to date on the latest and greatest. In this course, we will explore a wide … Continue reading CEC- Embedded Software Development Tools and Techniques
CEC- Embedded Software Development Tools and Techniques first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876852/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876852/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T14:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (busybox, getdata, and php), Mageia (couchdb, freerdp, openexr, postgresql, python-reportlab, and rsh), openSUSE (bind, java-1_8_0-openjdk, and kernel), SUSE (java-1_7_0-openjdk), and Ubuntu (icu).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: We’re thankful for smart cows]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9386</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-were-thankful-for-smart-cows/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heading into the holiday weekend, Kevin and I share what we’re thankful for (mostly y’all, our sponsors, each other, and Thread), while also talking about the sad sale of Tile to Life360. We also discuss Clevr, Qeexo, and efforts to make AI accessible to people who can’t or don’t want to code. After that, I discuss my desire […]
The post Podcast: We’re thankful for smart cows appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[로티 - 실용주의와 직관적 실재론]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222578622391</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222578622391"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T10:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[진리는 언명 가능한 것, 그 이상이다. 고통은 두뇌 상태, 그 이상의 것이다. 물리학과 도덕적 책임 사이에 중대한 차이가 있다. 이런 주장을 해명하는 철학적 견해를 찾아야 한다. 이것이 <직관적 실재론자>의 주장이다. 그러나 실용주의자는 그러한 주장에 대한 직관을 갖는 것을 그만하자고 역설한다. 사람들은 서로 공통된 요소가 있으며, 대문자 철학은 그것을 추출해서 모두가 합리적으로 수용할 수 있는 논제나 중요한 문제를 구성할 수 있다고 직관적 실재론은 주장한다. 즉 진짜 해결해야 할 철학적 문제가 있다. 실용주의는 모든 인간의 공통된 본성 같은 것을 거부한다. 그런 것을 추구할 유용성도 없다. 다양한 담론들을 통약 가.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AP, 미국이 세계를 바라보는 시각을 결정한다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82763</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82763"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T05:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한 국가 전체를 거의 혼자 취재해야 하는 상황에서 특파원들이 가장 먼저 해결해야 하는 기본적인 문제는 바로 무엇을 뉴스로 다룰 것인지 결정하는 것이다. AP에서 작성한 기사가 전 세계 주요 언론사들을 통해 나가기 때문에 AP 뉴스는 곧 국제 사회에서 의제를 설정하는 역할을 한다. AP 뉴스는 미국인은 물론 세계인이 세상을 바라보는 인식과 이해에 중대한 영향을 미친다. AP는 실제로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A gentle approach to AI and ML for all interested in the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9367</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/a-gentle-approach-to-ai-and-ml-for-all-interested-in-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T22:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often discuss Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) here on the site and in our weekly IoT Podcast. And we should: These technologies take data from sensors and other inputs, turning that data into actionable “smarts”. But for many, ML and AI are nebulous terms, akin to some dark magic taught at Hogwarts […]
The post A gentle approach to AI and ML for all interested in the IoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876799/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876799/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (openjdk-17), Fedora (libxls, roundcubemail, and vim), openSUSE (bind, java-1_8_0-openjdk, and redis), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, krb5, mailman:2.1, openssh, and rpm), Scientific Linux (kernel, krb5, openssh, and rpm), SUSE (bind, java-1_8_0-openjdk, redis, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (bluez).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need a HomeKit sensor and light strip for a closet? Here are some suggestions.]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9359</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/need-a-homekit-sensor-and-light-strip-for-a-closet-here-are-some-suggestions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Michael called in to our voicemail hotline with a closet question. More specifically, he’s looking for a HomeKit solution to enable light strips in his closets. The idea is to have the light strips turn on when he opens the door, and Michael is looking for some sensor […]
The post Need a HomeKit sensor and light strip for a closet? Here are some suggestions. appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does Matter mean to you?]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/fa3bb53a7793</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/what-does-matter-mean-to-you-fa3bb53a7793?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T09:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Sovani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시신 투척 사건이 아니라 ‘교제 살인’, ‘스토킹 살인’이다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82752</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82752"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T06:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여성 두 명이 교제했던 남성에 의해 살해당했다. 11월 17일 30대 남성이 전 연인인 여성을 흉기로 찌른 뒤 베란다에서 내던져 살해한 혐의로 체포됐다. 여성이 이별을 요구하자 죽인 것으로 알려졌다. 이틀 뒤인 11월 19일엔 옛 연인이 휘두른 흉기에 찔려 여성 한 명이 사망했다. 이 여성은 스토킹 피해를 호소해 신변보호를 받던 중이다. 108명. 2016년부터 3년간 ‘법적으로 결혼하지 않은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이클 데빗]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222577024933</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222577024933"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[왜 데빗(M. Devitt)이 계속 책을 쓰지 않는가 생각하다가 그의 나이를 살펴보니 벌써 83세이다. 나는 그가 이렇게 늙었다고 전혀 생각하지 못했다. 내가 데빗의 책을 열심히 수집한 것이 2000년 초 같은데, 내 시간 관념이 여전히 거기에 머무르고 있다. 게다가 이 당시에 전개되었던 분석철학이 오늘날 전개되는 양상보다 더 흥미롭다고 느낀다. 아마 이것이 바로 과거를 살고 있는 인간이 보여주는 전형적 모습일 것이다. 자기에게 친숙한 것을 좋아하는 그러한 경향 말이다. 그러나 어떤 공통적 주제 없이 산만하게 전개되는 철학적 활동보다는 그 당시에 여러 철학자들의 공통적 논의 주제가 되었던 실재론, 진리, 의미에 대한 논의가 더 철.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A variety of errors in C# code by the example of CMS DotNetNuke: 40 questions about the quality]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0890/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0890/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we discuss C# code quality and a variety of errors by the example of CMS DotNetNuke. We're going to dig into its source code. You're going to need a cup of coffee... DotNetNuke is an open-source content management system (CMS) written mainly in C#. The source code is available on GitHub. The project is part of the .NET Foundation. The project has its website, Twitter, YouTube channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your development workflow with Interactive Canvas DevTools]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/improve-your-development-workflow-with-interactive-canvas-devtools.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/improve-your-development-workflow-with-interactive-canvas-devtools.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nick Felker, Developer Relations Engineer
    Interactive Canvas helps developers build multimodal apps for games, storytelling, and educational experiences on smart displays like the Nest Hub and Nest Hub Max. Setting up an Interactive Canvas app involves building a web app, a conversational model, and a server-based fulfillment to respond to voice commands. All three of these components need to be built out to test your apps using the simulator in the Actions Console. This works for teams who are able to build all three at once… but it means that everything has to be hooked up, even if you just want to test out the web portion of your app. In many cases, the web app provides the bulk of the functionality of an Interactive Canvas app. We recently published Interactive Canvas Dev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using blockchain to share and monetize telecoms assets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471647</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/using-blockchain-to-share-and-monetize-telecoms-assets/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weaver Labs has created a software solution to enable sharing and monetization of telecom network infrastructure assets in a secure, open and interconnected network using blockchain technology in an internal cryptocurrency system.
The post Using blockchain to share and monetize telecoms assets appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876723/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876723/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (mbedtls), Red Hat (kernel and rpm), and Ubuntu (freerdp2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless BMS eliminates wires, adds intelligence to each battery cell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471641</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/wireless-bms-eliminates-wires-adds-intelligence-to-each-battery-cell/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless battery management system (BMS) from Dukosi puts chip and embedded software on each battery cell to enable ‘edge intelligence’ for safer and better performance batteries.
The post Wireless BMS eliminates wires, adds intelligence to each battery cell appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting the Advantages of ESP32-S3-BOX, Espressif’s AI Voice Development Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/56852737e229</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/presenting-the-advantages-of-esp32-s3-box-espressifs-ai-voice-development-kit-56852737e229?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Systems has recently released an AI voice development kit dubbed ESP32-S3-BOX, based on ESP32-S3 Wi-Fi + Bluetooth 5 (LE) SoC. It…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amey Inamdar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unbearable fussiness of the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9356</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/the-unbearable-fussiness-of-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head into another gifting season and more and more connected devices make their way onto gift guides, I want to offer a cautionary note. The smart home is like a cat — mostly self-sufficient and nice to have, but also possessing a mind of its own that can lead to frustration and confusion […]
The post The unbearable fussiness of the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A preview of Amazon's AL2022 distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876696/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876696/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T13:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has announced
a preview release of its upcoming AL2022 distribution.  The company plans
to support AL2022 for five years after its release.


	AL2022 uses the Fedora project as its upstream to provide customers
	with a wide variety of the latest software, such as updated
	language runtimes, as part of quarterly releases. In addition,
	AL2022 has SELinux enabled and enforced by default.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[종부세 폭탄론이 새빨간 거짓말인 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82744</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82744"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[종합부동산세(종부세) 고지서가 발부되자 올해도 어김없이 대다수 언론이 ‘세금폭탄’ 프레임을 쏟아내고 있다. 종부세가 생긴 지 15년이 지났건만 언론의 ‘세금폭탄’ 타령은 그칠 줄을 모른다. 하지만 과거에도, 지금도 종부세는 ‘세금폭탄’이 아니다.  언론은 15년째 ‘폭탄타령’ 정부 발표에 따르면 2021년 주택분 종부세 고지 인원은 94.7만 명이고, 세액은 5.7조 원이다. 국민의 98%는 종부세 과세대상이 아닌 것이다. 2%에 해당하는 종부세 과세대상 중에서도 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[헌재의 안으로 굽은 팔: 법관 임성근 탄핵심판 사건 (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82735</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82735"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[판사 출신이 8명, 그 중에서도 고법부장이나 법원장급의 경력자가 6명이나 자리하고 있는 헌법재판소가 마찬가지로 그 경력 사다리를 따라가고 있는 엘리트 법관을 파면시킬 수 있을까? 법원은 유달리 선례와 관행에 집착한다. 법원의 현재는 법원의 과거이자 동시에 법원의 미래다. 고법부장 승진을 목전에 둔 수석부장판사가 ‘휘하의’ 법관이 작성한 판결문에 ‘빨간펜’ 첨삭지도를 하였다면 그것은 선배 수석부장판사로부터 배운 것이자 후임의 수석부장판사가 따라 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocket article: How to implement and use `.noinit` RAM]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/noinit-memory</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/noinit-memory"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This pocket article will describe how a non-initialized region of memory works,
how to implement it, and how it can be used in a typical embedded system.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Metcalfe’s Law for Network Effects, and Towards a Better Model]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2573</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/metcalfes-law-network-effects-better-model-cold-start-problem/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is an excerpt from the book The Cold Start Problem: How to Start and Scale Network Effects by Andrew Chen. Copyright © 2021 by Andrew Chen. Published on Future/ a16z, with permission from Harper Collins, an imprint of HarperCollins Publishers. A core pillar in the study of network effects is Metcalfe’s Law, where... Read More
The post Beyond Metcalfe’s Law for Network Effects, and Towards a Better Model appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876661/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876661/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second 5.16 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Nothing especially noteworthy stands out for the last
week, it all felt pretty normal for a rc2 week".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Student Leader Promotes Neurodiversity Awareness in Brazil and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdsc-lead-joao-in-brazil.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdsc-lead-joao-in-brazil.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:17:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rodrigo Hirooka, Regional Lead for Brazil Developer Communities
           
Perceiving that one is not like everyone else can be painful. Yet, the experience can also be illuminating. As a child in Brazil, João Victor Ipirajá, lead of the Google Student Developer Club (GDSC) at the Federal Institute of Science and Technology of Ceará (IFCE), knew he was different. He often felt overwhelmed by physical sensations and missed social cues. When he was eventually diagnosed as being on the autistic spectrum, he was actually relieved. Far from being a limitation, the realization gave him a new perspective on his intellectual strengths—such as his ability to perceive mathematical concepts in a highly visual way and his capacity for logical thinking and computer programming. “I was reborn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876655/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876655/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firebird3.0, libmodbus, and salt), Fedora (js-jquery-ui and wordpress), Mageia (arpwatch, chromium-browser-stable, php, rust, and wireshark), openSUSE (barrier, firefox, hylafax+, opera, postgresql12, postgresql13, postgresql14, and tomcat), SUSE (ardana-ansible, ardana-monasca, crowbar-openstack, influxdb, kibana, openstack-cinder, openstack-ec2-api, openstack-heat-gbp, openstack-heat-templates, openstack-horizon-plugin-gbp-ui, openstack-keystone, openstack-neutron-gbp, openstack-nova, python-eventlet, rubygem-redcarpet, rubygem-puma, ardana-ansible, ardana-monasca, documentation-suse-openstack-cloud, openstack-ec2-api, openstack-heat-templates, python-Django, python-monasca-common, rubygem-redcarpet, rubygem-puma, firefox, kernel, postgresql, postgresql13, postgresql14, postgresql10, postgresql12, postgresql13, postgresql14, postgresql96, and samba), and Ubuntu (libreoffice).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876610/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876610/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.15.4,
5.14.21,
5.10.81, and
5.4.161 stable kernels have been released.
Each contains another set of important updates, but it's worth
noting that 5.4.161
hasn't been through the usual review process due to an amusing bit of
scripting confusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kinetic offers IoT-enabled workers’ comp insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9352</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/kinetic-offers-iot-enabled-workers-comp-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T14:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I saw the first instance of IoT being used in insurance outside of the auto industry. Nationwide Insurance and Kinetic, a seven-year-old maker of a wearable device that tracks worker movements, have launched a policy for workers’ compensation. Companies will buy the policy from Kinetic and deploy its wearable among their workforces. The goal […]
The post Kinetic offers IoT-enabled workers’ comp insurance appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노동감시 대응 가이드: 일하면서 감시받고 있다고 느낄 때]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82728</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82728"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T08:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘노동감시 대응 가이드’ 홈페이지에서 보기 (클릭!) PDF 다운하기 (클릭!) 노동감시 대응 사업단은 일터에서 진행되는 노동감시를 유형별로 분류하고 이에 대한 대응 방법을 소개하는 [노동감시 대응 가이드]를 발간 했습니다. 이번 가이드는 지난 2021년 8월 2일 발간한 [디지털 노동감시 실태조사 및 법제도 개선방안] 보고서를 바탕으로 노동감시와 관련된 여러 법제를 살펴보고 개별 노동자들이 각자의 현장에서 어떻게 대응할 수 있을지에 관한 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NoHat 21]]></title>
        <id>https://limitedresults.com/?p=1364</id>
        <link href="https://limitedresults.com/2021/11/nohat-21/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T08:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[20 November 2021, Bergamo The event Webpage here. My talk Conclusion Solid and high technical program, perfect organisation, fun people all around. Premium. Grazie a tutti!
The post NoHat 21 appeared first on LimitedResults.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LimitedResults</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[명예훼손, 네 가지 구제 방법과 그 한계]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82720</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82720"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T07:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[민법은 ‘명예훼손의 경우의 특칙'(제764조)으로 ‘타인의 명예를 훼손한 자에 대하여는 법원은 피해자의 청구에 의하여 손해배상에 갈음하거나 손해배상과 함께 명예회복에 적당한 처분을 명할 수 있다’고 규정한다. 언론중재 및 피해구제 등에 관한 법률은 정정보도, 반론보도, 사후보도 청구의 근거를 둔다. 또한, 판례는 인격권 침해를 이유로 한 방해배제청구권으로서 기사삭제청구권을 인정하고 있다. 즉, 피해자의 명예 회복을 위해 가해자(언론)가 할 수 있는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designated Initializers in C++20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/designated-init-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/designated-init-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Standard, new ways to initialize objects!
With C++20, we get a handy way of initializing data members. The new feature is called designated initializers and might be familiar to C programmers.
Let’s have a look at this small feature:
The basics
Designated Initialization is a form of Aggregate Initialization.
As of C++20, an Aggregate type::
is an array type or,
is a class type that:

has no private or protected direct non-static data members
has no user-declared or inherited constructors
has no virtual, private, or protected base classes
has no virtual member functions
In a basic form in C++20, you can write:
Type obj = { .designator = val, .designator = val2, ... };
// or
Type obj = { .designator { val }, .designator { val2 }, ... };


For example:
struct Point { 
    double x { 0.0 }…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major errors on this blog (and their corrections)]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/corrections/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/corrections/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a list of errors on this blog that I think were fairly serious. While what I think of as serious is, of course, subjective, I don't think there's any reasonable way to avoid that because, e.g., I make a huge number of typos, so many that the majority of acknowledgements on many posts are for people who e-mailed or DM'ed me typo fixes.
A list that included everything, including typos would both be uninteresting for other people to read as well as high overhead for me, which is why I've drawn the line somewhere. An example of an error I don't think of as serious is, in this post on how I learned to program, I originally had the dates wrong on when the competition programmers from my high school made money (it was a couple years after I thought it was). In that case, and many others, I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/live-immediately/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/live-immediately/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T23:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE WHOLE FUTURE LIES IN UNCERTAINTY: LIVE IMMEDIATELY. @subliming.jpg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks, Mario, but the code needs fixing — checking TheXTech]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0889/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0889/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's cool when enthusiastic developers create a working clone of a famous game. It's even cooler when people are ready to continue the development of such projects! In this article, we check TheXTech with PVS-Studio. TheXTech is an open implementation of the game from the Super Mario universe. TheXTech is the SMBX 1.3. game engine rewritten on C++. The original SMBX (Super Mario Bros. X) was written on Visual Basic 6 by Andrew Spinks in 2009. It allows to create levels from the elements of the Nintendo's Super Mario Bros games. TheXTech accurately reproduces the original game's behavior. It also includes optional bug fixes. It runs not only on Windows, but also on macOS, and Linux systems with x86, ARM or PowerPC processors. Some developers also ported it on 3DS and PS Vista The TheXTech developer — Vitaliy Novichkov (Wohlstand) — described the development process in detail on Habr. He also described the techniques he used to smooth out the differences when porting the project from VB6 to C++. There's a disclaimer on the GitHub page that explains why the source code is not in the best condition. It's because the original code is unstructured something fierce. Its fragments you'll see below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한류 – 한국의 문화경제와 대중문화의 파도 (번역)]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2811</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2021/11/21/korean-wave-hallyu/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T08:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국의 비즈니스, 문화, 국가 이미지에 한류는 그야말로 축복입니다. 1999년대부터 한류는 아시아 전역에서 가장 큰 문화적 현상으로 자리를 잡았습니다. 한류의 영향은 점점 엄청나게 커져 2004년 한국 GDP의 0.2%, 약 18억 7천만 불을 차지하였으며 2019년에는 약 123억 불로 한국 경제를 부양하고 있습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 범주의 초월적 연역으로 이행]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222574305908</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222574305908"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T22:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<종합적 표상과 그 대상이 함께 만나는, 서로 필연적으로 관계 맺는, 그러니까 이를테면 서로 마주칠 수 있는 경우는 오로지 두 경우가 있을 수 있다. 대상이 표상을 가능하게 한 경우이거나 표상이 대상을 가능하게 한 경우이다. 앞의 경우라면, 그 양자의 관계맺음은 단지 경험적인 것이고, 그 표상은 결코 선험적으로 가능한 것일 수 없다. 현상에서 감각에 속하는 것을 살피는 경우가 바로 이에 해당한다. 그러나 뒤의 경우에는 표상 자신이 - 여기서는 의지에 의한 인과성은 문제삼지 않으므로 - 그것의 대상을 현존의 면에서 산출하지는 않는다. 그럼에도 표상은 그것에 의해서만 어떤 것을 하나의 대상으로 인식하는 것이 가능할 대상.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAOs, A Canon]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2532</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/dao-canon/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T03:26:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is (and isn’t) a DAO? Why do DAOs matter? How do DAOs fit into web3, crypto, the creator economy, future of work, and many other areas? Inspired by our NFT Canon earlier this year (and original Crypto Canon), we’ve culled the below list of resources for those seeking to understand, build, and otherwise get... Read More
The post DAOs, A Canon appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonal Chokshi, Zoran Basich and Guy Wuollet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시간 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222573561190</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222573561190"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T21:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<시간과 타자>의 <서문>을 겨우 겨우 읽는다. 그것을 읽는데 아주 대단한 인내심이 필요하다. 그의 비유법을 흉내해면 <인내심 없는 인내심>이 필요하다. 그런데 <인내심 없는 인내심>은 더 이상 <인내심>이 아니다. 오히려 <더 이상 인내할 수 없을 정도의 인내심>이 요구된다고 표현해야 한다. 이런 글을 더 읽어야 하는가? 이 글에 대한 <전문가>가 구절 하나하나를 자상하게 설명해 주면 좋겠다. 혹은 내가 구절 하나하나의 의미에 너무 목매달고 있는 것은 아닌가? 그냥 무시해 버리면서 그 핵심 논점을 파악하는 것이 더 중요한 것은 아닌가? 이럼에도 다음 구절과 같은 것에 대해서 도대체 그.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 19, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9350</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-19-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T18:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung SmartThings adds whole-home energy monitoring: It seems like there’s a gold rush of sorts going on in electricity monitoring. The latest prospector is Samsung SmartThings, which this week announced three new partnerships to bring whole-home energy monitoring to customers. The company says products and services from Copper Labs, Eyedro, and Wattbuy are now integrated with […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 19, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: FPGA launches, poor IoT vulnerability disclosure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471629</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-fpga-launches-poor-iot-vulnerability-disclosure/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes two new FPGA announcements, one for entry level and the other for HPC, plus a look at how the IoT industry is doing on vulnerability disclosure, the latest on Nvidia and Arm, plus news of products, funding, people and events.
The post embedded news week: FPGA launches, poor IoT vulnerability disclosure appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] In search of an appropriate RLIMIT_MEMLOCK default]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876288/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876288/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One does not normally expect a lot of disagreement over a 13-line patch
that effectively tweaks a single line of code.  Occasionally, though, such
a patch can expose a disagreement over how the behavior of the kernel
should be managed.  This patch
from Drew DeVault, who is evidently taking a break from stirring up
the npm community, is a case in point.  It brings to light the question
of how  the kernel community should pick default values for configurable
parameters like resource limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876528/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876528/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T14:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (chromium, grafana, kubectl-ingress-nginx, and opera), Debian (netkit-rsh and salt), Fedora (freeipa and samba), Mageia (opensc, python-django-filter, qt4, tinyxml, and transfig), openSUSE (opera and transfig), Red Hat (devtoolset-11-annobin, devtoolset-11-binutils, and llvm-toolset:rhel8), SUSE (php72 and php74), and Ubuntu (mailman and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renesas enters FPGA market with sub-5000 gate devices for consumer & IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471621</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/renesas-enters-fpga-market-with-sub-5000-gate-devices-for-consumer-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T11:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Renesas ForgeFPGA family targets high-volume applications needing less than 5,000 logic gates, with initial device sizes costing less than $0.50 in volume and with standby power of less than 20 microamps.
The post Renesas enters FPGA market with sub-5000 gate devices for consumer & IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lynx MOSA.ic now manages multiple hybrid IT/OT mission critical systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471610</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/lynx-mosa-ic-now-manages-multiple-hybrid-it-ot-mission-critical-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lynx Software Technologies’ MOSA.ic now adds more flexible management of multiple devices and systems from cloud or on-premise servers, and provides air-gap between OT and IT networks.
The post Lynx MOSA.ic now manages multiple hybrid IT/OT mission critical systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[또! 공군 성추행 은폐 의혹 (ft. 보수 언론의 무관심)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82712</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82712"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T09:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 5월 성추행과 군의 2차 가해로 숨진 이 모 중사가 사망하기 열흘 전 또 다른 공군 부사관이 비슷한 피해를 당한 뒤 사망했다는 사실이 뒤늦게 드러났습니다. 군인권센터는 11월 15일 공군이 강제추행 피해 정황을 확인하고도 피해 부사관을 ‘스트레스로 인한 사망’으로 종결했다가 가해자를 늑장 기소했다는 의혹을 제기했습니다. 공군은 이 중사 사망으로 비판이 높아지자 재발 방지를 대대적으로 약속하면서도 다른 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AP 특파원의 여섯 가지 조건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82687</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82687"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T08:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AP특파원 4명 중 3명은 미국 내에 있는 1) AP 지국에서 기자로서 경력을 시작한다. 지역에서는 고등학교 운동 경기나 주의회 등을 취재하러 다니고, 방송이나 야간 근무도 하며 온갖 잡일을 한다. 그런 생활을 하다가 2) ‘AP 테스트’라고 불리는 글쓰기 시험을 보고, 이 시험에 합격한 이들은 3) 뉴욕으로 와서 포린데스크나 월드데스크에서 국제뉴스 편집자로 일한다. 그렇게 편집자로 활동하다가 자리가 나면 4) 특파원으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[야구장, 축구장엔 수만 명씩 모이는데 집회는 500명 미만?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82676</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82676"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T07:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 하에서 시민들이 사회적 거리두기를 해온 지가 벌써 내년이면 2년이 되어갑니다. 그 동안에 많은 시민들은 2020년 작년 보수세력의 ‘광복절 집회’와 뒤이은 수도권의 폭발적인 감염 확산을 야기했다는 많은 언론보도를 보셨을 것입니다. 또, 지난 11월 13일, 민주노총이 서울시의 전면 금지에도 불구하고 ‘전국노동자대회’를 불시에 동대문에서 개최했고, 그 일대 교통이 마비되어 결혼식에 늦었다는 사연도 언론에서 접하셨을 것입니다. 아무리 ‘위드 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xilinx doubles Alveo HBM, adds clustering for HPC & big data workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471600</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/xilinx-doubles-alveo-hbm-adds-clustering-for-hpc-big-data-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T21:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xilinx said its new Alveo U55C card is purpose-built for HPC and big data workloads, offering the highest compute density and HBM capacity in the Alveo accelerator portfolio.
The post Xilinx doubles Alveo HBM, adds clustering for HPC & big data workloads appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Carla car simulator helped us level up the static analysis of Unreal Engine 4 projects]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0888/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0888/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the mechanisms of static analysis is method annotations of popular libraries. Annotations provide more information about functions during errors detecting. CARLA is an impressive open-source project in C++ that helped us implement this mechanism to our analyzer. Subsequently, the simulator became a test-target for the improved PVS-Studio static analyzer. CARLA is an open-source simulator for autonomous driving research. CARLA has been developed from the ground up to support development, training, and validation of autonomous driving systems. In addition to open-source code and protocols, CARLA provides open digital assets (urban layouts, buildings, vehicles) that were created for this purpose and can be used freely. The simulation platform supports flexible specification of sensor suites and environmental conditions. The project is cross-platform and contains almost 78,000 lines of C++ code. In the project repository, we also found code written in Python, XML, YAML, DOS Batch, CMake and other languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What to do in response to a kernel warning]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876209/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876209/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel provides a number of macros internally to allow code to generate
warnings when something goes wrong.  It does not, however, provide a lot of
guidance regarding what should happen when a warning is issued.  Alexander
Popov recently posted a
patch series adding an option for the system's response to warnings;
that series seems unlikely to be applied in anything close to its current
form, but it did succeed in provoking a discussion on how warnings should
be handled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two more stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876425/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876425/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released two more stable kernels. 5.14.20 reverts three patches from the
5.14.19 release, while 5.10.80 is one of the
massive updates mentioned yesterday.  The
other massive release mentioned, 5.15.3, is still under
review and can be expected in the next day or two.  As usual, the
kernels released contain important fixes and users should upgrade.

Update: 5.15.3 was also released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Decentralized Identity, Your Reputation Travels With You Across Cyberspace]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2484</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/decentralized-identity-on-chain-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second installment of a two-part series on reputation systems in web3. Read part one here. Web3 is based on the premise that each internet user will have a unique internet identifier, like an email address, that can be natively linked to any piece of software and stored on a blockchain. As part... Read More
The post With Decentralized Identity, Your Reputation Travels With You Across Cyberspace appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Kominers and Jad Esber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: McKinsey reevaluates IoT’s impact]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9347</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-mckinsey-reevaluates-iots-impact/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show has a lot of big numbers starting with $12.6 trillion, which is at the upper end of what McKinsey believes the economic impact from IoT will be by 2030. We cover the latest report, which is a reassessment of McKinsey’s famous 2015 report on the IoT that said it would be worth […]
The post Podcast: McKinsey reevaluates IoT’s impact appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876413/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876413/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (binutils, firefox, flatpak, freerdp, httpd, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, kernel, openssl, and thunderbird), Fedora (python-sport-activities-features, rpki-client, and vim), and Red Hat (devtoolset-10-annobin and devtoolset-10-binutils).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대화의 파토스와 에토스 vs. 글의 로고스]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82657</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82657"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T09:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[70년대 말 미국은 바야흐로 수사학의 르네상스였다고 해도 과언이 아니었다. 매년 수십 종의 그리스로마 수사학 저술들을 번역출간되면서 아리스토텔레스로부터 출발한 고전수사학이 본격적으로 부활했다. 마치 자신들에게 부재하는 글쓰기전통을 빠르게 채워 넣고자 하는 듯, 미국 대학들은 고전수사학의 내용과 형식을 대대적으로 차용하기 시작했다. 결국, 미국의 글쓰기 연구는 고대그리스 이소크라테스 학파의 문체술까지 거슬러올라가 전통을 확보하는 데 성공한다. 아리스토텔레스는 다양한 시민 활동 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[더팩트의 ‘스토킹’ 오보, 그걸 옹호하는 TV조선]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82648</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82648"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T08:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인터넷매체 ‘더팩트’가 11월 15일 오후 6시 7분 [단독/이재명 부인 김혜경 씨 ‘깜짝 변신’, ‘낙상 사고’ 후 첫 외출 포착]이라는 보도를 내놨습니다. 이재명 더불어민주당 대선후보 배우자 김혜경 씨가 낙상사고 6일 만에 외출하는 모습을 취재했다며 사진기사를 내보낸 겁니다. 더팩트가 사진 속 검은 망토 차림 여성을 ‘김혜경 씨’로 특정하면서 김 씨 낙상사고 이후 쏟아진 풍문이나 허위 조작 정보에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 18, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875755/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875755/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 18, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM relicensing update & call for help]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2021-11-18-relicensing-update/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2021-11-18-relicensing-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’d like to summarize the main points I talked about in the
relicensing update presentation at the 2021 LLVM Developer’s meeting.
The very short summary is that we are currently in the long tail phase of
collecting relicensing agreements of past contributors. We already at the time
of this writing have more than 94% of older code relicensed. We hope to crowd
source getting through the long tail to get as close to 100% as possible.
Call for help
You can help by looking through the list of remaining individuals and
corporations we need to get agreements
from,
and reaching out to them, or letting us know at license-questions@llvm.org how
we can reach out to them. Also, if you’d happen to have any other information that you think could help us, please do let us know at licen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The LLVM Project Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rollercoaster: group messaging for mix networks]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876239/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876239/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T19:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even encrypted data sent on the internet leaves some footprints—metadata
about where packets originate, where they are bound, and when they are sent. 
Mix networks are
meant to hide that metadata by routing packets through various intermediate
nodes to try to thwart the traffic analysis used by nation-state-level
adversaries to identify "opponents" of various kinds. Tor is perhaps the
best-known mix network, but there are others that make different
tradeoffs to increase the security of their users.  Rollercoaster
is a recently announced mechanism that extends the functionality of mix
networks in order to more efficiently communicate among groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build AI-powered customer conversations in Google Maps and Search with Google's Business Messages]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/build-ai-powered-customer-conversations.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/build-ai-powered-customer-conversations.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sean Falconer, Staff Developer Relations Engineer Sean Falconer 
 Google’s Business Messages let customers message a business directly from Google Search, Google Maps, and any brand-managed property. Developers of Business Messages can leverage tools like Dialogflow to create AI-powered conversational experiences, where customers can chat with lifelike virtual agents that understand, interact, and talk in natural ways. Meanwhile the business can leverage real life agents when needed. 
In this article, I’ll give a brief overview of Business Messages, how to get started developing with the platform, and then walkthrough how to set up an AI-powered conversion using the Bot-in-a-Box feature.  
Let’s get started! 
What is Google's Business Messages?
  
Business Messages is a mobile co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer IoT: vulnerability disclosure practice “unacceptably low”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471591</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/consumer-iot-vulnerability-disclosure-practice-unacceptably-low/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite small year-on-year improvements, progress on vulnerability disclosure for consumer IoT security is unacceptably low according to the IoT Security Foundation. 
The post Consumer IoT: vulnerability disclosure practice “unacceptably low” appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876327/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876327/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (389-ds-base and libxml2), Debian (atftp, axis, and ntfs-3g), Fedora (digikam, freerdp, guacamole-server, and remmina), openSUSE (java-11-openjdk, kernel, samba, and tomcat), SUSE (firefox, java-11-openjdk, kernel, libarchive, samba, and tomcat), and Ubuntu (accountsservice, hivex, and openexr).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controller for HomeKit: The smart home app for power users]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9330</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/controller-for-homekit-the-smart-home-app-for-power-users/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple iPhone users with a smart home are surely familiar with the HomeKit platform as well as Apple’s Home app. Home is a simple but effective way to manage and use HomeKit devices. And it works well. But there’s room for improvement and that’s exactly what Controller for HomeKit, a third-party iOS app, brings to […]
The post Controller for HomeKit: The smart home app for power users appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876285/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876285/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T13:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.14.19 and 5.4.160 stable kernels have been released;
these updates contain a huge number of important fixes.  The equally
massive 5.15.3
and 5.10.80
updates were also intended for release but, as the result of some problems
that turned up in testing, they will be going through one
more round of review first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting your embedded software against memory corruption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471585</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/protecting-your-embedded-software-against-memory-corruption/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T12:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aim of this article is to provide a software method that explains how to deal with corruption of memory data sets stored in non-volatile...
The post Protecting your embedded software against memory corruption appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lendaro Francucci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[congatec and SYSGO team up for functional safety & security on COM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471576</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/congatec-and-sysgo-team-up-to-for-functional-safety-security-on-com/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T11:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[congatec and SYSGO partnership for Arm and x86 based computer-on-module (COM) solutions aims to simplify development process of safety and security-critical systems, with certification support for functional safety of electronic systems.
The post congatec and SYSGO team up for functional safety & security on COM appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release 3.0 of the IoT Security Assurance Framework Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21387</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/release-3-0-of-the-iot-security-assurance-framework-announced/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T09:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Business ready: extends use into supply chain and aligns with more security standards November 17th, 2021 The IoT Security Foundation today announced the availability of Release 3.0 of it's ever-popular IoT Security Assurance Framework. The Framework is a practical resource that helps IoT vendors provide fit-for-purpose security in their products and services. It is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[상속세 개정 논의에 부쳐: 가업상속공제와 물납제도 손봐야]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82639</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82639"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T02:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기획재정부가 지난 12일 국회 기획재정위원회 조세소위원회에 ‘상속세 주요 쟁점에 대한 검토의견 보고서’를 제출했다. 정부의 상속세 개편 방향은 연부연납(*), 가업상속공제(*) 등 세부 내용을 담고 있으며, 국회는 이를 바탕으로 15일부터 상속세 개편 논의를 진행하고 있다. 극심한 불평등과 양극화에, 코로나19로 유래 없는 가혹한 경제 현실을 마주한 국민에게 소득재분배 기능을 하는 상속세 개편 논의는 매우 중요하다. 부의 집중과 편중 심화를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Networks and the Human Factor: How to Know Whether They’re Accessible]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2497</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/blockchain-networks-and-the-human-factor-how-to-know-whether-theyre-accessible/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T23:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As blockchain technology rapidly gains the attention of a mass audience, the conversation is still centered solely around technical topics related to the scalability of a network — transactions per second, latency, and throughput, for example.  To successfully build consumer-scale experiences, however, developers must think beyond performance metrics and consider the human factor: Accessibility —... Read More
The post Blockchain Networks and the Human Factor: How to Know Whether They’re Accessible appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dieter Shirley and Benjamin Ebner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge Storage Boxes Update]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=11819</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2021/11/16/huge-storage-boxes-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I release a huge update of my storage boxes system for 3d-print. This update not only further improves the geometries of the models, but also extend the available sizes and variants. There are now 1000+ model files in the full set you can buy in the shop. As a buyer of one of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Trojan Source and Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875964/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875964/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trojan Source vulnerabilities have been
rippling through various development
communities since their disclosure on 
November 1.  The oddities that can arise when handling Unicode, and
bidirectional Unicode in particular, in a programming 
language have led Rust, for
example, to check for
the problematic code points in strings and comments and, by default,
refuse to compile if they are present.  Python has chosen a different path,
but work is underway to help inform programmers of the kinds of pitfalls that
Trojan Source has highlighted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio checks the code quality in the .NET Foundation projects: LINQ to DB]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0887/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0887/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The .NET Foundation is an independent organization, created by Microsoft, to support open-source projects around the DotNet platform. Currently, the organization gathered many libraries under its wing. We have already tested some of these libraries with the help of PVS-Studio. The next project to check with the analyzer - LINQ to DB.  LINQ to DB is a database access framework based on LINQ. LINQ to DB has collected the best of its predecessors. It allows you to work with various DBMS, whereas LINQ to SQL back in the day allowed you to work only with MS SQL. It's not as heavy and complicated as LINQ to SQL or Entity Framework. LINQ to DB provides more control and quick access to data. The framework is not that big: it's written in C# and contains more than 40,000 lines of code. LINQ to DB is also one of the .NET Foundation projects. We have previously checked the projects of this organization: Windows Forms, Xamarin.Forms, Teleric UI for UWP, etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[결론이 주는 함축]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222570517749</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222570517749"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T20:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주장해라. 그리고 그 근거를 제시하라. 특히 철학에서 더 그래야 한다. 이 간단한 주문 사항에 대해서 반발하는 이유가 도대체 무엇이란 말인가? 게다가 타당한 근거를 제시하라고 주문하지도 않았다. 그냥 주장했다면 적어도 그 이유나 논거를 제시해야 한다고 말했다. 그 다음이야 비로소 그 논거가 타당한지, 정당한지, 설득력이 있는지 따질 수 있다. 논증이 결여되어 있는, 즉 주장만이 있는 그 철학 분야에 대해 그 나름의 배경 지식을 갖고 있다면, 내 스스로 그 논증을 만들 수 있다. 그런데 이것이 가능하기 위해서도 단지 주장만 일방적으로 제시되어 있는지, 아니면 그 주장 배후에 암시적으로 그 주장에 대한 논거가 있는지 판단해야.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage your passes from Google Pay’s Business Console]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/manage-your-passes-from-google-pay.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/manage-your-passes-from-google-pay.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by: 
Ryan Novas, Product Manager, Google Pay’s Business Console
Jose Ugia, Developer Relations Engineer, Google Pay
    

 Last year we launched Google Pay’s Business Console, a platform that helps developers discover, integrate with, and manage Google Pay features for their businesses. Since then, integrating Google Pay products has become easier and faster, with features like a common business profile and a unified dashboard.  
Today, we are adding Passes as a new section to Google Pay’s Business Console, so you can manage all your Google Pay resources from one place. You can find the new Passes section in the console’s left-hand navigation bar, and from there, access your tickets, loyalty programs, offers and other passes resources. 
Google Pay’s Business Console features a more …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876227/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876227/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libxml-security-java), Fedora (botan2), openSUSE (drbd-utils, kernel, and samba), Red Hat (kernel and webkit2gtk3), SUSE (drbd-utils and samba), and Ubuntu (vim).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scythe has a cool name and a good idea for security]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9327</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/scythe-has-a-cool-name-and-a-good-idea-for-security/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I talk to companies offering connected devices, I often ask them how they design their products with security in mind. I usually get a lot of information about encryption, secure elements on the chips, and bug bounty programs. Some of the companies I talk to actively hire researchers to do penetration testing on the […]
The post Scythe has a cool name and a good idea for security appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software quality demands both static code analysis and dynamic testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471566</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/software-quality-demands-both-static-code-analysis-and-dynamic-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static code analysis and dynamic testing of executable software separately uncover only a part of the existing defects in code, requiring use of both methods...
The post Software quality demands both static code analysis and dynamic testing appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Royd Lüdtke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대장동 의혹 언론인, 소속 언론은 어떻게 보도했을까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82628</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82628"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T09:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대장동 개발 특혜 의혹이 잦아들지 않고 있습니다. 경기경제신문이 2021년 8월 31일 ‘대장동 사업에 참여해 높은 수익을 올린 민간사업자 화천대유와 이재명 경기도지사와의 연관성을 제기’하는 의혹 보도를 내놓으면서 시작됐는데요. 장기표 당시 국민의힘 대선 예비후보가 9월 12일 해당 의혹을 언급하며 이재명 경기도지사에게 진상규명을 요구했고, 조선일보는 9월 13일 화천대유 설립에 참여한 언론인 출신 김만배 씨와 이재명 지사의 연관성을 제기하는 보도를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[포털 ‘퇴출’ 연합뉴스의 적반하장]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82619</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82619"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T07:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 12일, 포털 내 언론의 입점과 퇴출을 심사하는 뉴스제휴평가위원회(이하 ‘제평위’)는 광고성 보도자료를 일반기사인 것처럼 포털에 전송한 연합뉴스에 ‘강등’을 결정했다. 한 언론사의 취재 결과 연합뉴스는 홍보사업팀을 통해 광고성 보도자료를 기사 형태로(이하 ‘기사형 광고’) 2,000여 건이나 포털에 전송해온 것으로 알려졌다. 연합뉴스는 이번 결정으로 인해 최소 1년간 포털 검색을 제외한 기사 송출을 할 수 없다. 연합뉴스는 제평위의 결정에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.9 hotfix release is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/11/python-399-hotfix-release-is-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/11/python-399-hotfix-release-is-now.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T22:09:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get it here: https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-399/

Python 3.9.9 is the eighth maintenance release of the legacy 3.9 series. Python 3.10 is now the latest feature release series of Python 3. Get the latest release of 3.10.x here.

3.9.9 was released out of schedule as a hotfix for an argparse regression in Python 3.9.8 which caused complex command-line tools to fail recognizing sub-commands properly. Details in BPO-45235. There are only three other bugfixes in this release compared to 3.9.8. See the changelog for details on what changed.

Upgrading to 3.9.9 is highly recommended if you’re running Python 3.9.8.

The next Python 3.9 maintenance release will be 3.9.10, currently scheduled for 2022-01-03.

We apologize for the inconvenience

…and still hope you’ll enjoy the new release!

Your friendly release team,

Ned Deily @nad

Steve Dower @steve.dower

Łukasz Langa @ambv]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.34.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876154/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876154/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.34.0 of the Git source-code management system is out.
"It is comprised of 834 non-merge commits since
v2.33.0, contributed by 109 people, 29 of which are new faces".  See
this
GitHub blog post for a look at some of the more significant changes in
this release:


	ort does just that: it’s a full-blown rewrite of the merge strategy
	that aims to emulate the same concepts behind recursive while
	avoiding many of its long-standing performance and correctness
	problems. In a merge containing many renames, ort outperforms
	recursive by 500x. For a series of similar merges (like in a rebase
	operation), the speedup is over 9000x since ort can cache and reuse
	results from previous merges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upload massive lists of products to Merchant Center using Centimani]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/upload-massive-lists-of-products-to-merchant-center-using-Centimani.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/upload-massive-lists-of-products-to-merchant-center-using-Centimani.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:21:00.036Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hector Parra, Jaime Martínez, Miguel Fernandes, Julia Hernández
     Merchant Center lets merchants manage how their in-store and online product     inventory appears on Google. It allows them to reach hundreds of millions     of people looking to buy products like yours each day. 

    To upload their products, merchants can make use of feeds, that is, files     with a list of products in a specific format. These can be shared with     Merchant Center in different ways: using Google Sheets, SFTP or FTP shares,     Google Cloud Storage or manually through the user interface. These methods     work great for the majority of cases. But, if a merchant's product list     grows over time, they might reach the usage limits of the feeds. Depending     on the case, quota extensions could…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] 5.16 Merge window, part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875135/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875135/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released
5.16-rc1 and ended the 5.16 merge window on November 14, as
expected.  At that point, 12,321 non-merge changesets had been pulled into
the mainline; about 5,500 since our summary of
the first half of the merge window was written.  As is usually the case,
the patch mix in the latter part of the merge window tended more toward
fixes, but there were a number other changes as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876135/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876135/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ffmpeg and tomcat9), Fedora (et and kernel), openSUSE (binutils, rubygem-activerecord-5_1, samba, and tinyxml), Oracle (freerdp and httpd:2.4), Red Hat (devtoolset-11-gcc, gcc-toolset-10-binutils, kernel, kernel-rt, and kpatch-patch), and Scientific Linux (freerdp).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s flexible ReSkin sensor has untapped potential in the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9243</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/metas-flexible-reskin-sensor-has-untapped-potential-in-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While looking for new research on robotics last week, I caught the news from Facebook — I mean, Meta — about its new flexible sensor. It unveiled what it calls ReSkin technology for tactile sensing, created in conjunction with Carnegie Mellon University researchers. I think this technology could have a lot of potential in the smart […]
The post Meta’s flexible ReSkin sensor has untapped potential in the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news for the week ending Nov. 5, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9321</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-for-the-week-ending-nov-5-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T14:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for IoT platform vendors to shine! Enterprise IoT is moving out of its custom-built phase, and now customers are fine with off-the-shelf solutions with connectivity built in, according to a survey released last week from Oracle. Oracle surveyed 800 executives who have already deployed some IoT project about their thoughts, finding that how […]
The post IoT news for the week ending Nov. 5, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aarch64 Linux kernel fuzzing - syzkaller]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/9075747</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/9075747"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개요
https://github.com/google/syzkaller/
syzkaller 는 QEMU 기반으로 운영체제를 부팅한 후 Host 와 Guest 사이에 ssh 연결을 수립하고 system call fuzzing 을 수행하는 도구다. 일반적으로 syzkaller 는 x86 리눅스 위에서 테스트 대상 x86 리눅스를 QEMU로 테스트하는 방식으로 많이 사용된다. 그러나 이 글에서는 Aarch64 리눅스를 테스트하고자 한다.
전체적인 과정은 공식 메뉴얼을 따랐지만, 설명이 친절한 편이 아니어서 직접 삽질을 하면서 다시 정리해보았다.


1. Kernel Build (with KASAN)
테스트 하고자 하는 리눅스 커널을 빌드한다. 앞선 글에서 설명했으나, 그때는 별다른 보안 옵션을 설정하지 않았다. 지금은 KASAN, KCOV 등의 새니타이징 기능을 켜고 퍼즈 테스트 성능을 측정할 수 있도록 하는 부분이 다르다. 
일단 x86에서 진행하는 것이라면 크로스 컴파일을 통해 Aarch64 리눅스 커널을 빌드할 필요성이 있다. 크로스 컴파일을 위한 툴 체인을 받아야 한다. 
Linaro toolchain 
https://releases.linaro.org/components/toolchain/binaries/latest/aarch64-linux-gnu/
$ wget http://releases.linaro.org/components/toolchain/binaries/latest-7/aarch64-linux-gnu/gcc-linaro-7.5.0-2019.12-x86_64_aarch64-linux-gnu.tar.x…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced verification: unlocking the door to a new era of AI chips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471570</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/advanced-verification-unlocking-the-door-to-a-new-era-of-ai-chips/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at how chip manufacturers will have to adjust hardware architecture in order to accommodate ever-growing demand for increased AI functionality. 
The post Advanced verification: unlocking the door to a new era of AI chips appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiran Vittal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경제 공포 마케팅: OECD·IMF 보고서 왜곡하는 언론 (ft. 결론은 규제 완화)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82602</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82602"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T09:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OECD(경제협력개발기구)는 11월 8일 [장기게임: 2060년까지 재정전망 구조개혁 필요성 강조] (The Long Game: Fiscal Outlooks to 2060 Underline Need for Structural Reform) 보고서를 발표했습니다. 2000년부터 2060년까지 장기 재정전망을 담은 보고서로 1인당 잠재 실질 GDP(국내총생산)와 잠재 실질 GDP 성장률, 고용동향 등을 담고 있습니다. 대부분 언론이 이를 주요하게 다루는 동시에 한 달 전 발표된 IMF(국제통화기금) [재정 점검 보고서: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876072/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876072/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T07:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc1 kernel prepatch is out and the
merge window is closed for this cycle.


	Anyway, it's not a huge release, although it's also not a
	remarkably small one like 5.15 was (ok, "remarkably small" is
	relative, when even such small releases have 10k+
	commits).. There's a bit of everything in here, and you can look to
	the appended mergelog for some kind of flavor, but I guess the
	folio work is worth mentioning, since it's an unusually core thing
	that we don't tend to see most releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20: Heterogeneous Lookup in (Un)ordered Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/heterogeneous-access-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/heterogeneous-access-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you like to gain 20…35 or even 50% speed improvements when searching in associative containers? In this blog post, we’ll explore a technique called “heterogenous access” that offers such impressive speedups. We’ll explore ordered containers, and the support for unordered collections added recently in C++20.
Recap on heterogeneous lookup in ordered containers
Let’s bring the example and have a look at how this feature works for ordered containers.
If you have the following code:
std::map<std::string, int> intMap { 
    { "Hello Super Long String", 1 }, 
    { "Another Longish String", 2 }, 
    { "This cannot fall into SSO buffer", 3 }
};

std::cout << "Lookup in intMap with by const char*:\n";
std::cout << intMap.contains("Hello Super Long String") << '\n';


In the above code, altho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Individuals matter]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/people-matter/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/people-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most common mistakes I see people make when looking at data is incorrectly using an overly simplified model. A specific variant of this that has derailed the majority of work roadmaps I've looked at is treating people as interchangeable, as if it doesn't matter who is doing what, as if individuals don't matter.
Individuals matter.
A pattern I've repeatedly seen during the roadmap creation and review process is that people will plan out the next few quarters of work and then assign some number of people to it, one person for one quarter to a project, two people for three quarters to another, etc. Nominally, this process enables teams to understand what other teams are doing and plan appropriately. I've never worked in an organization where this actually worked, where this actuall…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공감과 감명에 대한 논증적 정당화]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222568352620</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222568352620"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T21:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어떤 주장이 있다. 그 주장을 듣고 공감하면서 감명을 받는다. 그 공감과 감명의 정체가 무엇인지 스스로 생각해 보아야 한다. 가령 공자의 <논어> 첫 머리가 다음처럼 시작한다. 배우고 때맞춰 익히면 또한 기쁘지 않겠는가. 그렇다. 배우고 때에 맞게 익히고 연습하는 것이다. 그렇게 하면 기쁘다. 그런데 왜 기쁘단 말인가? 왜 배우고 때에 맞게 익히고 연습하는 것이 중요하단 말인가? 이런 질문을 하지 않은 채, 공자의 구절을 그대로 암송하거나 수동적으로 수용할 수 있다. 그러나 이렇게 해서 그 구절을 자기의 것으로 <소화>한다고 할 수 있는가? 나는 아니라고 생각한다. 박이문은 노장 사상뿐만 아니라, 공자의 <논어.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio to check the RPCS3 emulator]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0886/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0886/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RPCS3 is an interesting project that emulates the PS3 console. It is actively evolving. Recently we heard the news that the emulator learned how run all the games from the console's catalog. That's a good excuse to analyze the project. We'll see which errors remained after new fixes were added to the project. The project is quite hefty. It contains about 300 thousand lines of C++ code and relies upon many external dependencies that include the following: For the GUI part, the project uses Qt - however, that is taken from the system library. The screenshot below demonstrates the full list of dependencies:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spilling the Beans: C/C++ Header Files]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33956</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/11/14/spilling-the-beans-c-c-header-files/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T12:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Header files in C/C++ are defining the interface between different modules. In this article I share some tips and tricks how create such interface files. Creating Header File Most IDEs have a helper to create header files, including Eclipse. What … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유럽 법원 “구글에 물린 반독점 벌금 옳았다”]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73734</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/11/13/eucompetitiongoogle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=eucompetitiongoogle"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T23:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유럽연합 규제 당국이 구글을 상대로 법원에서 승소했습니다. 법원의 이번 판결에 힘입어 유럽연합은 앞으로 구글을 비롯한 빅테크 기업을 상대로 반독점 규제를 강화할 것으로 보입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[독단주의자의 역리]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222567488653</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222567488653"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T19:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주장이 있다. 그러나 그 논거가 없다. 논거가 없다는 것은 그 주장을 참으로 받아들일 단서가 주어지지 않았다는 것이다. 김광수의 <논리와 비판적 사고>에서 이것이 ‘독단주의의 역리’에 부딪치게 된다고 말한다. <독단(dogmatism)은 자적 사생아의 숨겨진 아버지이다. 독단에 빠진 사람은 자신의 주장이 옳다고 하면서도, 그 근거를 제시하지 않을 뿐만 아니라, 근거의 검토를 허용하지 않는다. 자신의 주장에 대한 근거를 검토하려는 것을 자신에 대한 도전으로 여긴다. 그 도전은 어리석고, 헛되고, 기분 나쁘고, 이단적인 것으로 여긴다. 만일 그가 친절하다면, 자명한 진리를 의심하는 꿈에서 깨어나라고 진지하게 조언하기도 하.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There actually is a compelling reason for Facebook to continue using facial recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9307</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/there-actually-is-a-compelling-reason-for-facebook-to-continue-using-facial-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T14:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week on the IoT Podcast, we discussed the news of Facebook ceasing the use of facial recognition across the photos its users upload. From our perspective, this was a big win for the Facebook user community. Why? Users had no control over whether Facebook would scan photos uploaded by others and then tag all […]
The post There actually is a compelling reason for Facebook to continue using facial recognition appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust data structures with circular references]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rust-data-structures-with-circular-references/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rust-data-structures-with-circular-references/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>To implement its safety guarantees, the Rust compiler keeps careful track
of ownership and references throughout a program. This makes writing certain
kinds of data structures challenging; in particular, data structures that have
circular references.</p>
<p>Let's start with a simple binary tree:</p>
<div class="highlight"><pre><span></span><span class="k">struct</span> <span class="nc">Tree</span><span class="w"> </span><span class="p">{</span><span class="w"></span>
<span class="w">    </span><span class="n">root</span>: <span class="nb">Option</span><span class="o">&lt;</span><span class="n">Node</span><span class="o">&gt;</span><span class="p">,</span><span class="w"></span>
<span class="p">}</span><span class="w"></span>

<span class="k">struct</span> <span class="nc">Node</span><span class="w"> </span><span class="p">{</span><span class="w"></span>
<span class="w">    </span><span class="n">data …</span></pre></div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 순수 지성개념과 초월적 연역]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222566749395</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222566749395"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T20:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<우리는 앞에서 공간과 시간 개념에 대해서, 이것들이 선험적인 인식으로서 그럼에도 어떻게 대상들과 관계를 맺어야만 하는가, 그리고 어떻게 모든 경험에 독립해서 대상에 대한 종합적인 인식을 가능하게 하는가를 가벼운 수고만으로도 이해할 수 있었다. 감성의 그러한 순수한 형식들에 의해서만 하나의 대상은 현상할 수, 다시 말해 경험적 직관의 객관일 수 있기 때문에, 공간과 시간은 현상으로서의 대상을 가능하게 하는 선험적인 조건을 함유하는 순수 직관이고, 이 아래에서 종합은 객관적 타당성을 가지는 것이니 말이다.> 공간과 시간 개념은 선험적 인식이다. 그럼에도 그것은 대상과 관계 맺는다. 따라서 그것은 선험적 종합.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: Nvidia GTC & metaverse, wireless & sustainability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471552</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-nvidia-gtc-metaverse-wireless-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T20:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes coverage from Nvidia GTC, CW (Cambridge Wireless), plus embedded news, products, funding and events.
The post embedded news week: Nvidia GTC & metaverse, wireless & sustainability appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Groups optimize smart metering IoT with OMS over LoRaWAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471548</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/groups-optimize-smart-metering-iot-with-oms-over-lorawan/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T18:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LoRa Alliance and OMS-Group to standardize smart metering IoT applications, with a standard use of the Open Metering System language over LoRaWAN, reducing complexity and cost of integration for utilities.
The post Groups optimize smart metering IoT with OMS over LoRaWAN appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[u-blox MQTT Flex lets you bring your own SIM to IoT sensor networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471544</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/u-blox-mqtt-flex-lets-you-bring-your-own-sim-to-iot-sensor-networks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T18:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bring your own SIM strategy enables users to take advantage of MQTT communication without the operational, logistical, or cost impact of changing their mobile network operator.
The post u-blox MQTT Flex lets you bring your own SIM to IoT sensor networks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Samsung H-Cube 2.5D technology integrates 6 HBMs for HPC applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471539</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-samsung-h-cube-2-5d-technology-integrates-6-hbms-for-hpc-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T17:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[H-Cube applies advanced 2.5D silicon interposer technology and hybrid-substrate structure, allowing efficient integration of 6 HBMs, and lowering barriers to entry in the HPC/AI market.
The post New Samsung H-Cube 2.5D technology integrates 6 HBMs for HPC applications appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClusterFuzzLite: Continuous fuzzing for all (Google Security blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875945/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875945/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T17:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Google Security blog, Jonathan Metzman announced the release of ClusterFuzzLite, which is "a continuous fuzzing solution that runs as part of CI/CD workflows to find vulnerabilities faster than ever before".   ClusterFuzzLite is a descendant of OSS-Fuzz, which we looked at in 2017.

Large projects including systemd and curl are already using ClusterFuzzLite during code review, with positive results. According to Daniel Stenberg, author of curl, “When the human reviewers nod and have approved the code and your static code analyzers and linters can't detect any more issues, fuzzing is what takes you to the next level of code maturity and robustness. OSS-Fuzz and ClusterFuzzLite help us maintain curl as a quality project, around the clock, every day and every commit.”

[...] To learn more, check out the ClusterFuzzLite documentation. ClusterFuzzLite currently supports GitHub Actions, Google Cloud Build and Prow. We built this with CI system extensibility in mind, and adding support for other CI systems is straightforward. Please contact us if you’re interested in contributing support, or have any questions, feedback or feature requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some upcoming memory-management patches]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875587/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875587/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The memory-management subsystem remains one of the most complex parts of
the kernel, with an ongoing reliance on various heuristics for
performance.  It is thus not surprising that developers continue to try to
improve its functionality.  A number of memory-management patches are
currently in circulation; read on for a look at the freeing of page-table
pages, kvmalloc() flags, memory clearing, and NUMA "home nodes".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875932/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875932/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of eight stable kernels: 5.15.2, 5.14.18, 5.10.79, 5.4.159, 4.19.217, 4.14.255, 4.9.290, and 4.4.292.  They contain a relatively small set
of important fixes, but, as usual, users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875931/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875931/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T14:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (node-tar, postgresql-11, postgresql-13, and postgresql-9.6), Fedora (autotrace, botan2, chafa, converseen, digikam, dmtx-utils, dvdauthor, eom, kxstitch, pfstools, php-pecl-imagick, psiconv, q, R-magick, radeontop, rss-glx, rubygem-rmagick, synfig, synfigstudio, vdr-scraper2vdr, vdr-skinelchihd, vdr-skinnopacity, vdr-tvguide, and WindowMaker), Mageia (kernel, kernel-linus, and openafs), openSUSE (kernel), Red Hat (freerdp), SUSE (bind and kernel), and Ubuntu (openexr, postgresql-10, postgresql-12, postgresql-13, and samba).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia GTC: New Jetson module offers 200 TOPS for embedded edge AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471535</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nvidia-gtc-new-jetson-module-offers-200-tops-for-embedded-edge-ai/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T13:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Jetson AGX Orin module built on Nvidia Ampere architecture claims to be smallest and most powerful AI supercomputer for embedded edge computing.
The post Nvidia GTC: New Jetson module offers 200 TOPS for embedded edge AI appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nvidia Jetson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia GTC: New 400 Gbps InfiniBand networking platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471530</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nvidia-gtc-new-400-gbps-infiniband-networking-platform/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T11:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New at Nvidia GTC is a 400Gbps InfiniBand switch and networking platform which features secure, cloud-native, multi-tenant, bare-metal performance for AI, data analytics, and HPC applications
The post Nvidia GTC: New 400 Gbps InfiniBand networking platform appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aarch64 Linux Kernel Debug]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11156632</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11156632"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T08:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미루고 미루던 리눅스 커널 취약점 연구를 올해가 가기 전에 최소한 '시작'은 해보려고 한다. 
아직 초보인데, Defenit팀의 김현우(V4bel)님께서 인프런에서 진행하시는 강좌가 정말 큰 도움이 되었다.
https://www.inflearn.com/course/%EB%A6%AC%EB%88%85%EC%8A%A4-%EC%BB%A4%EB%84%90-%ED%95%B4%ED%82%B9/
해당 강좌는 Intel x86_64 환경을 기준으로 되어있는데, 이를 Aarch64 리눅스로 하여 열심히 삽질 중이다. 변환했을 때 똑같이 적용되는 것도 있고, 안 되는 것도 많다..


우선 Aarch64 환경에서 커널 빌드 및 디버깅을 하기 위한 절차를 기록해둔다. 대부분의 내용은 위에서 언급한 강좌에서 김현우님께서 가이드해주신 방법을 참고했으며, Aarch64 로 변환할 때 필요한 수정사항들을 내가 작성했다(이 게시물은 강사님의 허락을 받고 기록해두는 것이다.)
 
(참고로 1~3번 과정을 생략하고, 내가 올려둔 파일을 다운로드 하셔도 됨)
1. 리눅스 커널 빌드
우선 리눅스 커널을 직접 빌드할 수 있는 환경이 마련되어야 한다. 강의에서는 인텔 리눅스 상에서 인텔 리눅스를 빌드하는 방식으로 진행되었다. 그러나 Aarch64 아키텍처용 리눅스를 빌드하려면 방법이 달라진다. 대략 두가지 방법이 있다.
1) Intel 리눅스상에서 cross-compiler 를 사용해서 Aarch64 리눅스 이미지를 빌드하는 방법.
2) Aarch64 리눅스 상에서 Aarch64 리눅스를 빌드하는 방법.
그동안은 대부분 1의 방법이 선호되었다. 왜냐…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글쓰기가 어려운 이유 (ft. 생각, 말, 글)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82593</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82593"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T04:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[흔히 우리는 ‘명료한 사고에서 명료한 글이 나온다’고 생각한다. 하지만 자신이 무슨 말을 하려고 하는지 분명히 알고 있다고 해도, 자신이 쓴 글이 명료하지 않다는 것을 깨닫는 경우가 많다. 열심히 글을 썼는데 상대방이 그것을 읽고 무슨 말이냐고 묻는 상황은 참으로 난감하다. 물론 사적인 메모나 편지를 쓸 때는 글 쓰는 것이 어렵지 않다. 하지만 공적인 보고서나 논문 같은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All hail bug reports: how we reduced the analysis time of the user's project from 80 to 4 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0885/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0885/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People often see work in support as something negative. Today we'll look at it from a different perspective. This article is about a real communication of 100+ messages, exceptions, the analysis that didn't complete in three days... Actually, bug reports are great If a bug report is adequately handled from both sides, it means that both the user and the software developer are interested in solving the problem. If both sides achieve the desired result, it's a win-win situation. Before we proceed to the story, here's a little introduction. We are the PVS-Studio team. We develop the analyzer that searches for errors and potential vulnerabilities in C, C++, C#, and Java code. Yours truly is the team lead of the C# analyzer development team, the author of articles and posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Play-to-Earn’ Gaming and How Work is Evolving in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2473</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/play-to-earn-gaming-and-how-work-is-evolving-in-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T19:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s episode we’re talking about an emerging model of gaming called play to earn, in which players can make actual money based on how much time and effort they put into a game. Play to earn is also part of broader trends — the changing relationship between players and platforms, new incentives for participants... Read More
The post ‘Play-to-Earn’ Gaming and How Work is Evolving in Web3 appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Zirlin, Gabby Dizon, Arianna Simpson and Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Exposing Trojan Source exploits in Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875229/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875229/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T16:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the "Trojan Source" vulnerabilities
have, thus far, generated far more publicity than examples of actual
exploits, addressing the problem still seems like a good thing to do.
There are several places where defenses could be put into place; text
editors, being the place where developers look at a lot of code, are one
obvious example.  The discussion of how to enhance Emacs in this regard has
made it clear, though, that there are multiple opinions about how an editor
should flag potential attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twelve Years of Go (The Go blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875817/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875817/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T16:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 10, the Go programming language community celebrated the 12th anniversary of its release as open-source software.  The post covers a number of different topics, including the consolidation of web sites at go.dev, releases and their features over the last year, as well as a look to the future:

In February, the Go 1.18 release will expand the new register-based calling convention to non-x86 architectures, bringing dramatic performance improvements with it. It will include the new Go fuzzing support. And it will be the first release to include support for generics.

Generics will be one of our focuses for 2022. The initial release in Go 1.18 is only the beginning. We need to spend time using generics and learning what works and what doesn’t, so that we can write best practices and decide what should be added to the standard library and other libraries. We expect that Go 1.19 (expected in August 2022) and later releases will further refine the design and implementation of generics as well as integrating them further into the overall Go experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rohde & Schwarz and MediaTek deliver Wi-Fi 6E production test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471527</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/rohde-schwarz-and-mediatek-deliver-wi-fi-6e-production-test/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohde & Schwarz CMP180 radio communications test platform is integrated into MediaTek ATE tool to offer production test solution for Wi-Fi 6E devices.
The post Rohde & Schwarz and MediaTek deliver Wi-Fi 6E production test appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Three IoT acquisitions and the infrastructure bill]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9303</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-three-iot-acquisitions-and-the-infrastructure-bill/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show focuses on three big deals happening in the IoT sector and a meaty enterprise IoT report. First up, we discuss ADT buying SunPro Solar for $825 million, which represents yet another deal bringing energy management to the smart home. We then talk about Level Home’s acquisition, the state of smart home deals, […]
The post Podcast: Three IoT acquisitions and the infrastructure bill appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875813/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875813/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T13:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (icinga2, libxstream-java, ruby-kaminari, and salt), Fedora (awscli, cacti, cacti-spine, python-boto3, python-botocore, radeontop, and rust), Mageia (firefox, libesmtp, libzapojit, sssd, and thunderbird), openSUSE (samba and samba and ldb), SUSE (firefox, pcre, qemu, samba, and samba and ldb), and Ubuntu (firejail, linux-bluefield, linux-gke-5.4, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-oem-5.10, linux-oem-5.14, and python-py).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NXP and Ford collaborate on connected cars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471523</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nxp-and-ford-collaborate-on-connected-cars/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T12:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NXP to provide vehicle networking, gateway and i.MX 8 Series processors to enable enhanced services, convenience and over-the-air updateable vehicles
The post NXP and Ford collaborate on connected cars appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시간]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222565350570</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222565350570"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T10:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[레비나스의 <시간과 타자> ‘서문’을 아주 쪼금 읽다가 생각한다. 시간에 대해서 나는 어떤 생각을 갖고 있는가? 나는 시간에 대해 철학적으로 중요하다고 생각하는 것인가? 도대체 시간에 대한 철학적 문제들이란 무엇인가? 기껏해야 내가 시간에 대해 갖고 있는 생각은 칸트의 그것, 즉 시간과 공간 형식이 경험의 구성 조건이라는 것이다. 시간에 대해서 레비나스가 다음처럼 주장한다. (1) 시간은 무한성과 자족성을 존재자에게 보장해 줄 수 없는 관계이다. (2) 시간은 사회성을 뜻하는 관계이다. (3) 시간은 존재자의 존재라는 존재의 지평이 아니라, 존재 저편의 방식으로, 즉 타자에 대한 사유 관계이다. (4) 시간은 타인의 얼굴.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[천국 문 앞에서도 AP 기자를 만날까 봐 무섭군]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82582</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82582"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T07:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[해외뉴스를 보다보면 AP라는 통신사가 작성한 기사를 본 적이 있을 것이다. AP(The Associated Press)는 국제뉴스 취재를 목표로 설립된 비영리 뉴스협동조합이다. 1846년 뉴욕을 기반으로 하는 다양한 신문사들이 멕시코 전선과 유럽 소식을 더 빠르게 전송받기 위해 자금을 모아서 설립했다. 하지만 20세기 초반까지 AP는 외국에 직접 나가 취재하기보다는 로이터(Reuters)와 같은 기존의 뉴스통신 카르텔에서 뉴스를 받아서 기사를 작성했다. AP의 위상  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14년째 표류하는 차별금지법 (일간지 보도 분석)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82567</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82567"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T06:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2007년 국회에 차별금지법이 처음 발의됐습니다. 노무현 정부 시절 정부 입법으로 처음 발의된 차별금지법은 14년간 발의와 폐기를 반복하며 아직도 국회 문턱을 넘지 못하고 있습니다. 제21대 국회에서는 장혜영 정의당 의원과 권인숙·박주민·이상민 더불어민주당 의원 등이 대표발의한 4건의 차별금지법안이 발의돼 있습니다. 지난 6월 10만 명 동의로 달성된 ‘차별금지법 제정에 관한 국민동의 청원’이 국회 법제사법위원회 심사를 기다리고 있습니다. 국민동의 청원 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 11, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875075/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875075/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T00:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 11, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The strong and weak forces of architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/strong-weak-arch.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/strong-weak-arch.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good technical design decisions are very dependent on context. Teams that
    regularly work together on common goals are able to communicate regularly
    and negotiate changes quickly. These teams exhibit a strong force of
    alignment, and can make technology and design decisions that harness that
    strong force. As we zoom out in a larger organisation an increasingly
    weak force exists between teams and divisions that work independently
    and have less frequent collaboration. Recognising the differences in these
    strong and weak forces allows us to make better decisions and give better
    guidance for each level, allowing for more empowered teams that can move
    faster.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: DefaultTrialRetire]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/DefaultTrialRetire.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/DefaultTrialRetire.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within each normal-sized team, limit the choice of alternatives for any class
	of technology to three. These are: the current sensible default, the one we're
	experimenting with as a trial, and the one that we hate and want to retire.
The conversation goes like this: We want to introduce a new messaging
  technology. How many do we have already in place? Oh we have three in active
  use, including one that's considered legacy and we're partway through
  migrating off and one that we experimented with previously but didn't gain
  traction. Ok, so we're at our limit now. If we want to add another messaging
  tech then we have two choices. Either migrate all of our apps off the legacy
  tech, or properly rid ourselves of the failed experiment. This is quite
  closely related to the idea of capping the number of Innovation Tokens in
  use within your teams.
At a team level these kinds of limits are relatively easy
  to maintain and discuss and act upon, because we have common priorities and
  ways of working and high trust, high bandwidth communication. At the scope of
  the whole organisation the challenge is similar, but getting alignment takes a
  lot longer and doing actual migration and consolidation work can take a long
  time - so we sometimes have to allow for more variation in technology. We also use 
  different techniques to discuss and communicate the status of our preferred technologies.
An approach we use at MYOB to engage our whole organisation in broader decisions about
  technology is by publishing our own MYOB Technology Radar, following the
  format of the Thoughtworks Technology Radar.
  This approach of building our own radar
  involves taking input from all of our verticals and teams, and making a clear
  statement on what technologies we encourage teams to adopt, trial, or more
  importantly which ones to keep clear of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the leap to pursue a passion in Machine Learning with Leigh Johnson #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:03:00.011Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
Leigh Johnson turned her childhood love of Geocities and Neopets into a web development career, and then trained her focus on Machine Learning. Now, she’s a staff software engineer at Slack, a Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning, and founder of Print Nanny, an automated failure detection system and monitoring system for 3D printers. 
Meet Leigh Johnson, Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning.
   
GDE Leigh Johnson
 The early days
Leigh Johnson grew up in the Bronx, NY, and got an early start in web development when she became captivated by Geocities and Neopets in elementary scho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the leap to pursue a passion in Machine Learning with Leigh Johnson #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/dlcSC-NJWtQ/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/dlcSC-NJWtQ/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:03:00.011Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
Leigh Johnson turned her childhood love of Geocities and Neopets into a web development career, and then trained her focus on Machine Learning. Now, she’s a staff software engineer at Slack, a Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning, and founder of Print Nanny, an automated failure detection system and monitoring system for 3D printers. 
Meet Leigh Johnson, Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning.
   
GDE Leigh Johnson
 The early days
Leigh Johnson grew up in the Bronx, NY, and got an early start in web development when she became captivated by Geocities and Neopets in elementary scho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Late-bound argument defaults for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875441/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875441/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T17:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python supports default values for arguments to functions, but those
defaults are evaluated at function-definition time.  A proposal to add
defaults that are evaluated when the function is called has been discussed
at some length on the python-ideas mailing list.  The idea came about, in part,
due to yet another resurrection of the proposal
for None-aware operators in Python.  Late-bound defaults would help
with one use case for those operators, but there are other, stronger
reasons to consider their addition to the language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875708/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875708/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T15:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (openjdk-8 and samba), Fedora (community-mysql, firefox, and vim), openSUSE (binutils, kernel, and tinyxml), Red Hat (annobin, autotrace, babel, bind, binutils, bluez, compat-exiv2-026, container-tools:2.0, container-tools:3.0, container-tools:rhel8, cups, curl, dnf, dnsmasq, edk2, exiv2, file, file-roller, firefox, gcc, gcc-toolset-10-annobin, gcc-toolset-10-binutils, gcc-toolset-10-gcc, gcc-toolset-11-annobin, gcc-toolset-11-binutils, gcc-toolset-11-gcc, glib2, glibc, GNOME, gnutls and nettle, go-toolset:rhel8, grafana, graphviz, grilo, httpd:2.4, jasper, java-17-openjdk, json-c, kernel, kernel-rt, kexec-tools, kpatch-patch, lasso, libgcrypt, libjpeg-turbo, libsepol, libsolv, libssh, libtiff, libwebp, libX11, linuxptp, lua, mingw-glib2, mutt, ncurses, NetworkManager, openjpeg2, openssh, openssl, pcre, pcs, php:7.4, python-jinja2, python-lxml, python-pillow, python-pip, python-psutil, python27:2.7, python3, python36:3.6, python38:3.8 and python38-devel:3.8, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9, qt5, resource-agents, rpm, rust-toolset:rhel8, spamassassin, sqlite, squid:4, tcpdump, tpm2-tools, vim, virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel, and zziplib), and SUSE (binutils and kernel).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Overlooked Levels of the Creator Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2450</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/creator-economy-levels/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems like everyone today is a creator — whether artist, developer, or other individuals following their craft — yet the creator economy still has room to grow. Despite being a multibillion-dollar market fueled by over 50 million people, this movement is much deeper than its monetization platforms, and bigger than the small percentage of... Read More
The post The Overlooked Levels of the Creator Economy appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Runcie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level raises $100M and acquires a smart apartment company]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9295</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/level-raises-100m-and-acquires-a-smart-apartment-company/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level Home, the maker of a slick smart lock, has raised an additional $100 million in a Series C round of funding, as well as completing an all-stock deal to buy multi-family residential software company Dwelo. The two moves are part of a master plan by Level Home CEO John Martin to grow into a […]
The post Level raises $100M and acquires a smart apartment company appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can blockchain accelerate IoT adoption?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471500</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/can-blockchain-accelerate-iot-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T12:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain can empower IoT with the needed security and transparency and is already playing an important role in many IoT applications. With the arrival of...
The post Can blockchain accelerate IoT adoption? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harikrishna Kundariya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[의심의 ‘한국’철학]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222564295930</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222564295930"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T09:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[니체가 말한다. 철학은 철학하는 자가 자기를 불태워 새롭게 하는 곳에 시작된다. 그런데 니체가 이런 말을 할 자격이 있는가? 도대체 그가 생각했던 철학이란 무엇인가? 나는 철학적 논증을 명백하게 보여주지 않는 자를 ‘철학자’라고 부르기 주저한다. 좋게 말하면 문학적 ‘사상가’일 것이다. 물론 니체를 좋아하는 사람들이나 니체 전공자들은 나를 비판할 것이다. “한국을 철학화한다.” 이 주장이 무슨 의미인가? 이 주장이 말이 되는 것인가? 도대체 어떻게 하는 것이 한국을 철학화하는 것인가? 그 구체적 내용과 실질적 결과를 보여주는 것이 중요하다. 단지 구호와 선언은 공허하기 짝이 없다. 한국철학을 해야 한다는 당위적 주장.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samba 4.15.2, 4.14.10, 4.13.14 security releases available]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875565/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875565/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T07:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a set of new Samba releases out there.  They fix a long and
intimidating list of security issues and seem worth upgrading to for any
but the most protected of Samba servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MSA’ 문제를 보완하는 설계와 디자인 트렌트]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82553</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82553"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T06:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 50여 년 동안 소프트웨어 아키텍처 및 애플리케이션 호스팅 모델은 메인프레임에서 마이크로서비스 및 서버리스로의 주요 전환을 경험했다. 메인프레임에서 최신 클라우드 네이티브 아키텍처(CNCF)에 이르기까지 다양한 호스팅 모델은 비즈니스 앱을 개발, 배포 및 유지 관리하는 방식에 영향을 미쳤다. IT 서비스 업계에서 새로운 호스팅 모델을 발견할 때마다 팀은 아키텍처의 이점을 최대한 활용하는 데 어려움을 겪었다. 이로 인해 아키텍처 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MSA’ 문제를 보완하는 설계와 디자인 트렌트]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82553</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/ch0DpmXKwoM/82553"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T06:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 50여 년 동안 소프트웨어 아키텍처 및 애플리케이션 호스팅 모델은 메인프레임에서 마이크로서비스 및 서버리스로의 주요 전환을 경험했다. 메인프레임에서 최신 클라우드 네이티브 아키텍처(CNCF)에 이르기까지 다양한 호스팅 모델은 비즈니스 앱을 개발, 배포 및 유지 관리하는 방식에 영향을 미쳤다. IT 서비스 업계에서 새로운 호스팅 모델을 발견할 때마다 팀은 아키텍처의 이점을 최대한 활용하는 데 어려움을 겪었다. 이로 인해 아키텍처 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to choose a static analysis tool]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0884/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0884/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tools to improve and control code quality can be a key success factor in a complex software project implementation. Static analyzers belong to such tools. Nowadays, you can find various static analyzers: from free open-source to cross-functional commercial solutions. On the one hand, it's great – you can choose from many options. On the other hand – you have to perform advanced research to find the right tool for your team. Before we talk about selection criteria, let's briefly discuss the methodology. Static analysis is an automated method to find errors in source code by means of specialized programs. The purpose of such analysis is to identify unsafe and problem parts of the project that can lead to more serious consequences – vulnerabilities. Keep in mind that users are not QA engineers. Bugs must not get into the release. That is why it's better to use a static analyzer regularly. Run the analyzer once – get lots of messages. Believe us, you don't want to sort them out. Moreover, to find and fix some errors you have to use more expensive methods at the following project stages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to choose a static analysis tool]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0884/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/Vv6z-LN8fhU/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tools to improve and control code quality can be a key success factor in a complex software project implementation. Static analyzers belong to such tools. Nowadays, you can find various static analyzers: from free open-source to cross-functional commercial solutions. On the one hand, it's great – you can choose from many options. On the other hand – you have to perform advanced research to find the right tool for your team. Before we talk about selection criteria, let's briefly discuss the methodology. Static analysis is an automated method to find errors in source code by means of specialized programs. The purpose of such analysis is to identify unsafe and problem parts of the project that can lead to more serious consequences – vulnerabilities. Keep in mind that users are not QA engineers. Bugs must not get into the release. That is why it's better to use a static analyzer regularly. Run the analyzer once – get lots of messages. Believe us, you don't want to sort them out. Moreover, to find and fix some errors you have to use more expensive methods at the following project stages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Concurrency in Julia]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875367/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875367/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T18:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Julia programming language has
its roots in high-performance scientific computing, so it is no surprise
that it has facilities for concurrent processing. Those features are not
well-known outside of the Julia community, though, so it is interesting to
see the different types of parallel and concurrent computation that the
language supports. In addition, the upcoming release of Julia
version 1.7 brings an improvement to the language's
concurrent-computation palette, 
in the form of "task 
migration".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875531/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875531/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T15:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (firefox, grafana, jenkins, opera, and thunderbird), Debian (botan1.10 and ckeditor), openSUSE (chromium, kernel, qemu, and rubygem-activerecord-5_1), SUSE (qemu and rubygem-activerecord-5_1), and Ubuntu (docker.io, kernel, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.11, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.11, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.11, linux-hwe-5.11, linux-kvm, linux-oem-5.13, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.11, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, and linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 논증적으로 생각하기]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222563292829</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222563292829"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 전제와 결론을 가진 논증으로 요약해 보라. 신탁은 내가 가장 현명하다고 이야기했습니다. 이 이야기를 들었을 때, 나는 신의 말은 무엇을 뜻하는가? 신의 수수께끼를 어떻게 해석할 것인가? 하고 자문해 보았습니다. 왜냐하면 나는 크든 작든 간에 지혜가 없다는 것을 알고 있기 때문입니다. 신이 내가 가장 현명한 사람이라고 말할 때 그는 무슨 말을 하려고 한 것일까? 그는 신이고, 따라서 거짓말을 할 수는 없는 일입니다. 거짓말을 한다는 것은 신에게는 어울리지 않는 일입니다. 오랫동안 숙고한 끝에 이 문제를 푸는 방법을 생각해 냈습니다. 만일 나 자신보다 더 현명한 사람을 찾아내기만 한다면 나는 신탁의 소리를 반박할 수 있을.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테크놀로지는 어떻게 미군을 변화시켰나]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82537</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82537"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T05:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[궁극의 군대]는 1945년 핵 혁명부터 2000년 무렵의 정보혁명까지 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계를 다룬 책이다. 저자인 토머스 G. 맨켄은 기술사를 다루는 정석적인 서술 방법을 취하는데, 기술’결정론’ 혹은 기술결정론의 무의미함을 논하기보다는 과학과 기술의 발전이라는 자체적인 동력과 그것을 수용하는 조직과 문화, 인식의 변화가 어떻게 함께 가는지를 설명한다. 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계  핵무기나 컴퓨터가 전장을 완전히 바꾸어놓았다는 서술이나, 핵무기나 컴퓨터의 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>임명묵</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테크놀로지는 어떻게 미군을 변화시켰나]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82537</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/QpvqTbuFw_8/82537"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T05:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[궁극의 군대]는 1945년 핵 혁명부터 2000년 무렵의 정보혁명까지 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계를 다룬 책이다. 저자인 토머스 G. 맨켄은 기술사를 다루는 정석적인 서술 방법을 취하는데, 기술’결정론’ 혹은 기술결정론의 무의미함을 논하기보다는 미 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계  핵무기나 컴퓨터가 전장을 완전히 바꾸어놓았다는 서술이나, 핵무기나 컴퓨터의 등장과 관계 없이 전장은 항상 똑같다는 반론보다 중요한 것은, 육해공군이라는 개별 조직이 그런 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>임명묵</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Memories of Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://jameshunt.us/?p=424</id>
        <link href="https://jameshunt.us/writings/early-memories-of-computers/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T18:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my earliest memory of computers starts on an airplane.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LXD 4.20 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875447/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875447/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LXD team has announced
the release of version 4.20 of the LXD system container and virtual
machine manager.

This is one very busy release with a lot of new features.

VM users will be happy to see the initial implementation of live migration and core scheduling support. Container users are getting new configuration keys to set sysctls.

Then the bulk of the new features are all network related with peer network relationships, network zones for auto-generated DNS and SR-IOV accelerated OVN networks.

And lastly, on the clustering front, it’s now possible to better control what servers will be receiving new workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Intel AMX support in 5.16]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874846/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874846/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The x86 instruction set is large, but that doesn't mean it can't get bigger
yet.  Upcoming Intel processors will feature a new set of instructions
under the name of "Advanced Matrix Extensions" (AMX) that can be used to
operate on matrix data.  After a somewhat bumpy development
process, support for AMX has found its way into the upcoming 5.16 kernel.
Using it will, naturally, require some changes by application developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy holidays! Here’s our 2021 gift guide!]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9252</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/happy-holidays-heres-our-2021-gift-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure that, for most people, 2021 isn’t going to be one of fond remembrances. For Kevin and I, it has been a year of reckoning, as people continue to lose trust in technology and the companies that sell consumer gadgets. Add to that the ongoing pandemic and the in-your-face reality of climate change, […]
The post Happy holidays! Here’s our 2021 gift guide! appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875420/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875420/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T13:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (containerd, redis, and sqlalchemy), Fedora (kernel, radeontop, rpki-client, and webkit2gtk3), openSUSE (java-1_8_0-openj9, libvirt, mailman, transfig, and webkit2gtk3), Oracle (thunderbird), SUSE (libvirt), and Ubuntu (icu).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글쓰기 십계명: 명확한 글쓰기 10가지 원칙]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82517</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82517"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T07:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제1원칙 이야기 속 행위자를 짧고 구체적인 명사에 담아 문장의 주어로 삼아라. 살아 움직이는 생명체가 주어가 되면 더 좋다. “행위자가 없으면 아무것도 없는 것이다.” (무명)    제2원칙 행위자의 주요 행동을 묘사하는 구체적인 동사를 서술어로 삼아라. 우리는 ‘누가 무엇을 한다’는 스토리텔링을 가장 잘 이해한다. “나는 생각한다. 고로 존재한다.” (데카르트)   제3원칙 주어와 동사를 최대한 문장 앞부분에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글쓰기 십계명: 명확한 글쓰기 10가지 원칙]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82517</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/72cjtKQBXd4/82517"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T07:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제1원칙 이야기 속 행위자를 짧고 구체적인 명사에 담아 문장의 주어로 삼아라. 살아 움직이는 생명체가 주어가 되면 더 좋다. “행위자가 없으면 아무것도 없는 것이다.” (무명)    제2원칙 행위자의 주요 행동을 묘사하는 구체적인 동사를 서술어로 삼아라. 우리는 ‘누가 무엇을 한다’는 스토리텔링을 가장 잘 이해한다. “나는 생각한다. 고로 존재한다.” (데카르트)   제3원칙 주어와 동사를 최대한 문장 앞부분에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 More Ways to Refactor new/delete into unique ptr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/more-refactor-into-uniqueptr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/more-refactor-into-uniqueptr/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our refactoring series, we covered (smart) pointers inside a function body; today, I’d like to show you cases for return types, data members, and a few others.
Let’s jump in and replace some new() and delete!
See the first part
This article is the second in the series about refactoring with unique_ptr. You can read the first part here:
6 Ways to Refactor new/delete into unique ptr - C++ Stories
Basic assumptions
The code presented here will usually contain explicit new and delete, and we’d like to reduce their use and wrap resources (pointers) into RAII.
We’ll try to follow the rule: R.11: Avoid calling new and delete explicitly from the Core C++ Guidelines:
The pointer returned by new should belong to a resource handle (that can call delete). If the pointer returned b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1ebb97d9e53b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/october-2021-1ebb97d9e53b?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T03:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[September 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/63d16d437db5</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/september-2021-63d16d437db5?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T03:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Culturally transmitted skills and values]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/culture/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/culture/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three major tools that companies have to influence behavior are incentives, process, and culture. People often mean different things when talking about these, so I'll provide an example of each so we're on the same page (if you think that I should be using a different word for the concept, feel free to mentally substitute that word).
Getting people to show up to meetings on time
Incentive: dock pay for people who are late
Process: don't allow anyone who's late into the meeting
Culture: people feel strongly about showing up on time



Getting people to build complex systems
Incentive: require complexity in promo criteria
Process: make process for creating or executing on a work item so heavyweight that people stop doing simple work
Culture: people enjoy building complex systems and/or build…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undefined behavior, carried through the years]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0883/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0883/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine: something in code goes wrong, you start searching for a bug and then it turns out that there was another bug behind this. Have you ever been in this situation? Searching for bugs is cool. It's almost like you're Sherlock Holmes and it's a detective story. Something from an extensive list of seemingly harmless classes and functions causes a program's unexpected and undefined behavior. And you, with your sharp eyes and experiments, are trying to find the "criminal".  We published and translated this article with the copyright holder's permission. The author is Eugene Zakharov (fnc12@me.com). The article was originally published on Habr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undefined behavior, carried through the years]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0883/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/ilNokXp9iio/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine: something in code goes wrong, you start searching for a bug and then it turns out that there was another bug behind this. Have you ever been in this situation? Searching for bugs is cool. It's almost like you're Sherlock Holmes and it's a detective story. Something from an extensive list of seemingly harmless classes and functions causes a program's unexpected and undefined behavior. And you, with your sharp eyes and experiments, are trying to find the "criminal".  We published and translated this article with the copyright holder's permission. The author is Eugene Zakharov (fnc12@me.com). The article was originally published on Habr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s in my smart home: November 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9182</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/whats-in-my-smart-home-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This story was published in the newsletter on October 22, but never made it to the site. So we updated the headline and published it here two weeks later. Slightly more than a year ago, I shared what was in my smart home. I started out by saying, “Wow, what a difference three years […]
The post What’s in my smart home: November 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding RGBW Wings and Enclosure to a Debug Probe]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33750</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/11/07/adding-rgbw-wings-and-enclosure-to-a-debug-probe/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T12:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m using debug probes on a daily base. They have to be functional, and I value functionality over aesthetics. For cost reasons many debug probe vendors either only provide a bare PCB without enclosure, or the enclosure is made of … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>