<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-17T03:55:15.342Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Insteon is down and may not be coming back]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10128</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/insteon-is-down-and-may-not-be-coming-back/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T16:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your Insteon smart home system down? I’m getting reports from dozens of Insteon users that as of Friday their smart home hubs have stopped working. So far, none of them have heard from the company, and Insteon’s Twitter account hasn’t been updated since June 2021. I reached out to Rob Lilleness, the president and […]
The post Insteon is down and may not be coming back appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU coreutils 9.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891574/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891574/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T14:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 9.1 of the GNU coreutils package has been released with lots of
small tweaks and improvements.  "ls no longer colors files with
capabilities by default, as file-based capabilities are very rarely used,
and lookup increases processing per file by about 30%.  It's best to use
getcap [-r] to identify files with capabilities."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are good wireless Z-Wave switch or button options?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10115</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/what-are-good-wireless-z-wave-switch-or-button-options/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, we chose an email listener question instead of a voicemail from our IoT Podcast Hotline. This week, Matt wrote in with a fairly specific question but it can be applied to any number of smart homes. Matt’s current setup is built with a “combination of SmartThings, several Echo devices, […]
The post What are good wireless Z-Wave switch or button options? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[<지각의 현상학> 서문 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222702490648</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222702490648"/>
        <updated>2022-04-16T07:06:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[현상학은 일차적 경험이나 체험을 기술 혹은 서술하는 것이다. 기술하고 서술하는 것은 설명하거나 분석하는 것과 다르다. 따라서 설명하고자 하는 과학과 현상학 혹은 철학은 다르다. 과학은 현상학에 비해 이차적이다. 혹은 과학적 도식화는 추상적이고 파생적인 기호언어에 지나지 않는다. 왜냐하면 과학이 탐구하는 세계에 대한 이론적 근거는 현상학이나 철학이 서술하는 세계에 대한 일차적, 근본적 경험에 의존하고 있기 때문이다. 과학은 이차적이다. 따라서 나는 과학에서 이야기하는 그런 존재가 아니다. 즉 나는 과학에서 이야기하는 생물이 아니다. 나는 과학에서 이야기하는 그런 특성을 지닌 인간이나 의식이 아니다. 나는 더 근본.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for April 15, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10125</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-april-15-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T19:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Diligent Robotics raises $30M: Diligent Robotics, a company in Austin, Texas that is building the Moxi robot designed for hospitals, has raised more than $30 million in funding. I’ve loved this company and its robot for years, ever since I took a group of fifth graders to the UT Engineering school and ran into a Moxi demo. However, […]
The post IoT news of the week for April 15, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Communities: Q1 ‘22 highlights and achievements]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/MLCommunities2022Q1.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/MLCommunities2022Q1.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T17:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nari Yoon, Hee Jung, DevRel Community Manager / Soonson Kwon, DevRel Program Manager


 Let’s explore highlights and accomplishments of vast Google Machine Learning communities over the first quarter of the year! We are enthusiastic and grateful about all the activities that the communities across the globe do. Here are the highlights! 
ML Ecosystem Campaign Highlights
 
   
ML Olympiad is an associated Kaggle Community Competitions hosted by Machine Learning Google Developers Experts (ML GDEs) or TensorFlow User Groups (TFUGs) sponsored by Google. The first round was hosted from January to March, suggesting solving critical problems of our time. Competition highlights include Autism Prediction Challenge, Arabic_Poems, Hausa Sentiment Analysis, Quality Education, Good Health and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] KOReader: a free electronic-book reader for e-ink devices]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889171/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889171/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T15:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your editor has a certain tendency to accumulate books, to the point that
they crowd everything else out of the house.  There is a lot to be said for
books: a physical book has a
user interface that has been optimized over centuries, and one can have a
reasonably high degree of certainty that any given book will still work a
few decades from now.  Neither of those can be said for electronic books,
but they do have the advantages of taking less shelf space and being more
portable.  So electronic books are part of the reading menu, which
naturally leads to the search for a free reader for those books; KOReader turns out to be an interesting
alternative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.4.189 and 4.19.238]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891460/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891460/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 5.4.189 and 4.19.238 stable kernels.  As usual, they
contain important fixes throughout the tree and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891453/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891453/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T12:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (fribidi and python-django), Fedora (postgresql-jdbc, stargz-snapshotter, and thunderbird), Slackware (git, gzip, and xz), and SUSE (kernel, SDL2, and tomcat).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이성과 윤리]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222701718484</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222701718484"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T07:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(A) 만약 윤리적으로 행위하는 것이라면, 그것이 보편화 가능해야 한다. 그런데 합리적인 것은 보편적으로 타당하다. 따라서 합리적인 것은 윤리적으로 행위하는 것이다. 이 논증은 형식적으로 부당하다. 매개념이 모두 부주연되어 있다. 따라서 다음처럼 고쳐야 한다. (B) 만약 보편화 가능하다면, 그것은 윤리적으로 행위하는 것이다. 그런데 합리적인 것은 보편적으로 타당하다. 따라서 합리적인 것은 윤리적으로 행위하는 것이다. 그런데 이렇게 고친 논증은 싱어가 의도하는 논증이 아니다. 윤리의 필요조건이 보편화 가능성이다. 그런데 (B)에서 보편화 가능성이 충분조건으로 되어 있다. 따라서 싱어가 의도하는 것이 바로 (A)이다. 분명.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사업 목표는 매출과 고객? 결국, 시스템과 확률!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85268</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85268"/>
        <updated>2022-04-15T06:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[일반인이 생각하는 마케팅에 관한 기본 개념은 ‘광고로 매출 올리기’입니다. 이 생각은 마케팅 모델 중, 퍼널 모델(funnel model)에서 나온 개념입니다. 퍼널 모델은 광고로 고객을 모으고, 모은 고객들을 대상으로 상품을 팔아서 매출을 올린다는 생각을 기반으로 하고 있습니다. 지금까지 대다수 마케팅 이론은 퍼널 모델 중심으로 정리되어 있습니다. 전통적인 대기업들은 대부분 이 모델을 기반으로 사업을 하고 있습니다. 이 […]
The post 사업 목표는 매출과 고객? 결국, 시스템과 확률! first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이상훈</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] ‘청부과학’의 진화: 의구심 뿌리기]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73876</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/14/npc_triumphofdoubt/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_triumphofdoubt"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T22:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[앞서 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 ‘왜 미국 사람 중에는 백신 회의론자나 백신을 안 맞으려는 사람이 많을까?’에 관한 글을 몇 편 썼습니다. 그러다 지난주 경제 지표와 체감 경기의 차이에 관한 글을 소개하면서 미국의 코로나19 백신 접종률을 찾아봤는데, 여전히 접종을 완료한 사람이 국민의 60%에 미치지 못했습니다. (백신을 맞을 수 있는 만 5세 이상 인구 중에는 64%.) 미국에는 여전히 코로나19 백신이 남아돕니다. 오미크론 변이가 본격적으로 퍼질 텐데, 아직도 최소 6천만 명 넘는 백신 회의론자들은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trojan Source: Invisible Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0935/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0935/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We present a new type of attack in which source code is maliciously encoded so that it appears different to a compiler and to the human eye. This attack exploits subtleties in text-encoding standards such as Unicode to produce source code whose tokens are logically encoded in a different order from the one in which they are displayed, leading to vulnerabilities that cannot be perceived directly by human code reviewers. 'Trojan Source' attacks, as we call them, pose an immediate threat both to first-party software and of supply-chain compromise across the industry. We present working examples of Trojan-Source attacks in C, C++, C#, JavaScript, Java, Rust, Go, and Python. We propose definitive compiler-level defenses, and describe other mitigating controls that can be deployed in editors, repositories, and build pipelines while compilers are upgraded to block this attack.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Embedded Systems at Scale with Device Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=20768</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2022/04/14/building-embedded-systems-at-scale-with-device-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T18:48:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[14 April 2022 by Phillip JohnstonEmbedded Artistry and Memfault are joining forces to host a quarterly embedded discussion panel that is focused on the technical aspects of building embedded systems at scale. We will be featuring guest panel members who are at the cutting edge of embedded development. Our goal is to spread beneficial techniques … 
Continue reading "Building Embedded Systems at Scale with Device Metrics"
The post Building Embedded Systems at Scale with Device Metrics appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rustaceans at the border]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889924/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889924/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T18:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for developing in the Rust
language is headed toward the kernel, though just when it
will land in the mainline is yet to be determined.  The Rust patches are
progressing, though, and beginning to attract attention from beyond the
kernel community.  When two languages — and two different development
communities — come together, the result can be a sort of cultural clash.
Some early signs of that are appearing with regard to Rust in the kernel;
if the resulting impedance mismatches can be worked out, the result could
be a better development environment for everybody involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-band LoRa transceiver features S-band for global asset tracking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474354</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/multi-band-lora-transceiver-features-s-band-for-global-asset-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new LR1120 targets global geolocation applications, providing multi band LoRa and LR-FHSS communication over sub-GHz and 2.4GHz ISM bands as well as licensed S-Band for satellites.
The post Multi-band LoRa transceiver features S-band for global asset tracking appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started is the hardest part: Find inspiration with Apps Script samples]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/getting-started-is-hardest-part-find.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/getting-started-is-hardest-part-find.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kara Ireland, Technical Writer & Charles Maxson, Developer Advocate
 

Google Apps Script is a hosted JavaScript development environment that makes it easy for anyone to build custom business solutions across several Google products.  Figuring out where to begin can be a hurdle for such an expansive tool, so we've recently released 10 new inspirational sample solutions to help you get started. These additions bolster the Apps Script documentation, which now hosts more than 30 sample solutions. 
Apps Script welcomes developers of all skill levels, from beginners to professionals. We’re consistently impressed with the creative and innovative ways developers have automated business processes with Apps Script–from published add-ons that help millions of users to simple automations th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존 앤디 재시의 2021년 첫 연례 주주서한 (번역)]]></title>
        <id>http://ebadak.news/?p=3437</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2022/04/15/andy-jassy-letter-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T16:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[반복적인 혁신, 이것은 아마존의 모든 팀에 널리 전파되어 있습니다. 광고, 신선식품, 게임, 음악, 헬스케어, 의약 모두에서 이런 혁신의 예를 찾아볼 수 있습니다. 우리의 이야기는 여전히 현재 진행형입니다. 우리가 빠르게 실험하고, 학습하고, 우리의 고객 경험을 좋게 하기 위해 매일같이 노력하기 때문입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2021-1782, an iOS in-the-wild vulnerability in vouchers]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/04/cve-2021-1782-ios-in-wild-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/04/cve-2021-1782-ios-in-wild-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw');ol{margin:0;padding:0}table td,table th{padding:0}.BGLtzooHlW-c13{border-right-style:solid;padding:5pt 5pt 5pt 5pt;border-bottom-color:#e0e0e0;border-top-width:1pt;border-right-width:1pt;border-left-color:#e0e0e0;vertical-align:top;border-right-color:#e0e0e0;border-left-width:1pt;border-top-style:solid;background-color:#fafafa;border-left-style:solid;border-bottom-width:1pt;width:468pt;border-top-color:#e0e0e0;border-bottom-style:solid}.BGLtzooHlW-c3{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:10pt;font-family:Consolas,"Courier New";font-style:normal}.BGLtzooHlW-c10{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:11pt;font-fa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renesas launches virtual development environment for automotive software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474348</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/renesas-launches-virtual-development-environment-for-automotive-software/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T13:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual turnkey platform allows engineers to develop application software before devices or evaluation boards are available, and multicore debug and trace tool lets users analyze and evaluate software as if it were running on an actual chip.
The post Renesas launches virtual development environment for automotive software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: What do you want in a home robot?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10111</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-what-do-you-want-in-a-home-robot/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this week’s show we question whether or not we want Amazon’s Astro home robot after seeing a few reviews. We then note that Google has introduced gaze as signal to wake up Google Assistant, which is one of the first uses of gaze as a wake-up indicator for the smart home. Then we talk […]
The post Podcast: What do you want in a home robot? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Marketplace 100: 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5354</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/marketplace-100/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 marks our third year releasing the Marketplace 100, a ranking of the largest consumer-facing marketplace startups and private companies.  When we started this series in early 2020 (based on data from 2019), we had no way of knowing how volatile the next few years would be. Many businesses were temporarily shuttered by covid, especially... Read More
The post The Marketplace 100: 2022 appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Olivia Moore and Brandon Barros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891354/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891354/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T12:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (lrzip), Fedora (community-mysql, expat, firefox, kernel, mingw-openjpeg2, nss, and openjpeg2), Mageia (ceph, subversion, and webkit2), openSUSE (chromium), Oracle (httpd:2.4), Red Hat (kpatch-patch), Slackware (ruby), SUSE (kernel and netatalk), and Ubuntu (gzip and xz-utils).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: Bosch acquires Five, Sony’s sports tech ambition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474337</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-bosch-acquires-five-sonys-sports-tech-ambition/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T12:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest news from the embedded world.
The post embedded news: Bosch acquires Five, Sony’s sports tech ambition appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[채널A 검언유착 의혹 사건: 수사 실패인가, 유착 조작인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85259</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85259"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T10:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[채널A 검언유착 의혹 사건으로 알려진 ‘취재원 강요 미수’ 사건에 대해 검찰이 한동훈 사법연수원 부원장(검사장)을 불기소 처분했습니다. 검찰은 4월 6일 ‘증거 불충분하여 혐의 없다’고 판단했다며, 핵심 증거인 한 검사장 휴대전화 비밀번호를 푸는 데 실패했다고 밝혔습니다. “현재 기술력으로는 잠금해제 시도가 더 이상 실효성이 없다고 판단했다”는 게 이유입니다. 수사팀은 2020년 12월부터 무혐의 결재를 올렸으나 서울중앙지검은 ‘한 검사장의 휴대전화 […]
The post 채널A 검언유착 의혹 사건: 수사 실패인가, 유착 조작인가 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A hint on the future direction of SUSE Linux Enterprise]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891315/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891315/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T10:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE has begun to
discuss its plans for the next version of SUSE Linux Enterprise on the
openSUSE lists.  It appears that there will be some significant changes.


	Intending to do radical changes (regarding technology-
	but also design-wise) we choose "Adaptable Linux Platform" or short
	"ALP" as codename for that next generation. This indicates already
	that some things will be quite different than a "mere "SLE 15++
	would be ;) [...]
	
	Another important point is that we intend to split what was a more
	generic, everything is closely intertwined into two parts: One
	smaller hardware enabling piece, a kind of "host OS", and the and
	the layer providing and supporting applications, which will be
	container (and VM) based.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESP USB Bridge]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/47ce9564807f</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/esp-usb-bridge-47ce9564807f?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T09:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ESP USB Bridge is an ESP-IDF project utilizing an ESP32-S2 (or optionally, an ESP32-S3) chip to create a bridge between a computer and…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Roland Dobai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Quarkus applications with Apache Cassandra: Workshop recap]]></title>
        <id>37d49695-28fb-437e-b0a4-043a649a72c8</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/14/building-quarkus-applications-apache-cassandra-workshop-recap"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you miss the free hands-on workshop Building Quarkus applications with Apache Cassandra, hosted by Red Hat's Eric Deandrea and Raghavan "Rags" Srinivas from DataStax, a Red Hat partner? This two-hour workshop showcases all the Developer Joy benefits of Quarkus, such as developer mode, debugging, containerization, and no-hassle native executable generation, coupled with an Apache Cassandra backend hosted in the cloud using DataStax Astra DB's multicloud database-as-a-service.
In the workshop, Rags explains some differences between relational and NoSQL databases. He introduces Apache Cassandra and the benefits it brings, explaining how Cassandra's configurable consistency level makes it highly scalable and reliable. He also introduces DataStax Astra Cassandra-as-a-service and explains so…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Deandrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate Helm charts for your Java application using JKube, Part 1]]></title>
        <id>d5df0b74-748e-4ed5-a419-222174683e62</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/14/generate-helm-charts-your-java-application-using-jkube-part-1"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tools provided with Kubernetes continually make it easier for Java developers to build applications, store them in registries, and deploy images. This article looks at Helm charts, the fundamental tool for building applications on Kubernetes and the Red Hat OpenShift cloud service, together with Eclipse JKube, which is available as a Kubernetes Maven or Gradle plugin.
The article demonstrates how combining Helm with JKube simplifies Kubernetes manifest management for Java projects. You'll learn how JKube makes it possible for Java developers to automatically generate and publish Helm charts (Figure 1).

  


          


Overview of Helm and JKube
Kubernetes has been here for a while now, and more and more organizations are showing interest in the platform. Java developers are becoming inc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rohan Kumar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[리빙스턴의 후기 비트겐슈타인]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222700495171</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222700495171"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T03:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin M. Cahill와 Thomas Raleigh는 리빙스턴을 후기 비트겐슈타인의 자연주의를 주장하는 학자로서 언급하고 있지만, 그런데 과연 리빙스턴이 후기 비트겐슈타인의 자연주의를 주장하는지 그렇게 분명하지 않다. 흥미롭게 리빙스턴은 플라톤과 후기 비트겐슈타인의 유사성을 주장한다. 플라톤의 대화록 <크라튈로스>에 나타난 이름과 사물의 관계에 대한 규약주의와 자연주의적 주장에 대해서 플라톤은 우리 언어 사용의 형식 혹은 형상을 강조하는 제3의 주장을 하고 있다고 리빙스턴은 논증한다. 플라톤의 이러한 입장이 바로 규칙 따르기에서 후기 비트겐슈타인이 보여주고 있는 입장과 유사하다는 것이 리빙스턴의 주장이다. 적어도.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for April 14, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/890577/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/890577/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T00:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for April 14, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in March (+ Announcements)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/march-2022-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/march-2022-roundup"/>
        <updated>2022-04-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
March, and we have a few announcements, the first being about Interrupt’s first Quarterly Panel co-hosted with Phillip from Embedded Artistry, and a blurb about this year’s Embedded Online Conference
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 호전적인 우리 뇌와 인간의 약점]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73865</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/13/npc_brainatwar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_brainatwar"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T22:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[브랜다이스 대학의 석좌교수인 마리 피츠더프의 새 책 “전쟁하는 뇌(Our Brains at War)”는 인간의 본성인 자기 집단을 위한 이기심이 상상 이상으로 매우 강력하다는 사실을 여러 최신 연구 결과를 가지고 이야기하는 책입니다. 피츠더프 교수는 이를 바탕으로 국민이 자신들을 대표할 정치인을 고르는 방법과 또 국가 간의 전쟁이 시작되는 방식을 바꾸어야 한다고 주장합니다. 여기서 인간의 본성이란, 인간의 생리적, 유전적 특징들이 다른 집단에 대한 반감을 매우 쉽게 가지도록 만들어져 있다는 것입니다. 이런 우리의 본성은 우리가 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A literal string type for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891082/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891082/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T21:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using strings with contents that are supplied by users can be fraught with
peril; SQL injection is a well-known technique for attacking applications
that stems from that, for example.  Generally, database frameworks and
libraries provide mechanisms that seek to lead programmers toward doing The
Right Thing, with parameterized queries and the like, but they cannot
enforce that—inventive developers will seemingly always find ways to inject
user input into places it should not go.  A recently adopted Python
Enhancement Proposal (PEP) provides a way to enforce the use of 
strings that are untainted by user input, but it uses the optional typing features
of the language to do so; those wanting to take advantage of it will need
to be running a type-checking program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A set of stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891248/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891248/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T20:11:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.17.3,
5.16.20,
5.15.34, and
5.10.111 stable kernel updates have been
released after a relatively quick review cycle.  Each contains a relatively
large set of important fixes.  Note that 5.16.20 is the final update in the
5.16.x series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing the Apps Script connector for AppSheet: Automate workflows for Google Workspace]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/apps-script-connector-for-appsheet.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/apps-script-connector-for-appsheet.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T17:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mike Procopio, Senior Staff Software Engineer 
 
 
This week, we launched the Apps Script connector for AppSheet, which now makes it possible to call Apps Script code functions from a no-code AppSheet app. This greatly extends the abilities of AppSheet apps by letting them access the power that Apps Script provides. For example, an AppSheet app can now use Apps Script to automate workflows with Google Workspace using the Workspace APIs for Drive, Docs, Sheets, and Admin SDK, and more – as well as other Google services like YouTube, Google Analytics, and BigQuery. 
Google AppSheet
  
AppSheet is Google’s platform for building no-code custom apps and workflows to automate business processes. It lets app creators build and deploy end-to-end apps and automations without writing code.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home Assistant’s newest release is big and awesome]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10091</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/home-assistants-newest-release-is-big-and-awesome/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T15:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although I’ve gone all-in on HomeKit for personal use, there are still other great smart home options out there. And one of them is Home Assistant, which often gets lost in the connected platform shuffle. If you’re not familiar with it, Home Assistant is an open-source smart home system you self-host on a small computer, […]
The post Home Assistant’s newest release is big and awesome appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcom launches Wi-Fi 7 chips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474319</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/broadcom-launches-wi-fi-7-chips/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T14:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcom’s new family of Wi-Fi 7 chips for enable will help implement the speed, latency and determinism, and features like multi-link operation offered by the new Wi-Fi standard.
The post Broadcom launches Wi-Fi 7 chips appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891182/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891182/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T13:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (gzip, python-django, and xz), Debian (chromium, subversion, and zabbix), Red Hat (expat, kernel, and thunderbird), SUSE (go1.16, go1.17, kernel, libexif, libsolv, libzypp, zypper, opensc, subversion, thunderbird, and xz), and Ubuntu (git, linux-bluefield, nginx, and subversion).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eval kit for Sony sensor featuring Prophesee event-based vision tech]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474311</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/eval-kit-for-sony-sensor-featuring-prophesee-event-based-vision-tech/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T11:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Evaluation kit provides computer vision engineers with a tested solution for efficient technology onboarding and rapid application prototyping and development.
The post Eval kit for Sony sensor featuring Prophesee event-based vision tech appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘극단적 선택’, 어떻게 보도해야 할까: ‘검사 사망’ 보도를 비판함]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85252</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85252"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T08:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4월 12일 서울남부지검에서 초임 검사 A 씨가 숨졌습니다. 검찰은 사망 경위 파악 등을 위한 진상조사에 착수했습니다. 현재까지 사망 원인은 극단적 선택으로 추정되고 있는데요. 언론은 이번에도 해당 소식을 전하며 스스로 마련한 자살보도 윤리강령을 지키지 않았습니다. 사건 당일 하루에만 자살보도 윤리강령을 어긴 100개에 이르는 기사들이 포털사이트 메인을 장식했습니다. 64개 언론사, 96개 기사에서 자살보도 윤리강령 위반  민주언론시민연합은 포털사이트 […]
The post ‘극단적 선택’, 어떻게 보도해야 할까: ‘검사 사망’ 보도를 비판함 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qt 6.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891121/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891121/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T07:45:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.3 of the Qt
graphics library has been released.  "Qt 6.3 also comes with a decent
set of new functionality. A total of 250 user stories and tasks
implementing new functionality have been completed for 6.3. Those are of
course too many to list individually, and if you want to have all the
details, have a look at our new
features page and our Release Notes."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[러시아의 우크라이나 침공 보도 비판: 인류애와 저널리즘]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85242</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85242"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T07:38:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 2월 24일 새벽 러시아가 우크라이나 영토를 침공하면서 전쟁이 시작됐다. 러시아가 우크라이나 동부 돈바스 지역에 군대를 주둔하면서 전쟁을 준비하고 있다는 미국 정부의 공식 발표 직후 상황은 어떠했던가. 나이와 성별, 직업에 상관없이 국가를 지키기 위해 국경 지역 민간인들도 나서서 무장하고 싸우는 법을 익혔고, 갑자기 시작된 전쟁은 전 세계 언론에 생중계됐다. 끝내 전쟁 일으킨 러시아, 평화 빼앗긴 […]
The post 러시아의 우크라이나 침공 보도 비판: 인류애와 저널리즘 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy a Java application on Red Hat OpenShift using JKube]]></title>
        <id>c37a4486-42a3-4a88-8237-f5fc1cf8248e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/13/deploy-java-application-red-hat-openshift-using-jkube"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Java applications don't run in a vacuum, but interact with other components such as databases, load balancers, monitoring, and so forth. Eclipse JKube makes it easier to build Java applications and connect them with the resources they need when running as containers under Kubernetes. This article builds on a previous article, Build a bootable JAR for cloud-ready microservices, and shows some advanced uses of JKube. We'll build and deploy a bootable JAR using Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application Platform (JBoss EAP) and Jakarta EE, and incorporate a PostgreSQL database and MicroProfile capabilities.
How JKube helps build and deploy Java applications
The previous article in this series listed all the commands needed to create the application's resources (buildConfig, deployment, s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mauro Vocale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage namespaces in multitenant clusters with Argo CD, Kustomize, and Helm]]></title>
        <id>b6f7bcb3-322c-4f97-a993-ee3073d528a3</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/13/manage-namespaces-multitenant-clusters-argo-cd-kustomize-and-helm"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cluster administrators on Kubernetes need to create namespaces for multiple developer teams and limit their use of resources by provisioning those namespaces with resource quotas and limit ranges. In this article, you'll learn how to automate these tasks with Argo CD, and how to use either Kustomize or Helm charts to simplify the process. The result implements the fundamentals of DevOps and GitOps, whereby any changes to the repository update the deployed resources.
There are two types of configuration that administrators have to deal with are:
Resource quota: A Kubernetes object that controls the amount of CPU or memory consumed by a namespace. This quota can also limit the number of resources that can be created in a namespace.
Limit range: This is used in Kubernetes along with resource …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saumeya Katyal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git security fixes released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891112/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891112/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T03:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git maintainer Junio C Hamano has 
announced the
release of v2.35.2, along with  multiple other Git versions
("v2.30.3, v2.31.2, v2.32.1, v2.33.2, and 
v2.34.2"), to fix a security problem that can happen on multi-user
machines (CVE-2022-24765).
This GitHub blog
post has more details, though the GitHub service itself is not
vulnerable.  The description in the announcement seems a bit
Windows-centric, but Linux multi-user systems are apparently vulnerable as well:

   On multi-user machines, Git users might find themselves
   unexpectedly in a Git worktree, e.g. when another user created a
   repository in `C:\.git`, in a mounted network drive or in a
   scratch space. Merely having a Git-aware prompt that runs `git
   status` (or `git diff`) and navigating to a directory which is
   supposedly not a Git worktree, or opening such a directory in an
   editor or IDE such as VS Code or Atom, will potentially run
   commands defined by that other user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[본질과 가족 유사성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222699369228</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222699369228"/>
        <updated>2022-04-13T01:15:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글에서 소개된 이리가라이의 주장을 평가해 보라. (이리가라이, 이리가레이, 이리가레 등으로 다양하게 지칭되는) Luce Irigaray는 플라톤의 <국가>에 나오는 동굴 신화를 정신분석학적으로 독해한다. 동굴 안에서 일렁이는 불빛에 의해 벽에 얼룩진 그림자 밖에는 볼 수 없기 때문에, 태양에 비친 진정한 사물의 모습을 보기 원한다면 철학자는 동굴에서 빠져 나와 위쪽 바깥 세계로 올라가야 한다. 전통적으로 로고스 중심주의에 따라서 이 신화는 다음과 같이 이해되었다. 동굴을 빠져 나와 태양을 향하는 오르막길 여행은 참된 철학자가 되기를 원한다면, 누구나 반드시 밟아야 하는 과정을 의미한다. 사물을 단순히 미혹된 현.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 데이터와 체감 경기의 동상이몽 경제]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73852</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/12/economyfeeling/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=economyfeeling"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뉴스에서는 경기가 살아나고 있다는데, 내 주머니 사정은 여전히 팍팍하게 느껴진 적 많으실 겁니다. (반대로 여러 지표에서 적신호가 켜졌다는 뉴스가 쏟아지는 와중에도 나는 운이 좋아서 사정이 괜찮을 수도 있겠죠.) 이런 일이 코로나19 팬데믹을 거치면서도 여러 차례 나타났습니다. 오늘은 지난해 12월 1일에 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 쓴 글을 소개합니다. 여러 경제 지표를 보면 미국 경제는 코로나19 팬데믹과 함께 왔던 최악의 침체기를 완전히 벗어난 것처럼 보입니다. 그런데 미국인들은 전혀 이를 느끼지 못하는 것 같습니다. 미국인들이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.18: updates and enhancements]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0934/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0934/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the latest PVS-Studio release — 7.18. This article will tell you about how we improved the analysis of modern C++, the search of security defects from the OWASP Top 10 list, and a new feature for embedded developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] trusted_for() bounces off the merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/890957/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/890957/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T20:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When last we looked in on the proposed
trusted_for() system call, which would allow user-space interpreters
and other tools to ask the kernel whether a file is "trusted" for execution, it
looked like it was on-track for the mainline.  That was back in
October 2020; the patch has been updated multiple times since then,
made its way into linux-next, and a pull
request was made by Mickaël Salaün for the 5.18 merge window.  But
it seems that there will be more to the story of getting this functionality
into the kernel, as Linus Torvalds declined to pull trusted_for(),
at least partly because he did not like the name, but there were other
reasons as well.  While he is not opposed
to the functionality it would provide, he also had strong feelings that a
new system call
was not the right approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Septentrio adds OSNMA anti-spoofing security to GNSS receivers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474304</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/septentrio-adds-osnma-anti-spoofing-security-to-gnss-receivers/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T16:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Falsification of GNSS signals can seriously impact any application relying on precise navigation and timing synchronization. OSNMA contributes to increasing the resilience of civil GNSS signals against such possible threats.
The post Septentrio adds OSNMA anti-spoofing security to GNSS receivers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shopping for smart locks is a mess, but here’s what I bought]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10074</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/shopping-for-smart-locks-is-a-mess-but-heres-what-i-bought/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T15:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last month, the Kwikset smart lock that came installed in the back door of my house when we moved in two years ago broke. I wasn’t in love with the lock, but I was even less happy with the timing of it breaking. I would have preferred to wait for Matter to come out before […]
The post Shopping for smart locks is a mess, but here’s what I bought appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thundercomm SOMs enhance food delivery robots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474299</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/thundercomm-soms-enhance-food-delivery-robots/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T14:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System on module products based on Qualcomm Snapdragon processors enable intelligent food delivery robots.
The post Thundercomm SOMs enhance food delivery robots appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Drive Business Growth By Fostering Your Community]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5202</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/drive-business-growth-by-fostering-community-gtc/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone’s familiar with the concept of a go-to-market (GTM) plan, but in the world of bottom-up adoption and product-led growth, a go-to-community (GTC) plan is equally as important.  As the name suggests, go-to-community is the process of operationalizing and optimizing your community-building efforts to align them with business outcomes. Growing a healthy community can create... Read More
The post How to Drive Business Growth By Fostering Your Community appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Woods</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malcolm: The state of static analysis in the GCC 12 compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891062/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891062/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T13:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Malcolm has posted an
update on the state of static analysis in GCC 12.


	Some other languages, such as Perl, can track input and flag any
	variable that should not be trusted because it was read from an
	outside source such as a web form. Flagging variables in this
	manner is called tainting. After a program runs the variable
	through a check, the variable can be untainted, a process called
	sanitization.

	Our GCC analyzer's taint mode is activated by
	-fanalyzer-checker=taint (which should be specified in
	addition to -fanalyzer). Taint mode attempts to track
	attacker-controlled values entering the program and to warn if they
	are used without sanitization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 4.9.310]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/891052/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/891052/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T10:10:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 4.9.310 stable kernel update has been
released; the changes consist mostly of backported Spectre mitigation patches.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1층이 있는 삶: GS25 차별 시정 판결의 의미]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85226</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85226"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T08:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘1층이 있는 삶’이란, 휠체어를 이용하는 장애인이 모든 장소를 1층처럼 접근할 수 있도록 하기 위한 활동에서 비롯된 말이다. 즉, 1층에 대한 접근성을 넘어 본질적으로 제품, 시설, 서비스를 설계할 때 이용하는 사람이 성별, 나이, 장애, 언어 등으로 인해 불편하지 않도록 하는 모두를 위한 디자인, ‘유니버설 디자인’과 일맥상통하는 의미라고 할 수 있다. 우리나라는 1997년 장애인등편의보장법을 제정하여 장애인 등이 […]
The post 1층이 있는 삶: GS25 차별 시정 판결의 의미 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The state of static analysis in the GCC 12 compiler]]></title>
        <id>d6c1ecb7-29cf-4660-ae1b-6e3273b83bbe</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/12/state-static-analysis-gcc-12-compiler"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building a static analyzer into the C compiler offers several advantages over having a separate tool, because the analyzer can track what the compiler and assembler are doing intimately. As a Red Hat employee, I work on GCC, the GNU Compiler Collection. Our static analyzer is still experimental but is making big strides in interesting areas, including a taint mode and an understanding of assembly-language code.

 

 
 

 
My work on adding static analysis has spanned the past three releases of GCC (versions 10, 11, and 12). The static analysis is enabled through the -fanalyzer option, and works together with several other options. This article describes what we've accomplished on static analysis in the upcoming major release of GCC, GCC 12, which is in feature-freeze and which I hope will …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Malcolm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Observability in 2022: Why it matters and how OpenTelemetry can help]]></title>
        <id>058dd256-91a7-4914-b9eb-7cc4fd8a2040</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/12/observability-2022-why-it-matters-and-how-opentelemetry-can-help"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains the basics of observability for developers. We’ll look at why observability should interest you, its current level of maturity, and what to look out for to make the most of its potential.
Two years ago, James Governor of the developer analyst firm Redmonk remarked, "Observability is making the transition from being a niche concern to becoming a new frontier for user experience, systems, and service management in web companies and enterprises alike." Today, observability is hitting the mainstream.
As 2022 gets underway, you should expect to hear more about observability as a concern to take seriously. However, lots of developers are still unsure about what observability actually is—​and some of the descriptions of the subject can be vague and imprecise. Read on to get …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Evans</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[<그것이 말한다>와 존재의 언어활동]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222698478995</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222698478995"/>
        <updated>2022-04-12T03:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<그것이 말한다.> 이 주장은 라캉의 주장이면서 동시에 하이데거의 주장이다. 김형효는 라캉의 주장을 ‘본능의 언어활동’이라고 규정하고, 하이데거의 주장을 ‘존재의 언어활동’ 혹은 ‘본성의 언어활동’이라고 규정한다. 하이데거의 주장이 ‘존재의 언어활동’이라면, 라캉의 그것은 ‘소유’의 언어활동이다. <그것은 말한다>라는 하이데거의 주장은 7-1 <진리와 비진리의 불일이불이(不一而不二)와 법성(法性)의 성기(性起)>와 7-2 <차연(差延)의 이중긍정과 해탈의 이중부정>으로 해명되고 있다. 7-1은 글의 순서에 따라 다음처럼 요약될 수 있다. (A) 중생의 욕계(欲界)에서 이기심을 치유할 수 있는 방법이.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 코로나19 오미크론 변이 WHO 발표]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73831</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/11/npc_omicron/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_omicron"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난해 가을만 해도 코로나19 종식을 말하는 사람들이 꽤 있었습니다. 그러나 겨울이 되면서 전염력이 강한 오미크론 변이가 빠르게 퍼지기 시작했죠. 오늘은 지난해 11월 28일에 쓴 세계보건기구(WHO)의 오미크론 변이 발표에 관한 내용을 다시 올립니다.   세계보건기구(WHO)가 코로나19 오미크론 변이 바이러스(B.1.1.529)를 ‘우려 변이(VOC, Variant of Concern)’로 지정했습니다. 세계보건기구 코로나19 바이러스 변이 분류표 새로운 변이가 발견되면 여기에 그리스 알파벳 순서대로 이름을 붙이고, 관찰(VBM, Variant Being Monitored), 주의(VOI, Variant of Interest), 우려(VOC), 고위험(VOHC, Variant of → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trojan Source attack for introducing invisible vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0933/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0933/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from the University of Cambridge described a technique that allows inserting invisible adversarial code in the reviewed source texts. The attack (CVE-2021-42574) is called Trojan Source. It is based on text formatting that makes the code look different for compilers/interpreters and human code reviewers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time the smart home got a do not disturb mode]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10063</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/its-time-the-smart-home-got-a-do-not-disturb-mode/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T18:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Jonathan called in with an interesting smart home problem to solve. He’s looking for a button or some other simple device that, when pressed, will disable any smart home routines. Jonathan’s wife has an irregular sleep schedule due to her job so he doesn’t want automations or routines to […]
The post It’s time the smart home got a do not disturb mode appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded devices remain vulnerable to ransomware threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474285</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-devices-remain-vulnerable-to-ransomware-threats/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded devices need more ransomware protection — right now. But it will require significant time and investment. OT systems are an established target for ransomware,...
The post Embedded devices remain vulnerable to ransomware threats appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ang Cui</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The battery-free IoT revolution is here!]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10072</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/the-battery-free-iot-revolution-is-here/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a good time to be excited about wireless technology that doesn’t require batteries. As a flush of recent news proves, energy-harvesting technology is poised to move from pilot applications to scaled out use in the real world in the coming year. If we want to deploy trillions of connected sensors, we have to dump batteries. […]
The post The battery-free IoT revolution is here! appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How is Dev Library useful to the open-source community?]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/dev-library-open-source.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/dev-library-open-source.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:00:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ankita Tripathi, Community Manager (Dev Library) 
   
   

Witnessing a plethora of open-source enthusiasts in the developer ecosystem in recent years gave birth to the idea of Google’s Dev Library. The inception of the platform happened in June 2021 with the only objective of giving visibility to developers who have been creating and building projects relentlessly using Google technologies. But why the Dev Library? 
Why Dev Library?
  
Open-source communities are currently at a boom. The past 3 years have seen a surge of folks constantly building in public, talking about open-source contributions, digging into opportunities, and carving out a valuable portfolio for themselves. The idea behind the Dev Library as a whole was also to capture these open-source projects and leverage …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주식 투자를 위한 주요 지표]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=585154</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/585154/%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%eb%a5%bc-%ec%9c%84%ed%95%9c-%ec%a3%bc%ec%9a%94-%ec%a7%80%ed%91%9c"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T13:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배제된 여신의 부활: 바울로의 삼위일체 vs. 민중의 마리아]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85188</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85188"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T09:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[하느님이 인간을 구원하기 위해 동정녀 마리아의 몸을 통해 독생자 예수를 이 땅에 보냈다는 사도 바울로의 주장은 언뜻 보기에는 매우 그럴듯 해보였다. 제우스가 인간 세멜레를 통해 디오니소스를 낳았다는 신화를 비롯하여 신과 인간이 통정하여 아기를 낳는 이야기는 이미 고대인들에게 익숙한 것이었기 때문이다. 바울로, 일신교 교리를 위해 ‘삼위일체’를 발명하다   하지만 이렇게 유일신 하느님을 핵가족의 가장으로 바꾸고나니 골치아픈 문제가 […]
The post 배제된 여신의 부활: 바울로의 삼위일체 vs. 민중의 마리아 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computing Breakthrough and Cognitive Router Technology Promises Secure Networking by Design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21523</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/computing-breakthrough-and-cognitive-router-technology-promises-secure-networking-by-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T08:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IoT Security Foundation, nquiringMinds and the University of Oxford collaborate to launch the Secure Networking by Design (SNbD) project for the development of advanced, open source, network protections for Internet Service Providers (ISPs) and router vendors. IoTSF has teamed up with nquiringMinds and the University of Oxford to launch the Secure Networking by Design (SNbD)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Summit 2022: A developer preview]]></title>
        <id>ea6eecd0-497d-4025-85af-1dfed0eb1dfe</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/11/red-hat-summit-2022-developer-preview"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a developer who works with Red Hat technologies—or is curious to learn more about them? Join us at Red Hat Summit 2022 on May 10 and 11 to learn from the experts behind the code, and find the tools you need to help solve your most pressing tech challenges. Over these two days—and beyond—you'll get access to sessions and technical presentations on the topics most relevant to your interests and career. Registration is now open!
One of the most anticipated presentations is "Ask the experts anything about developer product adoption," a live, interactive session that will stream at 12 p.m. Eastern Time on Wednesday, May 11. Red Hat Developer's Edson Yanaga, Mithun Dhar, and Ignacio Riesgo know all about increasing your developer productivity with developer tools for Red Hat OpenShift, R…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Hat Developer Editorial Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to the Node.js reference architecture, Part 8: TypeScript]]></title>
        <id>77b82ab1-239d-4d61-9ee6-f3ccffd31756</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/11/introduction-nodejs-reference-architecture-part-8-typescript"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the key choices you make when building an enterprise Node.js application is whether to use plain JavaScript or a dialect that supports type validation. While participating in the Node.js reference architecture effort, we've pulled together many internal Red Hat and IBM teams to discuss our experience with using both plain JavaScript and TypeScript. Our projects seem to be split between the two, and it's often "love it or hate it" when using types with JavaScript.
TypeScript is in widespread use, particularly among enterprise developers coming from other languages such as Java. TypeScript was recently voted the third most loved programming language in StackOverflow's annual developer survey—far ahead of JavaScript itself.
This article covers why you might want to use TypeScript and h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dominic Harries</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage Multiple BLE Peripherals in iOS [SwiftUI]]]></title>
        <id>https://www.novelbits.io/?p=18869</id>
        <link href="https://www.novelbits.io/manage-multiple-ble-peripherals-in-ios-swiftui/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T06:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial is an excerpt from a course available within the Bluetooth Developer Academy, developed in collaboration with Anas Imtiaz, Ph.D. For the purpose of this tutorial (separated into two parts), our goal is to create an iOS app that can manage multiple BLE peripherals. Our example will be an app that can be used…
The post How to Manage Multiple BLE Peripherals in iOS [SwiftUI] appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammad Afaneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15 니체와 발생적 오류]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222697404993</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222697404993"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T02:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글을 논증으로 요약하고 평가해 보라. 이 도덕의 역사학자들 가운데 위세를 부리고 싶어하는 선한 정령에게 경의를 표하자. 그러나 유감스럽게도 이들에게는 역사적 정신 자체가 결여되어 있으며, 그들이 바로 역사의 모든 선한 정령 자체에게서 방치되어버렸다는 것은 확실하다. 그들 모두는 낡은 철학자들의 관습이 그러하듯이, 본질적으로 비역사적으로 생각한다. 이 점에 관해서는 의심할 여지가 없다. 그들이 다루는 도덕 계보학의 미숙함은 ‘좋음’이라는 개념과 판단의 유래를 탐구하는 것이 문제될 때, 처음부터 바로 드러난다. 그들은 다음과 같이 선언한다. “원래 비이기적 행위란 그 행위가 표시되어, 즉 그 행위로 인해 이.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Benchmarks of C++20 Ranges vs Standard Algorithms]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/ranges-perf/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/ranges-perf/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With C++20, we have a new approach to writing algorithms and composing them. The significant question is their performance. Are they faster or slower than the standard C++ algorithms we have known for decades? Let’s find out in this article.
I’ll show you three use cases with performance results, and also we’ll compare build times.



     
    


I don’t think that comparing std::alg_name with its ranges counterpart like std::ranges::alg_name will give us any difference… but for completeness let’s make a simple sorting test:
static void Standard(benchmark::State& state) {
  auto data = words;
  for (auto _ : state) {
       std::sort(data.begin(), data.end());
       benchmark::DoNotOptimize(data);
    }
}
BENCHMARK(Standard);

static void Ranges(benchmark::State& state) {
  auto data = w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 손실 회피 효과에 대한 논쟁]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73810</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/10/npc_lossaversion/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_lossaversion"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T22:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리에게 ‘생각에 관한 생각’으로 잘 알려진 다니엘 카네만은 심리학자로 2002년 노벨경제학상을 수상했고 행동경제학이라는 분야를 만든 전설적인 학자입니다. 그에게 노벨경제학상을 안겨준 것은 1970년대 아모스 트버스키와 함께 연구한 전망 이론(prospect theory)입니다. 전망 이론에서 가장 중요한 요소는 인간이 같은 양의 이익에 비해 손실의 영향을 더 크게 생각한다는 손실 회피(loss aversion)입니다. 간단하게 줄이면 “손해는 이익보다 아프다”는 말 정도가 되겠죠. 실제로 그는 자서전에서 자신들이 이 분야에 한 가장 큰 기여로 손실 회피의 개념을 꼽았습니다. 손실 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating server-based system architecture compliance testing through emulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474278</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/accelerating-server-based-system-architecture-compliance-testing-through-emulation/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T12:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[System-level verification objectives raise a concern that validation might only be possible after the design and drivers are mostly fully assembled and debugged but waiting for the design to be finished before checking compliance isn’t helpful either.
The post Accelerating server-based system architecture compliance testing through emulation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Heaton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[심리분석과 철학]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222695768753</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222695768753"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T19:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[특히 인터넷에서 글에 ㅋㅋ나 ㅎㅎ를 습관적으로 자주 쓰는 경우를 본다. 이런 기호를 쓰는 심리 상태가 무엇인가? 그 심리 상태를 어느 정도 추측할 수 있지만, 그의 심리 상태가 무엇이든 간에 그러한 기호는 글의 내용이 정당한지, 그렇지 않은지와 무관하다. 그럼에도 이런 기호들이 자주 나타나는 글은 그다지 진지하지 못한 경우가 대부분이다. 따라서 그런 기호가 자주 나타나는 글은 그냥 무시하는 것이 좋은 방책이다. 철학에서 중요한 것은 상대방에 대한 심리분석이 아니다. 너는 바로 이런 동기에서 그 글을 썼다. 이런 주장에 대해서 “아닌데” 하면 그만이다. 내가 그런 동기에서 썼다는 것을 네가 어떻게 증명할 것인가? 나아가.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why China’s Version of Email Marketing Is So Effective]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5163</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/private-traffic-is-chinas-version-of-email-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T18:45:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to ecommerce, last year in China often means this year (or next) in the U.S. Numerous online shopping trends have swept China before landing stateside one or two years later. This is happening now with super apps (e.g., WeChat and Doordash), meaning platforms that customers initially use for one purpose (like ordering food... Read More
The post Why China’s Version of Email Marketing Is So Effective appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Connie Chan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for April 8, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10060</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-april-8-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest on the Sigfox sale: The French court met with bidders for Sigfox’s business and assets on April 5, and apparently only four credible bidders turned up. They were Singapore-based UnaBiz, Actility, a French LoRaWAN provider; OTEIS France, and Greybull Capital, an English venture capital company. For a bit more on the proceedings check out the article, […]
The post IoT news of the week for April 8, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use OAuth 2.0 tokens on your website, app, and servers]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/use-oauth-20-tokens-on-your-website-app.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/use-oauth-20-tokens-on-your-website-app.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T17:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Peter Jacobsen, Technical Writer
  

 OAuth 2.0 is an open standard authorization framework for token-based authorization on the internet. An OAuth 2.0 access token is a string that the OAuth 2.0 client uses to make requests to the resource server, and hides the user's identity or other information from the OAuth 2.0 client. Only use access tokens to make requests to the resource server. 
Offline refresh tokens
  
Access tokens periodically expire and become invalid credentials for a related API request. If you requested offline access to the scopes associated with the token, you can refresh an access token without prompting the user for permission, even when the user isn't present. 
As a best practice, set the expiration time for refresh tokens for a little longer than the acces…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: smart displays, smart badges and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474233</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-smart-displays-smart-badges-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T16:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest news from the embedded world. 
The post embedded news: smart displays, smart badges and more appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 Embedded Online Conference - Final Push!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1449.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1449.php"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T14:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the Embedded Online Conference only a couple of weeks away, we are now doing a final push to ensure that as many engineers as possible who could benefit from the conference are aware of it. 

If you'd like to help us spread the word, not only will you make our day, but you'll also earn a chance to win one of TWO Saleae Logic Pro 8.   ...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[채널A 검언유착 의혹: 풀리지 않은 의혹, 성급한 정치적 면죄부]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85180</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85180"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T08:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대선이 끝나자마자 검찰과 보수 언론을 중심으로 윤석열 당선자 최측근이자 ‘채널A 검언유착 의혹’ 사건 당사자인 한동훈 사법연수원 부원장(검사장)에 대한 무혐의 처분 주장이 잇달아 나오더니 결국 무혐의 처분으로 수사가 종결됐다. 서울중앙지검은 4월 6일 한동훈 검사장이 ‘나를 팔라’며 이동재 전 채널A 기자와 공모하여 수감 중인 이철 전 밸류인베스트코리아(VIK) 대표를 협박해 유시민 전 노무현재단 이사장의 비리정보를 제공하도록 강요했다는 의혹에 […]
The post 채널A 검언유착 의혹: 풀리지 않은 의혹, 성급한 정치적 면죄부 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[일 안 해도 생기는 수입? 그런 ‘패시브 인컴’은 없다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85162</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85162"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T07:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코칭을 하다 보면 ‘패시브 인컴’ 얘기를 가끔 듣습니다. “매일 같은 일을 반복하는 게 힘들다. 그간 진짜 열심히 일해서 사업은 좀 안정된 것 같은데, 이젠 여유를 갖고 싶다. 패시브 인컴을 만들 수 있으면 좀 나아질 것 같다.” 패시브 인컴에 관한 ‘착각’  패시브 인컴(Passive Income, 수동 소득)이란 잠자는 동안에도 들어오는, 일을 하지 않아도 따박따박 들어오는 수입을 얘기합니다. […]
The post 일 안 해도 생기는 수입? 그런 ‘패시브 인컴’은 없다 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이상훈</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서울신문 우리사주조합은 왜 건설재벌에 투항했는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85150</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85150"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T06:33:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4월 5일 서울남부지법은 KBS 1TV가 [시사기획 창] ‘누가, 회장님 기사를 지웠나’를 방송하기 몇 시간을 앞두고 호반건설이 낸 이 기획물의 방송금지 가처분 신청을 모두 기각했다. 이에 따라 [시사기획 창] 367회는 이날 밤 10시 예정대로 방영되었다. 호반건설의 방송금지 가처분 신청(기각)   서울신문은 2019년 7월 5일부터 2019년 11월 25일까지 ‘호반건설 대해부’ 시리즈로 65건의 기사를 게재했다. 그 소재와 주제는 다음과 […]
The post 서울신문 우리사주조합은 왜 건설재벌에 투항했는가 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 허이공실(虛以控實)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222694937057</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222694937057"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T00:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[9강의 제목은 <주관적 표상을 객관화하는 지성주체의 형식>이다. 지성주체의 형식인 범주와 칸트에게 매우 중요한 초월적 연역에 대한 이야기를 기대했지만, 이런 이야기는 나오지 않는다. 8강과 마찬가지로 어떻게 주관적 표상이 객관화될 수 있는지, 칸트가 주관주의인지, 아닌지, 시간과 공간의 형식이 마음의 주관적 형식이라는 것이 무엇을 의미하는지 이야기하고 있다. 칸트가 초월적 연역, 혹은 선험론적 연역에서 보여주는 문제는 선험적, 아프리오리 개념이 어떻게 객관적 실재성을 갖는가 하는 것이다. 아마 모종삼의 표현으로는 “지성주체의 형식이 어떻게 주관적 표상을 객관화하는가”라는 문제가 될 것이다. 어떻게 객관화.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 유전자 복권]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73799</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/07/npc_geneticlottery/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_geneticlottery"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T22:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[평등은 오늘날 가장 중요한 화두 중 하나입니다. 무엇이 평등인지에 관한 생각이 다를 뿐, 평등한 세상을 거부하는 사람이나 사상은 거의 없습니다. 흔히 우파는 개인의 노력을 강조하고, 좌파는 사회의 책임을 강조한다고 말합니다. 그러나 우파와 좌파 모두 인간에 대한 과학적 지식이 축적되면서 드러난 평등에 대한 새로운 사실에 관해서는 게으르거나 의도적으로 무시하는 태도를 보입니다. 그것은 바로 유전자에 의한 불평등입니다. 텍사스 오스틴 대학의 주목받는 유전학자 캐서린 페이지 하든이 지난 9월 출간한 “유전자 복권(Genetic Lottery)”은 제목부터 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio static analyzer to recheck Unity]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0932/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0932/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unity is one of the most popular game engines. It helps create many excellent cross-platform projects. It's been 4 years since the last time we checked Unity's source code. Time has come again to see what interesting things we can find.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralization for Web3 Builders: Principles, Models, How]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5098</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/web3-decentralization-models-framework-principles-how-to/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T16:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The promise of decentralization has been heavily discussed and debated, from why it matters to the bigger question of who will control the software that powers the internet. These questions are critical, because as we have seen, when control is held in the hands of a very few, encroachments on personal freedom, choice, and privacy... Read More
The post Decentralization for Web3 Builders: Principles, Models, How appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miles Jennings</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CVE-2021-30737, @xerub's 2021 iOS ASN.1 Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/04/cve-2021-30737-xerubs-2021-ios-asn1.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/04/cve-2021-30737-xerubs-2021-ios-asn1.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=lhDjYqiy3mZ0x6ROQEUoUw');ol{margin:0;padding:0}table td,table th{padding:0}.c5{border-right-style:solid;padding:5pt 5pt 5pt 5pt;border-bottom-color:#e0e0e0;border-top-width:1pt;border-right-width:1pt;border-left-color:#e0e0e0;vertical-align:top;border-right-color:#e0e0e0;border-left-width:1pt;border-top-style:solid;background-color:#fafafa;border-left-style:solid;border-bottom-width:1pt;width:468pt;border-top-color:#e0e0e0;border-bottom-style:solid}.c10{color:#434343;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:14pt;font-family:"Arial";font-style:normal}.c2{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:10pt;font-family:Consolas,"Courier New";font-style:normal}.c0…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 FIRST Robotics Competition – Team 7769]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14067</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/2022-first-robotics-competition-team-7769/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T13:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in the year 1998, the FIRST Robotics Competition gave me the opportunity to be involved in my first major engineering project. As a member of Team 67 (Heros of Tomorrow),  which was sponsored by the General Motors Proving Grounds in Milford, MI, I had the opportunity to be mentored by engineers and get hands-on … Continue reading 2022 FIRST Robotics Competition – Team 7769
2022 FIRST Robotics Competition – Team 7769 first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Meet a robot that weeds your garden]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10054</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-meet-a-robot-that-weeds-your-garden/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s podcast starts with an update on the state of Bluetooth adoption courtesy of the Bluetooth SIG. We discuss adoption of Bluetooth in the smart home, adoption of Bluetooth mesh and why Kevin prefers NFC to Bluetooth for secure keys. From there we discuss a new effort by the U.S. Congress to make it […]
The post Podcast: Meet a robot that weeds your garden appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열의 먹방로드: 당선자 먹방에 목멘 언론들]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85138</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85138"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T10:51:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 당선자는 “혼밥하지 않겠다”며 공개오찬을 소통 행보로 내세웠습니다. 이로 인해 지난 한달 간 ‘식사정치’라는 말이 언론에 많이 회자됐는데요. 윤 당선자의 공개오찬 일정은 언론에 수없이 대서특필되며 그가 다녀간 식당 주소와 메뉴까지 공개됐습니다. 윤 당선자에게는 ‘맛집을 섭렵한 대통령’, ‘음식에 진심인 윤석열’이란 수식어가, 식당에는 ‘윤석열 대통령 당선자 인증 맛집’이란 표현까지 붙었습니다. 민주언론시민연합은 윤석열 당선자의 ‘식사 정치’를 보도하고 있는 […]
The post 윤석열의 먹방로드: 당선자 먹방에 목멘 언론들 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[정치자금, 유권자 표현의 자유 vs. 정치적 불평등]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85113</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85113"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T09:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2021년 5월 27일 헌법재판소는 정치자금의 수입과 지출 등 회계보고된 자료의 열람기간을 3월간으로 제한한 “정치자금법 제42조 제2항”을 국민의 알 권리를 침해한다는 이유로 위헌 판정하였다(2018헌마1168). 이 판결은 정치자금의 민주적 운영을 위해 필수적인 수입과 지출의 공개를 강화한다는 측면에서 환영할 만하다. 현행 ‘정치자금법’은 정당, 후원회 등의 회계책임자가 회계장부에 모든 정치자금의 수입과 지출에 관한 사항을 기재하도록 의무화하고 있으며(제7장 제37조), 정해진 […]
The post 정치자금, 유권자 표현의 자유 vs. 정치적 불평등 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kafka Monthly Digest: March 2022]]></title>
        <id>06cbe08b-54e4-4f95-968d-0127abec6901</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/07/kafka-monthly-digest-march-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the 50th edition of the Kafka Monthly Digest, and covers what happened in the Apache Kafka community in March 2022.
For last month’s digest, please see Kafka Monthly Digest: February 2022.
Releases
On March 14, I released Kafka 3.0.1. This bugfix version addresses 29 JIRA tickets, including a few blockers. For more details, see the release notes or the release plan.
Two upcoming releases are in progress:

3.1.1: On March 9, Tom Bentley volunteered to run the Kafka 3.1.1 bugfix release. It is expected to release in April and you can find the release plan on the Kafka wiki.


3.2.0: The release process continues for this version. The feature freeze happened on March 16 and Bruno Cadonna cut the 3.2 branch on March 21. The first release candidate is expected in mid-April. For more det…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mickael Maison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to install a database with Helm charts]]></title>
        <id>f6ca6909-f9d0-4fc8-873e-9f17b651b575</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/07/3-ways-install-database-helm-charts"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helm is a package manager for Kubernetes. Helm uses a packaging format called charts, which include all of the Kubernetes resources that are required to deploy an application, such as deployments, services, ingress, and so on. Helm charts are very useful for installing applications and performing upgrades on a Kubernetes cluster.
In chapter 3 of my e-book Getting GitOps: A Practical Platform with OpenShift, Argo CD and Tekton, I discuss the basics of creating and using Helm charts. I also dig into the the use case of creating a post-install and post-upgrade job.
However, that chapter provided a very basic example that focused only on what's necessary to create and deploy a Helm chart. This article will demonstrate some more advanced techniques to create a chart that could be installed more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wanja Pernath</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[승조(僧肇)의 부진공론(不眞空論)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222694283494</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222694283494"/>
        <updated>2022-04-07T06:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[풍우란의 <중국철학사>에 소개된 승조(僧肇)의 <부진공론(不眞空論)>을 다음처럼 요약할 수 있다. <만물은 유(有)가 아닌 이유가 있으므로 유(有)가 아니다. 만물은 무(無)가 아닌 이유가 있으므로 무(無)가 아니다. 무(無)가 아니므로 절대적 무(無)가 아니고, 유(有)가 아니므로 진유(眞有)가 아니다. 유(有)와 무(無)는 명칭이 달라도 하나이다. 유(有)가 진유(眞有)라면, 영원할 것이다. 그러나 유(有)는 인연에 의해 생겨나므로 영원하지 않다. 따라서 유(有)는 진유(眞有)가 아니다. 무(無)가 진정한 무(無)라면, 영원할 것이다. 그러나 무(無)는 인연에 의해 생겨나므로 영원하지 않다. 따라서 무(無)는 절대적 무(無)가 아.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 팬데믹의 한가운데서 공공재를 외치는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73785</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/06/npc_commongoods/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_commongoods"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T22:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 팬데믹 이후에 쓴 예전 글을 다시 소개할 땐 ‘저때는 얼마 지나고 나면 팬데믹이 끝나 있겠지…’ 하고 기대하던 게 생각납니다. 오늘 소개하는 글도 그렇습니다. 지난해 11월에 이 글을 썼을 땐 오미크론 변이가 기승을 부리기 전이었습니다. 엔데믹(endemic)에 관한 희망 섞인 이야기가 나오던 때였죠. 안타깝게도 코로나19는 2022년에도 종식되지 않고 있습니다. 이 글을 쓴 일주일 뒤에는 세계보건기구(WHO)의 오미크론 변이 발표의 주요 내용을 우리말로 옮겨 소개하기도 했네요.   툴루즈 경제대학원이 지난 5월 말에 연 “공공재(common → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud projects: Tips and best practices]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-cloud-projects-tips-and-best.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-cloud-projects-tips-and-best.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Peter Jacobsen, Google Technical Writer  
Least privilege
  
Always apply the principle of least privilege when you provide access to Google Cloud resources. The best practice is to grant only the most limited predefined roles or custom roles that meet your needs.  
For more information, see Least privilege. 
Google Cloud billing alerts
  
Set up Google Cloud billing alerts for your projects at specified intervals for early warning of usage patterns, and to help reduce costs. 
For more information, see Create, edit, or delete budgets and budget alerts. 
API quotas
  
API quotas protect the Google infrastructure from excessive API requests. Traffic is blocked when the level of requests reaches the daily API quota level or a per-user rate limit.  
To avoid disruptions due to an API quota …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Gun Safe review: Bluetooth doesn’t really add that much value]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10039</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/wyze-gun-safe-review-bluetooth-doesnt-really-add-that-much-value/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T14:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been testing the new Wyze Gun Safe since a review unit arrived late last month. Although I generally like most Wyze products, this one seems underwhelming. While I’m sure it would keep any firearms in the home as safe as any competing, non-connected products, adding Bluetooth connectivity to this $154.99 (on-sale, normally $169.99) product […]
The post Wyze Gun Safe review: Bluetooth doesn’t really add that much value appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last Python 3.11 alpha (3.11.0a7) is available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/04/the-last-python-311-alpha-3110a7-is.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/04/the-last-python-311-alpha-3110a7-is.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T10:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brrrrr… do you feel that? That’s the chill of beta freeze coming closer. Meanwhile, your friendly CPython release team doesn’t rest and we have prepared a shiny new release for you: Python 3.11.0a7.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3110a7/

Major new features of the 3.11 series, compared to 3.10
Among the new major new features and changes so far:


PEP 657 – Include Fine-Grained Error Locations in Tracebacks
PEP 654 –  Exception Groups and except*
PEP 673 –   Self Type
PEP 646 –  Variadic Generics
PEP 680– tomllib: Support for Parsing TOML in the Standard Library
PEP 675– Arbitrary Literal String Type
PEP 655– Marking individual TypedDict items as required or potentially-missing
bpo-46752– Introduce task groups to asyncio
The Faster Cpython Project is already yielding some …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[V&V Testing: Signs you have a verification & validation issue]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/testing-signs-verification-validation-issue/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/testing-signs-verification-validation-issue/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T09:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Verification and validation (V&V) are vital in medical device software development regardless of where you’re looking to sell your device. But […]
The post V&V Testing: Signs you have a verification & validation issue appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bluefruit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[클라우드 게이밍: 루나, 엑스박스, ​스테이디어, 지포스 나우 등 현황]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85092</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85092"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T09:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[클라우드 게이밍은 구글, 마이크로소프트, 아마존 등 메이저 테크 기업이 몇 년 전부터 의욕적으로 등장을 알리고 새로운 시장 변혁을 일으킬 것 같았으나 아직 태동 중인 분야이다. 클라우드 게이밍 서비스는 TV, 스마트폰, 랩톱, 태블릿 어디서나 우리가 원하는 고급 수준의 게임을 손쉽게 사용할 수 있다는 얘기이다. 모든 렌더링은 클라우드 서버에서 하고 이를 스트리밍으로 보내주기 때문에 저가 장비에서도 고급 […]
The post 클라우드 게이밍: 루나, 엑스박스, ​스테이디어, 지포스 나우 등 현황 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[무(無)의 존재]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222693300208</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222693300208"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T06:09:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<그들은 무(無)에 대해서 진지하게 숙고하였다.> 그런데 나는 그럴 필요가 없다고 생각한다. 무(無), 즉 없는 것에 대해서 숙고하는 대신에 차라리 있는 것에 대해서 숙고하고 성찰하는 것이 더 낫다. 가령 ‘존재하는’ 규칙의 규범성을 어떻게 해명해야 하는지 숙고하는 것이 더 낫다. <도대체 왜 존재자이며, 오히려 무(無)가 아닌가?> 진짜 이 질문이 형이상학의 근본물음인가? 루우의 <형이상학 강의>에는 이 물음이 없다. 로이(Lowe)의 책, <형이상학 개관>에도 이 질문을 다루지 않는다. 도대체 이 질문은 무엇을 묻고 있는 것인가? 루이스가 지적하듯이 이 질문은 잘못된 가정, 즉 무(無)가 있다는 가정, 혹은 절.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In defense of simple architectures]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/simple-architectures/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/simple-architectures/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wave is a $1.7B company with 70 engineers1 whose product is a CRUD app that adds and subtracts numbers. In keeping with this, our architecture is a standard CRUD app architecture, a Python monolith on top of Postgres. Starting with a simple architecture and solving problems in simple ways where possible has allowed us to scale to this size while engineers mostly focus on work that delivers value to users.
Stackoverflow scaled up a monolith to good effect (2013 architecture / 2016 architecture), eventually getting acquired for $1.8B. If we look at traffic instead of market cap, Stackoverflow is among the top 100 highest traffic sites on the internet (for many other examples of valuable companies that were built on top of monoliths, see the replies to this Twitter thread. We don’t have a lot…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 의지력은 한정된 자원이 아니라 하나의 감정]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73768</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/05/npc_willpower/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_willpower"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1998년, 심리학자 로이 바우마이스터는 초콜릿 쿠키 냄새가 가득한 방에 자원자들을 들여보낸 다음 어떤 이들에게는 초콜릿 쿠키를 먹게 했고 다른 이에게는 그 옆에 둔 무만 먹게 했습니다. 그리고 이 두 집단에 어려운 퍼즐을 풀게 하고 언제 포기하는지를 보았습니다. 초콜릿 쿠키를 먹은 이들에 비해 쿠키 냄새를 참고 무를 먹은 이들은 시간이 절반도 지나지 않아 퍼즐을 포기했습니다. 바우마이스터의 연구진은 이 결과를 무를 먹은 이들이 초콜릿 쿠키에 대한 유혹을 참는 데 의지력을 이미 많이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDSC India’s Android Study Jams Boost Student Career Outcomes]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/gdsc-indias-android-study-jams-boost.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/gdsc-indias-android-study-jams-boost.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T17:06:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Tanvi Somani, Program Manager - Regional Lead, Google Developer Student Clubs, Google Developer Relations India 
 
   
Android Study Jams, hosted by Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSC) chapters across the globe and in India, leverage peer-to-peer teaching to train a new generation of student Android developers. The program aims to help student developers build their careers and put them on a solid path towards earning an Associate Android Developers Certification. Three students from the GDSC community in India, Amsavarthan Lv, Rishi Balamurugan, and Sanjay S. went the extra kilometer to earn their certifications.  
Meet the newly certified Android developers 
“From childhood onward, I was inspired by my brother to learn to program. He’s also a certified Android developer,” say…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re making sensors smarter — and more complicated]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10034</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/were-making-sensors-smarter-and-more-complicated/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T13:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the pandemic, we’ve seen major sensor vendors add more intelligence to their sensors. In 2020 Sony launched a vision sensor that can perform people tracking or object detection locally, and last year Bosch announced its BHI260AP sensor, which has accelerometers and gyroscopes along with a processor pre-loaded with activity-tracking algorithms that can actively learn to track new motions. […]
The post We’re making sensors smarter — and more complicated appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[리빙스턴의 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222692662327</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222692662327"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T12:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://blog.naver.com/sellars/100033129776 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거 1 하이데거에 대한 비트겐슈타인의 글이 <존재와 시간>에 대한 것이라고 리빙스턴이 주장한다. 나는 존재와 불안에 의해서 무엇을 의미하려고 하는지 잘 생각할 수 있다고 이야기하는 비트겐슈타인의 글이 하이데거 후기에 관한 것이라고 막연하게 생각했었다. 그러나 비트겐슈타인의 글은 하이데거의 <존재와 시간>이 나온 이년 후에 작성되었다고 한다. (이럼에도 머레이는 <존재와 시간>보다는 오히려 <형이상학이란 무엇인가>(1929)에 대한 것이라고 주장하고 있다.) 하여튼 무엇이 존재한다. 비트겐슈타인은 존재의 경이에 대해 질문으로 표.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T4 작전을 아십니까: 박경석 전장연 대표 인터뷰]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85070</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85070"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T08:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 대선 토론에서 한 후보가 장애인 이동권 시위를 하고 있다는 한 시민의 이야기를 했습니 다. 이후 후보가 현장을 방문하기도 했었죠. 그 시민, 전국장애인차별철폐연대 박경석 상임공동대표를 만나서 장애인의 권리에 대해서 이야기를 들었습니다. 인터뷰이: 박경석 전국장애인차별철폐연대 상임공동대표 인터뷰어: 이성윤 경실련 회원미디어국 간사 일시, 장소: 2022년 3월 22일, 전국장애인차별철폐연대 사무실 = 전국장애인차별철폐연대(‘전장연’)를 간단히 소개해주신다면요.  2001년에 장애인이동권연대라는 곳이 있었어요. […]
The post T4 작전을 아십니까: 박경석 전장연 대표 인터뷰 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 괜찮은 일자리는 다 어디로 갔을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73755</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/04/npc_tseacemoglu/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_tseacemoglu"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T22:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[툴루즈 경제대학원이 지난 5월 말에 연 “공공재(common good)” 학술회의에서 나온 이야기를 전하는 세 번째, 마지막 시간입니다. 앞서 MIT의 아피짓 베네르지, 에스더 듀플로 교수 부부의 주장을 전한 “팬데믹과 부유세” 이야기를 소개했죠. 또 앵거스 디튼 교수가 지적하는 “절망의 죽음과 두 개의 미국”에 관한 이야기도 전해드렸고요. 오늘은 계속해서 불평등이 심화해 공공재가 메말라가는 현상에 대한 진단과 해법에 관한 고민을 전합니다. 오늘의 주인공은 앞서 소개한 석학들처럼 노벨 경제학상을 아직 받지는 못했습니다. 그러나 가장 유력한 수상 후보군을 꼽을 때마다 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's with the PVS-Studio's coverage of Toyota ITC Benchmark?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0931/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0931/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toyota ITC Benchmark is a synthetic test set for C and C++. It consists of approximately 650 examples, and it's designed for testing code analyzers. This article is an answer to the question: "How well does the PVS-Studio static analyzer cover the Toyota ITC Benchmark?".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can ‘Community Composability’ Help Web2 Users Make the Jump to Web3?]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=5068</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/can-community-composability-help-web2-users-make-the-jump-to-web3/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T17:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 has infiltrated mainstream culture, from Paris Hilton showcasing her NFTs on the Tonight Show to ConstitutionDAO attempting to buy one of the last remaining copies of the Constitution. Joining web3, however, is still a complex and confusing process geared toward early adopters. There’s a whole cohort of digitally native people — let’s call them... Read More
The post Can ‘Community Composability’ Help Web2 Users Make the Jump to Web3? appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jenny Wang and Michael Chiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[차트로 읽는 2월 온라인쇼핑 동향, 13.7% 증가 & 비중 41.2%로 최고기록 갱신]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=585146</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/585146/22%eb%85%84-2%ec%9b%94-%ec%98%a8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8%ec%87%bc%ed%95%91%eb%8f%99%ed%96%a5-%eb%b6%84%ec%84%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T13:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[의미 소여주의 혹은 개방적 자연주의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222691573860</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222691573860"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T11:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[맥도웰은 비트겐슈타인 철학이 실질적 철학이론을 개진하는 것에 대해서 비판적이라는 것을 강조한다. 철학은 어떤 실질적 철학적 이론을 주장하거나 개진하는 것이 아니다. 이런 의미에서 철학은 치유적이다. 즉 철학은 우리 오해를 제거하는 것이다. 비트겐슈타인의 치유적 철학 혹은 비트겐슈타인의 정적주의를 맥도웰은 자기 철학의 한 요소로서 수용하고 있다. 그런데 이런 철학관을 지탱하는 기본 주장의 하나가 바로 의미나 지향성, 혹은 이것들이 갖고 있는 규범성이 우리에게 주어져 있다는 것이다. 이 주어져 있는 것에 대해서 우리가 잘못 이해할 때, 철학적 이론을 구성하려는 시도가 생겨난다. 그러나 비트겐슈타인이 말하고 있듯이.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[산 예수 vs. 죽은 예수 (혹은 영지주의 vs. 바올로)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85027</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85027"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T09:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[예수가 태어난 뒤 기독교가 성립하는 시기에 로마제국에서 가장 큰 인기있던 종교는 바로 오르페우스교와 유대교였다. 오르페우스교와 유대교  오르페우스교는 그리스 디오니소스 신앙에서 유래한 것으로, 타락과 방종으로 물든 속세에 환멸을 느낀 신도들에게 단순하고 정직하게 연민을 베풀며 살라고 가르쳤으며, 그 대가로 사후에 더 나은 삶을 살 수 있는 ‘구원’을 약속했다. 로마제국의 혼란이 심해질수록 오르페우스의 인기는 더욱 높아졌다. AD 70년 유대지역에서 대규모 폭동이 […]
The post 산 예수 vs. 죽은 예수 (혹은 영지주의 vs. 바올로) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30만대 판매 시대를 연 22년 1분기 테슬라 판매 동향 분석]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=585137</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/585137/22%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T07:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/9d7e899e7f64</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/march-2022-9d7e899e7f64?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T06:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 애플이 쏘아올린 ‘앱 추적 투명성’이라는 작은 공의 파괴력은 $100억]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73741</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/04/03/npc_appleatt/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_appleatt"/>
        <updated>2022-04-03T22:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 먼저 페이스북이 지난해 말 월스트리트저널, 뉴욕타임스, 워싱턴포스트 등 주요 신문에 냈던 전면 광고를 같이 보겠습니다. 이례적으로 애플의 정책을 공개적으로 신랄하게 비판해 많은 주목을 끌었던 광고라서 기억하시는 분들도 꽤 계실 겁니다. “전 세계 모든 영세 업체, 중소기업과 함께 애플에 맞서 싸우겠습니다.”라는 다소 비장한 제목의 광고에서 페이스북은 애플이 당시 기준으로 시행을 예고한 앱 추적 투명성 정책(ATT, App Tracking Transparency)이 특히 중소기업에 끔찍한 결과를 가져올 거라고 경고했습니다. 광고 내용을 옮겨보면 아래와 같습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick tip: Easy test assertions with Go generics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/easy-test-assertions-with-go-generics</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/easy-test-assertions-with-go-generics"/>
        <updated>2022-04-03T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that Go 1.18 has been released with support for generics, it's easier than ever to create helper functions for your test assertions.
Using helpers for your test assertions can help to:
Make your test functions clean and clear;
Keep test failure messages consistent; 
And reduce the potential for errors in your code due to typos.
To illustrate this, let's say that you have a simple greet() function that you want to test: 




In the past, your test for the  greet() function would probably look something like this:



With Go 1.18, we can use generics and the comparable constraint to create an Equal() helper function which carries out our test assertions. Personally, I like to put this in a reusable assert package.
Like so:





    Note: The t.Helper() function indicates to the Go test runner that our Equal() function is a test helper. This means that when t.Errorf() is called from our Equal() function, the Go test runner will report the filename and line number of the code which called our Equal() function in the output. 
And with that in place, the TestGreet() test can be simplified like so:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[위대한 스타트업에서 배우는 10가지 스타트업 교훈]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=585128</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/585128/%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%80%ed%8a%b8%ec%97%85-%ea%b5%90%ed%9b%88-10%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80"/>
        <updated>2022-04-03T08:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faster sorting with Go generics]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/faster-sorting-with-go-generics/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/faster-sorting-with-go-generics/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-02T13:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Recently, a new set of sorting functions <a class="reference external" href="https://go-review.googlesource.com/c/exp/+/378134">has landed</a> in Go's
<tt class="docutils literal">golang.org/exp/slices</tt> package <a class="footnote-reference" href="#id4" id="id1">[1]</a>. These functions leverage Go generics
to provide a more ergonomic API for sorting (without requiring users to
implement <a class="reference external" href="https://pkg.go.dev/sort#Interface">sort.Interface</a>), and also
deliver a nice performance improvement, as the CL demonstrates.</p>
<p>In this …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to remove phantom Amazon devices from Home Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10017</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-remove-phantom-amazon-devices-from-home-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-02T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Justin called in with a question about devices connected to both Home Assistant and Amazon. He’s looking for a way to remove a bunch of old smart home devices all at once: They’re no longer on his network but are still appearing in either the Amazon app or Home […]
The post How to remove phantom Amazon devices from Home Assistant appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 테슬라 수익성은 자동차 업계 최고 수준이 될 수 있었을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584921</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584921/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5%eb%a5%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-04-02T08:31:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[플라톤과 니체]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222689568615</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222689568615"/>
        <updated>2022-04-02T01:12:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글이 주장하는 여섯 가지 함축에 대해서 평가해 보라. 첫째, 플라톤은 동굴 안의 세계와 밖의 세계의 대조를 통해서 가상의 세계와 진상의 세계를 구분하고 있다. 이러한 구분과 동시에 우리 인간들의 일상적 삶은 바로 동굴 안의 가상의 세계에서의 삶이며, 상식적 상태에서의 인간은 동굴의 수인임을 시사하고 있다. 플라톤의 견해로서 감각적 경험이 주축이 되어 정립되는 상식적 세계란 인식론적으로, 존재론적으로, 가치론적으로 그림자의 세계에 불과한 것이며, 이 모든 측면에서 진상의 세계가 따로 존재한다는 것이 플라톤의 믿음이다. 이 진상의 세계를 플라톤은 형상계라고 부르고 있는 바 이 세계에는 형상(eidos, idea)이라고.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CodeReady Workspaces scales up, is now Red Hat OpenShift Dev Spaces]]></title>
        <id>f964d602-70d4-4bd8-b17d-364ea8b01374</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/04/01/codeready-workspaces-scales-now-red-hat-openshift-dev-spaces"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat will soon release a higher-performing, richer version of the Red Hat CodeReady Workspaces development platform, along with a name change to Red Hat OpenShift Dev Spaces. The platform has been significantly upgraded by moving to a Kubernetes Operator. This article explains the major changes in this upgrade and their effects on administrators and users.
The team worked on this version for over a year and introduced the new platform as a tech preview after CodeReady Workspaces 2.10. The official name of this release is Red Hat OpenShift Dev Spaces 3.0.
Changes to the workspace engine
The core of CodeReady Workspaces used to be a Java REST web service named che-server, which provisioned pods and other objects to run development environments on Red Hat OpenShift. With OpenShift Dev Spac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mario Loriedo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for April 1, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10025</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-april1-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T17:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another IoT network nabs funding: Based out of Seattle, practically in Stacey’s backyard, is an IoT network startup named Teal Communications. This week, Teal raised $10.8 million in a Series A funding round, valuing the company at $100 million. The company’s core product is one of convenience and simplicity: It provides an eSIM platform to […]
The post IoT news of the week for April 1, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Developer Student Club 2022 Lead applications are open!]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-developer-student-club-2022-lead.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/04/google-developer-student-club-2022-lead.html"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Erica Hanson, Global Program Manager, Google Developer Student Clubs 
 
   
Hey, student developers! If you’re passionate about programming and are ready to use your technology skills to help your community, then you should become a Google Developer Student Clubs Lead! 
The application form for the upcoming 2022-2023 academic year is NOW OPEN. Get started at goo.gle/gdsc-leads. 
Want to know more? Learn more about the program below. 
What are Google Developer Student Clubs?
  
Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSC) are university based community groups for students interested in Google developer technologies. With clubs hosted in 110+ countries around the world, students from undergraduate and graduate programs with an interest in leading a community are welcome. Together, student…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boucher: rustc_codegen_gcc can now bootstrap rustc]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889989/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889989/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T14:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On his blog, Antoni Boucher updates the status of rustc_codegen_gcc, which "is a GCC codegen for rustc, meaning that it can be loaded by the existing rustc frontend, but benefits from GCC by having more architectures supported and having access to GCC’s optimizations".   A significant milestone has been reached: "the GCC codegen has made enough progress to be able to compile rustc itself". For the Rust programming language, rustc is the standard compiler, so this work will eventually allow programs to be built for a number of architectures that are not supported by rustc. He also made progress beyond just building the compiler as he "was able to compile rustc using the GCC codegen and use the resulting rustc to compile a Hello World".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A security fix briefly breaks DMA]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889593/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889593/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T14:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In theory, direct memory access (DMA) operations are simple to understand;
a device transfers data directly to or from a memory buffer managed by the
CPU.  Almost all contemporary devices perform DMA, since it would not be
possible to obtain the needed performance without it.  Like so many things,
DMA turns out to be a bit more complicated in practice.  That complexity
led to an erroneous patch, intended to improve security, breaking DMA for
some devices in 5.17 and some stable kernels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889983/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889983/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T14:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (wireshark), Fedora (389-ds-base), Mageia (golang, wavpack, and zlib), openSUSE (yaml-cpp), SUSE (expat and yaml-cpp), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.13, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-aws-hwe, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-oracle, linux-intel-5.13, and tomcat9).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[22년 3월 수출입 동향, 사상최고치이나 에너지 상승으로 무역수지 적자 전환되다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=585102</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/585102/22%eb%85%84-3%ec%9b%94-%ec%88%98%ec%b6%9c"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T12:22:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chip design in the cloud? Now you can have pay-as-you go EDA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474170</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/chip-design-in-the-cloud-now-you-can-have-pay-as-you-go-eda/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T12:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synopsys Cloud will provide access to a suite of cloud-optimized design and verification products with pre-optimized infrastructure on Microsoft Azure, or customers can also bring their own cloud and access the EDA tools.
The post Chip design in the cloud? Now you can have pay-as-you go EDA appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: EDA, vision processing, SOMs and memory]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474166</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-eda-vision-processing-soms-and-memory/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T12:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of the latest news, products and articles in the embedded industry.
The post embedded news: EDA, vision processing, SOMs and memory appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동굴의 비유]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222689140058</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222689140058"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T09:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글에 대해서 논평해 보라. (가) 사람들이 빠지기 쉬운 여러 가지 과오에 대한 베이컨의 설명은 그의 철학 중에서 가장 생기 있는 부분이다. 베이컨은 사람들이 네 가지 유형의 정신적 약점들을 스스로 만들어내는 성향이 있다고 지적한다. 그것이 바로 우상(idol)이다. 첫 번째 우상은 “종족의 우상”이다. 우리는 인간이라는 종족이므로 바로 인간을 우상으로 받드는 경우를 말한다. 희망에 의거한 사고, 즉 이랬으면 하고 바라는 생각을 그대로 사실이라고 믿는 경우가 그 실례의 하나이다. 특히 자연 현상에 실제로 존재하는 질서보다 더 위대한 질서가 있었으면 하는 희망을 그대로 사실이라고 믿는 경우이다. 두 번째 우상은 “동굴.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비문명적 불법시위? 이준석의 장애인 혐오와 받아쓰기 언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85015</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85015"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T09:56:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이준석 국민의힘 대표가 장애인 단체의 ‘이동권 보장 시위’를 연일 비판하고 있습니다. “지하철 엘리베이터 설치율이 100%가 아니라는 이유로 다수를 볼모 삼는다”, “박원순 시정에서 약속을 못 지켰다는 이유로, 오세훈 시장 때에 지속적으로 시위하는 건 의아하다”라며 이동권 보장 시위를 “비문명적 불법시위”로 규정했습니다. 국민의힘을 포함한 정치권, 당사자 단체 등은 “주요 사실을 왜곡한 발언으로 장애인 단체에 대한 혐오를 조장한다”, “약자 […]
The post 비문명적 불법시위? 이준석의 장애인 혐오와 받아쓰기 언론 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[영업은 사람이 하고, 마케팅은 시스템이 한다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=85006</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/85006"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T08:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코칭을 하다 보면 영업과 마케팅의 차이에 대한 얘기가 자주 나옵니다. 영업과 마케팅은 여러 가지가 다른 점이 있겠지만, 가장 근본적인 차이점은 취업과 창업의 차이와 같습니다. 취업은 시간을 팔아 돈을 버는 것이고, 창업은 상품을 팔아 돈을 버는 것입니다. 영업이 시간으로 고객을 만드는 행위라면, 마케팅은 상품으로 고객이 생기는 과정입니다. 영업이 영업자의 행동이라면, 마케팅은 시스템의 운영입니다. 영업 — 사람 […]
The post 영업은 사람이 하고, 마케팅은 시스템이 한다 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이상훈</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of reading: January - March 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/summary-of-reading-january-march-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/summary-of-reading-january-march-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T02:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<ul class="simple">
<li>&quot;How We Got to Now&quot; by Steven Johnson - a short book discussing some of the
most important scientific innovations of the last 3 centuries, adapted for
young readers. The writing is very good and the illustrations are pretty
and relevant.</li>
<li>&quot;Distributed Services with Go&quot; by Travis Jeffery - describes how to …</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 달리기를 잘하는 비결: 딴 생각]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73723</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/31/npc_running/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_running"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T22:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 자신의 몸에 얼마나 많은 권한을 가지고 있을까요? 이 질문에서 권한을 내 의지로 그 부위를 움직일 수 있는가로 정의하면, 우리는 우리 몸에 그리 많은 권한을 가지고 있지 않습니다. 의지와 무관하게 무릎이 올라가는 무릎 반사 같은 잘 알려진 동작 외에도 심장의 박동이나 소화기관의 운동 역시 우리의 권한 밖에 있는 신체의 움직임입니다. 추울 때 몸을 떨고 더울 때 땀을 흘리는 것도 마찬가지입니다. 그럼 우리가 스포츠를 즐기는 중에 나오는 행동들은 어떨까요? 날아오는 공을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TOPS vs. real world performance: Benchmarking performance for AI accelerators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474140</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/tops-vs-real-world-performance-benchmarking-performance-for-ai-accelerators/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T19:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI workloads and their supporting computing architectures evolve, ensuring their predictability through accurate performance measurements has a significant impact. Burgeoning machine learning and AI...
The post TOPS vs. real world performance: Benchmarking performance for AI accelerators appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rehan Hameed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 tools to take your PCB design online]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474133</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3-tools-to-take-your-pcb-design-online/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T17:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Online PCB design tools can help streamline your design process and make collaboration easier. Printed circuit board (PCB) design is a complex endeavor, but it’s...
The post 3 tools to take your PCB design online appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FORCEDENTRY: Sandbox Escape]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/03/forcedentry-sandbox-escape.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/03/forcedentry-sandbox-escape.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ol{margin:0;padding:0}table td,table th{padding:0}.c16{padding-top:16pt;padding-bottom:4pt;line-height:1.5;page-break-after:avoid;orphans:2;widows:2;text-align:left}.c11{padding-top:18pt;padding-bottom:6pt;line-height:1.5;page-break-after:avoid;orphans:2;widows:2;text-align:left}.c7{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:11pt;font-family:"Arial";font-style:italic}.c1{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:11pt;font-family:"Courier New";font-style:normal}.c5{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:16pt;font-family:"Arial";font-style:normal}.c4{color:#000000;font-weight:400;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;font-size:11pt;font-family:"Arial";font…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Indirect branch tracking for Intel CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889475/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889475/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T14:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Control-flow integrity" (CFI) is a set of technologies intended to prevent
an attacker from redirecting a program's control flow and taking it over.
One of the
approaches taken by CFI is called "indirect branch tracking" (IBT); its
purpose is to prevent an attacker from causing an indirect branch (a
function call via a pointer variable, for example) to go to an unintended
place.  IBT for Intel processors has been under development for some time;
after an abrupt turn, support for protecting the kernel with IBT has been
merged for the upcoming 5.18 release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889852/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889852/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T14:30:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libgc and pjproject), Fedora (cobbler, mingw-openjpeg2, and openjpeg2), Mageia (openvpn), openSUSE (abcm2ps, fish3, icingaweb2, kernel-firmware, nextcloud, openSUSE-build-key, python2-numpy, salt, and zlib), Slackware (vim), SUSE (kernel-firmware, opensc, python2-numpy, python3, salt, and zlib), and Ubuntu (dosbox, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-hwe-5.13, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-snapdragon, rsync, twisted, and zlib).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Tips for Rapid Prototyping with the Raspberry Pi Pico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14072</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/5-tips-for-rapid-prototyping-with-the-raspberry-pi-pico/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T14:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last several years, Raspberry Pi’s have proliferated into all sorts of applications. As a microcontroller-focused embedded software consultant, I’ve always found them fun and interesting, but not exactly my cup of tea. However, in January 2021, the Raspberry Pi Pico was released which at its heart has an RP2040 dual-core microcontroller based on … Continue reading 5 Tips for Rapid Prototyping with the Raspberry Pi Pico
5 Tips for Rapid Prototyping with the Raspberry Pi Pico first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Helium gets a new name and $200 million]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10012</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-helium-gets-a-new-name-and-200-million/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show was recorded on the road, but we still cover all of the big news starting with LoRaWAN network Helium changing its name to Nova Labs and raising $200 million. We then discuss research from MIT that offers privacy for people captured on video and several options for connecting beehives. I then get […]
The post Podcast: Helium gets a new name and $200 million appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android GDE Maryam Alhuthayfi shares her passion for mobile development with fledgling developers]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/android-gde-maryam-alhuthayfi-shares.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/android-gde-maryam-alhuthayfi-shares.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T13:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Janelle Kuhlman, Developer Relations Program Manager
      

For Women’s History Month, we’re celebrating a few of our Google Developer Experts. Meet Maryam Alhutayfi, Android GDE. The GDE program team encourages qualified candidates that identify as women or non-binary to express interest in joining the community by completing this form.
Android GDE Maryam Alhuthayfi has loved programming since high school, when she learned programming in Visual Studio and basic website development.  
“We didn't get much beyond that because there weren’t many Arabic resources,” she says. “That experience got me excited to dig deeper into technology. I wanted to know how the web functions, how software is made, and more about programming languages.” 
Maryam studied computer science at university …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bind workloads to services easily with the Service Binding Operator and Red Hat OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>599c8903-5790-4727-ba2e-96251c2f02e2</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/11/binding-workloads-services-made-easier-service-binding-operator-red-hat"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applications running under Kubernetes must expose secrets in order to connect to external services such as REST APIs, databases, and event buses. Each service provider suggests a different way to access their secrets, and for a long time, each application has consumed those secrets in a custom way. The Service Binding Operator makes the life of the application developer a lot easier by providing a consistent and declarative service binding method.
This article will show you how to use the Service Binding Operator to bind an application to a database, enhanced by help from the Red Hat OpenShift console. The example in this article installs a MySQL database and a simple application: the Spring PetClinic sample application, enriched by Spring Cloud Bindings library.
Prerequisites
To bind to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kartikey Mamgain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[바이든의 행정명령에 11번 등장한 ‘제로 트러스트’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84989</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84989"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T04:42:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제로 트러스트(zero trust)는 네트워크 경계와 관계없이 누구도, 그리고 어떤 활동이든 기본적으로 ‘신뢰하지 않는’ 것에 바탕을 둔 보안 개념이다. 전통적인 네트워크 보안은 물리적(또는 논리적) 네트워크 경계를 설정하고, 그 경계를 기준으로 신뢰할 수 있는 영역과 그렇지 않은 영역을 구분하는 것이다. 경계 내에서의 활동은 기본적으로 신뢰할 수 있다는 전제하에 보안 기준이 적용된다. 반면, 제로 트러스트 모델에서는 설정된 네트워크 […]
The post 바이든의 행정명령에 11번 등장한 ‘제로 트러스트’ first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 도덕적이어야 하는가? 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222687846998</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222687846998"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T04:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[왜 도덕적이어야 하는가? <윤리학의 기본원리>에서 폴 데일러는 이 질문을 더 정확하게 “나는 왜 도덕적이어야 하는가”로 정형화한다. 이 질문은 일인칭적 질문이지, 삼인칭적 질문이 아니다. 내가 왜 자기 이익에 따르지 않고 도덕적인 것에 따라야 하는가? “궁극적(ultimate) 질문”이라는 이름이 가르쳐 주듯이, 이 질문에 대한 이성적 답변은 이미 궁극적이지 못하게 된다. 그 이성적 근거에 대해서 우리는 계속 그 근거를 물을 수 있기 때문이다. 이 점에서 테일러는 이 질문이 자기 결단에 근거한 것이라고 주장한다. <우리는 당신이 어떤 선택을 해야만 하는가를 보여줄 이유를 제시할 수 없다. 당신 스스로 결정해야만 한다.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 31, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889124/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889124/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T03:26:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 31, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 절망의 죽음과 두 개의 미국]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73714</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/30/npc_deaton/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_deaton"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[툴루즈 경제대학원이 지난 5월 말에 연 “공공재(common good)” 학술회의에서 나온 이야기를 전하는 두 번째 시간입니다. 지난번엔 MIT의 아피짓 베네르지, 에스더 듀플로 교수 부부의 주장을 전한 “팬데믹과 부유세” 이야기를 소개했죠. 오늘은 2015년에 “소비와 빈곤, 복지에 관한 연구 업적을 인정받아” 노벨 경제학상을 수상한 프린스턴 대학교의 앵거스 디튼(Angus Deaton) 교수의 주장을 전합니다. 새로운 주장은 아닙니다. 오히려 디튼 교수가 오랫동안 천착해 온 ‘절망의 죽음(deaths of despair)’에 관한 이야기로, 디튼 교수가 회의에서 한 기조연설을 요약한 내용입니다. 디튼 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Systemd discusses its kernel-version needs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889610/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889610/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T21:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A query regarding the possibility of dropping support for older kernels in systemd led
to some discussion on the systemd-devel mailing list recently.  As might be
guessed, exactly which kernel would be the minimum
supported, what kernel features systemd  is using, and when those kernel
features became available, were all part of that conversation.
A component like systemd that is closely tied to the kernel, and the interfaces
different versions
provide,  has a number of different factors to consider when making a
decision of this sort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checking Barotrauma with the PVS-Studio static analyzer]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0930/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0930/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barotrauma is an indie game where you can steer a submarine, hide from monsters, and even play the accordion to save your ship from going down. The Barotrauma project is developed by Undertow Games in collaboration with FakeFish. The source code is mainly written in C#. So, today, we're going to check it with the PVS-Studio static analyzer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helium rebrands to Nova Labs as it raises another $200M in funding]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9992</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/helium-rebrands-to-nova-labs-as-it-raises-another-200m-in-funding/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Depending on who you ask, the market for low-power, wide-area networks LPWAN is either really hot… or not. On the one hand, Sigfox and its proprietary LPWAN are facing the U.S. equivalent of bankruptcy proceedings in France. And on the other hand, Helium Inc is celebrating a 4,000% growth rate in its decentralized network deployments […]
The post Helium rebrands to Nova Labs as it raises another $200M in funding appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 ETF 투자를 위한 베스트 ETF 10]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=585024</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/585024/%eb%b2%a0%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8-etf-10"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T15:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSUSE adopts a new code of conduct]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889692/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889692/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T15:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE project has announced
the adoption of a new
code of conduct:
"We hope that by having a clear and concise Code of Conduct for the
project, the openSUSE Community can continue to grow and prosper in
the years to come".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZF invests in StradVision to enhance automated driving perception]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474158</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/zf-invests-in-stradvision-to-enhance-automated-driving-perception/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T14:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ZF said StradVision vision perception software expertise can provide key component of its environmental sensor fusion for shuttles, commercial and light vehicles that can be optimized for centralized electrical architectures.
The post ZF invests in StradVision to enhance automated driving perception appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889682/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889682/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (expat, firefox, httpd, openssl, and thunderbird), Debian (cacti), Fedora (kernel, rsh, unrealircd, and xen), Mageia (kernel and kernel-linus), openSUSE (apache2, java-1_8_0-ibm, kernel, openvpn, and protobuf), Oracle (openssl), Red Hat (httpd:2.4, kernel, kpatch-patch, and openssl), SUSE (apache2, java-1_7_1-ibm, java-1_8_0-ibm, kernel, openvpn, protobuf, and zlib), and Ubuntu (chromium-browser and paramiko).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New secure elements authenticate Qi 1.3 wireless charging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474154</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-secure-elements-authenticate-qi-1-3-wireless-charging/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New devices from Microchip Technology meet requirements of new version WPC Qi 1.3 specification which mandates secure storage subsystem with secure key provisioning including X.509 certificates to cryptographically verify the source and quality of the certified power transmitter.
The post New secure elements authenticate Qi 1.3 wireless charging appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The MCU shortage is sinking tech R&D]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474144</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-mcu-shortage-is-sinking-tech-rd/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T11:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A combination of factors like the pandemic disrupting global supply chains, stay-at-home orders increasing demand for consumer electronics, and electric vehicle adoption have all created a perfect storm for chip demand and especially supply of MCUs.
The post The MCU shortage is sinking tech R&D appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carsten Rhod Gregersen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[악마의 타임라인: ‘그알’ 가평계곡 살인사건 이은해 등 공개수배]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84977</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84977"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T10:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“(내가 죽으면) 보험금이 나온다.. (은해)가 이걸 알아야 보험금 탈텐데… (은해)는 나 삐졌다고 생각한다.. 바보 나 안삐졌다.. 그냥 지친거뿐… 더이상 버틸 힘이 없다.. 진짜 신기하다.. 내가 인터넷으로 목메달 로프두사구…^^ 자살은 그냥 다른세계 사람들이나 하는거라 생각했다.. 하지만 아니다.. 에너지란게 고갈돼믄 누구나 선택하는 것일뿐이다.. 나에겐 에너지가 없다.. (은해)한테 솔직히 미안하지만..그케 크게 미안하진 않아.. (은해)는 나 빈자리 못느낄 테니깐… […]
The post 악마의 타임라인: ‘그알’ 가평계곡 살인사건 이은해 등 공개수배 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IOT SECURITY FOUNDATION WELCOMES  TWO NEW EXECUTIVE STEERING BOARD MEMBERS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21508</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/iot-security-foundation-welcomes-two-new-executive-steering-board-members/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T08:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For immediate release 30 March 2022 (London, UK) – The IoT Security Foundation is delighted to announce the appointments of Nick Allott and Tim Snape as Executive Steering Board members. Joining the existing Executive Steering Board of 11 members, Nick Allott is also CEO of NquiringMinds, a British company with deep commercial experience in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate and save an HTML report in Jenkins on OpenShift 4]]></title>
        <id>ed097a95-68ee-4774-919c-153dddb7b95d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/30/generate-and-save-html-report-jenkins-openshift-4"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jenkins is one of the most popular CI/CD tools for automating builds and deployments. It is very flexible and can be deployed on almost every operating system, as well as on Red Hat OpenShift. This article shows you how to deploy Jenkins on OpenShift 4.9, create a simple pipeline to deploy a Java application to OpenShift, do some testing, save the test results as HTML, and publish it as an artifact so that people can see the results.
For this scenario, we'll generate an HTML report using Maven OWASP Dependency Check plugins. The report will contain a list of libraries that contain vulnerabilities. This pipeline runs on Jenkins 2.2 on top of OpenShift 4.9.
Use Jenkins to generate a report on OpenShift 4
There are multiple ways to set up Jenkins on OpenShift 4. This article uses a template p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Muhammad Edwin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14 발견과 정당화]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222686923011</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222686923011"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T04:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글을 통해 ‘발견’과 ‘정당화’의 문맥을 구분해 보라. 진술이 개진되었을 때, 두 가지 중요한 문제가 일어난다. 어떻게 그 진술이 생각나게 되었을까, 그리고 우리는 그 진술을 옳은 진술이라고 인정할 무슨 이유들을 가지고 있는가? 이 두 문제는 서로 다른 문제이다. 이 두 가지 문제를 혼동하는 것은 심각한 과오일 것이며, 결국 해답들을 혼동하는 심각한 과오를 일으킬 것이다. 첫 번째 문제는 발견에 관한 문제이다. 두 번째 문제는 정당화에 관한 문제이다. 이 물음이 묻고 있는 사항들은 정당화의 맥락 속에 있다. 한 진술에 대한 정당화는 하나의 논증을 이룬다. 정당화된 진술은 논증의 결론이다. 논증은 결론과 서로 관계를.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Two Cents #51] Web3 개념; 블록체인 L1 L2; De-Fi, NFT, 게임 메타버스, DAO, dApp; 인프라, 제도 규제, 생각할 꺼리들; Deep Dive — modular blockchains, DAO, dApp]]></title>
        <id>https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-51-web3-l1-l2-de-fi-nft</id>
        <link href="https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-51-web3-l1-l2-de-fi-nft"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T01:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Web3 관련 자료도 한번 정리하고 가야겠다는 생각으로 정리하였습니다. 최근 2–3개월 업데이트가 안 되었지만, Web3 전반적인 흐름의 이해, 앞으로 할 일을 고민하는데 방해가 되지는 않을 것입니다. 일부는 #50호에 포함되었던 내용도 있습니다. — 허진호] [Web3 개념] Web3 입문 Crypto 101: A Primer - @nicoglennon The Curious Beginner's Guide to Crypto - by Peter Yang - Creator Economy by Peter Yang]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin Ho Hur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with Large Symbol Files]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/dealing-with-large-symbol-files</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/dealing-with-large-symbol-files"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large applications can produce very large symbol files when debug information
is enabled (especially at the higher, more verbose levels of debug info!). This
article describes some techniques for reducing debug symbol file sizes!
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reading and Understanding Profitability Metrics from Financial Statements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1448.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1448.php"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T23:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whoa! That has got to be the most serious-minded title I’ve ever written. Profitability Metrics from Financial Statements, indeed. I’m still writing Part 2 of my Supply Chain Games article, and I was about to mention something about whether a company is profitable, when I realized something that didn’t quite fit into the flow of things, so I thought I’d handle it...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 회의를 회의하라]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73705</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/29/npc_wfh/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_wfh"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T22:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 소개하는 글은 지난해 11월 8일에 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 썼던 글입니다. 코로나19 팬데믹 상황은 넉 달이 더 지난 지금도 여전히 녹록지 않지만, 언젠가는 올 ‘코로나 이후’를 준비하는 마음으로 업무 환경이 어떻게 바뀔지에 관한 논의를 살펴보겠습니다.   “위드 코로나”, 일상으로의 복귀 정책과 함께 일터에서의 삶 역시 점차 제자리로 돌아오고 있습니다. 재택근무가 “뉴노멀”이 되리라던 예측도 있었지만, 최근 한국의 한 설문조사에서는 응답자 60%가 이미 재택근무를 종료했다고 답했습니다. 같은 조사에서 재택근무에 대한 의견을 물었더니, 긍정적인 견해와 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Problems emerge for a unified /dev/*random]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889452/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889452/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T21:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-February, we reported on the plan to
unite the two kernel devices that provide random numbers;
/dev/urandom was to effectively just be another way to access the
random numbers provided by /dev/random.   That change made it as
far as the mainline during the Linux 5.18 merge window, but it was
quickly reverted when problems were found.  It may be possible to
do that unification someday, but, for now, there are environments that need
their random numbers early on—without entropy or the "Linus jitter dance"
being available on the platform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora 36 beta released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889602/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889602/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T19:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fedora
36 beta release has been announced.


	Fedora 36 Workstation Beta includes GNOME 42, the newest release of
	the GNOME desktop environment. GNOME 42 includes a global dark
	style UI setting. It also has a redesigned screenshot tool. And
	many core GNOME apps have been ported to the latest version of the
	GTK toolkit, providing improved performance and a modern look.


If all goes well, the final Fedora 36 release will happen at the end of April.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889571/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889571/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T13:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libdatetime-timezone-perl, pjproject, and tzdata), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, docker, graphicsmagick, and libtiff), Oracle (expat), Red Hat (expat, httpd:2.4, openssl, and screen), Scientific Linux (expat and openssl), and Ubuntu (libtasn1-6, linux-oem-5.14, openjdk-lts, and paramiko).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino goes pro with Linux and a big chip on its latest board]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9985</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/arduino-goes-pro/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Arduino launched the Pro Portenta X8, the most massively powered Arduino board yet, with a quad-core Arm Cortex A53 processor along with a variety of MCUs and the ability to run Linux. This is a big step for Arduino, which bills itself as an open-source hardware and software company that makes systems on […]
The post Arduino goes pro with Linux and a big chip on its latest board appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[장애인도 버스 타고 고향에 가고 싶어요 (ft. 대법원, 어림없는 소리!)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84958</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84958"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T08:52:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[장애인 등 교통약자들이 모든 교통수단, 여객시설 및 도로를 차별 없이 안전하고 편리하게 이용하여 이동할 수 있는 권리인 이동권은 생존의 기본이자, 인간으로서의 존엄과 가치 및 행복의 실현을 위한 수단이 되는 권리이기도 하다. 하지만 고속버스와 광역형 시내버스 등 시외버스에 저상버스나 휠체어 탑승 설비가 갖추어져 있지 않은 탓에 휠체어를 이용하는 장애인들은 시외로의 이동에 많은 제약을 받아야 했다. 이에 […]
The post 장애인도 버스 타고 고향에 가고 싶어요 (ft. 대법원, 어림없는 소리!) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선종합적 상상력]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222686109456</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222686109456"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T07:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<모든 (종합적) 단일성은 원초적이고 근원적인 다수성으로부터 구성된다. 일체의 동일성, 나의 동일성과 개인의 동일성까지 포함한 일체의 동일성은 (무수한) 동일화작용의 종합들을 거쳐서 이루어졌었고, 고정 불변하는 사물로 나타나는 것들은 우선 연속되고 연계되는, 일련의 유동하는 흔적들과 같은 다량의 흐름으로 주어졌었다.> 이렇게 주장하는데, 어떻게 이것을 알았을까? 다수성으로부터 단일성이 <추상>된 것이라는 주장이다. 그러나 단일성, 혹은 범주나 종류(kind)가 없다면, 그것들이 한 부류에 속하는 다수임을 어떻게 알 수 있겠는가? 모든 동일성도 동일화 작용을 통해 이루어졌다. 저기 사과가 있다. 이미 사과 하.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Develop a basic rate limiter with Quarkus and Redis]]></title>
        <id>656fa398-7964-48ba-8a53-83ba4df1b025</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/29/develop-basic-rate-limiter-quarkus-and-redis"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rate limiting is a popular technique to protect services from excessive demand. For example, you can use this strategy to limit how often a user can enter or reset their password. The example in this article builds rate limiting on a per-client basis into a Java-based service for a given time period. The application tracks requests from clients using a Redis in-memory data structure store and limits usage when a client's demand exceeds the quota.
Here is a broad overview of the implementation:
Boostrap the ratelimit Quarkus project and use the quarkus-redis-client extension to connect to a Redis server.
Create a basic rate limiter that allows users to send 15 greeting requests with the same message in 1 minute.
Test the rate limiter.
Set up a Redis instance using the Redis template in Deve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ana-Maria Mihalceanu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ standardization (core language) progress in 2021]]></title>
        <id>158d176a-ef10-475d-b296-15db643e1140</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/29/c-standardization-core-language-progress-2021"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers the highlights of the C++ standardization proposals before the International Organization for Standardization (ISO) committee's Core and Evolution Working Groups last year. Read on to find out what's coming in C++23.
Virtual ISO working group meetings
For most of 2020, meetings about the C++ standard were held virtually and treated by the attendees as tentative, mostly filling time until we could meet in person again. As in-person meetings continue to be pushed out further into the future, and we've gotten more comfortable with the online format, we've gotten a lot more done in virtual meetings.
Now, instead of doing most of our business during the in-person meetings three times a year, the different working groups frequently meet throughout the year, some weekly, some …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Merrill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interface method calls with the Go register ABI]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/interface-method-calls-with-the-go-register-abi/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/interface-method-calls-with-the-go-register-abi/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T03:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This post takes a deeper look into how Go compiles method invocations;
specifically, how it compiles <em>interface</em> method invocations. Many online
descriptions of this process are outdated, because the Go compiler has switched
to a new, <a class="reference external" href="https://go.dev/s/regabi">register-based ABI</a> in
the <a class="reference external" href="https://go.dev/doc/go1.17">1.17 release</a> for AMD64. Go 1.18 enabled
the …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some nftables security vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889502/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889502/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T23:33:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A
new set of vulnerabilities has been disclosed in the nftables
subsystem; these lead fairly easily to a local system compromise, on some
configurations at least.  Fixes for these vulnerabilities were present in
the March 28 stable updates; upgrading
seems like a good idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 식곤증에 관하여]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73688</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/28/npc_tiredaftereating/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_tiredaftereating"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T22:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[언제부터인지 무언가를 먹고 나면 확실히 피곤하고 졸음이 오기 시작했습니다. 식곤증이라고 하지요. 물론 노화는 누구에게나 찾아오는 것이고, 이 순간에도 계속 진행되고 있는 것이니 어느 정도는 받아들여야겠지요. 그래도 이 증상에 조금이라도 대처할 방법이 있을까 해서 인터넷을 찾아보았습니다. 그리고 미국의 의학전문 사이트인 헬스라인에 지난 2020년 3월에 올라온 “음식을 먹고 나면 피곤한 이유”라는 기사를 발견했습니다. 기사는 먼저 음식을 먹고 나면 약간의 졸음이 오는 것은 지극히 정상이라고 이야기합니다. 다행이네요. 그리고 졸음을 유발할 수 있는 음식이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transitional Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-legacy-displacement/transitional-architecture.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-legacy-displacement/transitional-architecture.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T18:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The core to a successful legacy displacement is the gradual
        replacement of legacy with new software, as this allows benefits to
        delivered early and circumvents the risks of a Big Bang. During
        displacement the legacy and new system will have to operate
        simultaneously allowing behavior to be split between old and new.
        
Ian Cartwright, Rob Horn, and James Lewis explain
        how to build and
        evolve a Transitional Architecture that supports this collaboration as it
        changes over time. For this to work, intermediate configurations may require integrations
        that have no place in the target architecture of the new system.
Or to put this more directly - you will have to invest in work that
        will be thrown away. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How an Android developer in Guatemala advocates for women through the Google Developer Groups community]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/how-android-developer-in-guatemala.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/how-android-developer-in-guatemala.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:03:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rodrigo Akira Hirooka, Regional Lead, Latin America
 
  
Getting acquainted with Android career options 
  
Cecilia Castillo loves mobile development. She’s confident that she’d be happy focusing on it for the rest of her career. Cecilia’s career in mobile development began when her friend Adrian Catalan (Director of the Innovation Lab at Galileo University), launched a Google Developer Groups (GDG) chapter in Guatemala and began to teach Android courses.  
Up until that point, Cecilia had used technologies like ASPX and Ruby on Rails – and was no stranger to technical concepts, having studied computer science at Galileo University in Guatemala and earned a Master’s degree in information technology, but she was also itching to learn something new in a supportive environment. That…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Pointer tagging for x86 systems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888914/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888914/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T16:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pointers are a fact of life for developers working in numerous languages.
It is often convenient to be able to associate a small 
amount — a few bits at most — of ancillary information with a pointer.
This can often be done within the pointer value itself with some careful
masking and shifting.  CPU manufacturers have been adding ways to support
the addition of this sort of "tag" to pointers; the most recent may be
AMD's "upper address ignore" (UAI) feature, support for which was
recently posted
by Bharata B Rao.  This feature has an uncertain future in Linux, though,
as the result of a fundamental design decision.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RISC-V is coming to the internet of things]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9983</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/risc-v-is-coming-to-the-internet-of-things/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T15:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fans of this newsletter know I’m a major chip nerd. I started my tech career as a semiconductor reporter, and for the last seven or eight years I’ve been closely watching RISC-V, an open source chip architecture. The RISC-V architecture, which was developed a decade ago at UC Berkeley, competes with both that of Arm […]
The post RISC-V is coming to the internet of things appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debian decides to allow secret votes]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889444/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889444/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T15:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Debian project has been voting on a general
resolution that would allow secret voting on future issues.  The results have
been posted in unofficial form, and the winner was "proposal B": "Hide identities of
Developers casting a particular vote and allow verification".  One might
think that closes the discussion, but Debian project leader candidate Felix
Lechner is questioning
the election and calling for it to be redone — something that the
Debian constitution lacks provisions for.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889435/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889435/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T14:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of new stable kernels: 5.17.1, 5.16.18, 5.15.32, 5.10.109, 5.4.188, 4.19.237, 4.14.274, and 4.9.309.  They contain a relatively small set
of important fixes throughout the three; users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889423/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889423/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T14:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and faad2), Fedora (dotnet3.1, libass, linux-firmware, python-paramiko, seamonkey, and xen), openSUSE (perl-DBD-SQLite and wavpack), Slackware (seamonkey), SUSE (perl-DBD-SQLite and wavpack), and Ubuntu (binutils, python2.7, python3.4, python3.5, python3.6, python3.8, and smarty3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[솔로몬 성전의 파괴와 복구와 파괴: 메시아 사상의 탄생 과정]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84929</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84929"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T09:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BC 1,000년 예루살렘, 솔로몬왕은 야훼에게 제사를 지내는 ‘솔로몬의 성전’을 건설한다. (지난 글 참조) 솔로몬 성전의 파괴  그런데 BC 597년 바빌로니아의 네부카드네자르 2세(나부쿠두리우추르; 느브갓네살)가 메소포타미아를 통일한 뒤 레반트 지역까지 밀고 들어와 유대 왕국도 멸망시킨다. 그 당시 이집트 제국의 영향력 아래 명맥을 유지하고 있던 유대 왕국은 바빌로니아에 맞서 끝까지 항전하다가 패배하고 만다. 그들이 소중히 여기던 솔로몬의 […]
The post 솔로몬 성전의 파괴와 복구와 파괴: 메시아 사상의 탄생 과정 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Total Compute solutions for the XR market]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:7c86a3c0-fb82-479c-a024-fda795d1fd9c</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/total-compute-solutions-for-xr-wearable-devices"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog introduces the different Arm Total Compute solutions for wearable devices in the XR market, like VR headsets and AR smartglasses.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philippe Bressy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build your first Java serverless function using a Quarkus quick start]]></title>
        <id>a19dbd9f-c966-494c-ac11-fea08cfb8087</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/28/build-your-first-java-serverless-function-using-quarkus-quick-start"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you looking for the shortest path or cheatsheet to bring your Java application into a serverless platform based on Kubernetes? Perhaps you don't have enough time to stand up relevant infrastructure and configure settings for both the application and the platform. This article is a guide to developing Java serverless functions using a Quarkus quick start in the Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift. As you'll see, using quick starts in the Developer Sandbox lets you focus on the application development without needing to configure Knative.
The Developer Sandbox provides a shared, multi-tenant Red Hat OpenShift 4 cluster with a cloud IDE tool called Red Hat CodeReady Workspaces. All you need is a free account on Red Hat to get access for a limited time to a sandbox. Following the four …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Oh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify secure connections to PostgreSQL databases with Node.js]]></title>
        <id>f045aeec-19ed-4a10-a365-a0fcbfed01d6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/28/simplify-secure-connections-postgresql-databases-nodejs"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL is an advanced open source relational database that is commonly used by applications to store structured data. Before accessing a database, the application must connect and provide security credentials. As a Node.js developer, how can you safely share and provide those credentials in JavaScript code without a lot of work? This article introduces service bindings and the kube-service-bindings package, along with a convenient graphical interface in Red Hat OpenShift.
When using a database, the four basic operations are create, read, update, and delete (CRUD, for short). Our team maintains an example CRUD application on GitHub that shows how to connect to a PostgreSQL database and execute the four basic operations. We use that example to illustrate the security model in this articl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 Ranges The Key Advantage - Algorithm Composition]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/ranges-composition/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/ranges-composition/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conceptually a Range is a simple concept: it’s just a pair of two iterators - to the beginning and to the end of a sequence (or a sentinel in some cases). Yet, such an abstraction can radically change the way you write algorithms. In this blog post, I’ll show you a key change that you get with C++20 Ranges.
By having this one layer of abstraction on iterators, we can express more ideas and have different computation models.



     
    


Let’s look at a simple example in “regular” STL C++.
It starts from a list of numbers, selects even numbers, skips the first one and then prints them in the reverse order:
#include <algorithm>
#include <vector>
#include <iostream>

int main() {
    const std::vector numbers = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10};

    auto even = [](int i) { return 0 == i % 2…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이기심과 업감연기설(業感緣起說)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222684755974</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222684755974"/>
        <updated>2022-03-27T23:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<그것이 말한다>에 대한 라캉의 주장은 불교에서 말하는 업감연기설의 주장과 유사하다. 즉 인간이란 존재는 이기적 존재이며, 소유적 욕망의 존재라는 것이다. 이 엄연한 사실을 무시하는 것이 바로 당위의 철학, 즉 마르크스주의, 주자학, 토미즘과 같은 철학적 경향이다. 이런 철학은 겉보기에는 이기적 철학이 아닌 것처럼 보여도 사실은 다 이기심과 소유심에 뿌리박고 있는 철학이다. 우리가 이기적 존재이며 소유적 존재라는 엄연한 사실을 무시하기 때문에, 이러한 철학은 모두 낭만적이며 헛된 철학에 지나지 않는다. 오히려 진정한 철학은 우리의 자연적 본능이 아니라 자연적 본성에 주목해야만 한다. 이런 김형효의 주장에 대.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 귀신을 보게 되는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73668</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/27/npc_ghosts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_ghosts"/>
        <updated>2022-03-27T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[할로윈 데이가 지난 뒤 11월 초에 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 썼던 글입니다.   세상의 많은 일은 여러가지 요인이 복합적으로 작용한 결과이며, 따라서 어떤 현상의 원인을 딱 하나만 꼽기는 쉽지 않습니다. 우리 마음과 관련된 현상이라면 더 그럴 것입니다. 그리고 그 마음이 조금 이상한 상태라면 더욱더 그렇겠지요. 사람들은 귀신을 봅니다. 아마 인류의 조상이 언어를 사용하고 자연 현상의 이유를 생각하기 시작한 이래 사람들은 우리가 알 수 없는 현상을 설명할 수 있는 좋은 해답으로 귀신을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing a two-axis robot arm controller without an MCU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474123</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/implementing-a-two-axis-robot-arm-controller-without-an-mcu/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-27T22:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The circuit is designed without an MCU, using instead the GreenPAK SLG46620 chip, two Tower Pro SG90 servo motors, and an analog joystick. Robot arms...
The post Implementing a two-axis robot arm controller without an MCU appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anas Ajaj</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[재미로 만들어보는 게임 매크로 with python]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/12118970</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/12118970"/>
        <updated>2022-03-27T14:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[얼마 전 넥슨의 김정주 창업자께서 별세하셨다. (고인의 명복을 빕니다..)
내 나이 또래라면 넥슨 게임을 안 해본 사람이 없을 것이다.
흔히 클래식 RPG의 대명사라고 알려진 바람의 나라부터 시작해서, 중학교 때쯤엔 크레이지 아케이드, 메이플 스토리 등이 유행이었다. 나는 특히 E로 시작하는 어떤 게임을 초등학교 6학년 때부터 즐겨했는데, 이 게임은 특이하게 휴식기는 있을지언정 완전한 탈퇴를 하기 힘들다. 현재 접속자의 대다수는 아마 지금 30대 후반 정도 됐을 것이다. 이 게임이 무엇인지는 굳이 공개하지 않으려 한다. 왜냐하면 이번 글에서는 매크로 프로그램을 다룰 것이기 때문이다. 
참고로 넥슨에서는 불법 개조 프로그램에 대해 강경한 입장을 취하고 있으며 최근 법원 판결에 대한 공지도 있었다. 

안녕하세요. 넥슨 고객 여러분. 게임 클라이언트를 무단으로 변조/배포하는 사설서버 운영 행위는 명백한 불법 행위로 저작권을 침해하는 사설서버 운영에 대한 2021년 11월 법원의 판결 사례를 안내드립니다. 
앞으로 불법 사설서버를 비롯한 저작권 침해 행위를 근절하고자, 아래와 같은 법적 대응을 포함하여 더욱 강경하고 단호하게 대처해 나갈 것을 약속드립니다. 
[불법 사설서버 법적 대응 조치 안내]
- 2019년 주요 A 사설서버 운영자 검거 완료 후 저작권 침해 법적 대응 시작
- 2021년 11월 해당 사설서버 운영자 대상으로 승소 판결 (4.5억원 손해배상 지급 판결)
위처럼 공식 클라이언트를 허가 없이 변조/배포하는 행위는 명백한 저작권 침해 행위이며, 불법 사설서버 게임을 다운로드하고, 이를 이용하거나 홍보…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시간과 공간은 주관적인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222683995627</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222683995627"/>
        <updated>2022-03-26T22:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[칸트가 공간이나 시간에 대해서 <주관적>이라고 말하고 있다. 다음은 공간이 주관적이라는 칸트의 언명이다. <어떻게 대상들 자신보다 선행하며, 거기에서 대상들의 개념이 선험적으로 규정될 수 있는, 외적 직관이 마음에 자리 잡을 수 있는가? 그것은 외적 직관이 주관 안에서, 대상들에 의해 촉발되고 그럼으로써 대상들에 대한 직접적 표상, 즉 직관을 얻는 그런 <주관의 형식적 성질>로서, 그 자리를 갖는 한에서 이다. 그러므로 오직 외감 일반의 형식으로서 이다.> <공간은 대상들 자체에 부착해 있어서 사람들이 <직관의 모든 주관적 조건>들을 추상해 버려도 남는, 그런 사물들 자체의 규정이 아니다.> &.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding software-defined-radios and -networks in 5G architectures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474105</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/understanding-software-defined-radios-and-networks-in-5g-architectures/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-26T19:33:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SDRs and SDNs provide fundamental tools to enable unique 5G features, such as network slicing and DSS. The world of wireless communication is about to...
The post Understanding software-defined-radios and -networks in 5G architectures appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaue Morcelles and Brendon McHugh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Level locks or the Level Keypad work with Apple Home Key?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9969</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/do-level-locks-or-the-level-keypad-work-with-apple-home-key/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-26T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Billy called in with a HomeKit question. He has a Level Bolt lock and is interested in the recently released Level Keypad. Billy wants to know if the Level Keypad might be able to use Apple’s Home Key technology that locks or unlocks by putting an Apple Watch or […]
The post Do Level locks or the Level Keypad work with Apple Home Key? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8-2 칸트 사유는 주관주의인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222683459528</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222683459528"/>
        <updated>2022-03-26T04:53:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이미 말한 것처럼 8장과 9장에서 모종삼은 우리 지식을 해명하는 칸트의 철학이 주관주의인지, 아닌지 문제 삼고 있다. 그에 의하면, 이 문제는 매우 중요하고, 또한 이해하기 어려운 문제이다. 이렇기 때문에 그런지, 주관주의가 아니라고 명확하게 이야기하지 않고 있다. <하나의 현상이 시간과 공간 내에 펼쳐져 있으면 바로 객관성과 실재성을 갖는다. 시간, 공간은 주관적 형식이고, 그들은 주관적 표상으로 하여금 초보적으로 객관화하게 한다. 두 번째 단계에서는 범주에 의지하여 결정하는데, 이것이 바로 두 번째 단계의 객관화이다. 여기에 이르러서 충분한 객관화가 완성되는 것이다. 칸트의 사고 흐름은 대체로 이와 같다. 외재세.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making the case for intelligent displays and edge visualization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474065</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/making-the-case-for-intelligent-displays-and-edge-visualization/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T18:54:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Human machine interfaces, or HMIs, increasingly have to present a visualization of data and decisions made by edge artificial intelligence devices and products. The solution is more intelligent displays, according to ADLINK Technology and AUO.
The post Making the case for intelligent displays and edge visualization appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for March 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9979</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-march-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T18:02:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why isn’t 5G happening in factories yet? This week on the podcast, Kevin asked why we have seen so much hype but so few deployments around 5G for manufacturing. I blamed it on the fact that Release 17 of the 3GPP standard was just finalized, so we can finally get network equipment and end devices to the market […]
The post IoT news of the week for March 25, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] 5.18 Merge window, part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888736/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888736/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T14:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of this writing, 4,127 non-merge changesets have found their way into
the mainline repository for the 5.18 development cycle.  That may seem like
a relatively slow start to the merge window, but there are a lot of changes
packed into those commits.  Read on for a summary of the most
significant changes to land in the first half of the 5.18 merge window.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889265/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889265/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T14:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (tiff), Fedora (nicotine+ and openvpn), openSUSE (bind, libarchive, python3, and slirp4netns), Oracle (cyrus-sasl, httpd, httpd:2.4, and openssl), Red Hat (httpd and httpd:2.4), Scientific Linux (httpd), SUSE (bind, libarchive, python3, and slirp4netns), and Ubuntu (firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter: Distributed Compliance Ledger (DCL)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/4013c2376e7</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-distributed-compliance-ledger-dcl-4013c2376e7?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T04:30:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #8]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shu Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[로티의 반표상주의와 선험론적 관념론]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222682443062</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222682443062"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T01:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[로티에 의하면, 정확한 표상, 실재에 대한 올바른 표상이라는 개념이 그렇게 쓸모가 있는 개념이 아니다. 그것은 우리가 언어, 마음, 사회적 실행 바깥으로 나갈 수 없기 때문이다. 따라서 우리 언어, 마음, 사회적 실행과 정확하게 대응되고 표상되는 실재라는 개념 자체가 공허한 개념이다. 그런데 이러한 로티의 주장, 또는 반표상주의는 언어적 모습을 지닌 선험론적 관념론이 아닌가? 즉 반표상주의는 대상이 주체나 언어에 의존한다는 주장이 아닌가? 로티는 그렇지 않다고 주장한다. 즉 반표상주의는 일종의 언어적 모습의 선험론적 관념론이 아니다. 버나드 윌리엄스는 반표상주의가 바로 관념론처럼 언어와 실재, 문장과 사실의 구분을.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 6년 만에 사형 집행한 미국 오클라호마주]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73662</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/24/npc_deathpenalty/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_deathpenalty"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T22:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 10월 28일, 미국 오클라호마주에서 6년 만에 사형이 집행되었습니다. 오클라호마주는 사형 제도를 시행하고 있는 미국의 27개 주 가운데서도 사형 건수가 가장 많은 지역 가운데 하나였으나, 2014년과 2015년 사이 약물주사형 집행 과정에서 여러 차례 사고가 발생해 집행이 일시 유예된 상태였습니다. 앞서 27일 미국 대법원은 5:3으로 유예 중지 판결을 내렸고, 오클라호마주는 바로 다음날 사형수 존 그랜트에 대한 사형을 집행했습니다. 그랜트는 무장강도죄로 130년형을 선고받고 수감 생활을 하다가 교도소 식당 직원을 살해한 죄로 사형을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horn: Racing against the clock]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889183/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889183/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T22:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jann Horn describes
in great detail the process he went through to exploit a tiny race
window in the kernel.


	Luckily for us, the race window contains the first few memory
	accesses to the struct file; therefore, by making sure that the
	struct file is not present in the fastest CPU caches, we can widen
	the race window by as much time as the memory accesses take. The
	standard way to do this is to use an eviction pattern / eviction
	set; but instead we can also make the cache line dirty on another
	core.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ekstrand:  How to write a Vulkan driver in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889176/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889176/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T21:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Collabora blog, Jason Ekstrand has a detailed look at writing a Vulkan graphics driver in today's world. "Not only has Vulkan grown, but Mesa has as well, and we've built up quite a suite of utilities and helpers for making writing Vulkan drivers easier."  The blog post takes the form of a tutorial of sorts, though the end result is not a functioning Vulkan driver,  the framework of one is shown.

At the time we were developing ANV (the Intel Vulkan driver), the Vulkan spec itself was still under development and everything was constantly in flux. There were no best practices; there were barely even tools. Everyone working on Vulkan was making it up as they went because it was a totally new API. Most of the code we wrote was purpose-built for the Intel driver because there were no other Mesa drivers to share code. (Except for the short-lived LunarG Intel driver based in ilo, which we were replacing.) If we had tried to build abstractions, they could have gotten shot to pieces at any moment by a spec change. (We rewrote the descriptor set layout code from scratch at least five or six times before the driver ever shipped.) It was frustrating, exhausting, and a whole lot of fun.

These days, however, the Vulkan spec has been stable and shipping for six years, the tooling and testing situation is pretty solid, and there are six Vulkan drivers in the Mesa tree with more on the way. We've also built up a lot of common infrastructure. This is important both because it makes writing a Vulkan driver easier and because it lets us fix certain classes of annoying bugs in a common place instead of everyone copying and pasting those bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for errors in the C# code of the Eto.Forms GUI framework]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0929/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0929/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GUI frameworks are becoming increasingly popular: new ones appear, and old ones get a new life. At PVS-Studio, we are watching this trend very closely. Today we'll examine suspicious code fragments in one of C# frameworks — Eto.Forms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Racing against the clock -- hitting a tiny kernel race window]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/03/racing-against-clock-hitting-tiny.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/03/racing-against-clock-hitting-tiny.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T20:51:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.lst-kix_oh8g77k3z2ge-8>li:before{content:"\0025a0  "}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-2.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_94mysn7p9quk-2 0}.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-5>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_94mysn7p9quk-5}.lst-kix_oh8g77k3z2ge-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf  "}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-7{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-6{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_oh8g77k3z2ge-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb  "}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-8{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_oh8g77k3z2ge-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb  "}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-3{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-2{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-5{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-4{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_oh8g77k3z2ge-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0  "}ol.lst-kix_94mysn7p9quk-1{list-style-type:none}ol.lst-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm adds smart camera SoC targeting surveillance in smart cities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474057</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/qualcomm-adds-smart-camera-soc-targeting-surveillance-in-smart-cities/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T18:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Qualcomm QCS7230 processor is aimed at enterprise security and public safety, using connected intelligent edge cameras.
The post Qualcomm adds smart camera SoC targeting surveillance in smart cities appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ternary Operator Revisited]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14051</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/the-ternary-operator-revisited/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:02:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago, I wrote a blog post entitled Ternary Operator vs. if/else, which was supposed to be an interesting comparison between the two, except that I totally botched it! The premise is that the ternary operator and if/else statements should compile into identical, so why not just use if/else statements to make the code … Continue reading The Ternary Operator Revisited
The Ternary Operator Revisited first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A way out for a.out]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888741/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888741/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T15:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The a.out executable
format dates back to the earliest days of Linux — and before.  It has
not been used in any serious way for decades, but support still exists in
the Linux kernel and has resisted all attempts at its removal.  Back in
January, Borislav Petkov tried yet
again to delete support for this format, leading to another extended
discussion.  There is one difference this time around, though: the effort
to get rid of a.out support might just succeed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Online Conference 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.state-machine.com/?p=14715</id>
        <link href="https://www.state-machine.com/embedded-online-conference-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T15:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Embedded Online Conference has emerged as the one of the most important learning events for embedded software in the U.S. This year, Quantum Leaps’ Miro Samek will present again. This year, the subject is: NOTE: You can use the promo code QL to save $100 on the conference registration fee. Testing of Event-Driven Embedded […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quantum Leaps</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889120/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889120/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T14:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (php-twig), Mageia (abcm2ps, libpano13, and pesign), openSUSE (nextcloud and xen), Oracle (kernel, kernel-container, and openssl), SUSE (java-1_7_1-ibm and xen), and Ubuntu (linux-oem-5.14, openvpn, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Speed queens and Matter dreams]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9974</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-speed-queens-and-matter-dreams/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A week after the CSA said that the Matter smart home interoperability standard would be delayed we get a chance to talk about why the standard is delayed until fall, and what it means for consumers and smart home device makers. We then share Omdia data on how much ownership of different smart home devices […]
The post Podcast: Speed queens and Matter dreams appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10.4 and 3.9.12 are now available out of schedule]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/03/python-3104-and-3912-are-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/03/python-3104-and-3912-are-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T12:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did anybody say cursed releases?
 Well, it turns out that 3.10.3 and 3.9.11 both shipped a regression 
which caused those versions not to build on Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6. 
While this 11-year-old version is now out of maintenance support, it’s still used in production workloads. Some of those rely on Python 3.9 and/or 3.10. In particular, our own manylinux2010 image used to build widely compatible Linux wheels is based on CentOS 6. (Don’t worry, we do have newer manylinux* variants, see PEP 599 and PEP 600 for details.)

Due to the out-of-schedule release, the respective versions released 
today contain a very limited set of changes. Python 3.9.12 only contains
 12 other bug fixes on top of 3.9.11. Python 3.10.4 only contains 10 
other bug fixes on top of 3.10.3.

Get 3.10.4 here: Python Release Python 3.10.4 | Python.org

Get 3.9.12 here: Python Release Python 3.9.12 | Python.org

Hopefully, the third time’s a charm and we’ll return no sooner than 
May with the regularly scheduled bug fix releases of 3.9 and 3.10.


We hope you enjoy the new releases

Your friendly release team,

Łukasz Langa @ambv

Pablo Galindo Salgado @pablogsal

Ned Deily @nad

Steve Dower @steve.dower]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조선일보의 분열증: (집무실 이전) 도와주는 게 도리 v. 엄청난 시행착오]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84916</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84916"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T08:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 당선자의 대통령 집무실 이전 계획을 두고 청와대와 윤 당선자 측 입장 차이는 여전합니다. 청와대는 3월 21일 촉박한 일정과 안보 공백을 우려하며 용산 이전은 무리라는 의견을 냈고, 윤 당선자 측은 유감을 표하며 취임 뒤 통의동 집무실과 청와대 지하벙커를 활용해 대통령 직무를 수행하겠다고 밝혔습니다. 조선일보는 3월 22일 청와대의 반대 입장을 비난하는 사설을 실었는데요. 하지만 이번 사설은 […]
The post 조선일보의 분열증: (집무실 이전) 도와주는 게 도리 v. 엄청난 시행착오 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부자처럼 살면 부자 됩니까? 돈 벌어야 부자 됩니다!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84904</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84904"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T07:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[부자처럼 살면 부자가 되는 게 아니라, 돈을 벌어야 부자가 된다. 브랜드를 만들어야 잘 팔리는 게 아니라, 많이 팔면 브랜드가 된다.   이제 막 창업을 시작한 분들을 대상으로 강의를 하다 보면 아래와 같은 질문을 제일 많이 합니다. “어떻게 하면 내 제품을 알릴 수 있을까요?” 그러고는 보통 아래와 같은 대화가 오고 갑니다. = 왜 알리려고 하죠?  […]
The post 부자처럼 살면 부자 됩니까? 돈 벌어야 부자 됩니다! first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이상훈</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Developer roundup: Best of March 2022]]></title>
        <id>6a2bad30-cb7f-432d-9c3a-88c8e666c6b7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/24/red-hat-developer-roundup-best-march-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our monthly recap of the articles we published in March 2022! This month, Red Hat Developer readers flocked to articles to help them write code on the platforms they trust. You can learn more about modular Perl in Red Hat Enterprise 8, get into the details of testing and code coverage in the Node.js reference architecture, or dive deeper into Quarkus in the latest installment of our Quarkus from the ground up series.
And there's much more as well! Read on for the March highlights.
Note: See the end of this article for the full lineup published in March 2022.
Podman and container development
Are you a .NET user interested in rolling out containerized applications with Podman? Another one of our most popular articles of the month explains how to control Podman from .NET. .NET user…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Red Hat Developer Editorial Team</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 24, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888223/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888223/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T01:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 24, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 플랫폼 경제 독점 기업의 초상화: 아마존 검색결과]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73633</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/23/npc_amazonmarketplace/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_amazonmarketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T22:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[팟캐스트 아메리카노 지난 시즌에서는 우리나라 공정거래위원회에 해당하는 미국 연방거래위원회(FTC, Federal Trade Commission)의 리나 칸(Lina Khan) 위원장이 쓴 논문 “아마존의 반독점 역설(Amazon’s Antitrust Paradox)”을 같이 읽었습니다. 리나 칸 위원장이 지적한 플랫폼 기업의 이해관계 충돌에 관해 대표적인 사례를 마크업이 자세히 분석해 쓴 기사를 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 요약, 소개한 글입니다.   칸 위원장은 예일 법학대학원을 졸업하기 전, 28살에 쓴 논문에서 보여준 통찰을 바탕으로 미국 반독점 규제를 총괄하는 기관장으로 발탁됐습니다. 논문의 핵심은 플랫폼 경제에서는 플랫폼 사업자에게 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A method for replacing Python tuple entries]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888945/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888945/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T21:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent discussion on the python-ideas mailing list gives some insight
into how to—or how not to—propose a feature to be added to the language.  At first
blush, adding a method to Python's immutable tuple
type for replacing one of its elements is not a particularly strange idea,
nor one that would cause much in the way of backward-compatibility
concerns.  Even though there was some evidence offered that such a method might be
useful, it seems pretty unlikely that the idea will go anywhere, at least
in part because of the repetitive, bordering on aggressive, manner in which its
benefits were argued.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android GDE Zarah Dominguez believes in the power of technology to help others]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/android-gde-zarah-dominguez-believes-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/android-gde-zarah-dominguez-believes-in.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T17:00:00.030Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by The Google Developers Team
        
For Women’s History Month, we’re celebrating a few of our Google Developer Experts. Meet Zarah Dominguez, Android GDE. The GDE program team encourages qualified candidates that identify as women or non-binary to express interest in joining the community by completing this form.
 
Zarah Dominguez started Android development in 2009 and hasn’t looked back. “When I first discovered Android, I thought it was super cool seeing what I have coded come to life on a device within just a few clicks,” she says.  
Learning Android on her own, Zarah began documenting what she learned, to remember it herself and to help others. “Sometimes, I'd see answers on StackOverflow that said, ‘It's simple,’ or ‘It's straightforward,’ but it wasn't simple or straightfo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME 42 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/889025/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/889025/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T16:10:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 42 of the GNOME desktop environment is out.


	This release introduces Dark mode and an entirely new screenshot
	workflow. Beyond that, there are several improved Settings panels,
	many of the GNOME applications have been ported to GTK 4 and
	libadwaita, and much more.


See the release notes for more
information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888999/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888999/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.16.17,
5.15.31,
5.10.108,
5.4.187,
4.19.236,
4.14.273, and
4.9.308
stable kernels have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888994/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888994/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (cyrus-sasl, openssl, sphinx, and swtpm), openSUSE (qemu), Red Hat (expat, rh-mariadb103-mariadb, and rh-mariadb105-mariadb), SUSE (apache2, binutils, java-1_7_0-ibm, kernel-firmware, nodejs12, qemu, and xen), and Ubuntu (ckeditor and linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data50: The World’s Top Data Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=4859</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/data50/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a decade after the idea of “big data” was first born, data continues to be one of the most important and furiously growing innovation drivers across both large enterprises and new startups. From providing pulse checks that are foundational to business operations to intelligently automating daily tasks through machine learning, data has become the... Read More
The post Data50: The World’s Top Data Startups appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jennifer Li, Sarah Wang and Jamie Sullivan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving high-performance computing from the server room to the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474050</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/moving-high-performance-computing-from-the-server-room-to-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T12:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The integration of Intel Xeon D processors on COM-HPC Server-on-Modules allows edge server installations to break free from the tight thermal constraints of air-conditioned server...
The post Moving high-performance computing from the server room to the edge appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Demers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Settling into the new norm for an embedded engineering workforce]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474039</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/settling-into-the-new-norm-for-an-embedded-engineering-workforce/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T11:59:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid working practices will be adopted to keep the workforce happy and this is likely to continue. Working from home (WFH) trends fuelled by the...
The post Settling into the new norm for an embedded engineering workforce appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard McCullagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eero’s new Wi-Fi routers take advantage of new spectrum]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9953</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/eero-pro-6e-review/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T11:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been spending a few days testing Eero’s latest Pro 6E Wi-Fi system and I can tell you I see a significant speed increase over my existing Eero Pro 6 routers. Eero, which is owned by Amazon, has also released a system of mesh routers called Eero 6+ which is cheaper, but I didn’t review […]
The post Eero’s new Wi-Fi routers take advantage of new spectrum appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마리 맥긴의 비트겐슈타인 자연주의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222681020398</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222681020398"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T10:22:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인의 자연주의를 주장하는 학자들은 거의 다 비트겐슈타인의 자연주의가 과학적, 환원적 자연주의가 아니라는 것에 일치하고 있다. 비트겐슈타인의 자연주의는 이미 스트로슨이 지적한 것처럼 ‘딱딱한 자연주의’, 즉 ‘경성 자연주의’가 아니다. 마리 맥긴은 후기 비트겐슈타인의 자연주의와 맥도웰의 해방적(liberal) 혹은 개방적 자연주의를 비교하면서 비트겐슈타인의 자연주의에 대해서 다음처럼 말한다. (가) 우리의 개념적 탐구는 언어를 추상적으로 바라 보아서는 안 된다. 우리의 언어는 우리 인간 삶에 자연적으로 뿌리박고 있다. 따라서 우리는 그것이 언제 작동하는지, 어디에서 모든 것이 다 드러나 있는지 바라 보아야.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to build, train, and run a PyTorch model]]></title>
        <id>d603f47c-465a-4b9b-8858-ca5cba433b90</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/23/learn-how-build-train-and-run-pytorch-model"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We hope you have enjoyed the first four Red Hat OpenShift Data Science learning paths:
Launch Red Hat OpenShift Data Science
Red Hat OpenShift Data Science resources
How to access, download and analyze data for S3
How to create a TensorFlow model
To complement these resources, we have released a new data science learning path that will guide you through developing a PyTorch model that will be used to predict the onset of diabetes. This article describes the PyTorch learning path and provides an overview of OpenShift Data Science.
Note: Visit the OpenShift Data Science page to see our complete library of learning paths and other resources for developers and data scientists collaborating on intelligent applications.
Build, train, and run a PyTorch model
In How to create a PyTorch model, you …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Audrey Reznik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use Valgrind Memcheck with a custom memory manager]]></title>
        <id>963cde56-ac0e-46f8-9935-a2f1bab8fe8c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/23/use-valgrind-memcheck-custom-memory-manager"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Valgrind is an instrumentation framework for building dynamic analysis tools that check C and C++ programs for errors. Memcheck is the default tool Valgrind uses when you don't ask it for another tool. Valgrind Memcheck can detect various memory leaks and keep track of whether memory is accessible and defined. But what if you have built your own memory manager? Memcheck keeps track of memory by observing the standard malloc/free, new/delete, and mmap/munmap system calls. But Memcheck doesn't know how a program subdivides that memory internally without a little help, and this article will show you how to provide that help through specialized code annotations.
Replacing malloc
If you simply replace the whole GNU C malloc implementation by defining your own functions with the same names (for …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Wielaard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quarkus Superheroes: Managed services save the day]]></title>
        <id>fc4ac9e3-f97b-4a22-b32d-bb1728224dcc</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/23/quarkus-superheroes-managed-services-save-day"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a developer building microservices? Do you struggle with developing and testing individual microservices that are part of a more extensive system? Would you rather focus on your applications and let something else manage the services they require?
This article introduces the Quarkus Superheroes sample application, shows how to deploy it to the free Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift, and then illustrates how Java developers can modify the application to replace the backing services with fully managed services provided by Red Hat OpenShift Application Services. The article might seem long, but running the steps should take only 15 to 20 minutes. There are many screenshots to help guide you on your way.
Prerequisites
Here's what you will need if you want to follow along with the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Deandrea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마돈나 망언 2년 그리고 K-방역의 처참한 현실]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84886</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84886"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T06:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“그것은 엄청난 평등자입니다.” “It’s the great equalizer.” “그것은 당신이 부자인지, 당신이 얼마나 유명한지, 당신이 얼마나 똑똑한지, 당신이 어디에 사는지, 당신이 얼마나 나이를 먹었는지, 당신이 얼마나 놀라운 이야기를 말할 수 있는지 신경 쓰지 않습니다.” 2년 전쯤(2020. 3. 22.) 마돈나는 꽃잎이 흩뿌려진 고급 욕조에서 여유 있게 목욕하는 모습을 자신의 SNS에 올리며 코로나19에 관해 이렇게 썼습니다. 많은 이들이 […]
The post 마돈나 망언 2년 그리고 K-방역의 처참한 현실 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reconciling the grid and EV charging infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474092</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/reconciling-the-grid-and-ev-charging-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T05:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic charging is one of the methods that can increase the availability of charging infrastructure while also protecting the grid. The world is moving toward...
The post Reconciling the grid and EV charging infrastructure appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stefano Lovati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Three candidates vying for Debian project leader]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888752/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888752/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T23:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three candidates have thrown their hat into the ring as candidates for the
2022 Debian project
leader (DPL) election.  One is Jonathan Carter, who is now in his
second term as DPL, while the other two are Felix Lechner and Hideki
Yamane.  As is the norm, the candidates self-nominated during the
nomination period and are now in the campaigning phase until April 1.
The vote commences April 2 and runs for two weeks; the results will be
announced shortly thereafter and the new DPL term will start on
April 21.  The candidates have put out platforms and are fielding
questions from the voters, Debian developers, thus it seems like a good
time to look in on the election.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 콜린 파월이 남긴 것]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73591</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/22/npc_colinpowell/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_colinpowell"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T22:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[콜린 파월 전 미국 국무부 장관이 숨진 뒤 부고 기사들의 내용을 종합해 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 지난 10월 27일에 쓴 글입니다.   조지 W. 부시 정부 시절 국무부 장관을 지낸 콜린 파월(Colin Powell)이 지난 18일 코로나 합병증으로 사망했습니다. 파월은 군인으로서, 관료로서 많은 업적을 남겼지만, 9.11 테러 대응 과정에서 제대로 된 근거 없이 이라크 전쟁을 시작한 정부의 최고 책임자 가운데 한 사람으로 역사에 남는 일은 피할 수 없어 보입니다. 처음부터 내켜 하지 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDE Profile: Danielle Monteiro, Cloud GDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/gde-profile-danielle-monteiro-cloud-gde.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/gde-profile-danielle-monteiro-cloud-gde.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T19:03:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Janelle Kuhlman, Developer Relations Program Manager
 
       
Cloud GDE Danielle Monteiro seeks to introduce more women and underrepresented people to data and the Cloud
For Women’s History Month, we’re celebrating a few of our Google Developer Experts. Meet Danielle Monteiro, Cloud GDE.
“There are few Black women working with data,” says Cloud GDE Danielle Monteiro, who works full-time as a Cloud Solutions Architect - Data & Artificial Intelligence at Microsoft in São Paulo, Brazil. “Being a Black woman working with data and recognized by Google is a very important recognition, and it helps me bring possibilities to women who share the same origin as me.” 
In her almost 20 years of experience in technology, Danielle has worked as a developer, a Database Administrator, a Data Ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU Coverage (gcov) with NXP S32 Design Studio IDE]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=34579</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/03/22/gnu-coverage-gcov-with-nxp-s32-design-studio-ide/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T18:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open-source GNU tools provide a rich set of tools to help developing software. Some are clearly more for the high-end application development. But many of the tools are applicable for the more restricted embedded software development process as well. … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new for developers in the OpenShift 4.10 console]]></title>
        <id>c7dc78fe-0fd6-41c4-a62b-a646da6dbba2</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/22/whats-new-developers-openshift-410-console"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article covers what’s new for developers in the Red Hat OpenShift console in OpenShift 4.10. This release includes many usability improvements, including changing your defaults for routes in creation flows and the ability to quickly troubleshoot misbehaving pods from the user interface (UI).
Additionally, there are new features available in the console when you install the following operators on your cluster: Service Binding Operator, gitops-primer, Red Hat OpenShift Serverless, Red Hat OpenShift Pipelines, and Red Hat OpenShift GitOps. Let’s dive into the details.
Secure routes by default
In 4.10, we now default to secure routes in our Import from Git and Deploy Image flows. In the detailed settings, you'll find secure routes with Transport Layer Security (TLS) termination set to Edg…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serena Chechile Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guidelines for research on the kernel community]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888891/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888891/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T16:45:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of the response to last year's UMN
fiasco, Kees Cook and a group of collaborators have put together a set
of guidelines for researchers who are studying how the kernel-development
community (or any development community, really) works.  That document has
just been merged into
the mainline as part 
of the 5.18 merge window.


	This document seeks to clarify what the Linux kernel community
	considers acceptable and non-acceptable practices when conducting
	such research. At the very least, such research and related
	activities should follow standard research ethics rules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source Initiative elects a new board]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888863/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888863/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T14:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source Initiative has announced
the results of its 2022 board election.


	Congratulations to the elected directors: Pamela Chestek, Carlo
	Piana, Josh Berkus and Amanda Brock.  Pamela Chestek has been
	confirmed and is joined by Carlo Piana as the directors elected by
	the Affiliate organizations. Josh Berkus and Amanda Brock collected
	the votes of the Individual members.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Activists are targeting Russians with open-source "protestware" (Technology Review)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/888860/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/888860/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T14:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MIT Technology Review has taken
a brief look at open-source projects that have added changes protesting
the war in Ukraine and drawn some questionable conclusions:


	No tech firm has gone that far, but around two dozen open-source
	software projects have been spotted adding code protesting the war,
	according to observers tracking the protestware
	movement. Open-source software is software that anyone can modify
	and inspect, making it more transparent—and, in this case at least,
	more open to sabotage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why aren’t there any battery-powered Wi-Fi smart home switches?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9921</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-arent-there-any-battery-powered-wi-fi-smart-home-switches/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Keith called in with a unique question. He’s using Wi-Fi devices exclusively in his smart home. That might sound like a good idea at first, but his specific question raises a potential problem. There really aren’t any options for this solution because of the potential problem of relying solely […]
The post Why aren’t there any battery-powered Wi-Fi smart home switches? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인수위 이대로 좋은가: 론스타, 국정농단, 삼바 회계, SK 편향, 안철수의 두 얼굴까지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84866</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84866"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T08:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 3월 17일 김은혜 윤석열 대통령 당선인 대변인은 여의도 국민의힘 당사에서 제20대 대통령직 인수위원회(이하 ‘인수위’) 최종 명단을 발표했다. 국민은 공정과 상식을 내걸고 제20대 대통령으로 당선된 윤석열 당선인의 첫 번째 공식적인 국정 행보를 깊은 관심과 기대를 가지고 지켜보았다. 그러나 막상 뚜껑이 열린 인수위의 모습은 공정과 상식은커녕, 오히려 깊은 우려를 자아내기에 충분했다. 론스타 사태, 박근혜 정부의 국정농단 […]
The post 인수위 이대로 좋은가: 론스타, 국정농단, 삼바 회계, SK 편향, 안철수의 두 얼굴까지 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Kubernetes in Java with the Java Operator SDK, Part 2]]></title>
        <id>a5f72d15-f7dc-4129-a9dd-fbc46277c218</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/22/write-kubernetes-java-java-operator-sdk-part-2"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Java Operator SDK, or JOSDK, is an open source project that aims to
simplify the task of creating Kubernetes Operators using Java. The
project was started by Container Solutions, and Red Hat is now a major contributor.
Part 1 in this series
introduced JOSDK and explained why it could be interesting to create Operators in Java. In this article and its sequels,
you will take a deeper look at JOSDK's concepts and learn how it simplifies Operator development. Along the way, you'll
build a simple example using JOSDK and its quarkus-operator-sdk
extension for Quarkus, a Kubernetes-native Java stack.
Use case
Deploying an application on Kubernetes requires creating multiple resources: you need to create a Deployment and an
associated Service at the very least. If you intend to access your applica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christophe Laprun</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[존재자 없는 존재 혹은 익명적 존재]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222679662701</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222679662701"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T03:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<존재자 없는 존재가 가능하다. 존재자들이 다 사라진다. 사물들이 다 사라진다. 빛조차 사라진다. 그렇다면 무엇이 남아 있는가? 무(無)가 남는다. 무(無)는 비존재가 아니다. 무(無)는 ‘없는 것’이 아니다. 그것은 이것, 저것으로 규정할 수 없는 것이지 ‘없는 것’은 아니다. 무(無)는 어떤 것이 아니다. 무(無)는 무엇이라고 말할 수 없는 것이다. 이런 무(無)를 어디에서 경험하는가?> 지금 내가 보는 존재자들이 진짜 다 사라진다면 아무 것도 없을 것이다. 레비나스는 말하고 있지 않지만, 시간과 공간도 다 사라진다고 해보자. 나아가 빛도 사라진다. 일체의 모든 것들이 다 사라진다. 따라서 남아 있는 것은 진짜 아무 것도 없.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 첩첩산중 바이든 정부 기후변화 법안]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73560</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/21/npc_joemanchin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_joemanchin"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[전쟁을 일으킨 러시아를 향한 경제 제재로 미국과 유럽 각국이 러시아산 원유와 천연가스 수입을 중단하면서 전 세계적으로 기후변화에 효과적으로 대응하는 능력은 오히려 떨어질 수 있다는 우려가 나왔습니다. 그러나 그 전부터 바이든 행정부는 미국 안에서 기후변화 관련 법안을 쉽사리 통과시키지 못했습니다. 어떻게 대통령과 같은 민주당 소속 상원의원 한 명을 설득 못해서 진전을 이뤄내지 못한 건지, 조 맨신은 누구인지에 관해 지난 10월 25일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 올린 글입니다. 당시 쓴 글의 제목은 “바이든 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspicious sortings in Unity, ASP.NET Core, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0928/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0928/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some believe that experienced developers do not make silly errors. Comparison errors? Dereferencing null references? Bet you think: "No, it's definitely not about me..." ;) By the way, what about errors with sorting? As the title suggests, there are some nuances.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has PCB design run out of steam?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474088</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/has-pcb-design-run-out-of-steam/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T18:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The multiple conflicting demands and mandates on PC boards may soon result in there being no acceptable design solution. Every system and circuit design is...
The post Has PCB design run out of steam? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Schweber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Jira for Google Chat uses the latest platform features for app and bot building]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/How-Jira-for-Google-Chat-uses-the-latest-platform-features-for-app-and-bot-building.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/How-Jira-for-Google-Chat-uses-the-latest-platform-features-for-app-and-bot-building.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by By Kyle Zhao, Software Engineer and Charles Maxson, Developer Advocate
 





      
Nothing breaks the flow of getting work done like having to stop what you’re doing in one application and switch over to another to look up information, log an event, create a ticket or check on the status of a project task. For Google Workspace users who also rely on Atlassian’s Jira Software for their issue tracking and project management needs, Jira for Chat helps bridge the gap between having conversations with your team in Google Chat and seamlessly staying on top of issues and tasks from Jira while keeping everyone in the loop.  
Recently, there have been a number of enhancements to the Google Chat framework for developers that allows them to make connections between applications like Jira …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How mmWave bolsters real-world 5G networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474081</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-mmwave-bolsters-real-world-5g-networks/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[mmWave technology can help address of the limitations of sub 6 GHz 5G networks, but there are still challenges ahead. Expectations from 5G are huge....
The post How mmWave bolsters real-world 5G networks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Rofougaran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the complexities of software-defined vehicles]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474074</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/navigating-the-complexities-of-software-defined-vehicles/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T16:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we enter the software-defined vehicle era, OEMs must develop, purchase and manage large amounts of software to remain leaders in this software-centric generation. The...
The post Navigating the complexities of software-defined vehicles appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Egil Juliussen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Matter standard is taking so long]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9943</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-the-matter-standard-is-taking-so-long/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T14:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The news that the Matter smart home interoperability standard is going to be delayed by a few more months has a lot of folks wondering why. There are plenty of people who never believed that Google, Amazon, Apple, Samsung and other industry players would really work together to create a viable standard, and think the […]
The post Why the Matter standard is taking so long appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[두 얼굴의 부동산 보도: 문 ‘폭등·분노’ vs. 윤 ‘호재·기대’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84853</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84853"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T10:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 국민의힘 후보가 당선되자 부동산 가격이 들썩이고 있습니다. 이번 선거 결과를 두고 문재인 정부에서 폭등한 집값으로 성난 부동산 민심이 반영된 결과라는 해석이 언론에 다수 등장했는데요. 같은 시각에서 바라보면 윤석열 후보 당선 이후 부동산 시장이 들썩이는 것 역시 같은 잣대로 비판해야 하지만 언론은 무슨 이유에서인지 이를 ‘긍정적’으로 포장하고 있습니다. 민주언론시민연합은 집값 상승을 부추길 윤 당선자의 부동산정책과 […]
The post 두 얼굴의 부동산 보도: 문 ‘폭등·분노’ vs. 윤 ‘호재·기대’ first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노자의 후예들, 노자를 죽이고 도교만 살리다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=84820</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/84820"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T08:57:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[비옥한 초승달 문화가 서쪽으로는 유럽, 동쪽으로는 인도까지 퍼져나갔으나, 그 너머 중국에는 미치지 못했다. 인도 북동부를 가로막고 있는 거대한 히말라야 산맥을 넘어 대규모 인구가 이동하는 것은 불가능했기 때문이다. 덕분에 히말라야 서쪽과 동쪽의 문화적 풍경은 완전히 달랐다. 한자 문화권의 기본적인 사상을 가장 단적으로 보여주는 상징은 바로 태극이다. 음양의 조화, 남자와 여자의 평등과 상보성을 상징한다. 두 개의 물방울이 […]
The post 노자의 후예들, 노자를 죽이고 도교만 살리다 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Podman using .NET]]></title>
        <id>eeabf8d6-6a68-41f4-b98e-dac599296061</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/21/hello-podman-using-net"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article shows how to control Podman from .NET. Podman is a container engine, like Docker, that is available on Linux, Windows (using the Windows Subsystem for Linux), and macOS (using a Linux virtual machine). The Podman executable is command-line compatible with Docker, and Podman also supports the Docker HTTP API. Now .NET programmers can use Podman and Docker through the Docker.DotNet library.
Prerequisites
Make sure you have the latest version of .NET installed. On Fedora and on Red Hat Enterprise Linux version 8 or 9, the latest stable version can be installed from the default repositories:
$ sudo dnf install -y dotnet-sdk-6.0
If you are running another flavor of Linux, you can find installation instructions at Install .NET on Linux.
If you haven't already, install Podman using t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Deseyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy Infinispan automatically with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>30c57a95-23dd-4486-9c33-9c487565aeaa</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/03/21/deploy-infinispan-automatically-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infinispan, an in-memory data store, is popular among Java programmers as a fast and scalable key-value store that can be deployed in a variety of settings. This article describes how to use Ansible to automate the installation and setup of an Infinispan instance. Along the way, you'll learn about many aspects of Ansible's capabilities.
The most straightforward use for Infinispan is as an in-memory cache, embedded into an application. Infinispan can also be a separate, standalone cache offering transient memory to separate applications that access the cache using different protocols. A third option is to treat Infinispan as a kind of NoSQL database. And these are only the most common use cases; additional options are available.
Infinispan can be resilient, even across data centers or avail…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romain Pelisse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[무(無)와 유(有)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222678590330</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222678590330"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T01:54:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* (가)를 참조하여 (나)를 요약하고 평가해 보라. (가) 레비나스의 존재론은 하이데거의 존재론, 특히 ‘존재’와 ‘존재자’의 구별을 뜻하는 ‘존재론적 차이’를 전제한다. 레비나스는 존재자와 존재자의 존재를 구별하고 존재는 명사가 아니라 동사임을 분명히 한다. 그러나 그의 존재 개념은 하이데거와 다르다. 존재는 빛이나 밝음 보다는 무거움과 어두움으로 체험된다. 인간이 갖는 불안은 ‘무’에 대한 불안이 아니라, ‘존재에 대한 불안’이다. 존재가 인간에게 문제인 까닭은 인간의 유한성 때문이 아니다. 설사 인간이 무한한 존재였다고 해도 존재 문제는 해결되지 않을 것이다. 존재는 그것이 지닌 익명성과 어두움, 인간에게 주.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFINAE, Immediate Context, Operator <<  and '\n']]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/sfinea-immediate-context/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/sfinea-immediate-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’ll show and explain a strange-looking error about tuple_size_v and instantiation for \n character. You’ll see some tricky parts of SFINAE and how the compiler builds the overload resolution set.
Let’s go.



     
    


When doing experiments with tuple iteration (see part one and part two) I got this strange-looking compiler error:
error: incomplete type 'std::tuple_size<char>' used in nested name specifier


Something for a char??
This comes from the second line of the following snippet:
std::tuple tp { 10, 20, "hello"};
std::cout << tp << '\n';		  // << err ??


And it points to the custom operator<< for tuples:
template <typename TupleT, std::size_t TupSize = std::tuple_size_v<TupleT>>
std::ostream& operator <<(std::ostream& os, const TupleT& tp) {
    return prin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 청소년의 정신건강과 인스타그램]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73565</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/03/20/npc_instagrammentalhealth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_instagrammentalhealth"/>
        <updated>2022-03-20T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[페이스북 내부고발자 프랜시스 하우건의 폭로 이후 소셜미디어, 특히 인스타그램이 청소년, 특히 10대 소녀들에게 끼치는 영향에 관한 논의가 뜨겁게 달아올랐습니다. 오늘은 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 10월 22일 소개한 글을 다시 싣습니다. —- 지난주 뉴욕타임스 오피니언란은 인스타그램이 10대 소녀들에게 끼치는 영향에 대한 논의로 뜨거웠습니다. 먼저 10월 8일, 뉴욕타임스의 에디터이자 영화감독인 린지 크라우스는 “10대 소녀에게 인스타그램은 악의 소굴(cesspool)”이라는 제목의 글을 올렸습니다. 논의를 촉발한 건 우리 모두 알고 있는 페이스북 내부고발자 프랜시스 하우건의 폭로였습니다. 하우건은 페이스북이 10대 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 도덕적이어야 하는가? 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222678053039</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222678053039"/>
        <updated>2022-03-20T09:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[왜 도덕적이어야 하는가? 왜 옳은 것을 해야 하는가? 왜 나는 항상 옳은 것을 해야 하는가? 웨스트팔의 <어떻게 철학을 할 것인가>는 이런 질문에 대해 네 가지 답변을 소개하고 있다. (가) 당신에게 이롭기 때문에 당신은 도덕적이어야 한다. 즉 왜 도덕적이어야 하는가? 그것이 나에게 이익을 주기 때문이다. 우리가 우리의 도덕적 측면을 도야하고 타인의 이익을 배려한다면, 타인의 이익을 무시하고 이기적이고 자기 중심적인 태도를 취할 때보다 더 행복하고 더 만족스럽게 될 것이다. 나아가 내가 이기적으로 산다면, 나를 존경하는 사람이 거의 없을 것이다. 또한 나와 교제를 꺼려할 것이고, 내가 도움이 필요할 때, 결코 나를 도.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why coding interviews aren't all that bad]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/why-coding-interviews-arent-all-that-bad/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/why-coding-interviews-arent-all-that-bad/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-19T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Coding interviews have never been popular in the programming community; I mean,
they are prevalent, since many companies still use them to filter
candidates, but they are vastly unpopular <em>in the community</em> because people find
them too hard, too unfair, too unrepresentative of reality and so on. There are
viral …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[실험실에서 극심한 고통을 느끼는 동물]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222677203451</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222677203451"/>
        <updated>2022-03-19T07:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* <15년 전 심리학과에 지원했을 때, 냉혹하게 생긴 심리학자인 면접관이 나에게 지원동기를 물어보았다. 이와 더불어 그는 심리학이 무엇이며, 무엇을 실험대상으로 삼는지 아느냐고 친절하게 물어보았다. 당시 어설프고 순박했던 나는 심리학이 마음을 연구하는 학문이며, 인간이 연구 대상이 된다고 답변했다. 면접관은 나를 움츠리게 하는 환성을 지르면서 심리학자들은 인간 마음에는 관심이 없으며, 인간이 아닌 쥐들을 주요 연구 대상이라고 했다. 이윽고 그는 나에게 바로 옆 철학과에 가보는 것이 어떠냐고 강력하게 권유했다.> (피터 싱어, <동물 해방>) 옆 철학과로 가보라는 권유가 오히려 비꼬는 빈정거림처럼 들린다. .......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for March 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9945</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-march-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T19:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Georgia-Pacific chooses MachineQ’s LoRaWAN network to connect public bathrooms: Georgia-Pacific, which makes paper towel dispensers, soap dispensers and other hygiene products, has signed a deal with Comcast’s MachineQ network to connect its KOLO Smart Monitoring System. This system automates restroom device monitoring and management, and is designed for airports, shopping centers, stadiums, schools, or other large buildings with […]
The post IoT news of the week for March 18, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stepping up as a Machine Learning Developer —My Experience With the Google Machine Learning Bootcamp]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/GoogleMachineLearningBootcamp.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/03/GoogleMachineLearningBootcamp.html"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T17:07:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hyunkil Kim, Software Quality Engineer at Line Corp.
 
          
This article is written by Hyunkil Kim who participated in the Machine Learning Bootcamp which is a machine learning training program conducted in Korea to nurture next-generation ML engineers and help them to find jobs.
       
As a developer, I had developed a certain level of curiosity about machine learning. I had also heard that many former developers were switching their specialization over to machine learning. Thus, I signed up for the <Google Machine Learning Bootcamp>, thinking it would be a good chance to get my feet wet.  
I was a bit nervous and excited at the same time after getting the acceptance notification. Wondering if I should go over my Python skills one more time in preparation, I installed the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: RISC-V developments, engineers in demand]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4474001</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-risc-v-developments-engineers-in-demand/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T16:45:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of recent embedded news and products.
The post embedded news: RISC-V developments, engineers in demand appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>