<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-08-26T20:15:56.891Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sovereign Tech Fund (STF) to invest in FreeBSD infrastructure modernization]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/987311/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/987311/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:36:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FreeBSD Foundation has announced that Germany's Sovereign Tech
Fund (STF) has agreed to invest €686,400 toward improvements in the
FreeBSD project's infrastructure, security, regulatory compliance, and
developer experience:
August
9, 2024 summary report released by the U.S. Office of the
National Cyber Director (ONCD), consolidating feedback from the 2023
request for information on key priorities for securing the open source
software ecosystem. By enhancing security controls and SBOM tooling,
the FreeBSD Foundation is helping to keep FreeBSD at the forefront of
improved vulnerability disclosure mechanisms and secure software
foundations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A new version of modversions]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986892/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986892/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:19:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The genksyms tool has long been buried deeply within the kernel's
build system; it is one of the two C-code parsers shipped with the kernel
(the other being the
horrifying kernel-doc script).  It is a key part of how the
kernel's module-loading infrastructure works.  While genksyms has
quietly done its job for decades, that period may soon be coming to an end.
It would seem that genksyms is not up to the task of handling Rust
code, so Sami Tolvanen is proposing
a new tool to handle this task going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/987309/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/987309/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T17:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium, python-html-sanitizer, and trafficserver), Fedora (nginx, nginx-mod-fancyindex, nginx-mod-modsecurity, nginx-mod-naxsi, nginx-mod-vts, python-webob, python3-docs, python3.11, python3.12, python3.9, and zabbix), Red Hat (bind, bind and bind-dyndb-ldap, bind9.16, httpd, kernel, kernel-rt, and nodejs:20), SUSE (caddy, chromium, chromium, gn, rust-bindgen, cockpit, fetchmail, gdcm, gh, keybase-client, libhtp, libofx, nano, plasma5-workspace, python-nltk, python-notebook, xen, and znc), and Ubuntu (linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-azure-5.4, and linux-oracle-5.15).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“예산 없어요 내년에 고칠게요” 창녕박물관 엉터리 해설]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114978</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114978"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T08:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[김훤주의 지역에서 본 세상] 베테랑 기자 김훤주가 세상 이야기를 따뜻하고 담백한 시선으로 전합니다. 8월 15일에 창녕박물관을 찾아갔었다. 전시 내용을 둘러보는데 적지 않게 당황스러웠다. 설렁설렁 훑어보았는데도 잘못되거나 적당하지 않은 표현이 여러 군데 있었다. 안내데스크에 말했더니 “휴일이라 학예사가 없고 자기는 해설사라 책임 있는 대답을 하기 어렵다”면서 “전달해 드릴 수는 있지만 이런 지적은 담당자에게 직접 해야 더 효과가...
The post “예산 없어요 내년에 고칠게요” 창녕박물관 엉터리 해설 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI 진화가 생물학적 지옥문을 열 수도 있다: 4가지 역량, 5가지 예방책]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=115167</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/115167"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:48:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. AI는 기술 부채를 해결하는 데 아주 효과적인 도구다 아마존 앤디 재시의 트윗, 8월 22일 개인적으로 AI에 대한 가장 많은 소식과 의견을 듣는 공간은 아직 과거 트위터였던 X.com이다. 8월 22일에 아마존의 사장인 앤디 재시가 올린 트윗을 보았다. 그는 아마존의 Q라는 소프트웨어 개발 어시스턴트를 이용해 아마존이 기술 부채를 어떻게 효과적으로 해결할 수 있었는지 알렸다. 기업에서 개발자들도...
The post AI 진화가 생물학적 지옥문을 열 수도 있다: 4가지 역량, 5가지 예방책 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Running applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat UBI container images in OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>46002878-1316-4b3d-b780-2ef219d3e29e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/26/running-applications-paketo-buildpacks-and-red-hat-ubi-container-images"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the growth in the use of containers, the need to bundle your application into a container has never been stronger. Many Red Hat customers will be familiar with Source-to-Image (S2I) as an easy way to build container images from application source code. While S2I is a convenient way to build images on Red Hat OpenShift, Red Hat works to support our customers when using a variety of approaches, and we’ve recently seen an increasing interest in building applications using Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) Buildpacks.  
This is the second in a 5-part series of articles on building your applications with CNCF Buildpacks and Red Hat Universal Base Image (UBI). The series will include:

Building applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat UBI container images 
Running applications…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson, Costas Papastathis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “마녀사냥에 복수” 다짐하는 그, 정말로 ‘제왕적 대통령’ 될까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79621</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/25/npsp_imperialpresidency/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_imperialpresidency"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 7월 5일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지구상에서 가장 막강한 권력을 지닌 사람을 꼽으라면, 많은 사람이 미국 대통령을 몇 손가락 안에 꼽을 겁니다. 세계에서 가장 강력한 나라 미국의 군대를 움직일 수 있는 통수권자이자 정부를 이끄는 정치지도자인 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[검찰총장의 마지막 자존심, 수심위는 김건희를 건드릴 수 있을까: 슬로우레터 8월26일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=115090</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/115090"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T22:19:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 사건, 수사심의위로 간다. 이원석의 결단. “수사심의위 망설일 것 없다.” 쟁점과 현안. 정부+가계 부채 3000조 원 시대. 글로벌 피벗 임박했는데. 이스라엘-헤즈볼라 폭격. 더 깊게 읽기. 한은 압박하는 대통령실. 간호사 총파업. 피할 수 있었던 죽음 늘어난다. 추석 연휴 셧 다운 우려. 다르게 읽기. 샤이 트럼프 얼마나 될까. 선 벨트와 러스트 벨트. 해법과 대안. ‘세이 온 클라이밋’....
The post 검찰총장의 마지막 자존심, 수심위는 김건희를 건드릴 수 있을까: 슬로우레터 8월26일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1970s: the founding decade of software reliability research]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9308</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/08/25/1970s-the-founding-decade-of-software-reliability-research/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T21:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reliability research is a worthwhile investment for very large organizations that fund the development of many major mission-critical software systems, where reliability is essential. In the 1970s, the US Air Force’s Rome Air Development Center probably funded most of the evidence-based software research carried out in the previous century. In the 1980s, Rome fell, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.11-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/987164/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/987164/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T15:35:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.11-rc5 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Other than the timing, there's not a whole lot unusual
here. The diffstat looks fairly flat, which means 'mostly pretty small
changes'." Linus Torvalds added a
note that today marks the 33rd anniversary of the first Linux
announcement; "A third of a century. And it *still* isn't ready".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use SystemView Data Plot Feature for Real-time Data Visualization]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=41143</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/08/25/how-to-use-systemview-data-plot-feature-for-real-time-data-visualization/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T14:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEGGER SystemView, a real-time recording and visualization tool for embedded systems, now supports plotting custom data and offers deeper insights into timing and application behavior. The new feature includes a data plot window, support for data sampling events, and an API update. With this addition, users can send and visualize arbitrary data with ease. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지역 기반 솔루션 저널리즘 네트워크 모델을 만들자.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=115049</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/115049"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T12:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기록적인 폭우, 물 폭탄과 침수, 고립, 피해… 장마철마다 반복되는 기사다. 어떻게 다른 방식으로 쓰고 다른 문제의식을 끌어낼 수 있을까. JIBS제주방송 기사 두 건이 눈길을 끈다. “유역 차원에서 배수를 시켜줘야 한다”는 박창열(제주연구원 연구위원)의 인터뷰와 함께 “분담형 치수 대책이 시급하다”고 지적했다. “정확한 홍수량조차 파악하지 못하고 있다”는 기사도 있었다. 10년 이상 데이터를 축적해야 분석이 가능한데 4개 관측소에서 유량과...
The post 지역 기반 솔루션 저널리즘 네트워크 모델을 만들자. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SentencePiece BPE Tokenizer in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/sentencepiece-bpe-tokenizer-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/sentencepiece-bpe-tokenizer-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T17:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Earlier this year I wrote a <a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/tokens-for-llms-byte-pair-encoding-in-go/">post about implementing BPE tokenization in Go</a>,
which made it possible to reproduce OpenAI's tokenizer.</p>
<p>Today I want to mention a new project I've been hacking on recently:
<a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/eliben/go-sentencepiece">go-sentencepiece</a>
- a pure Go implementation of the <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/google/sentencepiece">SentencePiece</a> tokenizer
that's used for Google AI's models like …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The history, status, and plans for reproducible builds]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985739/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985739/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T13:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the second day of DebConf24
in Busan, South Korea, Holger Levsen provided a history lesson on the
"first 11 years" of the Reproducible Builds project.
He has been involved in the project for most of that time and has been a
Debian user since the mid-1990s, contributor since 2001, and a Debian
member since 2007; "I love Debian".  Meanwhile, his aim is to make all free
software be reproducible, so that anyone can check that a binary program
comes from the source code it purports to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forgejo changes license to GPLv3+]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986998/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986998/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T13:39:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 

Forgejo project has announced that, starting from version 9.0, Forgejo will be released under the GPLv3 license (or a later version). Older versions of the software forge remain MIT-licensed.



A copyleft license makes reusing other copyleft software easier. Recently, we discovered that 

some of the dependencies we used were incompatible with the license Forgejo was distributed with, and they had to be removed for now. Choosing copyleft licenses enables us to reuse more work, and saves us precious time to focus on improving Forgejo itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986997/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986997/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T13:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (community-mysql, iaito, and radare2), Oracle (python3.12-setuptools and tomcat), Red Hat (krb5 and podman), Slackware (ffmpeg), SUSE (apache2, expat, firefox, webkit2gtk3, and xen), and Ubuntu (imagemagick and libxstream-java).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“조선인 강제노동 사실무근” 사도광산의 역사적 진실 부정하는 일본의 극우 언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114983</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114983"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T08:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[7월 27일, 일본 니가타현의 ‘사도광산’이 유네스코 세계문화유산으로 등재되었다. 2010년 일본 정부가 사도광산을 유네스코 세계 유산 추천 잠정 목록에 등재한 이후 14년 만의 일이다. 한국에서는 사도광산의 세계 유산 등재에 대한 비판적인 목소리가 끊이지 않고 있다. 사도광산이 일제 강점기 당시 조선인을 강제 동원해 가혹한 노동을 시켰던 아픈 역사의 현장이기 때문이다. 한국 정부는 등재 과정에서 역사적 사실이 충분히...
The post “조선인 강제노동 사실무근” 사도광산의 역사적 진실 부정하는 일본의 극우 언론 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘문자 한 통 해고’ 아사히글라스 9년 투쟁… 얼마나 더 싸워야 하는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114963</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114963"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T07:29:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[비정규직 차별에 맞서 노동조합을 설립한 이후, 회사로부터 ‘문자 한 통’으로 해고됐던 아사히글라스 해고 노동자들이 출근길에 나섰습니다. 이에 이르기까지 9년의 시간과 대법원의 세 판결이 있었습니다. 직접고용을 구하는 민사, 부당노동행위가 쟁점인 행정, 파견법 위반이 문제 된 형사의 세 판결입니다. 대법원은 아사히글라스 하청업체 해고 노동자의 근로자 지위를 인정하고, 사측의 파견법 위반 인정했지만, 사측의 부당노동행위에 대해선 인정하지 않았습니다. 각각의...
The post ‘문자 한 통 해고’ 아사히글라스 9년 투쟁… 얼마나 더 싸워야 하는가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 만약 바이든이 후보 사퇴한다면? 이렇게 진행될 겁니다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79603</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/22/npsp_openconvention/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_openconvention"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T01:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 7월 2일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. *** 글을 시차 발행하는 오늘(8월 22일) 밤 카말라 해리스는 민주당 전당대회 마지막날 대통령 후보 지명을 수락할 예정입니다. 불과 두 달도 채 되지 않는 시점에는 상상도 하기 어려웠던 일이 현실로 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘주머니 사정’이 선거 승패 가른다면 누가 더 유리할까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79864</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/22/npsp_economicplanharristrump/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_economicplanharristrump"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T00:15:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[민주당 전당대회를 앞둔 지난 금요일, 카말라 해리스 부통령은 자신의 경제 공약을 발표했습니다. 바이든 행정부에서 치솟은 물가를 안정시키고 서민과 중산층에게 도움이 되는 정책을 위해 해리스가 꺼낸 카드는 치솟는 집값을 안정화시키겠다는 일련의 정책이었습니다. 뉴욕타임스 칼럼니스트 피터 코이가 수요와 공급이라는 경제학의 기본 원리를 바탕으로 해리스의 경제 공약을 분석했습니다. 해설에서는 이번 선거의 향방을 가를 경합주의 경제 상황을 함께 진단해 봤습니다. 전문 번역: “해리스의 경제 공약, 완벽하지는 않지만 트럼프보다는 낫다” 해설: ‘주머니 사정’이 선거 승패 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열이 요즘 술을 자제하고 있다는 놀라운 사실: 8월23일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114859</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114859"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T22:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최장기 금리 동결. 쟁점과 현안. 윤석열의 불만, “선제 대응 아쉽다.” 집값에 달렸다. 윤석열의 뒤끝, 보수판 광복회 만든다. 디올 백 무혐의, 수사심의위 거쳐라. 더 깊게 읽기. 이자 장사로 30조 원 이익. “누구 때문인데.” 윤석열이 술을 안 먹는다고? “저 사람이 우리 아빠야.” 다르게 읽기. “최저임금 다 줄 필요 있나.” 한동훈의 차별화. 저출산 대책, 세금 더 낼 수...
The post 윤석열이 요즘 술을 자제하고 있다는 놀라운 사실: 8월23일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ programmer's guide to undefined behavior: part 4 of 11]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1156/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1156/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your attention is invited to the fourth part of an e-book on undefined behavior. This is not a textbook, as it's intended for those who are already familiar with C++ programming. It's a kind of C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemma explained: What’s new in Gemma 2]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-explained-new-in-gemma-2/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-explained-new-in-gemma-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T20:15:18.792Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemma 2 is a new suite of open models that sets a new standard for performance and accessibility, outperforming popular models more than twice its size.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LibreOffice 24.8 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986906/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986906/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T18:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
24.8 of the LibreOffice office suite has been released.  Changes
include the ability to filter identifying information from exported files,
easier creation of cross reference, better control over hyphenation, a
number of new spreadsheet functions, accessibility improvements, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rewriting Strangler Fig]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-strangler-fig-rewrite.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-strangler-fig-rewrite.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T15:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two decades ago, I posted that I found that the strangler fig plant was an interesting metaphor for the gradual replacement of a legacy system. I didn’t refer to the metaphor since, but meanwhile it grew a life of its own. Other people increasingly referred to the strangler fig approach to modernization, and traffic to that post steadily increased: currently it gets about 5000 page views a month, one of the more popular pages on this site. So I decided I needed to update that page, and have rewritten it, focusing on the core activities we need to do to make a success of such a venture.
(This summarizes more detailed writing from Ian Cartwright, Rob Horn, and James Lewis.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A review of file descriptor memory safety in the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985853/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985853/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T15:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 30, Al Viro sent

a patch set to the linux-fsdevel mailing list with a
comprehensive cover letter explaining his
recent work on ensuring that the kernel's internal representation of
file descriptors are used correctly in the kernel.
File descriptors are ubiquitous; many system calls
need to handle them. Viro's review
identified a few existing bugs, and may prevent more in the future. He also had
suggestions for ways to keep uses consistent throughout the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 엔비디아 실적 전망, 기대보다 좋을 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595828</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595828/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-%ea%b8%b0%eb%8c%80%eb%b3%b4%eb%8b%a4-%ec%a2%8b%ec%9d%84-%ea%b2%83"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T14:31:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garrett: What is an SBAT and why does everyone suddenly care]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986844/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986844/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T14:25:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Garrett describes
the role of the Secure Boot Advanced Targeting mechanism and how it
played into the recent Windows upgrade problems.


	So why is this suddenly relevant? SBAT was developed
	collaboratively between the Linux community and Microsoft, and
	Microsoft chose to push a Windows update that told systems not to
	trust versions of grub with a security generation below a certain
	level. This was because those versions of grub had genuine security
	vulnerabilities that would allow an attacker to compromise the
	Windows secure boot chain, and we've seen real world examples of
	malware wanting to do that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986841/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986841/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T14:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (.NET 8.0, bind, bind9.16, curl, edk2, firefox, gnome-shell, grafana, jose, krb5, libreoffice, mod_auth_openidc:2.3, orc, pcs, poppler, python-setuptools, python-urllib3, python3.11-setuptools, python3.12-setuptools, thunderbird, tomcat, and wget), Fedora (webkitgtk), SUSE (apache2, glib2, and roundcubemail), and Ubuntu (kernel, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15,
 linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15,
 linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm,
 linux-ibm-5.15, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-kvm,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux-oracle,
 linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4,
 linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm,
 linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-ibm,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-nvidia, linux-nvidia-6.8, linux-nvidia-lowlatency,
 linux-oem-6.8, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, linux, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-bluefield, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-raspi-5.4, and qemu).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“직무 관련 없으면 선물 가능”, ‘괴짤’의 실체는?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114838</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114838"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T13:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[국민권익위원회에서 만든 카드뉴스가 화제다. 언뜻 보면 ‘가짜뉴스’로 오해할 정도로 믿기 어려운 내용이다. 가뜩이나 김건희(대통령 부인)를 닮은 것 같은 캐릭터까지 있는데 놀랍게도 이 카드뉴스는 진짜였다. 국민권익위가 만들어서 홈페이지에 올려놓은 카드뉴스다. ‘가짜뉴스’가 아니었다. 이 카드뉴스가 말하지 않는 것. 직무 관련성이 없으니 괜찮다고? 최재영과 윤석열이 직무 관련성이 없는 건 맞나? 대통령 부인에게 300만 원 상당의 엿을 선물한다면? 핵심은...
The post “직무 관련 없으면 선물 가능”, ‘괴짤’의 실체는? appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your second GPU algorithm: Quicksort]]></title>
        <id>9238ff3b-7314-45b2-9436-902d19ef618a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/22/write-gpu-algorithm-quicksort"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using the algorithm for prefix sum/scan, covered in the previous module, we’re going to now write an algorithm for quicksort.
This is part 3 of a 4-part series. Catch up on the previous articles:

What is GPU programming

Your first GPU algorithm: Scan/prefix sum

The quicksort algorithm
The reason we’re doing quicksort, rather than something like merge sort, is that it’s very easy to parallelize– once you partition the array, each partition can be sorted completely independently. Plus, it is efficient in the average case, especially if you use randomness to select your pivot. 
Recall that the pseudocode for quicksort is as follows:
def quicksort(array, BLOCK_SIZE):
	p = randomly select pivot from array
	let below_arr = global, reused array that stores the number of items in each block les…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenny Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing K8s operators for managing REST resources]]></title>
        <id>e8daa423-226f-44f0-947e-74711bd17892</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/21/design-kubernetes-operator-rest-resources"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operators are the standard way to package software and to automate day 1 and 2 operations for applications running on Red Hat OpenShift. Even the platform itself is based on cluster operators that encapsulate a single aspect of the OpenShift platform (e.g., how to deploy and update the DNS, API server, etc.), database or the internal registry. There is also a huge ecosystem of third party providers that are delivering their software via an operator. 
The general idea behind the concept of operators is to automate installation, updates, backups, configuration, and many other operational tasks that are specific to the application the operator is managing. A concept that will also be useful for managing your own applications on the OpenShift platform. But how to start writing your own operato…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Benjamin Schmeling, Andrea Peruffo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민주당 부통령 후보 월즈의 일곱 가지 연설 전략: 역대 최고(🐐) 인정!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114783</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114783"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T02:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[팀 월즈 미네소타주지사가 카멀라 해리스 부통령의 러닝메이트로 발표된 지 몇 시간 만에 펜실베이니아주 필라델피아에서 14,000명이 운집한 미 민주당 첫 정∙부통령 후보 공동 유세를 본 몇 가지 느낌을 공유한다. 대학 부전공(커뮤니케이션)과 20년 회사 경력(홍보)에 의거한 지극히 개인적 평가이며 반박 시 반박하는 분이 맞는 걸로. 😉 월즈 주지사. 민주당 역대 대선후보 중 케네디 이후 연설(stump speech) 가장...
The post 민주당 부통령 후보 월즈의 일곱 가지 연설 전략: 역대 최고(🐐) 인정! appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>홍윤희</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 22, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985783/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985783/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T01:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 22, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “그렇게만 할 거면… 올림픽 왜 하니?” 배제와 포용, 답은 정해져 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79588</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/21/npsp_sextestingolympics/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_sextestingolympics"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T22:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 28일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. *** 파리 올림픽에서 실제로 XY 염색체를 지닌 복싱 선수 이마네 칼리프(알제리)와 린위팅(대만)의 여성 종목 출전이 논란을 낳기도 했습니다. 이에 관해 언론에도 많은 기사가 소개됐습니다. 연합뉴스: IOC, XY염색체 여자 복싱선수 논란에 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“이게 나라냐”, 디올 백은 무혐의, 경제는 엉망, 보수 언론도 ‘부글부글’:슬로우레터 8월22일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114744</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114744"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T22:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 디올 백 무혐의. 윤석열 검사라면 어땠을까. 총장 패싱? 이원석의 시간이 됐다. 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈-이재명 회담 생중계가 변수. 윤석열 정부 경제가 빠진 세 가지 함정. 세수 56조 원 펑크, 순방비는 예비비로. 민주당 방통위원 2명 추천한다. “이게 나라냐”, 중앙일보 논설위원의 한숨. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명표 감세 법안. 뜬금없이 문재인 사위 털기. 재일동포 학교 교토국제고, 고시엔 결승...
The post “이게 나라냐”, 디올 백은 무혐의, 경제는 엉망, 보수 언론도 ‘부글부글’:슬로우레터 8월22일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Years of Innovation: Student developers solving real-world problems using Google tech]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T20:15:16.569Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Developer Student Clubs globally are tackling the United Nations' Sustainable Development Goals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Something has gone seriously wrong," dual-boot systems warn after Microsoft update (Ars Technica)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986659/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986659/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T18:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ars Technica covers
a recent update
that is causing problems for users with systems that dual-boot Windows
and Linux.
"Note that Windows says this update won't apply to systems that
dual-boot Windows and Linux," one frustrated person wrote. "This
obviously isn't true, and likely depends on your system configuration
and the distribution being run. It appears to have made some linux efi
shim bootloaders incompatible with microcrap efi bootloaders (that's
why shifting from MS efi to 'other OS' in efi setup works). It appears
that Mint has a shim version that MS SBAT doesn't recognize."
The reports indicate that multiple distributions, including Debian,
Ubuntu, Linux Mint, Zorin OS, and Puppy Linux, are all
affected. Microsoft has yet to acknowledge the error publicly, explain
how it wasn't detected during testing, or provide technical guidance
to those affected. Company representatives didn't respond to an email
seeking answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Górny: Gentoo: profiles and keywords rather than releases]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986655/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986655/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T17:31:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gentoo developer Michał Górny has written a lengthy blog
post that explains how Gentoo approaches releases:


Gentoo is something of a hybrid, as it combines the best of both
worlds. It is a rolling release distribution with a single shared
repository that is available to all users. However, within this
repository we use a keywording system to provide a choice between
stable and testing packages, to facilitate both production and
development systems (with some extra flexibility), and versioned
profiles to tackle major lock-step upgrades.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Modernizing openSUSE installation with Agama]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974969/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974969/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T15:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux installers receive a disproportionate amount of attention
compared to the amount of time that most users spend with them. Ideally,
a user spends only a few minutes using the installer, versus years using
the distribution after it is installed. Yet, the installer sets the
first impression, and if it fails to do its job, little else matters.
Installers also have to continually evolve to keep pace with new
hardware, changes in distribution packaging (such as image-based Linux
distributions), and so forth. Along those lines, the SUSE team that maintains the
venerable YaST installer has
decided it's time to start (almost) fresh with a new Linux installer
project, called Agama,
for new projects. YaST is not going away as an administration tool,
but it is likely to be relieved of installer duties at some point.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The RTOS renaissance: closing the OS gap with Linux in IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490678</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-rtos-renaissance-closing-the-os-gap-with-linux-in-iot/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, Linux has dominated the embedded and IoT landscape, lauded for its flexibility and mature ecosystem. However, a renaissance is unfolding in real-time operating systems (RTOS). Propelled by open-source initiatives, big tech backing, and a growing demand for low-latency and resource-constrained applications, RTOS development environments are rapidly closing the gap with their more established […]
The post The RTOS renaissance: closing the OS gap with Linux in IoT appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986628/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986628/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T13:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (aom, cinder, dovecot, glance, and nova), Fedora (mysql8.0), Oracle (curl and libreoffice), SUSE (oniguruma, openssl-1_0_0, openssl1, and xen), and Ubuntu (cacti, curl, exfatprogs, firefox, and vim).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빗물에 세금을? 도쿄∙베를린에서 ‘힌트’ 얻는 극한호우 대책]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114701</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114701"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T09:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 8월 서울엔 시간당 최대 141.5㎜의 기록적인 폭우가 쏟아졌다. 극한호우 기준인 시간당 72㎜의 두 배가량으로 신림동과 상도동 반지하 주택에서는 다수의 사망자가 발생했다. 문제는 역대급 폭우가 더 새로운 일이 아니라는 것이다. 기후위기로 ‘더 자주, 더 세게’ 폭우가 발생할 가능성이 높아지고 있다. 앞으로 50년 이내 시간당 200㎜의 비가 내릴 수 있다니, 이제 폭우는 여름철 일상이 되었다. 변화된...
The post 빗물에 세금을? 도쿄∙베를린에서 ‘힌트’ 얻는 극한호우 대책 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to back up and restore virtual machines with OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>788ec1d5-4de5-422f-ad23-e7ff2de65d40</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/21/how-back-and-restore-virtual-machines-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are planning a move to Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization, you may have a list of features that need to be checked to demonstrate similar capabilities to more established virtualization platforms. This article will guide you through one such feature: backing up and restoring virtual machines. There are several partner products that can simplify this operation, but these steps show a quick way to get started directly with the OpenShift APIs for Data Protection, provided by Red Hat.
Preparation
These instructions assume you have administrative access to an OpenShift cluster. On this cluster, install and configure the following three Operators:

Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization: Refer to these instructions to install OpenShift Virtualization and create a HyperConverged Operator instance.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthew Arnold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices to safely navigate pointers in C/C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490671</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/best-practices-to-safely-navigate-pointers-in-c-c/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T22:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As someone who has spent over two decades in the embedded systems industry, I’ve seen the vast evolution of technology—from 8-bit microcontrollers to today’s sophisticated, multicore systems. Yet, one thing remains constant: pointers in C and C++. They are a double-edged sword that can lead to incredible flexibility in memory management but can also wreak […]
The post Best practices to safely navigate pointers in C/C++ appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마약 외압 사건에 김건희 개입 의혹이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 8월21일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114654</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114654"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T22:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“용산에서 심각하게 보고 있다고, 머리가 하얘지는 느낌이었다.” 채 상병 사건 경찰판? 여기도 김건희의 그림자. 쟁점과 현안. 가계부채 1896조 원, 골든타임 놓쳤나. 윤석열 거부권 행사한 전세사기법 여야 합의로 통과. 추석이 두렵다. 의대생 1년 유급, 감당할 수 있나. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명 앞의 세 가지 태풍. ‘임대 문의’ 늘어나는 이유. “나는 내 일을 사랑했지만 미국을 더 사랑했다.”...
The post 마약 외압 사건에 김건희 개입 의혹이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 8월21일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python subinterpreters and free-threading]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985041/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985041/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T22:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At
PyCon 2024 in Pittsburgh,
Pennsylvania, Anthony Shaw looked at the various kinds of parallelism
available to Python programs.  There have been two major developments on
the parallel-execution front over the last few years, with the effort to
provide subinterpreters, each with its own
global interpreter lock (GIL), along with the work to remove the GIL entirely.  In the talk, he
explored the two approaches to try to give attendees a sense of how to make
the right choice for their applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing vehicle design through rugged, miniaturized connectors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490665</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/optimizing-vehicle-design-through-rugged-miniaturized-connectors/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T22:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronics are expected to comprise roughly half the cost of a new car by 2030, which ups the ante for automotive engineers tasked with “designing in” more features and functionality in the same or less space while meeting rigorous demands for enhanced reliability. Fueling this challenge are four transformational trends: connectivity, autonomous driving, in-vehicle experience […]
The post Optimizing vehicle design through rugged, miniaturized connectors appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[uv 0.3.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986528/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986528/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T21:31:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 0.3.0 of the uv
Python package and project manager has been released. Introduced in
February, uv is written in Rust and aims to be "Cargo for
Python".  Notable changes in this release include the addition of
interfaces for managing projects, installing
Python, and running scripts,
along with adding new documentation. See the
accompanying blog post for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“이민자들이 몰려온다”는데… 문제 못 풀게 발목 잡은 건 누구였나]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79845</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/20/npsp_usimmigrationelection/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_usimmigrationelection"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T20:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이번 미국 대선의 중요한 이슈 가운데 하나가 이민 문제입니다. 얼핏 보기엔 이민 문제에 있어서 주로 공세를 펴는 쪽은 트럼프와 공화당이고, 반대로 민주당은 정책을 방어하는 경우가 많아 보입니다. 그러나 자세히 뜯어 보면, 이민 문제가 지금처럼 심각해진 데는 공화당과 민주당, 진보와 보수 할 것 없이 현실에 한참 뒤처진 이민 제도를 방치한 정치권 전반의 책임이 큽니다. 실제로 미국에 합법적으로 정착하기 위해 비자를 받거나 영주권을 얻는 일은 굉장히 어렵습니다. 전문 번역: 미국에 ‘합법 이민’이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Per-call-site slab caches for heap-spraying protection]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986174/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986174/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T13:29:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One tactic often used by attackers set on compromising a system is heap spraying; in
short, the attacker fills as much of the heap as possible with crafted data
in the hope of getting the target system to use that data in a bad way.  If
heap spraying can be blocked, attackers will lose an important tool.  The
kernel has some heap-spraying defenses now, including the dedicated bucket allocator merged for the
upcoming 6.11 release, but its author, Kees Cook, thinks that more can be
done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986450/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986450/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T13:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (squid), Fedora (putty), Mageia (quictls), Oracle (bind, curl, python-setuptools, python3.11-setuptools, and python3.12-setuptools), Red Hat (kernel, kpatch-patch-4_18_0-305_120_1, kpatch-patch-4_18_0-372_87_1 and kpatch-patch-4_18_0-372_91_1, kpatch-patch-4_18_0-477_43_1, kpatch-patch-4_18_0-553, kpatch-patch-5_14_0-284_48_1 and kpatch-patch-5_14_0-284_52_1, kpatch-patch-5_14_0-427_13_1, and libreoffice), SUSE (cosign, dri3proto, presentproto, wayland-protocols, xwayland, freerdp, fwupdate, git, gnome-settings-daemon, hdf5, jasper, java-17-openjdk, java-1_8_0-ibm, java-1_8_0-openjdk, kernel, kernel-firmware, libaom, libqt5-qt3d, libqt5-qtquick3d, ntfs-3g_ntfsprogs, osc, python, python-aiohttp, python-azure-core, python-azure-storage-blob, python- azure-storage-queue, python-typing, python-typing_extensions, python-Jinja2, python-PyMySQL, python-requests, python-tqdm, python-WebOb, python3-sqlparse, python310, python311, qemu, sssd, thunderbird, tiff, unixODBC, uriparser, and wireshark), and Ubuntu (intel-microcode, linux-azure-5.4, and postgresql-12, postgresql-14, postgresql-16).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git-based operations (GitOps) for Operators managed by Operator Lifecycle Manager (OLM)]]></title>
        <id>2479ff32-6704-4cce-b2a3-dcf6156297f2</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/20/git-based-operations-gitops-operators-managed-operator-lifecycle-manager-olm"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Operator Framework was paradigm shifting for managing infrastructure and providing services to users on Kubernetes by introducing a methodology for capturing a human operator's knowledge as a Kubernetes-native application, an Operator. The Operator Lifecycle Manager (OLM) brought systematic installation, removal, and update management for Operators. In parallel, the rise and recognition of the power and need for Git-based operations (GitOps) has brought much needed consistent, repeatable, and scalable management of not only Kubernetes and its surrounding ecosystem, but the management of the entire platform as a software product with full software development lifecycle (SLDC) for all the reasons end user applications have been refining their SDLC for all these years.
Challenge
OLM only …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Tewksbury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가격통제, 해리스의 승부수 또는 해프닝]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114607</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114607"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T04:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 해리스의 약진 여론조사에 따라 조금씩 다르게 나오지만 해리스가 지지율에서 트럼프를 약간 앞서고 있을 뿐 아니라 차이를 벌리고 있다는 점은 공통적이다. 아직 결과를 알 수는 없으나 불과 45일 전 바이든이 TV 토론에서 참패한 이래 민주당의 승리 가능성이 곤두박칠쳤던 것을 고려하면 상전벽해라고 할 수 있을 정도이다. 자신의 돈을 걸고 대통령 당선 결과를 맞추는 정치 예측 플랫폼에서도...
The post 가격통제, 해리스의 승부수 또는 해프닝 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>신현호</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless Connectivity Solutions for ESP32-P4]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/8c64ca156a81</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/wireless-connectivity-solutions-for-esp32-p4-8c64ca156a81?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T03:14:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Anant Raj Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[삿갓배미, 가난의 간절함이 만든 아름다운 다랑논]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114594</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114594"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T02:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[김훤주의 지역에서 본 세상] 베테랑 기자 김훤주가 세상 이야기를 따뜻하고 담백한 시선으로 전합니다. 며칠 전 삿갓배미를 보았다. 옛날에는 흔했지만 요즘은 귀해진 삿갓배미를 보니 기분이 좋았다. 삿갓은 삿갓처럼 조그맣다는 말이고 배미는 한 배미 두 배미 세 배미 하며 논을 헤아리는 단위다. 삿갓배미의 유래는 이렇다. 옛날 농부가 논에서 김을 매다가 세어 봤더니 한 배미가 모자랐다. 아무리 찾아도...
The post 삿갓배미, 가난의 간절함이 만든 아름다운 다랑논 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[광복절 ‘나비부인’ 사고, 실수도 우연도 아닐 수 있다: 슬로우레터 8월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114550</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114550"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T22:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[쟁점과 현안. 네이버 항의 방문한 국민의힘. 한동훈-이재명 만난다. 더 깊게 읽기. 긱 이코노미 시대. 자영업자도 계속 줄고 있다. 쌀값 폭락, 풍년이 반갑지 않다. 다르게 읽기. “오염수 괴담 1년도 못 갔다.” 투자자 상위 1%가 401조 원 주식 보유. 지나치게 좋은 건 좋지 않을 수도 있다. 해법과 대안. 골든아워 도착률, 서울은 94%, 충북은 41%. 보호출산제 한 달...
The post 광복절 ‘나비부인’ 사고, 실수도 우연도 아닐 수 있다: 슬로우레터 8월20일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] FreeBSD considers Rust in the base system]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985210/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985210/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T15:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FreeBSD Project is, for the second
time this year, engaging in a long-running discussion about the
possibility of including Rust in its base
system. The sequel to the first discussion included some work by
Alan Somers to show what it might look like to use Rust code in the
base tree. Support for Rust code does not appear much closer to being
included in FreeBSD's base system, but the conversation has been
enlightening.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986229/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986229/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T14:43:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's crop of new stable kernels consists of seven new versions: 6.10.6, 6.6.47, 6.1.106, 5.15.165, 5.10.224, 5.4.282, and 4.19.320.  As usual, each contains important
fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986225/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986225/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T14:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (python-asyncssh), Fedora (bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, httpd, and tor), SUSE (cosign, cpio, curl, expat, java-11-openjdk, ncurses, netty, netty-tcnative, opera, python-Django, python-Pillow, shadow, sudo, and wpa_supplicant), and Ubuntu (firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi HaLow smart IoT products emerge, and real world field trials’ success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490657</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/wi-fi-halow-smart-iot-products-emerge-and-real-world-field-trials-success/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T13:31:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two separate announcements around the Wi-Fi HaLow standard caught our eye over the last few weeks. One is the collaboration between Milesight and Morse Micro to launch Wi-Fi HaLow variants of smart IoT products, and the other was the announcement by the Wireless Broadband Alliance of successful completion of real-world field trials of Wi-Fi HaLow […]
The post Wi-Fi HaLow smart IoT products emerge, and real world field trials’ success appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supercharge your Red Hat OpenShift local environment with Red Hat OpenShift Lightspeed]]></title>
        <id>c0c9fef6-8188-4523-8358-9b7e538f965e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/19/supercharge-your-red-hat-openshift-local-environment-red-hat-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Local is a development environment where Red Hat OpenShift applications run on a local machine, and it provides a sandbox environment for developers to build, test, and iterate on applications without requiring access to a full-scale cloud infrastructure. And it’s just been made better with the addition of Red Hat OpenShift Lightspeed!
Red Hat OpenShift Lightspeed is a generative AI virtual chat assistant that exists to improve productivity and accessibility for OpenShift users of all skill levels, from novices to experts. 
OpenShift Lightspeed on OpenShift Local
OpenShift Lightspeed is easy to access since it’s integrated directly into the OpenShift web console. Furthermore, it allows you to bring your own large language models (LLMs) through the following supported prov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivian Chinoda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring OpenShift Virtualization using user-defined projects and Grafana]]></title>
        <id>da421abc-57e1-408a-a5c6-c622cb5ef954</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/19/monitoring-openshift-virtualization-using-user-defined-projects-and-grafana"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will teach you how to install and configure the Grafana Operator and integrate it with the openshift-monitoring stack using user-workload-monitoring. At the end of the article, we will import a dashboard with general metrics about Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization, which will give us an overview of the amount of resources in use, virtual machines (VMs) created, and their consumption.
In this article we use the following versions:

Red Hat OpenShift v4.13.4
Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization Operator v4.13.7
Grafana Operator v5.6.0

Prerequisites

User with the cluster-admin cluster role.
Grafana Operator.
User-Defined Projects enabled.

Enable user-defined projects

Execute this command to add enableUserWorkload: true under data/config.yaml:
oc -n openshift-monitoring patch confi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leonardo Araujo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI 학습용 데이터가 말라가고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114521</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114521"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T06:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 당신의 논문이 AI 학습용으로 사용될 가능성이 높아졌다 네이처, 8월 14일 지금 생성형 AI의 큰 과제는 품질이 높은 학습용 데이터 확보다. 그래서 오픈AI를 필두로 빅 테크 기업은 고품질 데이터를 갖고 있는 기업이나 조직과 협의를 통해 경쟁적인 데이터 라이센스 계약을 하고 있다. 들리는 얘기로는 2022년 말에 이미 인터넷의 거의 모든 데이터를 학습용으로 사용했으며 더 이상의 의미...
The post AI 학습용 데이터가 말라가고 있다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiprocessing - Python's best kept secret]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-08-19:/multiprocessing-pythons-best-kept-secret.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/multiprocessing-pythons-best-kept-secret.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I use Python for most of my offline data processing needs.
Recently I had to analyze a big set of data from an experiment.
The unit task was not that difficult, open a file, run a couple of
algorithms, and calculate several metrics from the signal.
It took around ten seconds. All done in Scipy and NumPy.
The "only" problem that I had thousands of files with
a total volume around 20 GB.
It should be trivial to parallelize - or so I thought.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 흡연 이상으로 해로운 소셜미디어? “지금은 비상상황”… 여기에 공감하나요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79580</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/18/npsp_socialmediasurgeongeneral/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_socialmediasurgeongeneral"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T22:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 25일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 흡연자든 흡연자가 아니든 담뱃갑에 흉측한 사진과 함께 충격적인 경고 문구가 등장했던 때를 기억할 겁니다. 2015년 통과된 새로운 국민건강증진법에 따라 담뱃갑에 흡연의 위험성을 경고하는 그림이 삽입된 것은 2016년 말이었습니다. 그전까지는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Formatted Rust kernel documentation available]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986167/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986167/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T22:28:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust code being added to the kernel is documented using the usual rustdoc
conventions; that documentation is now available on kernel.org in
formatted form.  There is also the linux-next version of
the documentation for Rust code that will land in the kernel soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.11-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986163/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986163/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T22:23:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth 6.11 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  According to Linus:


	But it all looks fairly normal. rc4 is bigger than either rc2 or
	rc3 were, but not hugely so, and it's actually a normal pattern,
	where it takes a while before people find some issues. So nothing
	feels all that odd.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“중요한 건 일본의 마음”? 어느 나라 정부인가: 슬로우레터 8월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114450</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114450"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T22:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘중일마’ 파문. 쟁점과 현안. 이재명 연임 성공. 정봉주 탈락. “배타적 행태 배격하자”, 문재인 축사에 야유. 더 깊게 읽기. 채 상병 특검법 새로운 변수. 25만 원도, 노란봉투법도 거부권. “그냥 쉰다”는 청년 5.4%. 개딸 닮아가는 한동훈 강성 팬덤. “회의록은 없습니다.” “대통령 주위에 이상한 역사의식 부추기는 이들.” 다르게 읽기. 5억 상속은 0원, 5억 소득은 1억 원. 총주주수익률을 아십니까....
The post “중요한 건 일본의 마음”? 어느 나라 정부인가: 슬로우레터 8월19일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The units of measurement for software reliability]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9296</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/08/18/the-units-of-measurement-for-software-reliability/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T22:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do the people define software reliability? One answer can be found by analyzing defect report logs: one study found that 42.6% of fault reports were requests for an enhancement, changes to documentation, or a refactoring request; a study of NASA spaceflight software found that 63% of reports in the defect tracking system were change […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google URL Shortener links will no longer be available]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-url-shortener-links-will-no-longer-be-available/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-url-shortener-links-will-no-longer-be-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T20:13:42.773Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand how you will be impacted by our decision to turn off the serving portion of Google URL Shortener.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[삼바 승소? 이재용이 떨고 있는 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114422</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114422"/>
        <updated>2024-08-18T07:04:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 바이오로직스 과징금 처분은 취소, 제일모직 분식회계는 인정… 이재용 편법 승계 항소심 뒤집힐 수도 있다. 분식회계 의혹 승소? 이게 왜 중요한가. 이재용의 복잡한 사연. 이재용의 세 가지 꼼수. 4조8085억 원, 바이오로직스의 마법. 세 가지 범죄 의혹. 2015년 9월15일 무슨 일이 있었나. 결국 이재용 지분 늘려주기 프로젝트였다. TMI지만 결정적인 변수. 두 가지 충돌하는 재판 결과. 이것이...
The post 삼바 승소? 이재용이 떨고 있는 이유. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The I/O journey continues in Bengaluru]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/the-io-journey-continues-in-bengaluru/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/the-io-journey-continues-in-bengaluru/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T20:14:16.968Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's I/O Connect event in Bengaluru highlighted India's contributions to AI and introduced new tools for app development, including AI agents for coding and testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemma for Streaming ML with Dataflow]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-for-streaming-ml-with-dataflow/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-for-streaming-ml-with-dataflow/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T20:14:16.966Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use the Gemma language model to gauge customer sentiment, summarize conversations, and assist with crafting responses in near real-time with minimal latency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Genkit for Go: Build scalable AI-powered apps in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-genkit-for-go-build-scalable-ai-powered-apps-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-genkit-for-go-build-scalable-ai-powered-apps-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T20:14:16.966Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genkit for Go is an open source framework for building AI-powered applications in Go. It leverages Go's simplicity, scalability, and security, and is currently in alpha.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutorial: GNU Coverage with C++ for Embedded Applications]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=41100</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/08/17/tutorial-gnu-coverage-with-c-for-embedded-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T13:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an earlier article I explained how to generate GNU coverage information, for an embedded application written in C. In this article, I show the steps and configuration needed to use GNU gcov targeting an embedded application with C++. Outline … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “밖에서 편하게 사회생활하니까 애 키우는 게 고된 줄 모른다” 맞는 말일까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79558</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/16/npsp_dadbrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_dadbrain"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T22:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 21일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 한국 사회의 저출생 문제를 진단할 때마다 원인으로 지목되는 것 중 하나가 점점 더 심해지는 젠더 갈등입니다. 지난번에 소개한 닉 크리스토프의 칼럼에도 한국 사회의 저출산 대책의 발목을 잡는 근본적인 문제 중 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup comes out of stealth with RISC-V processors to challenge Arm and others]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490652</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/startup-comes-out-of-stealth-with-risc-v-processors-to-challenge-arm-and-others/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T20:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Akeana, a well-funded, 150-strong configurable RISC-V processor startup came out of stealth mode earlier this month to challenge the ‘status quo’ of the semiconductor industry, hoping to unseat both Arm as well as RISC-V companies like SiFive and Andes from design sockets. In the briefing to announce its launch, Akeana CEO Rabin Sugumar said it […]
The post Startup comes out of stealth with RISC-V processors to challenge Arm and others appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indie Games Fund: Google Play’s $2m fund in Latin America is back]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/indie-games-fund-google-plays-2m-fund-in-latin-america-is-back/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/indie-games-fund-google-plays-2m-fund-in-latin-america-is-back/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T20:15:15.945Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Play's Indie Games Fund is back in Latin America for 2024, offering up to $2 million in funding and hands-on support to small game studios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gentoo Linux drops IA-64 (Itanium) support]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/986030/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/986030/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:46:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gentoo Linux project has
announced
that it is dropping support for Itanium:
IA-64 (Itanium)
support in the Linux kernel
and glibc,
and subsequent discussions on our mailing list, as well as
a vote by the Gentoo Council, Gentoo will discontinue all ia64
profiles and keywords. The primary reason for this decision is the
inability of the Gentoo IA-64 team to support this architecture
without kernel support, glibc support, and a functional development
box (or even a well-established emulator). In addition, there have
been only very few users interested in this type of hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Custom string formatters in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985346/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985346/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T15:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has had
formatted string literals
(f-strings), a syntactic shorthand for building
strings, since 2015. Recently, Jim Baker, Guido van Rossum, and Paul Everitt have
proposed

PEP 750 ("Tag Strings For Writing Domain-Specific Languages") which would
generalize and expand that mechanism to provide Python library writers with additional
flexibility. Reactions to the proposed change were somewhat positive, although
there was a good deal of discussion of (and opposition to)
the PEP's inclusion of lazy evaluation of template parameters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985980/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985980/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:07:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (389-ds-base, dotnet8.0, python3.13, roundcubemail, thunderbird, and tor), Mageia (roundcubemail), Oracle (.NET 8.0, bind and bind-dyndb-ldap, bind9.16, container-tools:ol8, edk2, firefox, gnome-shell, grafana, httpd:2.4, jose, kernel, krb5, mod_auth_openidc:2.3, orc, poppler, python-urllib3, python3.11-setuptools, thunderbird, and wget), Red Hat (kernel), SUSE (apptainer, curl, kernel, kernel-firmware, libqt5-qtbase, python-aiosmtpd, and ucode-intel), and Ubuntu (bind9, gnome-shell, libreoffice, and orc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘구글 소송’ 승리한 미국 정부… 구글, 어떻게 할 것인가]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79829</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/16/npsp_googleantitrust/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_googleantitrust"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T12:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국 법무부가 구글을 상대로 한 반독점 소송에서 승소했습니다. 연방법원 아밋 메타 판사는 검색 시장에서 구글이 불법으로 독점적인 지위를 유지해왔다고 판결했습니다. 법원은 다음달 심리를 거쳐 검색 시장에서 구글의 독점을 해소하고 경쟁을 복원하는 시정 명령을 내립니다. 이번 판결의 의미와 앞으로의 전망에 관해 컬럼비아대학교 팀 우 교수의 칼럼을 번역하고, 해설을 덧붙였습니다. 전문 번역: ‘구글 쪼개기’ 초강수 나올까… ‘검색 공룡’ 어떻게 해야 하나 해설: ‘구글 소송’ 승리한 미국 정부… 구글, 어떻게 할 것인가]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create software templates for VMs with OpenShift Virtualization]]></title>
        <id>0e072e19-b716-47b1-b9f7-0fb60153663c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/16/create-software-templates-vms-openshift-virtualization"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous articles in these series, we demonstrated how Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization and Red Hat Developer Hub can increase developer productivity by building virtual machines with a click of a button and showcased the user experience for developers when building a new virtual machine based on the definitions of platform engineering and operations. In this installment, we explore software templates concepts, architecture, and how to use them to build virtual machines (VMs).
The technology stack 
Figure 1 depicts the various technologies used in this solution.


  
      
        
  


  

Figure 1: The technology stack used for this solution.

Red Hat OpenShift is a unified platform to build, modernize, and deploy applications at scale. Work smarter and faster with a complete set…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentina Rodriguez Sosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[요리는 어디에서 시작되는가: 여름 복숭아를 곁들인 가스파초]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114370</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114370"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T02:39:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[필자는 음식 공부한 것에 비해 미식 경험이 풍부한 편은 아니다. 미식과는 전혀 동떨어진 가정환경에서 자랐고 남들은 어려서 한 두 번쯤 충분히 먹어봤을 법한 요리도 성인이 되어서야 경우 경험해 본 것들이 대부분이다. 물 건너 음식을 공부한 덕에 자연스럽게 세계에서 손꼽힌다는 레스토랑도 가볼 기회도 있었지만 ‘에체바리’(바스크의 전설적인 차콜 레스토랑)를 제외하고는 대단하게 큰 인상을 받은 기억도 잘 없다....
The post 요리는 어디에서 시작되는가: 여름 복숭아를 곁들인 가스파초 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최명진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한국 정부의 무지와 일본 정부의 이중성이 만날 때? 사도광산 문화유산 등재 축하하므니다!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114363</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114363"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T01:43:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자신이 얼마나 무지한가를 모르면서 신념을 가진 상태가 가장 위험하다고 했던가. 근대 이후 대부분 전쟁은 지도자의 무지와 오판에서 시작되었다. 광복회장의 일갈, 윤석열 정부의 ‘친일’ 외교 최근 윤석열 정부의 극우 행보가 위험한 지경에 이르렀다. 광복회를 비롯한 독립운동가 단체들이 불참한 광복절 기념식을 누가 상상이나 했을까. 이종찬 광복회장은 “반역자들이 일본 우익과 내통하여 2차 세계대전 이전 일본과 같이 간다는 위기감을 느낀다”고...
The post 한국 정부의 무지와 일본 정부의 이중성이 만날 때? 사도광산 문화유산 등재 축하하므니다! appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[분열과 퇴행, 적의로 가득찬 최악의 광복절 경축사: 슬로우레터 8월16일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114323</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114323"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T22:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[예견된 파국, 윤석열은 아무것도 하지 않았다. “자유가 북한으로 확장하는 통일.” 통일 독트린, 공허했다. ‘검은 세력들’은 누굴까. 쟁점과 현안. 광복절에 기미가요 논란. 김건희 디올 백은 무혐의로 가나. 변호사법 위반 적용도 가능하다. 더 깊게 읽기. 기관장 39%가 문재인 정부 인사, 27%는 사실상 공석. 검찰의 수사 포퓰리즘. 다르게 읽기. 건국절 논란은 이제 그만. “내 딸 삼성전자 주식에 금투세...
The post 분열과 퇴행, 적의로 가득찬 최악의 광복절 경축사: 슬로우레터 8월16일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.32: enhanced analysis, new plugins and more]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1155/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1155/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.32 has been released. Discover enhanced C++ analysis optimization, new plugins and features, and a host of other updates! See more details in this note.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemma explained: An overview of Gemma model family architectures]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-explained-overview-gemma-model-family-architectures/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-explained-overview-gemma-model-family-architectures/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T20:15:06.405Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn more about the different variations of Gemma models, how they are designed for different use cases, and the core parameters of their architecture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI innovation is outpacing security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490648</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ai-innovation-is-outpacing-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T18:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest PSA Certified report for 2024 indicates that 71 percent of AI-driven cyber threats are a significant cause for concern and that while AI innovation maybe be beneficial, its proliferation at the edge also significantly increases attack surfaces. Overall, the report found a gap in AI-security integration that needs to be addressed if organizations […]
The post AI innovation is outpacing security appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Catherine C Lanucha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding to a "legacy" codebase with the help of AI]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-gen-ai.html#memo-09</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-gen-ai.html#memo-09"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T14:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Much of the attention to generative AI in software development is
       about generating code. But it may have a more useful role in helping us
       understand existing code. This is especially true for older codebases
       that are getting hard to maintain ("legacy") or to improve onboarding in
       teams that have a lot of fluctuation.
Birgitta Böckeler demonstrates the possibilities here
       by picking an issue from an open-source hospital management system and
       exploring how AI could help her deal with it.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Memory-management: tiered memory, huge pages, and EROFS]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984839/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984839/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T14:14:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's memory-management developers have been busy in recent times;
it can be hard to keep up with all that has been happening in this core
area.  In an attempt to catch up, here is a look at recent work
affecting tiered-memory systems, underutilized huge pages, and duplicated
file data in the Enhanced Read-Only Filesystem (EROFS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985845/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985845/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T14:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (container-tools:rhel8), Debian (flatpak), Fedora (389-ds-base, dotnet8.0, and roundcubemail), Red Hat (bind9.16, firefox, python-setuptools, and thunderbird), Slackware (dovecot), SUSE (389-ds, curl, kernel, kernel-firmware, kubernetes1.25, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, python-Pillow, and zziplib), and Ubuntu (busybox, linux-azure, and ruby-rmagick).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in version 7.1 of Red Hat’s Migration Toolkit for Applications]]></title>
        <id>6fd190c3-184b-4315-98a4-058673f98711</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/15/whats-new-version-71-red-hats-migration-toolkit-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are pleased to announce the general availability of Red Hat’s Migration Toolkit for Applications (MTA) 7.1.
If you are not familiar with this tool, know that this tool is designed to help you replatform or refactor your existing applications to run on Red Hat OpenShift or Red Hat Application Foundations. With containerization-readiness, source-code analysis, and project management capabilities this tool can help your organization benefit from faster, safer legacy application modernization.
This new release is focused on improving the overall user experience and performance of the tool while introducing new features that address needs coming from modernization and migration field practitioners.
On top of that, the analysis engine that powers MTA has been fine tuned to considerably increa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramon Roman Nissen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your first GPU algorithm: Scan/prefix sum]]></title>
        <id>47d9832d-59e9-4551-9873-487790be950f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/15/your-first-gpu-algorithm-scanprefix-sum"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Part 1 of this series, I explained what GPU programming is on a high level. Now we can move on to exploring your first GPU algorithm: scan/prefix sum.
If you've ever tried programming a GPU before, you're probably familiar with vector addition. This is the use case where you have two large arrays of numbers, and you want to build a new array, representing the element-wise sum. This algorithm is normally used to demonstrate the power of GPU programming, by showcasing one way to exploit its massively parallel capabilities. However, although this example is useful, it misses out on the techniques involved in more advanced GPU programming, because it views parallel programming as simply a tool that exists to parallelize certain workloads, rather than a language or set of computational tools…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenny Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내 철학적 목소리(2020)-1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223548745573</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223548745573?fromRss=true&amp;trackingCode=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T04:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 나는 철학이란 철학적 논증을 비판적으로 검토하는 작업이라고 생각한다. 따라서 제시된 논증이 타당성이 있는지, 건전성이 있는지 비판적으로 검토하는 것이 철학이다. 그런데 우리는 어떤 명제에 대해서 결정적으로 완벽한 정당화를 할 수 없다. 가령 나는 칸트가 주장하는 인간을 목적으로 대우하라는 정언명법을 옳은 것으로 받아들이지만, 그것이 어찌 옳은지 철학적으로 정당화할 수 없다. 그럼에도 불구하고 나는 칸트의 정언명법을 받아들인다. 그것이 바로 내 실존적 선택이다. 이런 의미에서 철학은 논증을 정당화하고 그 부당성을 따지는 지성적 작업이지만, 동시에 그것은 마치 예술 작품이 보여주는 세계를 받아들이는 것처럼 실.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 15, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984770/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984770/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T01:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 15, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희는 공동정범 아니라 방조범? 빠져나가기 어렵게 됐다: 슬로우레터 8월15일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114277</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114277"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T22:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“나라가 있는데도 억울하다.” 광복절 반쪽 경축식. 뭐라고 변명하나. “김건희가 살인자” vs. “책임은 민주당에.” 외교를 뭐로 보고. 쟁점과 현안. 기시다 연임 포기. 관리재정수지 적자 103조 원. 대통령실‧관저 공사 의혹, 무엇을 감추나. 더 깊게 읽기. 공범과 방조범. 김건희는 공동정범이 아니라 방조범? 다르게 읽기. 34도 폭염에 에어컨 설치하다 사망. 출생 신고하고 왔더니 폭격으로 가족 몰살. 금투세 공포는 과장됐다....
The post 김건희는 공동정범 아니라 방조범? 빠져나가기 어렵게 됐다: 슬로우레터 8월15일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a text-based adventure game with Gemma 2]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-a-text-based-adventure-game-with-gemma-2/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-a-text-based-adventure-game-with-gemma-2/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T20:14:32.234Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Create a text-based adventure game using Gemma 2. Here are code snippets and tips for designing the game world, enhancing interactivity and replayability, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing vision sensor capabilities with a 3D image stitching algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490633</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/enhancing-vision-sensor-capabilities-with-a-3d-image-stitching-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T14:58:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rising popularity of time of flight (TOF) cameras in industrial applications, particularly in robotics, is attributed to their exceptional depth computing and infrared (IR) imaging capabilities. Despite these advantages, the inherent complexity of the optical system often constrains the field of view, limiting standalone functionality. This article discusses a 3D image stitching algorithm designed […]
The post Enhancing vision sensor capabilities with a 3D image stitching algorithm appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The need for change in mobile radio front end design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490622</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-need-for-change-in-mobile-radio-front-end-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T14:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global data usage has skyrocketed since the launch of the first smartphones. In 2010 the figure stood at just 2 ZB. Fast forward to now and it has reached 120 ZB and this figure is predicted to increase by a further 150% by the end of 2025. It is estimated that 90% of this data […]
The post The need for change in mobile radio front end design appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 6.10.5, 6.6.46, and 6.1.105]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985669/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985669/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T14:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three new stable kernels have been released: 6.10.5, 6.6.46, and 6.1.105. As usual, they contain important
fixes all over the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Standards for use of unsafe Rust in the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982868/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982868/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T14:17:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust is intended to let programmers write safer code.
But compilers are
not omniscient, and writing Rust code that interfaces with hardware (or that
works with memory outside of Rust's lifetime paradigm) requires, at
some point, the programmer's assurance that some operations are permissible. Benno Lossin

suggested adding
some more documentation to

the Rust-for-Linux project clarifying the
standards for commenting uses of unsafe in kernel code. There's general
agreement that such standards are necessary, but less agreement on exactly when
it is appropriate to use unsafe.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Rust: The Cortex-M QuickStart Template]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490616</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-rust-the-cortex-m-quickstart-template/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:47:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Embedded Rust requires understanding high-level language concepts and the low-level details to interact with hardware. I recommend starting at the high level by reading The Rust Programming Language book. Once you understand those concepts, diving into the embedded side of the equation is easier. We’re not going to take that approach, though, in this […]
The post Embedded Rust: The Cortex-M QuickStart Template appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985654/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985654/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:28:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (389-ds-base), Debian (ffmpeg), Fedora (chromium), Red Hat (.NET 8.0, container-tools:rhel8, edk2, firefox, gnome-shell, grafana, jose, kernel, kernel-rt, krb5, open-vm-tools, orc, pcs, poppler, python-urllib3, and wget), SUSE (gtk2, gtk3, kernel, python-setuptools, python310-setuptools, python312-setuptools, python39-setuptools, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (dotnet8, libcroco, linux-azure, linux-lowlatency, linux-raspi, and linux-oracle).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A self-service approach to building virtual machines at scale]]></title>
        <id>d5a20b96-6f09-4e8a-8a85-f91d06e8f967</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/14/self-service-approach-building-virtual-machines-scale"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Red Hat Developer Hub using Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization, developers can build and deploy their applications and build new virtual machines (VMs) by creating a component and choosing a pre-defined template. 
Platform engineers and operations can extend self-service of creating VMs for developers and enable each software template via RBAC. 
In the previous article in this series, we demonstrated how Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization and Red Hat Developer Hub can increase developer productivity by building virtual machines with a click of a button. In this article, we showcase the user experience for developers when building a new virtual machine based on the definitions of platform engineering and operations. We will define the developer experience, such as how much a developer can co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentina Rodriguez Sosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Tempo Monolithic mode]]></title>
        <id>5ca1298e-548f-4e01-ab7c-9b679d2daa58</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/14/introducing-tempo-monolithic-mode"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting with Red Hat OpenShift distributed tracing 3.2 (tempo-operator v0.10.0), the Tempo operator supports an additional mode of deploying Tempo: the Tempo Monolithic mode, as a tech preview feature.
In this article, we introduce Tempo Monolithic mode, describe the pros and cons, and present example deployment manifests.
What is Tempo Monolithic mode?
In Tempo Monolithic mode all core components such as compactor, distributor, ingester, querier, and query-frontend of Tempo are contained in a single binary, in a single container. This vastly simplifies the deployment, as only a single pod is created, and avoids potential issues arising from distributed deployments such as connectivity issues between pods or nodes, scheduling issues, etc. Additionally, this mode supports storing traces in…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andreas Gerstmayr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오래된 편법과 합법적 약탈, 두산밥캣 합병은 성공할까.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114192</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114192"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T03:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이복현(금융감독원 원장)이 화가 났다. 기자들을 만난 자리에서 “지배주주의 이익을 우선하는 기업 경영 사례가 반복적으로 발생하고 있다”고 지적했다. 두산그룹을 콕 찍어 한 말이다. “만에 하나 조금이나마 부족한 부분이 있다면 횟수 제한을 두지 않고 지속적으로 정정 요구를 하겠다는 게 감독원 입장이며 당국 내에서도 어느 정도 합의가 있는 상황”이라고 했다. 이복현이 과연 두산을 건드릴 수 있을까. 한국 사회의...
The post 오래된 편법과 합법적 약탈, 두산밥캣 합병은 성공할까. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving into JTAG — Security (Part 6)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-6</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-6"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The JTAG interface is an important tool for debugging and testing embedded
systems, providing low-level access to the internal workings of microcontrollers
and other integrated circuits. However, this powerful interface also presents
significant security threats. In the sixth and final part of this Diving into
JTAG article series, we will focus on security issues related to JTAG and the
Debug Port.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 일론 머스크의 관심 값이 64조 원… 인류의 희망을 거는 대가, 맞나요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79531</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/13/npsp_muskpaypackage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_muskpaypackage"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T22:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 18일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 시간은 금이라는 격언이 있습니다. 누구나 이 말을 알지만, 그렇다고 모두가 시간을 금쪽같이 아껴 쓰지는 못합니다. 시간을 효과적으로 쓴다고 반드시 성공하는 건 아니지만, 성공한 사람 가운데는 시간을 소중히 아껴 쓰는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“정상이 아니다”, 조선일보도 못 참는 윤석열 인사 참사: 슬로우레터 8월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114150</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114150"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T22:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[검사 윤석열의 적폐 청산, 대통령 윤석열이 사면. “공감하기 어렵지만 언급하지 않겠다.” 쟁점과 현안. “차별금지법 도입하면 에이즈 확산.” 김형석에 점수 몰아줬다. 상속세 개편되면 김건희도 4억 원 이익. 더 깊게 읽기. 쓴소리 듣는 걸 좋아하는 사람은 없다. “정상이 아니다.” 실세는 김태효, 권력 암투 있었나. 충암파가 국방파 밀어냈다. 우크라이나의 반격, 당황한 푸틴. 다르게 읽기. 안세영의 이유 있는 불만....
The post “정상이 아니다”, 조선일보도 못 참는 윤석열 인사 참사: 슬로우레터 8월14일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to develop code analyzer in 48 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1154/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1154/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static analysis is a robust tool that helps developers to control code quality. Let's try to develop a simple analyzer for Lua using Java and see what's under the static analyzer hood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlining LLM Inference at the Edge with TFLite]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/streamlining-llm-inference-at-the-edge-with-tflite/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/streamlining-llm-inference-at-the-edge-with-tflite/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T20:14:43.218Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[XNNPack, the default TensorFlow Lite CPU inference engine, has been updated to improve performance and memory management, allow cross-process collaboration, and simplify the user-facing API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“여론조사 믿기 어렵다”는 반응까지… 8월을 해리스의 시간이라 하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79812</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/13/npsp_harristrump/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_harristrump"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T19:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[바이든 대통령이 재선 출마를 포기하며 해리스 부통령을 지지한다고 선언한 뒤 새롭게 정해진 매치업에서 해리스가 트럼프 전 대통령을 조금씩 따라잡더니, 지지율에서 역전했다는 여론조사 결과가 나오기 시작하고 있습니다. 이에 관해 공화당 여론조사 전문가가 쓴 칼럼을 분석하고, 최근 새로 발표된 뉴욕타임스와 시에나대학의 여론조사 결과를 분석한 기사를 정리했습니다. 전문번역: 트럼프 캠프는 ‘이 여론조사 결과’를 싫어합니다 해설: “여론조사 믿기 어렵다”는 반응까지… 8월을 해리스의 시간이라 하는 이유]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Zettlr: note-taking and publishing with Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984502/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984502/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T17:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown editors are a dime a dozen. Cheaper than that, actually,
since many of them are open‑source software. Despite the sheer number of
options, finding an editor that has all of the features that one might want can
be tricky. For some users, Zettlr
might the right tool. It is a What You See is What You
Mean (WYSIWYM) editor that stores its work locally as plain Markdown
files. The project is billed as a "one-stop publication
workbench", and is suitable for writing anything from blog posts to
academic papers, maintaining a personal journal, or keeping notes in a Zettlekasten. It
is simple to get started with, but rewards deeper exploration and
customization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Changes coming in PostgreSQL 17]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984599/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984599/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:10:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The

PostgreSQL project has

released beta
versions of PostgreSQL 17 containing several interesting security and usability
improvements, alongside the usual performance improvements and bug fixes. If the
release proceeds according to the usual timeline, the full release of version 17
is expected in September or October.
The most important changes are in what PostgreSQL does when a database
supervisor has their credentials revoked, and added
support for incremental database backups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lix makes its second release]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985484/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985484/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lix, the fork of Nix that LWN covered in July, has made its second release since forking. This one includes substantial changes to the backend code, including removing a dependency on Bison, and getting a change to the Nix language back upstream.




The general theme of Lix 2.91 is to perform another wave of
refactorings and design improvements in preparation for our evolution
plans.



Nevertheless, there are a few exciting user facing changes[.]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incus 6.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985482/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985482/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.4 of the Incus container manager is out.


	This release builds upon the recently added OCI support from Incus
	6.3, making it even easier to run application containers. It also
	adds a number of useful new features for clustered and larger
	environments with more control on the virtual CPU used when live
	migrating VMs and finer grained resource constraints within
	projects.


See this
announcement for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985481/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985481/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:28:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel and roundcube), Fedora (microcode_ctl, pypy, python2.7, and python3.6), Oracle (389-ds-base, httpd, kernel, kernel-container, and linux-firmware), Red Hat (kernel-rt), SUSE (firefox, kubernetes1.23, libqt5-qtbase, openssl-1_1, python-gunicorn, python-Twisted, python-urllib3, and qt6-base), and Ubuntu (linux-aws-5.15, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-raspi, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-oem-6.8, linux-oracle-5.15, and qemu).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Podman Desktop to containers in production]]></title>
        <id>173632a6-e43f-4a47-933b-d865d6d42123</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/13/podman-desktop-containers-production"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will take you through the process of getting started with Podman Desktop, creating a Node.js application (you can use your preferred programming language instead, if you like) and building it into a container using Podman Desktop, and configuring a continuous integration (CI) pipeline to build and push your container images to Quay.io using GitHub Actions workflows. In essence this is an introduction to the inner and outer loops of cloud-native development.
To get started, install Podman Desktop. This step is pretty straightforward, owing to the fact that Podman Desktop has a downloads page that supports typical installation flows for Linux, macOS, and Windows and has setup guides for each platform. Once installed, it will look something like this (Figure 1).



  
        


…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evan Shortiss</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[작비와 금시: 이진숙을 생각함]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114128</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114128"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T04:16:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 이광진이라는 사람 500년 전에 이광진(1513~1566년)이라는 사람이 있었다. 역사적으로 유명한 인물은 아니지만 어릴 적 공부할 때는 똑똑하다는 소리를 들었고 나이가 들어 벼슬에 나가서는 유능하고 강직하다는 세평을 얻었다. <명종실록>과 그의 행장·묘지명 등을 보면 1548년 예문관 검열로 벼슬살이를 시작해 수재들에게 주어졌던 승문원과 교서관의 여러 관직을 맡았다. 학문이 높은 성균관에서도 일했고 맑고 깨끗한 사간원·사헌부·홍문관의 벼슬도 두루 맡았다. 호조·공조·예조·병조에서는...
The post 작비와 금시: 이진숙을 생각함 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열이 텔레그램을 보냈다, “기도 좀 해주세요”: 슬로우레터 8월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114093</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114093"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T22:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사상 초유 광복절 경축식 취소. 우리가 모두 합의한 세 가지 역사 원칙. “친일 논란? 학문적 논의가 필요하다.” 뉴라이트가 장악한 윤석열 정부. 쟁점과 현안. 채 상병 외압 의혹 김용현을 국방부 장관으로. 결국 방송 4법 거부권 행사. 더 깊게 읽기. “안이한 건가. 대범한 건가.” “행정은 내가 더 잘한다.” “남 좋은 일만 시킬 수도 있다.” 다르게 읽기. 전기차...
The post 윤석열이 텔레그램을 보냈다, “기도 좀 해주세요”: 슬로우레터 8월13일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flax Engine. Exploring game engine & analyzing its source code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1153/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1153/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["It's like Unreal and Unity had a baby," as the GameDev community has affectionately described the engine. Not only is that a cute way to describe the engine, but it's also quite spot-on. It's...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How it's Made: GenType Alphabet Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T20:14:35.684Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of our newest experiments in the series is GenType. This tool uses generative AI to create an alphabet out of anything you want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] COSMIC desktop makes its debut]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984638/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984638/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T17:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux hardware vendor System76 started promoting
its work on a Rust-based, Wayland
desktop environment for its Pop!_OS
Ubuntu-derivative distribution almost two years
ago. On August 8, the company released an alpha version of the COSMIC desktop environment for
users to test out. While it has rough edges and missing features, it
is stable enough to get a good feel for what the finished product has
in store—and the initial results are promising.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magit 4.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985350/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985350/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.0 of the Magit text-based
Git user interface for Emacs has been released. Changes since the 3.3.0
release include the addition of context menus, a makeover for the
menu-bar menu, new menu commands, and many other new features and bug
fixes. See the release
notes for full details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust Project goals for 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985296/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985296/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:47:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust project has developed a
set of goals for the latter half of 2024.


	Rust
	for Linux. The experimental support for Rust
	development in the Linux kernel is a watershed moment for Rust,
	demonstrating to the world that Rust is indeed capable of targeting
	all manner of low-level systems applications. And yet today that
	support rests on a number of
	unstable features, blocking the effort from ever going beyond
	experimental status. For 2024H2 we will work to close the largest
	gaps that block support.


Other goals include completing the 2024 Rust
Edition and improving the language's async support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985336/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985336/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T15:08:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (httpd:2.4), Fedora (chromium, firefox, frr, neatvnc, nss, python-setuptools, and python3.13), Gentoo (AFLplusplus, Bundler, dpkg, GnuPG, GPAC, libde265, matio, MuPDF, PHP, protobuf, protobuf-python, protobuf-c, rsyslog, Ruby on Rails, and runc), Red Hat (389-ds-base, container-tools:rhel8, and httpd:2.4), SUSE (bind and ca-certificates-mozilla), and Ubuntu (linux-azure).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지방선거제도 개혁, 2년도 부족하다 당장 시작하자]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114064</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114064"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T08:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[22대 국회가 개원했습니다. 유권자의 소중한 한 표, 한 표를 읍소하며 당선된 300명의 국회의원이 과연 유권자를 위해 제대로 일하는지 지켜보고 감시해야 할 때입니다. 이들이 어떤 일을 하는지, 어떤 일을 해야 하는데 안 하는지에 따라 우리의 삶이 달라지니까요. 참여연대 의정감시센터는 칼럼을 통해 유권자의 시각에서 22대 국회와 정치를 비평합니다. 무엇보다 ‘중’요한 건 ‘꺾’이지 않는 ‘정’치개혁이니까요. 이번 칼럼의 필자는...
The post 지방선거제도 개혁, 2년도 부족하다 당장 시작하자 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Greenboot: Automate rollbacks for atomically updated systems]]></title>
        <id>6aa6d960-df0e-4eba-80d1-40e7e47541b1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/12/greenboot-automate-rollbacks-atomically-updated-systems"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In mid-July, a faulty configuration update caused a significant global IT disruption, leading to transportation delays, point-of-sale issues, telecommunications outages and more. Affected machines entered a boot loop or boot recovery mode, rendering them inoperative; this underscores  the critical need for robust automated recovery mechanisms in IT infrastructure. One answer being iterated upon by the open source community is Greenboot, which is currently available in Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) for Edge, Red Hat In-Vehicle Operating System and Fedora IoT.
Greenboot is designed to automatically recover from failed upgrades by integrating with systemd and atomically updated distros. It acts as a guardian for your system’s health, so that if an update goes awry, the system can automatica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eliane Pereira, Eric Curtin, Micah Abbott, Sayan Paul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrate a private AI coding assistant into your CDE using Ollama, Continue, and OpenShift Dev Spaces]]></title>
        <id>5e1e4057-01f3-481f-9f5f-e763e17870a3</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/12/integrate-private-ai-coding-assistant-ollama"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, developers are looking for ways to include powerful new technologies like AI assistants to improve their workflow and productivity. However, many companies are reluctant to allow such technology due to privacy, security, and IP law concerns. 
This activity addresses the concerns about privacy and security and describes how to deploy and integrate a private AI assistant in the emulated air-gapped on-premise environment. We will guide you through setting up a CDE (cloud development environment) using Ollama, Continue, Llama3, and Starcoder2 large language models (LLMs) with Red Hat OpenShift Dev Spaces, empowering you to code faster and more efficiently.  
Ready to streamline your cloud development workflow and bring some AI into it? Grab your favorite beverage, and let's emb…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilya Buziuk, Manuel Hahn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Network Observability 1.6]]></title>
        <id>4e0d9b7b-d792-441c-86aa-cf75af7d3244</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/12/whats-new-network-observability-16"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network Observability 1.6 was released in June 2024. Even though this is considered a minor version upgrade from 1.5, it is a significant release that could lower the barrier to adoption into production.
But before we go further, for those of you new to Network Observability, it is an optional operator that provides a slew of capabilities to track and provide insight into your network traffic flows. While it works on any Kubernetes cluster, it works even better in a Red Hat OpenShift environment, which is what I will focus on in this article. I will only discuss the new features in this release so if you want the full feature list, read the documentation on About Network Observability.
Graphs and logs without Loki and Storage
Prior to 1.4, Network Observability required an external compone…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“비트코인을 다시 위대하게”, 미국 대선 흔드는 크립토 정치 경제학.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=114016</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/114016"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T04:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사토시 나카모토라는 익명의 사용자가 2008년 [비트코인: 피어 투 피어 전자 현금 시스템]이라는 글을 온라인 게시판에 포스팅하고 이듬해 첫 발굴이 시작된 뒤에도 비트코인은 한동안 첨단 기술에 능통한 소수의 괴짜나 관심을 두는 기이한 대상으로 취급되었다.  하지만 가격이 급등하면서 수많은 사람이 비트코인과 다양한 암호 자산을 투자 대상의 하나로 인식하게 됐다. 시가총액(8월9일 기준) 상위 기업들과 비교하면 비트코인은 1.2조 달러로...
The post “비트코인을 다시 위대하게”, 미국 대선 흔드는 크립토 정치 경제학. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>신현호</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[뱀 기름 장수에게 속지 않는 방법: AI가 당신을 더 똑똑하게 해주진 않는다는 불편한 진실.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113973</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113973"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T03:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[연재를 시작하며. 얼마 전에 슬로우뉴스 이정환 대표를 만나 얘기하던 중 과거 슬로우뉴스에 ‘테크 뉴스 브리핑’을 썼던 기억이 나서 AI 뉴스와 칼럼 중 우리가 관심 있게 보면 좋겠다는 것을 선정해 위클리로 알려주는 코너를 만들어 보자고 했다. 먼저 제목을 정하려고 하다가 앤스로픽의 클로드와 상의했다. 클로드가 몇 개를 제안했고 ‘AI in a Week’와 ‘AI Weekly Digest’를 비교하다 클로드가...
The post 뱀 기름 장수에게 속지 않는 방법: AI가 당신을 더 똑똑하게 해주진 않는다는 불편한 진실. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.11-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985233/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985233/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T22:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.11-rc3 right on
schedule.  "Nothing particularly strange or interesting going on, things
look normal".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김경수 복권? 윤석열과 한동훈, 둘 중 하나는 지는 싸움: 슬로우레터 8월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113957</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113957"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T22:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“송구하고 힘들다.” 유철환‧정승윤 물러나야 한다. 쟁점과 현안. 김경수 복권? 윤석열과 한동훈의 다른 셈법. “김건희 조사, 법과 원칙 따랐을 것.” 광복회, 광복절 기념식 불참 선언. 더 깊게 읽기. 전기차 포비아 원인은 정보 비대칭. 유럽에서는 배터리 여권제. 완충차 출입금지? 경합주도 해리스가 앞서나. 학교 기도실에 폭격. 다르게 읽기. ‘독재의 평범성’. 수사기관이 국민 10% 개인정보 수집. 해법과 대안. 맥주병...
The post 김경수 복권? 윤석열과 한동훈, 둘 중 하나는 지는 싸움: 슬로우레터 8월12일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Student projects for 2024/2025]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9278</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/08/11/student-projects-for-2024-2025/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T21:13:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It will soon be that time of year when university students are looking for an interesting idea for a project. On an irregular basis, I post some ideas for thesis projects (here and here); primarily for students studying computing. In a change of direction, this post suggests software related ideas for business student projects. Two […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get me two! PVS-Studio plugin update for SonarQube]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1152/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1152/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PVS-Studio plugin for SonarQube has been around for a long time. However, in the latest update, we've turned one plugin into two plugins! This post will explain why it happened, what's new, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling more private generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/enabling-more-private-gen-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/enabling-more-private-gen-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T20:14:12.101Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has developed a number of technologies that you can use to start experimenting with and exploring the potential of generative AI to process data that needs to stay private.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three weekend stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985198/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985198/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T14:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.10.4,
6.6.45, and
6.1.104
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important updates as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[쇼트] 가능성의 예술로서 다현장문화기술지]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=4127</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2024/multisite/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T09:20:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[동시에 그는 말리노프스키(Bronisław Kasper Malinowski)가  파푸아뉴기니 남동부의 여러 섬들 사이의 교환 체계인 쿨라링(Kula Ring)을 따라 이동하며 연구했던 점을 지적하면서 다현장 연구가 아주 최근의 것만은 아님을 지적하기도 한다. 그럼에도 문화기술지 쓰기가 '가능성의 예술'이라면, 오늘날 어떠한 방식의 방법론적 변화가 가능할 것인가?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost File Scanning Speed: Query File Attributes on Windows 50x Faster]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/cpp-query-file-attribs-faster/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/cpp-query-file-attribs-faster/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you’re developing a tool that needs to scan for file changes across thousands of project files. Retrieving file attributes efficiently becomes critical for such scenarios. In this article, I’ll demonstrate a technique to get file attributes that can achieve a surprising speedup of over 50+ times compared to standard Windows methods.
Let’s dive in and explore how we can achieve this.



     
    


The inspiration for this article came from a recent update for Visual Assist - a tool that heavily improves Visual Studio experience and productivity for C# and C++ developers.
In one of their blog post, they shared:
The initial parse is 10..15x faster!
What’s New in Visual Assist 2024—Featuring lightning fast parser performance [Webinar] - Tomato Soup
After watching the webinar, I notic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How good can you be at Codenames without knowing any words?]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/codenames/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/codenames/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About eight years ago, I was playing a game of Codenames where the game state was such that our team would almost certainly lose if we didn't correctly guess all of our remaining words on our turn. From the given clue, we were unable to do this. Although the game is meant to be a word guessing game based on word clues, a teammate suggested that, based on the physical layout of the words that had been selected, most of the possibilities we were considering would result in patterns that were "too weird" and that we should pick the final word based on the location. This worked and we won.

[Click to expand explanation of Codenames if you're not familiar with the game]
Codenames is played in two teams. The game has a 5x5 grid of words, where each word is secretly owned by one of {blue team, re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 fun Gemma project ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/3-fun-gemma-project-ideas/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/3-fun-gemma-project-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T20:14:10.811Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Gemma models to translate an old language, brainstorm game design ideas, and write a letter to Santa.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[학교에...]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223543049809</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223543049809?fromRss=true&amp;trackingCode=rss"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T03:53:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오랜기간.. 많은 시간을 보낸 학교.. 그 많은 시간들이 때로는 힘들고 지치고 많은 고민들로 채워졌을거라 생각하면 우리에겐 가슴아픈 장소로 남았다. 외로웠을 그시간들.. 그 허기진 마음을 술로 다 채우지 않았을까.. "홀로 황량한 모래바람이 부는 사막을 걷는 기분이였다"라고..했던... 그 길 끝에 그의 나무가 있다..... 언제쯤 편히 이곳을 찾을수 있을까...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Meeting the Debian Technical Committee]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984720/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984720/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T01:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is something of a DebConf tradition that members of the Debian Technical
Committee (TC) take the stage to talk about the work that the committee
does—and more.  DebConf24 in
Busan, South Korea was no exception, as TC chair Sean Whitton, who
will complete his term at the end of the year, and one
of its newest members, Stefano Rivera, described the constitutional
underpinnings of the TC, how it tries to make decisions when it needs to,
and the constant process of recruiting new members.  After that, they took
a few questions from the audience.  The session provided a nice overview of
the TC and its role in Debian, but it may well be of interest further afield.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with Gemma on Ray on Vertex AI]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/get-started-with-gemma-on-ray-on-vertex-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/get-started-with-gemma-on-ray-on-vertex-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T20:15:19.586Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Gemma Supervised tuning on Ray on Vertex AI to train and serve machine learning models efficiently and effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new kernel-version policy for Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/985043/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/985043/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T19:47:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Canonical Kernel Team has announced
a new policy regarding the version of the kernel that will ship with each
Ubuntu release; the result will generally be the shipping of newer
releases.


	To provide users with the absolute latest in features and hardware
	support, Ubuntu will now ship the absolute latest available version
	of the upstream Linux kernel at the specified Ubuntu release freeze
	date, even if upstream is still in Release Candidate (RC) status.


The post goes on to acknowledge that "there are issues with this
approach"; there are a lot of policy details that will apply depending
on just how raw the shipped kernel is.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Distinguishing Debian testing from unstable]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984635/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984635/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T15:12:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, the smallest changes create the longest discussions.  As a case
in point, a proposal to make a one-line change in an informational text
file on systems running the Debian unstable distribution has blown up into
an interminable and sometimes unfriendly debate.  At its core, though, this
discussion comes down to a seemingly simple question: should a program be
able to determine whether it is running on a Debian testing or unstable
system?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New attack against the SLUB allocator]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984984/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984984/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T15:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from Graz University of Technology have
published details of a new attack
on the Linux kernel called SLUBStick. The attack uses timing information to turn an ability to trigger use-after-free or double-free bugs into the ability to overwrite page tables, and thence into the ability to read and write arbitrary areas of memory. The good news is that this attack does require an existing bug to be usable; the bad news is that the kernel regularly sees bugs of this kind.



We assume that an unprivileged user has code execution. 
Additionally, we consider the presence of a heap vulnerability
in the Linux kernel. We assume that the Linux kernel 
incorporates all defense mechanisms available in version 6.4, the
most recent Linux kernel version when we started our work.
These mechanisms include features such as WˆX, KASLR,
SMAP, and kCFI. We do not assume any microarchitectural 
vulnerabilities, e.g., transient execution, fault
injection, or hardware side channels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[극단적 소수의 폭정, 어디서부터 무엇을 해야할까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113908</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113908"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T15:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[하버드 정치학과 교수인 저자들은 두 번 충격받았다. 처음 트럼프 당선에 당황해 절치부심 쓴 책이 [어떻게 민주주의는 무너지는가] (How Democracies Die, 2018). 트럼프 덕분에 세계적 베스트셀러를 내놓은 저자들은 4년 뒤 트럼프 지지자들의 국회의사당 습격 사건에 다시 경악했다. 당시 현직 대통령 트럼프는 물론, 공화당의 주류까지 바이든이 이긴 선거 결과에 불복했다. 저자들은 민주주의에, 특히 미국 민주주의에 구멍이 있다는...
The post 극단적 소수의 폭정, 어디서부터 무엇을 해야할까 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984966/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984966/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T13:23:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (httpd, kernel, kernel-rt, and libtiff), Debian (postgresql-13, postgresql-15, and thunderbird), Fedora (frr, thunderbird, vim, and xrdp), Gentoo (Librsvg, Nautilus, ncurses, Percona XtraBackup, QEMU, and re2c), Red Hat (httpd, kernel, kernel-rt, openssl, and python-setuptools), SUSE (bind, ffmpeg-4, kubernetes1.23, kubernetes1.24, python-Django, and python3-Twisted), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-raspi, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-ibm, linux-nvidia, linux-nvidia-6.8, linux-oem-6.8, linux-nvidia-lowlatency, linux-oracle, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, and salt).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building virtual machines with Red Hat Developer Hub: The what, why, and how]]></title>
        <id>bbbd5780-a5de-4cf2-92aa-1671287bf566</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/09/building-virtual-machines-red-hat-developer-hub-what-why-and-how"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization enables teams to run and deploy their new and existing virtual machine (VM) workloads into Red Hat OpenShift. OpenShift Virtualization offers a path for infrastructure and application modernization, taking advantage of the simplicity and speed of a cloud-native application platform and aims to preserve existing virtualization investments while embracing modern management principles.
What are the main benefits of Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization?
Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization offers developers, IT operations, and platform engineers a comprehensive solution that simplifies VM migration and deployment, speeds up time to production, and unifies management across VMs, containers, and serverless workloads (Figure 1). Integrating existing virtual machines with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentina Rodriguez Sosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[화장하되 표정까지 가려선 안 된다: 두릅 에그베네딕트]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113894</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113894"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[봄의 재료를 이야기하면 누구나 봄나물을 떠올릴 것이다. 혹독한 겨울을 인고해 봄의 생동감과 생명력을 표현하는데 봄나물만큼 좋은 재료가 또 있을까? 오늘의 주인공은 그 중에서도 ‘봄나물의 왕’ 이라고 불리는 두릅이다. 인터넷에 두릅을 치면 여지없이 건강에 관한 정보가 쏟아져 나온다. 사포닌 성분으로 혈당을 낮추고 당뇨병을 예방하고 신경안정의 효과도 있다고 한다. 혹시 내일부터 두릅을 아침마다 한 뿌리씩이라도 씹어야 하나...
The post 화장하되 표정까지 가려선 안 된다: 두릅 에그베네딕트 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최명진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8/9, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595822</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595822/8-9-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T00:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSoC 2024: GPU Libc Benchmarking]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2024-08-09-libc-gpu-benchmarking/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2024-08-09-libc-gpu-benchmarking/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey everyone! My name is James and I worked on LLVM this summer through GSoC. My project is called GPU Libc Benchmarking. The main objective of this project was to develop microbenchmarking infrastructure for libc on the GPU.
Background
The LLVM libc project was designed as an alternative to glibc that aims to be modular, configurable, and sanitizer-friendly. Currently, LLVM libc is being ported to Nvidia and AMD GPUs to give libc functionality (e.g. printf(), malloc(), and math functions) on the GPU. As of March 2024, programs can use GPU libc in offloading languages (CUDA, OpenMP) or through direct compilation and linking with the libc library.
What We Did
During this project, we developed a microbenchmarking framework that is directly compiled for and run on the GPU, using libc function…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The LLVM Project Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이미지와 프레임: ‘위어드’는 어떻게 2024 미 대선 판도를 흔들고 있나]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113486</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113486"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T22:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인트로: 이미지와 프레임 이제는 미국인의 절반 이상이 게이 결혼을 지지한다. 19개 주에서는 게이 결혼이 합법이다. 그러나 나머지 31개 주에서는 아직 갈 길이 멀다. 게이 결혼은 성경에 위배된다, 결혼의 정의 자체를 위협한다, 아이들을 동성애로 유인할 것이다, 게이 결혼은 섹스가 전부다 등의 보수적 프레임은 바뀌지 않았다. 최근의 보수주의자들은 ‘섹스’라는 단어와 ‘호모’라는 비어가 들어간 ‘호모 섹슈얼(homosexual)’이라는 말을 반복해서...
The post 이미지와 프레임: ‘위어드’는 어떻게 2024 미 대선 판도를 흔들고 있나 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 디올 백 조사했던 권익위 국장 의문의 죽음: 슬로우레터 8월9일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113843</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113843"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T22:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[외교부가 국민들을 속였다. 광복절에 KBS 이승만 미화 다큐멘터리. 쟁점과 현안. 김건희 명품 백 조사했던 권익위 국장 자살. 한동훈의 첫 작품은 취약계층 전기요금 1만5000원. “민주당 제안 받아들여라.” 더 깊게 읽기. 그린벨트 풀어 부동산 잡는다고? 윤석열은 검찰을 이길 수 있을까. 2명 방통위는 뭘 해도 위법. 미국 실업수당 청구 줄었다. 다르게 읽기. “보수도 포퓰리즘을 해야 한다.” 김대중의 79석과...
The post 김건희 디올 백 조사했던 권익위 국장 의문의 죽음: 슬로우레터 8월9일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even great mathematicians make mistakes]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1151/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1151/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We know that math is a science of precision. Can we say the same about GeoGebra, an interactive math learning software? Let's analyze the project source code using PVS-Studio!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Built Purrfect Code: A Puzzle Game for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-we-built-purrfect-code/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-we-built-purrfect-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T20:15:27.158Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Purrfect Code is a sokoban style box pushing puzzler Purrfect based on Google tech (Flutter, IDX, FLAME, Firebase) and designed to be playable on web browsers. Open the game in Project IDX, earn badges for each level, and showcase your badges on your Developer Profile.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Flash price drop with tuning rollout complete, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-flash-updates-google-ai-studio-gemini-api/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-flash-updates-google-ai-studio-gemini-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T20:15:27.157Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Flash is now available to developers at more than 70% lower prices. Set up billing for Gemini API in Google AI Studio and access other new features like 1.5 Flash tuning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0.0.0.0 Day: Exploiting Localhost APIs From the Browser (Oligo Security)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984838/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984838/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T17:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Oligo Security blog discloses
a web-browser vulnerability that has been named "0.0.0.0 day".  In short,
browsers will allow JavaScript code to open connections to the all-zeroes
IPv4 address; the result is that any port that is open on the local host
can be accessed by a remote site.  "When services use localhost, they
assume a constrained environment. This assumption, which can (as in the
case of this vulnerability) be faulty, results in insecure server
implementations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Endless OS aimed at educational and offline environments]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984086/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984086/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T13:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Endless OS is a Linux distribution with a focus on improving access to
educational tools by providing a simple-to-manage, full-featured desktop for
educators and students — one that works offline, with minimal maintenance. The
distribution also aims to be suitable for older devices, in order to promote access to
computers by ensuring those systems remain usable.
In pursuit of those goals, it makes some unusual technical
choices. But what makes the distribution really shine is its curated collection
of software and educational resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984807/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984807/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T13:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (freeradius and freeradius:3.0), Debian (chromium, odoo, and roundcube), Fedora (microcode_ctl, mingw-qt5-qtbase, mingw-qt6-qtbase, opentofu, orc, python-setuptools, and vim), Gentoo (Nokogiri), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (go-toolset:rhel8, golang, kernel, krb5, libtiff, python-setuptools, and python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9), SUSE (python-Django), and Ubuntu (krb5).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using GDB to time travel]]></title>
        <id>928f76cf-1c65-4c3e-8c9f-097b04ddfabf</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/08/using-gdb-time-travel"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Time traveling is an extremely useful tool for developers that found a bug in their code. Beyond wanting to travel to a future where the bug is fixed, developers will usually try to slow down time with a debugger, so they can examine where things go wrong. But what if even with a debugger, it is still too late and the bug has already happened? Wouldn’t it be nice to be able to go back in time and see it happening in real time?
Let’s talk about time travel debugging. In this post, I’ll go over the following commands:

record
record stop
record save
record full restore
reverse-next (rn)
reverse-step (rs)
set exec-direction
reverse-continue (rc)

As a final note, there are many implementations on many different debuggers, but this post will be focusing on GNU Debugger’s (GDB) record-full impl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Guinevere Larsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with OperatorPolicy]]></title>
        <id>c2913360-d3d6-403e-9695-1b5b0ed59b57</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/08/getting-started-operatorpolicy"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We introduced OperatorPolicy as a tech preview feature in Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes (RHACM) version 2.10 to improve the management of Kubernetes-native applications packaged with the Operator Lifecycle Manager (OLM) across a fleet of clusters. With the RHACM 2.11 release, this feature is now ready for you to try, with improvements in the following scenarios:

Getting started: you have fewer required fields, lowering your barrier to entry.
Controlling upgrades: an initial installation is treated separately from later upgrades, and you can have either restricted to specific versions of the operator.
Alert control: you can configure which situations are considered as violations, or are just informational for your specific needs.
Uninstallation: you have new tools to a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Justin Kulikauskas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stand-by or boot-up]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1688.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1688.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T06:49:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like most people nowadays, I have a selection of electronic devices that have become part of the fabric of my life. I have certain expectations: I want a device to do what it is supposed to do. I want it to be easy to use. I am after reliability. I want it to consume the minimum amount of power – either to conserve battery life or to simply be environmentally friendly. Lastly, I want the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984216/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984216/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T01:37:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 8, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in July (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/july-2024-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/july-2024-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
July.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“한동훈은 바보 아니면 사기꾼, 자기 돈이어도 그랬을까”: 슬로우레터 8월8일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113733</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113733"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T22:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“얼마나 잘하나 보자.” 윤석열의 꿀 휴가. 쟁점과 현안. “다시는 사과하지 않겠다.” “친일을 넘어 숭일.” 통신 조회도 영장 받아야 한다. 다르게 읽기. 한국 주식 시장은 왜 찔끔 올랐을까. 일본은 “당분간 금리 인상 없다.” 세 번째 채 상병 특검법 발의. 더 깊게 읽기. 월즈와 밴스, 중간이 없다. “걔들 좀 이상하지 않아요?” 해리스-트럼프 초접전 양상. 해법과 대안. 가입...
The post “한동훈은 바보 아니면 사기꾼, 자기 돈이어도 그랬을까”: 슬로우레터 8월8일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox support added to Puppeteer]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984733/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984733/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T19:20:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has announced that Puppeteer, a browser automation and testing library, now has first-class support for Firefox using the
WebDriver BiDi protocol. Puppeteer can be used to drive headless browser instances, and is commonly used for automated end-to-end web site tests.



Whilst the features offered by Puppeteer won't be a surprise,
bringing support to multiple browsers has been a significant
undertaking. The Firefox support is not based on a Firefox-specific
automation protocol, but on WebDriver BiDi, a cross browser protocol
that's undergoing standardization at the W3C, and currently has
implementation in both Gecko and Chromium. This use of a
cross-browser protocol should make it much easier to support many
different browsers going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] CRIB: checkpoint/restore in BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984313/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984313/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T15:35:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The desire for the ability to checkpoint a process — to record its state in
a form that can be restarted at a future time — on Linux is almost as old as
Linux itself.  See, for example, this announcement of a checkpoint
project that appeared in LWN in 1998.  While working solutions exist, they
can be somewhat fragile and difficult to use; it is not surprising that
some people are interested in finding a better alternative.  A current
effort goes by the name CRIB,
for Checkpoint/Restore in (naturally) BPF.  It is far from clear that CRIB
will replace the existing solutions, but it is an interesting look at a
different way of solving the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Tracing the source of filesystem errors]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984556/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984556/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T14:18:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are lots of places in the kernel where an EINVAL can be
returned to user space, but it is often unclear what the actual underlying
problem is because the errno
error codes are too generic.  That is the problem that Miklos Szeredi
wanted to discuss in a filesystem session that he led remotely at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  He would like to help
those who are trying to debug problems trace where in the kernel a
particular error code is being generated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/08/python-3125-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/08/python-3125-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T13:17:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.12.5:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3125/

 
This is the fifth maintenance release of Python 3.12
Python 3.12 is the newest major release of the Python programming 
language, and it contains many new features and optimizations. 3.12.5 is
 the latest maintenance release, containing more than 250 bugfixes, 
build improvements and documentation changes since 3.12.4.
This version of Python 3.12 also comes with pip 24.2 by default. However,
 due to an incompatibility with older macOS versions, macOS 10.9 through
 10.12 will downgrade their version of pip to 24.1.2 during the 
installation process (in the Install Certificates step). See the installer ReadMe and the pip issue on the matter
 for more information. Versions of macOS o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984702/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984702/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T13:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr, openjdk-17, and wpa), Gentoo (aiohttp, Bitcoin, Cairo, Go, json-c, Levenshtein, libXpm, nghttp2, PostgreSQL, and Redis), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, python-setuptools, python-urllib3, python3.11-setuptools, and wget), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (bind, curl, docker, ffmpeg, ffmpeg-4, kernel, kernel-firmware, libnbd, patch, shadow, and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (python-django and wpa).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is GPU programming]]></title>
        <id>f773cd03-dec8-4c51-bffd-04599a174f03</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/07/what-gpu-programming"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome! This guide will help you get started with general purpose graphics processing unit (GPU) programming, otherwise known as GPGPU. It is intended to:

Teach you the basics of parallel GPU programming, such as the SIMD model.
Walk you through some key algorithms, such as scan/prefix sum, quicksort, and game of life.
Show you working examples of code from OpenAI’s Triton, CUDA, OpenCL, torch.compile, Numba, and HIP/HCC.
Help you determine which framework to use, and go over any common pitfalls.

This guide focuses more on the algorithms and architecture, with a heavy emphasis on how to effectively use the computational model. In my personal experience, I found GPU programming to be a fascinating concept, although many of the existing resources seemed to be focused primarily on system-l…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kenny Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사람을 귀하게 여겨야 하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=13437</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2024/08/07/why-value-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T03:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자기 꿈이 있는 사람은 사람을 귀하게 여깁니다.누가 언제 어떻게 나를 도와줄지 모르기 때문입니다.이렇게 도와달라고 말을 합니다. 자기 꿈에 도취된 사람은 사람을 허투루 여깁니다.내 꿈을 위해 희생시킬 사람이 필요하거든요.이렇게 하라고 부추깁니다. 전자는 옆에 있는 사람이 자꾸 불어납니다.후자는 옆에 있는 사람이 자꾸 사라지죠. 전자는 자꾸 자기 실력을 기릅니다.일은 자기가 하는 거고, 다른 사람은 나를 도와줄 뿐이니까요. 후자는... Continue Reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘인구소멸’ 한국을 위해 할 수 있는 일]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79516</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/06/npsp_aging/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aging"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T22:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 14일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 대한민국 모든 시·도의 고령 인구 비중이 7%를 넘어서면서 본격적인 고령화 사회에 진입했다는 뉴스가 나온 게 어느덧 13년 전의 일입니다. 이후 한국 사회의 인구 구조가 어떻게 바뀌었는지는 모두 아실 겁니다. 통계를 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사도광산 외교 참사, 알고도 속고 국민들도 속였다: 슬로우레터 8월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113610</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113610"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T22:19:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“강제 동원 명시” 요구했다가 거절당했다. 외교를 포기하고 외교를 했다는 거짓말. 코스피 하루 만에 반등. 알고리즘 매매가 변동성 키웠다. 쟁점과 현안. 원전 3기만큼 전력 수요 늘었다. 독립기념관장도 뉴라이트. 더 깊게 읽기. 영향력 1위면서 불신하는 언론사 1위는? 한국판 셔먼법 가능할까. 해리스 러닝메이트는 팀 월즈. 다르게 읽기. 1억 전기차에 왜 중국 배터리 넣었을까. 전기차는 주차장 출입 금지? 자살이...
The post 사도광산 외교 참사, 알고도 속고 국민들도 속였다: 슬로우레터 8월7일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to find job for Rescue Rangers: analyzing Godot Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1150/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1150/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developing and playing games can be an incredibly engaging, addictive, and satisfying activity. But nothing spoils the gameplay experience like a tricky hidden bug. So, today we'll be looking at an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 lessons every developer should learn from CrowdStrike’s Doomsday update]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490592</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/lessons-every-developer-should-learn-from-crowdstrikes-doomsday-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T16:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, opening social media or your favorite news application is impossible without hearing about the latest security incident. This time, it wasn’t a security breach that caught headlines; it was a security company that rolled out an update that crashed Windows computers, causing a massive IT outage that affected 8.5 million computers. Those customers […]
The post 7 lessons every developer should learn from CrowdStrike’s Doomsday update appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] CircuitPython: Python for microcontrollers, simplified]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983870/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983870/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T14:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CircuitPython is an open-source
implementation of the Python programming language for microcontroller
boards.  The project, which is sponsored by Adafruit Industries, is designed with
new programmers in mind, but it also has many features that may be of
interest to more-experienced developers. The recent 9.1.0 release
adds a few minor features, but it follows just a few months after CircuitPython 9.0.0,
which brings some more significant changes, including improved graphics and
USB support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 129.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984617/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984617/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T14:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
129.0 of the Firefox browser has been released.  Changes include some
improvements to the reader mode, tab previews, and use of HTTPS by default.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 3: Matrix-matrix multiplication. Neon, SVE, and SME compared]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:56463e5b-511a-4cf0-9b93-3559823e3980</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/matrix-matrix-multiplication-neon-sve-and-sme-compared"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post describes how to implement the same matrix-matrix multiplication algorithm using three different Arm technologies: Neon, SVE, and SME.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Khalid Saadi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984598/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984598/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T13:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libreoffice), Gentoo (containerd and firefox), Red Hat (httpd), SUSE (ca-certificates-mozilla, ksh, openssl-3-livepatches, podman, python-Twisted, and skopeo), and Ubuntu (imagemagick).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shelf operation of an OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490572</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/shelf-operation-of-an-ocp-orv3-smart-battery-backup-unit/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T12:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The backup battery shelf is an important feature of power management systems in an Open Compute Project (OCP) Open Rack V3 (ORV3) battery backup unit (BBU) architecture and data center application, especially in the field of uninterruptible power supplies (UPSs). These shelves, with a precise design focused on housing and organizing backup batteries, emerge as […]
The post Shelf operation of an OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“국회가 탄핵감”? 채널A의 물타기와 정치 혐오가  탄핵감]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113579</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113579"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T08:09:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[더불어민주당을 비롯한 야6당이 8월 1일 이진숙 방송통신위원장 탄핵소추안을 발의했습니다. 같은 날 더불어민주당은 민생회복지원금 지급법, 이른바 ‘전국민 25만원 지원법’을 본회의에 상정했습니다. 국민의힘은 즉각 무제한토론(필리버스터)을 신청했습니다. 더불어민주당의 토론종결 요청에 따라 24시간이 지나는 8월 2일 오후 3시경 필리버스터가 끝나면 해당 법안이 통과될 것으로 보입니다. 더불어민주당은 전국민 25만원 지원법 처리 후 노동조합 및 노동관계조정법 일부개정안(노란봉투법) 상정을 예정하고 있는데요. 국민의힘은...
The post “국회가 탄핵감”? 채널A의 물타기와 정치 혐오가  탄핵감 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사람들이 ‘손석희의 질문들’을 보고 화를 냈던 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113545</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113545"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T07:24:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유시민(전 노무현재단 이사장)은 “뉴스를 안 본다”고 했다. 왜 안 보냐고 하니 “너무 괴로워서”라고 말했다. “종이신문 안 본 지는 여러 해 된 것 같고요. 포털 뉴스 검색을 안 한 지도 꽤 오래된 것 같아요.” 며칠 전 손석희(전 JTBC 사장)가 진행하고 유시민과 김희원(한국일보 뉴스스탠다드실장)이 패널로 참여한 토크쇼가 화제였다. 두 사람의 대화도 흥미로웠지만 몇 가지 중요한 질문이 남았다....
The post 사람들이 ‘손석희의 질문들’을 보고 화를 냈던 이유. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift AI and machine learning operations]]></title>
        <id>ce00ac7e-132c-4801-9d1d-a7644d946f3e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/06/red-hat-openshift-ai-and-machine-learning-operations"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's data-driven world, organizations are always looking for new ways to get insightful information from their new or existing data in order to spread their business. Red Hat OpenShift AI enables data scientists and developers to efficiently collaborate and create solid, scalable, and reproducible data science projects in response to this demand. 
Architecture of Red Hat OpenShift AI
Red Hat OpenShift AI helps you build out an enterprise grade AI and MLOps platform to create and deliver GenAI and predictive models by providing supported AI tooling on top of OpenShift. It’s based on Red Hat OpenShift, a container based application platform that efficiently scales to handle workload demands of AI operations and models. You can run your AI workloads across the hybrid cloud, including ed…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gaurav Midha</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[예약이 ‘하늘의 별 따기’인 식당들, 이런 것까지 할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79790</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/05/npsp_finedining/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_finedining"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T00:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기후변화는 더는 먼 미래의 일도, 남의 이야기도 아닙니다. 기후변화의 영향을 받는 수많은 분야 가운데 우리가 눈 떠 있는 동안 하루도 빼놓지 않고 하는 행위, 바로 먹는 것에 관한 식문화도 생각해볼 거리가 많은 주제입니다. 뉴욕타임스가 “불타는 지구에서 우리는 무엇을 어떻게 먹어야 하는가”라는 주제에 관해 칼럼을 연재하기 시작했습니다. 그 가운데 호주 출신 문화 비평가 애런 팀스가 이른바 “지속가능한 파인다이닝”에 관해 글을 썼습니다. 이 글을 번역하고, 요식업계가 탄소 발자국 대신 물 사용 발자국을 따져 볼 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[금융 시장 패닉, “국가적 위기 상황에 윤석열은 휴가 중”: 슬로우레터 8월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113493</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113493"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T22:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[완전히 다른 세상이 됐다. 나쁜 뉴스가 나쁜 뉴스였다. 더 깊게 읽기. 미국 고용 지표 어떻길래. 샴의 법칙, 이번에도 맞을까. 예측이 의미 없는 상황. 중앙은행의 판단 착오. 수습할 수 있을까. 윤석열은 휴가 중. 쟁점과 현안. “통신기록 조회? 미친 사람들 아니냐.” “구글은 독점 기업이다.” 다르게 읽기. 더 강력해진 노란봉투법 국회 통과. “대표팀 계속하기 어렵다”는 수상 소감. “감옥이...
The post 금융 시장 패닉, “국가적 위기 상황에 윤석열은 휴가 중”: 슬로우레터 8월6일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Google Developer Program: Unlock New Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-the-google-developer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-the-google-developer-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T20:14:24.665Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Developer Program gives developers access to a range of new tools and benefits,  to allow them to discover and explore all the Google sponsored communities we already offer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Handling filesystem interruptibility]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983714/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983714/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T19:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Howells wanted to discuss changing the way filesystem code handles
the ability to interrupt or kill operations, in order to fix some
longstanding problems with network 
(and other) filesystems, in a session at
the 2024 Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.   As noted in
his session
proposal, some filesystems may be expecting to not be interruptible,
but are calling code can take locks and mutexes that are interruptible (or
killable), which are effectively
changing the state of the task incorrectly.
He would like to find a solution for that problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The complexity of BUSL transformation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984249/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984249/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Business
Source License (BUSL) is a source-available license that "converts"
to an open-source license after a period of time. In theory, this
means that a few years after a version of a product is released under
the BUSL, it becomes open source and is fair game for Linux
distributions to package along with regular open-source projects. In
practice, the license throws a few curveballs that require special
consideration and caution, as the Fedora Project recently discussed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU Binutils 2.43 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984539/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984539/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.43 of the GNU Binutils package is out.  Changes include some
improvements to the assembler and the linker, better support for hardware
event counters in the Gprofng profiler, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984552/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984552/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (openjdk-11), Fedora (bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, chromium, ffmpeg, hostapd, trafficserver, and wpa_supplicant), and Ubuntu (curl and linux-oem-6.5).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TDK forms new entity to bring edge AI and sensor fusion to industry 4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490558</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/tdk-forms-new-entity-to-bring-edge-ai-and-sensor-fusion-to-industry-4-0/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T14:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TDK Corporation has formed a new wholly owned corporate legal entity to focus on solutions for industry 4.0 and particularly the intersection of artificial intelligence (AI) and sensor fusion at the edge for machine and production health. Headquartered in Singapore, the new entity, called TDK SensEI, will create industry 4.0 solutions combining multiple TDK assets […]
The post TDK forms new entity to bring edge AI and sensor fusion to industry 4.0 appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microchip digital signal controller enhances precision real-time control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490563</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/microchip-digital-signal-controller-enhances-precision-real-time-control/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microchip Technology has launched a new family of digital signal controllers (DSCs) which offer faster computation and precision in real-time control applications. Built around a 32-bit central processing unit (CPU) architecture with a 200 MHz operating speed, the new dsPIC33A family’s advanced core includes a double-precision floating-point unit (DP FPU) and DSP instructions for numerically […]
The post Microchip digital signal controller enhances precision real-time control appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to avoid too much solder on your RF PCB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490546</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-avoid-too-much-solder-on-your-rf-pcb/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T10:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced printed circuit boards (PCBs) are so complex, OEMs often scratch their heads and wonder if they are going down the right path with their PCB assemblies. With many challenges for their specific board applications, not all assembly houses are equipped to deal with one key area, the radio frequency (RF) PCB. When an RF […]
The post How to avoid too much solder on your RF PCB appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빈사에 빠진 최저임금: 세 가지 징후]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112918</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112918"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T08:48:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[함께 읽으면 좋음! 세 가지 징후 두 을의 서로 다른 입장은 ‘최저임금 1만 원 시대’의 의미를 돌아보는 첫 질문으로 적당한 것 같다. 2025 최저임금은 징후적이다. 세 가지 징후가 있다. 그리고 그 징후가 가리키는 ‘질병’은 현 최저임금 시스템의 종말이다. 1. 물가상승률에도 못 미치는 상승률 첫 번째, 2025년 적용 최저임금을 놓고 보면, 결정액과 인상률(1만30원, 1.7%)이 물가상승률(2.6% 전망치)보다...
The post 빈사에 빠진 최저임금: 세 가지 징후 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How InstructLab enables accessible model fine-tuning for gen AI]]></title>
        <id>5ee8f3d8-91af-47f8-aac5-483a7e5e6fc8</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/05/how-instructlab-enables-accessible-model-fine-tuning-gen-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adapting large language models (LLMs) for specific use cases traditionally requires extensive resources and expertise. While Gartner says more than 80% of enterprises will have deployed generative AI-enabled applications by 2026, the challenge of customizing these models for domain-specific tasks remains significant. InstructLab, an open-source project developed by IBM and Red Hat, aims to address this gap by democratizing LLM tuning. Let’s take a look at how InstructLab enables developers (and domain experts) to enhance and specialize language models efficiently, even on consumer-grade hardware, potentially accelerating the adoption of tailored AI solutions across industries. This article is accompanied by a conference presentation given by Legare Kerrison and Cedric Clyburn at WeAreDevel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Clyburn, Legare Kerrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[돈이 말한다? 도박사들이 선거 결과를 예측할 수 있을까.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113406</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113406"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T01:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[조 바이든 현 대통령과 도널드 트럼프 전 대통령의 리턴 매치로 치러질 거라고 예상됐던 올해 미국 대선에 이변이 속출하고 있다. 그때마다 미국 언론은 수많은 분석과 예측 기사를 쏟아내는데, 특이한 항목 중 하나가 예측 시장에 나타난 당선 가능성 변화이다. 오늘은 도대체 정치 예측 시장은 무엇이고, 그 평가는 얼마나 정확하고 중요한 것인가 살펴본다. 예측 시장 반응 아래 차트는...
The post 돈이 말한다? 도박사들이 선거 결과를 예측할 수 있을까. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>신현호</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.11-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984501/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984501/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T00:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.11-rc2 for testing.
"Hopefully we've gotten rid of the bulk of the silly noise here in rc2,
and not added too much new noise, so that we can get on with the process of
finding more meaningful issues."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엘리엇 취소 소송도 패소, 한동훈 고집에 이자 부담만 늘었다: 슬로우레터 8월5일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113363</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113363"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T22:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기자들 통화 내역 탈탈 털었다. ‘구대명’ 안 된다, 호남의 선택. 쟁점과 현안. 오늘은 노란봉투법 간다. 엘리엇 소송 취소 소송도 패소. 이진숙 이틀 만에 업무 정지. 식물 방통위, 이대로 가나. 더 깊게 읽기. 한동훈이 만나 달라고 해서 만난 것. “헛소리는 그만.” 이스라엘은 전쟁을 끝낼 생각이 없다. 다르게 읽기. 불붙은 전기차, 불 끄는 방법. 전기차 화재, 배상은...
The post 엘리엇 취소 소송도 패소, 한동훈 고집에 이자 부담만 늘었다: 슬로우레터 8월5일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory bandwidth: 1991-2009]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9263</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/08/04/memory-bandwidth-1991-2009/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T22:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Stream benchmark is a measure of sustained memory bandwidth; the target systems are high performance computers. Sustained in the sense of distance running, rather than a short sprint (the term for this is peak memory bandwidth and occurs when the requested data is in cache), and bandwidth in the sense of bytes of memory […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ programmer's guide to undefined behavior: part 3 of 11]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1149/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1149/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your attention is invited to the third part of an e-book on undefined behavior. This is not a textbook, as it's intended for those who are already familiar with C++ programming. It's a kind of C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 아마존 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595820</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595820/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T00:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enum class improvements for C++17, C++20 and C++23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/enum-improvements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/enum-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The evolution of the C++ language continues to bring powerful features that enhance code safety, readability, and maintainability. Among these improvements, we got changes and additions to enum class functionalities across C++17, C++20, and C++23. In this blog post, we’ll explore these advancements, focusing on initialization improvements in C++17, the introduction of the using enum keyword in C++20, and the std::to_underlying utility in C++23.
Let’s go.



     
    


Before diving into the enhancements, let’s briefly recap what enum class is. An enum class (scoped enumeration) provides a type-safe way of defining a set of named constants. Unlike traditional (unscoped) enums, enum class does not implicitly convert to integers or other types, preventing accidental misuse. Here’s a basic e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three stable kernel updates for Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984448/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984448/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T13:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10.3, 6.6.44, and 6.1.103 stable kernel updates have all been released. As usual, they
contain important fixes throughout the tree. Users of those kernels
should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 미국이 자칫하면 ‘한국 꼴’ 될 수 있다고? 달갑지 않은 최신 ‘K-트렌드’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79498</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/02/npsp_birthrategendernorm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_birthrategendernorm"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T22:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 10일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 일찌감치 산업화를 달성한 서구의 많은 나라와 소위 선진국에서 사람들이 아이를 낳지 않아 인구가 정체되는 건 새로운 현상이 아닙니다. 미국의 사정도 다르지 않습니다. 미국 질병통제예방센터는 지난 4월 2023년 출산 통계를 발표하며, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Divvi Up: privacy-respecting telemetry aggregation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983843/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983843/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T13:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is ongoing discussion about the ethics and effectiveness of
telemetry following some recent LWN articles that touched on

Thunderbird's use of opt-out
telemetry and planned metrics in Fedora. The

Internet Security Research Group (ISRG), the nonprofit behind

Let's Encrypt, has a potential solution to the problem of how to collect and
aggregate telemetry without violating users' privacy. The scheme is based on a
draft
protocol being standardized with the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF),
and has an
open-source implementation
available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984370/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984370/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T13:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium), SUSE (docker and patch), and Ubuntu (bind9, gross, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, and tomcat8, tomcat9).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[스페인의 진짜 대표선수: 토르티야 데 파타타]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113333</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113333"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T05:28:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여러분은 스페인 하면 어떤 음식이 떠오르는지 궁금하다. 빠에야? 감바스? 유명한 요리들이긴 하지만 사실 이들은 스페인을 아우를 수 있는 대표성을 가진 요리는 아니다. 무슨 말이냐? 이들은 특정 지역의 토속 요리에 가깝다. “한국음식은 뭐가 유명한가요?”라고 물으면 “돼지국밥이 유명합니다.”라고 대답하는 느낌과 비슷하달까. 돼지국밥은 모두가 아는 음식이긴 하지만 주로 부산 및 경남권에서만 만날 수 있는 지역색 강한 음식이다. 한국을...
The post 스페인의 진짜 대표선수: 토르티야 데 파타타 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최명진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이진숙 ‘2인 체제’ 방송 장악 속도전, 엄호 나선 조선∙경제지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113321</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113321"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T01:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 대통령은 7월 31일 이진숙 방송통신위원장 임명을 강행했습니다. 국회 인사청문회 과정에서 부적절한 법인카드 유용과 극우·편향적 발언, 노조탄압, 사회적 참사 공감능력 결여 등 공직자 후보로서 부적격한 사유가 차고 넘쳤음에도 윤 대통령은 보고서 채택이 불발된 후보자를 방송통신위원장으로 임명했는데요. 이진숙 방송통신위원장은 대통령실 임명발표가 나기도 전에 통상적인 임명장 수여식과 현충원 참배도 생략한 채 정부과천청사로 출근했습니다. 이후 같은 날 임명된...
The post 이진숙 ‘2인 체제’ 방송 장악 속도전, 엄호 나선 조선∙경제지 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지금 민주당과 해리스의 최우선 과제?… “두 마리 토끼 쫓는 셈”]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79766</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/01/npsp_harrisvtrump/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_harrisvtrump"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T01:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[바이든 대통령이 재선에 도전하지 않기로 하면서 카멀라 해리스 부통령 지지를 선언했고, 해리스는 바이든 캠페인을 이어받아 빠르게 민주당 내 지지를 규합하고 트럼프 전 대통령과의 일전을 준비하고 있습니다. 해리스의 등판 이후 부진을 면치 못하던 민주당은 빠르게 지지율을 회복했습니다. 바이든을 상대하는 한 선거에서 대승을 거둘 수도 있다고 본 공화당 일각의 기대는 물거품이 됐습니다. 참패가 예상되던 선거를 다시 박빙, 접전으로 돌려놓긴 했지만, 해리스는 과연 트럼프를 넘어설 수 있을까요? 이에 대해 책 “정의란 무엇인가”로 한국에는 특히 잘 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동아일보의 경고, “윤석열, 가장 무능한 대통령으로 남을 수도”: 슬로우레터 8월2일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113290</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113290"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T22:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이진숙의 3일 방통위. 쟁점과 현안. 25만 원 민생 지원금법도 필리버스터 돌입. “분열 막기 위해 그만둔다.” 세금을 안 걷나, 못 걷나, 예측을 잘못했나. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘킹 달러’의 퇴장, 9월 금리 인하 가능성. 한국도 10월 인하? 가계 빚이 변수다. 환율 착시 효과. 미국 금리는 트럼프가 변수. ‘슈퍼 엔저’가 끝났나. 이란 보복 공격 카운트 다운. 다르게 읽기....
The post 동아일보의 경고, “윤석열, 가장 무능한 대통령으로 남을 수도”: 슬로우레터 8월2일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Digest #2]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1148/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1148/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our second news and event digest for the .NET world! The first digest resonated with you, so the PVS-Studio C# team has gathered the most awesome and handy insights for you again. Let's...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better Code with Block Diagrams and Flowcharts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1685.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1685.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contents

	
Introduction

	
Software block diagrams
	

		
What is it?

		
How do I draw one?

		
Implementing a block diagram in code

		
Ready for a small challenge?

	

	
Flowcharts
	

		
What is it?

		
How do I draw one?

		
Implementing a flowchart in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GNU Coverage (gcov) in a Freestanding Environment for Embedded Systems]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40990</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/08/01/how-to-use-gnu-coverage-gcov-in-a-freestanding-environment-for-embedded-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNU Coverage (gcov) tool is a part of the GNU gcc suite and is commonly used in hosted environments like Linux or Windows. However, it can also be utilized in embedded systems without a debugger, semihosting, or file I/O. This article provides a detailed guide on setting up a freestanding environment to collect gcov data, improving performance and enabling flexible data collection. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sovereign Tech Fund introduces fellowship pilot program]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984266/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984266/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T15:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sovereign Tech Fund (STF) has announced
a fellowship program to support "the dedicated individuals who keep
our digital infrastructure running":
According to the fellowship
page the STF plans to fund five fellowships, beginning in the
fourth quarter of this year, for a period of 12 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Maximal min() and max()]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983965/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983965/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many projects written in C, the kernel makes extensive use of the C
preprocessor; indeed, the kernel's use is rather more extensive than most.
The preprocessor famously has a number of sharp edges associated with it.
One might not normally think of increased compilation time as one of them,
though.  It turns out that some changes to a couple of conceptually simple
preprocessor macros — min() and max() — led to some truly
pathological, but hidden, behavior where those macros were used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mel Chua RIP]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984213/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984213/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have received the
sad news that Dr. Mel Chua has passed away. Mel was probably best
known in the free-software community as a contributor to the Fedora
Project in its early days. The Fedora Community blog honored
Mel recently after she had moved to hospice care with tributes
from several Fedorans. Stephen Jacobs wrote:
Mel will be greatly missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984212/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984212/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (kernel, obs-cef, and xen), Mageia (emacs), Oracle (freeradius, freeradius:3.0, and kernel), Red Hat (emacs, httpd, and kpatch-patch-4_18_0-305_120_1), Slackware (curl), SUSE (apache2, cockpit-wicked, glibc, gnutls, gvfs, less, nghttp2, opensc, python-idna, python-requests, qemu, rpm, tpm2-0-tss, tpm2.0-tools, and unbound), and Ubuntu (clickhouse, exim4, libcommons-collections3-java, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, mysql-8.0, openssl, php-cas, prometheus-alertmanager, and snapd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command — Response Framework in ESP RainMaker]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5e8273db7d22</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/command-response-framework-in-esp-rainmaker-5e8273db7d22?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T10:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 release candidate 1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/08/python-3130-release-candidate-1-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/08/python-3130-release-candidate-1-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T09:30:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.13 release candidate 1.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130rc1/
 
This is the first release candidate of Python 3.13.0
This release, 3.13.0rc1, is the penultimate release 
preview. Entering the release candidate phase, only reviewed code 
changes which are clear bug fixes are allowed between this release 
candidate and the final release. The second candidate (and the last 
planned release preview) is scheduled for Tuesday, 2024-09-03, while the
 official release of 3.13.0 is scheduled for Tuesday, 2024-10-01.
There will be no ABI changes from this point forward in the 3.13 series, and the goal is that there will be as few code changes as possible.
Call to action
We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source AI coding assistance with the Granite models]]></title>
        <id>ae9ecad3-fa26-4c36-b0c7-13f072dfbb10</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/01/open-source-ai-coding-assistance-granite-models"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, we're always looking for ways to be more productive and write higher-quality code. While tools like GitHub Copilot have gained popularity as AI pair programmers, the downside is they run on closed models and you might have to pay a subscription to use them. Imagine instead being able to use state-of-the-art free AI coding assistants right on your local machine using powerful open source models, with auto-completions and confidence that your data stays private! 
Let’s take a look at how to integrate an AI code assistant into your IDE using a combination of open source tools, including Continue (an extension for VS Code and JetBrains), Ollama or InstructLab as a local model server, and the Granite family of code models to supercharge your development workflow without any cost …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Clyburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrustyAI Detoxify: Guardrailing LLMs during training]]></title>
        <id>4b523a23-28b5-4e53-bd32-45d5e56a8702</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/01/trustyai-detoxify-guardrailing-llms-during-training"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Detoxifying or preventing toxic content generation from large language models (LLMs) is challenging. Data used to train these models is usually scraped from the internet which often contains toxic content. Without proper guardrails, a model can learn undesirable properties and in turn, generate toxic text. Removing toxic samples from training data can be expensive as it usually requires data annotators to manually identify samples that align with human values. Inherent bias in the annotators themselves can also affect the data labeling process in a negative way. By using the open source project TrustyAI Detoxify in conjunction with Hugging Face's SFTTrainer (Supervised Fine-Tuning Trainer) on Red Hat OpenShift AI, we can help lower the costs of detoxifying LLMs during training. 
In this ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christina Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimize downtime when migrating from VMware to OpenShift Virtualization]]></title>
        <id>8f690152-28e1-42b3-9eb4-d084ae1e9055</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/01/minimize-downtime-when-migrating-vmware-openshift-virtualization"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Gartner, despite the growing trend towards cloud migration and container adoption, a significant portion of datacenter x86 workloads will remain hypervisor-based virtualization through 2027, albeit reduced from previous years. See this e-book for more information on this topic. Managing a hybrid infrastructure that includes both hypervisor-based virtual machines and Kubernetes clusters can be a daunting task.
For platform teams, the challenge lies in efficiently managing diverse environments while optimizing existing investments. Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization offers a compelling solution by allowing organizations to run both virtual machines (VMs) and containers on a single, unified platform. This enables them to have a platform that addresses their current needs while also…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vamsi Ravula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 1, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983267/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983267/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T04:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 1, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8/1, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595812</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595812/8-1-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T02:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions for STM32CubeIDE]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/github-actions-for-stm32cubeide</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/github-actions-for-stm32cubeide"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore how to use GitHub Actions to automate building
STM32CubeIDE projects. Eclipse-based IDEs like STM32CubeIDE are often used for
developing embedded systems but can be a little tricky to build in a headless
environment.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving _Generic in C2y]]></title>
        <id>https://thephd.dev/improving-_generic-in-c2y</id>
        <link href="https://thephd.dev/improving-_generic-in-c2y"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first two meetings of C after C23 was finalized are over, and we have started working on C2y. We decided that this cycle we’re not going to do that “Bugfix” followed by “Release” stuff, because that proved to be a REALLY bad idea that killed a ton of momentum and active contributors during the C11 to C17 timeframe. So, this time, we’re hitting both bugfixes AND features so we can make sure we don’t lose valuable contributions and fixes by stalling for 5 to 6 years again. So, with that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Pasture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“한동훈 나오면 이재명이 된다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 8월1일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113206</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113206"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T22:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이스마일 하니야 암살. 김문수가 돌아왔다. 취임 첫날 이진숙이 한 일. 탄핵과 사퇴 무한 반복. 이동관이 돌아온다고? 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈의 ‘마이웨이.’ 정점식을 갈아치우려 하는 이유. 윤석열-한동훈 미팅 뒷이야기. 더 깊게 읽기. 한동훈은 퇴로가 없다. 민주당이 한동훈 제안을 받는다면? “한동훈 나오면 이재명이 된다.” 다르게 읽기. 티메프가 드러낸 그림자 금융. 스타벅스 선불 충전금 3000억 원. 3일 정산, 네이버는...
The post “한동훈 나오면 이재명이 된다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 8월1일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A deprecation timeline for older Arm CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984143/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984143/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arnd Bergmann has posted a
detailed timeline for the deprecation of support for old Arm CPUs in
both the kernel and the compiler toolchain.  Anybody who is working with
that hardware will likely want to review this list and let the relevant
developers know if any of that support is still needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro and 1.5 Flash GA, 1.5 Flash tuning support, higher rate limits, and more API updates]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:14:19.665Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re incredibly excited to see what you build with these new models. Get started with Gemini 1.5 Flash and 1.5 Pro free of charge in Google AI Studio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smaller, Safer, More Transparent: Advancing Responsible AI with Gemma]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/smaller-safer-more-transparent-advancing-responsible-ai-with-gemma/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/smaller-safer-more-transparent-advancing-responsible-ai-with-gemma/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:14:19.664Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ShieldGemma is a suite of safety content classifiers models built upon Gemma2 designed to keep users safe. GemmaScope is a new model interpretability tool that offers unparalleled insight into our models' inner workings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refresh of the PoEAA catalog page]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-eaa-catalog-refresh.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-eaa-catalog-refresh.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From time to time I take a look at my site analytics to see how much traffic various bits of this site get. When doing this I saw that I continue to get a lot of traffic to the Catalog of Patterns of Enterprise Application Architecture. I put this together not long after writing the book, and it’s rather minimal. Since it still gets traffic I felt it was time for some sprucing up. The content is the same, summaries of the patterns in the book. I’ve changed the main catalog page to include the pattern intents. I’ve also added deep links to the book on oreilly.com, so if you have a subscription to that, it will jump directly to that text. Hopefully these changes will make the catalog page a bit more useful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022-2023 Quarterly Discussion Panel Archives]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=42412</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2024/07/31/2022-2023-quarterly-discussion-panel-archives/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T19:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[31 July 2024 by Phillip JohnstonDuring 2022-2023, Embedded Artistry and Memfault teamed up to run a series of embedded-focused discussion panels. These discussion panels were rich with insight and advice for embedded teams. Even if you missed the live broadcasts, we hope you will take time to watch the recordings. Building Embedded Systems at Scale … 
Continue reading "2022-2023 Quarterly Discussion Panel Archives"
The post 2022-2023 Quarterly Discussion Panel Archives appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep list copy: More than meets the eye]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/07/31/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/07/31/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T18:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across a take-home C programming test which had more depth
and complexity than I suspect the interviewer intended. While considering
it, I also came up with a novel, or at least unconventional, solution. The
problem is to deep copy a linked list where each node references a random
list element in addition to usual linkage — similar to LeetCode problem
138. This reference is one of identity rather than value, which has
murky consequences.

typedef struct node node;
struct node {
    node *next;
    node *ref;   // arbitrary node in the list, or null
};

node *deepcopy(node *);


In the copy, nodes have individual lifetimes allocated using malloc
which the caller is responsible for freeing. While thickheaded, this
is conventional, and I cannot blame the test’s designer for st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla OS 2 "Orchid" released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984117/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984117/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T18:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.0 of the Vanilla OS image-based Linux distribution has
been released. Dubbed
"Orchid", Vanilla OS is now based on Debian Sid (prior versions were Ubuntu-based),
allows creation
of customized Linux environments, support for running Android
applications using Waydroid, and many other improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Showing up for Python in GNOME]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983897/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983897/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years ago, PyGObject—the Python
package that provides bindings for GTK and GNOME applications—was not
faring particularly well. Several maintainers had left the project and its
development was not keeping pace with changes in GTK. At this year's
GUADEC, Dan Yeaw presented a talk
about the project's decline, improvements in the last year, and his
experience getting involved in an undermaintained project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poor roads, money, and cybercriminals: why sci-fi cars are not here yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490505</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/poor-roads-money-and-cybercriminals-why-sci-fi-cars-are-not-here-yet/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The flying taxis with smart assistants from the Fifth Element, a stunning Audi RSQ, custom built by Audi for I, Robot, and the Lexus 2054 with advanced biometric systems and automatic driving mode from Minority Report: it seems automakers from around the world are racing to be the first to make these dreams come true. While such advanced hi-tech vehicles have […]
The post Poor roads, money, and cybercriminals: why sci-fi cars are not here yet appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forgejo v8.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984116/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984116/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T15:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.0 of the Forgejo
software-development platform has been released. Notable
changes include the removal
of non-free software found in the codebase, improved stability, and a
reduction
in "seemingly random User Interface changes":
See the release
notes for a full list of changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배롱나무 명소, 물놀이 계곡을 즐기기 좋은 밀양 표충사 베롱나무]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595796</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595796/%eb%b0%80%ec%96%91-%ed%91%9c%ec%b6%a9%ec%82%ac-%eb%b0%b0%eb%a1%b1%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Pulling Linux up by its bootstraps]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983340/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983340/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T13:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 
bootstrappable build is one that builds existing
software from scratch — for example, building GCC without relying on an existing
copy of GCC. In 2023, the Guix project
announced that the project had reduced the size
of the binary bootstrap seed needed to build its operating system to just 357-bytes —
not counting the Linux kernel required to run the build process. Now, the
live-bootstrap project
has gone a step further and removed the need for an existing kernel at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984080/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984080/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T13:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (xdg-desktop-portal-hyprland), Red Hat (freeradius, freeradius:3.0, git-lfs, httpd, kernel, openssh, and varnish:6), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, cont, git, gtk2, gtk3, kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-exportproxy-container, virt-exportserver-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-t, orc, postgresql14, python-dnspython, python-urllib3, shadow, and xen), and Ubuntu (openjdk-17, openjdk-21, openjdk-8, openjdk-lts, and python3.10, python3.8).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A software-connected approach to automated post-silicon device validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490486</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/a-software-connected-approach-to-automated-post-silicon-device-validation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T12:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst the many disruptions faced by the global semiconductor industry, the relentless pursuit of higher performance silicon to power the ever-evolving landscape of modern technology has only increased. While Covid-19 underscored the vulnerability of the semiconductor supply chain, the demand for innovative silicon remains steadfast, driving continual advancements in product development . For semiconductor organizations […]
The post A software-connected approach to automated post-silicon device validation appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alphawave Semi launches 3nm UCIe IP for chiplet ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490482</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/alphawave-semi-launches-3nm-ucie-ip-for-chiplet-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T11:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alphawave Semi said it has launched the industry’s first successful silicon bring-up of Universal Chiplet Interconnect Express (UCIe) die-to-die (D2D) IP with TSMC’s 3nm chip-on-wafer-on-substrate (CoWoS) advanced packaging technology. The complete PHY and controller subsystem was developed in collaboration with TSMC and targets applications such as hyperscaler, high-performance computing (HPC) and artificial intelligence (AI). Using […]
The post Alphawave Semi launches 3nm UCIe IP for chiplet ecosystem appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debian derivative eLxr addresses simplifies and enhance edge-to-cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490476</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/debian-derivative-elxr-addresses-simplifies-and-enhance-edge-to-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new community-driven open source project based on a derivative of Debian and designed to deliver enterprise-grade Linux for edge-to-cloud deployments has launched its first release. The eLxr project, spearheaded by Wind River and supported by AWS, Intel, Supermicro, SAIC, and Capgemini, is an enterprise-grade Linux distribution that addresses the challenges of near-edge networks and […]
The post Debian derivative eLxr addresses simplifies and enhance edge-to-cloud appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily expanding Red Hat OpenShift clusters]]></title>
        <id>e6d51a6d-803f-45f4-bfec-27f5d25a97bb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/31/easily-expanding-red-hat-openshift-clusters"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding nodes to Red Hat OpenShift clusters on-premises is a laborious and sometimes complex endeavor. With various methods available, each with different levels of automation, users often find themselves navigating through complex and even unsupported solutions, leading to a less-than-ideal user experience. 
A new feature is now available as a Developer Preview in OpenShift 4.16, that makes cluster expansions faster, simpler, and more user-friendly than ever before.
This new method leverages the Agent Based Installer technology under the hood, but doesn’t need the cluster to have been installed by it, it will work on any cluster where its nodes can be installed from an ISO image.
It first gets information of the cluster to be expanded, then it provides a bootable ISO image, and after booti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramon Acedo Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation for developers and data scientists]]></title>
        <id>11ed32d2-2b95-4194-aa59-1f3bb41441b5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/31/red-hat-openshift-data-foundation-developers-and-data-scientists"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you develop applications with a cloud-first mindset, you probably use (or plan to use) object storage with the S3 API from Amazon Web Services (AWS). Even if you do not use AWS, all large and smaller public cloud providers offer object storage compatible with the S3 API.
If you plan to work with artificial intelligence (AI), most AI tools require S3 storage to store data from models, training, and tuning, besides the raw data on which AI models make inferences and the results of such inferences.
But, if you have to work on premises, or have to create applications which must work both on premises and on cloud, you require something that provides an S3-compatible API outside of cloud providers. Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation is a nice alternative proven to support large scale deploymen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Lozano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[강릉여행, 활래정과 둘레길이 아름다웟던 강릉 선교장 방문기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595782</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595782/%ea%b0%95%eb%a6%89%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89-%ed%99%9c%eb%9e%98%ec%a0%95%ea%b3%bc-%eb%91%98%eb%a0%88%ea%b8%b8%ec%9d%b4-%ec%95%84%eb%a6%84%eb%8b%a4%ec%9b%9f%eb%8d%98-%ea%b0%95%eb%a6%89-%ec%84%a0%ea%b5%90"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T06:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/31, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595784</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595784/7-31-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T06:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘억만장자들만의 세상’, 이제는 대놓고 펼쳐진다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79483</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/30/npsp_buylongerlife/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_buylongerlife"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T22:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 5일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 불로초를 찾으려 했던 진시황의 이야기는 다들 잘 아실 겁니다. 굳이 진시황이 아니라도 인류 역사에 이름을 남긴 권력자 가운데는 다시 젊어지려고 애쓴 사람이 많습니다. 그게 어렵다면 늙지 않는 비결을 찾아 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“용산이 괘씸하게 보고 있다”, 마약 수사 외압 사건 또 터진다: 슬로우레터 7월31일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113137</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113137"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T22:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[디올 백 알고도 신고 안 했다. 김건희 벙커? 제2부속실로 생색내기. 쟁점과 현안. 800억 원밖에 없다. 공정위는 몰랐다. 얼마가 부족한지도 몰랐다. 더 깊게 읽기. 5박6일 필리버스터 종료, 방송4법 국회 통과. 이진숙 프로젝트 속도전. 필리버스터+거부권+재의결 부결 3종 세트. “용산이 괘씸하게 보고 있다.” 다르게 읽기. 도청‧미행 당할 거 몰랐나. 댐 만들어 기후 대응한다고? 골칫덩어리 영주댐 잊었나. 해법과 대안....
The post “용산이 괘씸하게 보고 있다”, 마약 수사 외압 사건 또 터진다: 슬로우레터 7월31일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building static binaries with Go on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/building-static-binaries-with-go-on-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/building-static-binaries-with-go-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of Go's advantages is being able to produce statically-linked
binaries <a class="footnote-reference" href="#footnote-1" id="footnote-reference-1">[1]</a>. This doesn't mean that Go always produces such binaries by default,
however; in some scenarios it requires extra work to make this happen.
Specifics here are OS-dependent; here we focus on Unix systems.</p>
<div class="section" id="basics-hello-world">
<h2>Basics - hello world</h2>
<p>This post …</p></div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Famfs: a filesystem interface to shareable memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983105/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983105/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2024 Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, John Groves led
a session on famfs, which is a filesystem he has developed that uses the
kernel's direct-access (DAX)
mechanism to access memory that is shareable between hosts.  The discussion
was aimed at whether a different approach should be taken and, in
particular, whether FUSE should be used instead of implementing as an
in-kernel filesystem.  As noted in the thread about his
proposal for an LSFMM+BPF session, and the mailing-list discussions on the first and second
version of his patch set, there is some skepticism that a new in-kernel
filesystem is warranted for the use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search query for bugs in Apache Solr]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1147/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1147/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, we're checking the Apache product. This time we chose Solr, an open-source search server platform. Solr enables you quickly and efficiently search for information in databases and online...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API for Custom LLMs on Device]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:13:36.471Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API enables developers to bring powerful new capabilities on-device, such as summarization, content generation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Google Pay at I/O 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:13:36.471Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re adding new features to Google Pay so you can offer richer and more accessible payment experiences for your customers, and improved APIs to simplify your payments integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funtoo Linux is being discontinued]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983977/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983977/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T17:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Robbins, founder of the Gentoo Linux distribution and its
spinoff Funtoo Linux, has
announced
that he has decided to end the Funtoo project:
Funtoo
container, it will continue to be online through the end of August
so you have time to find another hosting solution if you need one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Ansible plug-ins for Red Hat Developer Hub]]></title>
        <id>1ef09165-659e-4bc1-81e6-09ab9d398e39</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/30/announcing-ansible-plug-ins-red-hat-developer-hub"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T16:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Developer Hub is an enterprise-grade internal developer portal (IDP). It allows platform engineering teams to offer software templates based on your best practices to maximize developer skills, ease onboarding, increase development productivity, and focus on writing great code by reducing friction and frustration for development teams.
Red Hat is constantly curating a set of plug-ins and ensuring the best experience on Red Hat Developer Hub. Red Hat supported and validated  plug-ins let you extend the Red Hat Developer Hub environment with confidence, eliminating compatibility and operational issues.
As part of these efforts, we are pleased to announce Technology Preview of Ansible plug-ins for Red Hat Developer Hub. With Ansible plug-ins, organizations using Red Hat Developer Hub …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Himanshu Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of restricting AI and algorithms, make them explainable]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-restrict-algorithm.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-restrict-algorithm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The steady increase in deployment of AI tools has led a lot of people concerned about how software makes decisions that affect our lives. In one example, its about “algorithmic” feeds in social media that promote posts that drive engagement. A more serious impact can come from business decisions, such as how much premium to charge in car insurance. This can extend to affecting legal decisions, such as suggesting sentencing guidelines to judges.
Faced with these concerns, there is often a movement to restrict the use of algorithms, such as a recent activity in New York to restrict how social media networks generate feeds for children. Should we draw up more laws to fence in the rampaging algorithms?
In my view, the restricting the use of algorithms and AI here isn’t the right target. A regu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Report from the annual general meeting at GUADEC]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983203/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983203/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At GUADEC
in Denver, Colorado on July 21, the GNOME Foundation held its annual
general meeting (AGM) to provide updates from the foundation's board and committees.
Topics included work accomplished in the past year, challenges
facing the GNOME Foundation–including fundraising and finding a new
executive director–and some insight into plans for the next year. And
last, but not least, the awarding of the Pants of Thanks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983935/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983935/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (curl), Mageia (virtualbox), Oracle (squid), Red Hat (kernel), SUSE (apache2, bind, cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, devscripts, espeak-ng, freerdp, ghostscript, gnome-shell, gtk2, gtk3, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, kubevirt, libgit2, openssl-3, orc, p7zip, python-dnspython, and shadow), and Ubuntu (kernel, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-ibm, linux-nvidia, linux-oem-6.8, linux-raspi, linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-raspi, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-aws-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-raspi, linux-gcp-5.15, and linux-lowlatency).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure boot with auto-signing in ESP RainMaker OTA]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d1a2e1161059</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/secure-boot-with-auto-signing-in-esp-rainmaker-ota-d1a2e1161059?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How multi-sensory data enhances advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490453</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-multi-sensory-data-enhances-advanced-driver-assistance-systems-adas/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T09:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cars have become intelligent, manufacturers have focused on implementing certain smart features at the expense of others. Sensors tied to rear view cameras and blind spot warnings are now nearly ubiquitous, but other safety tools have lagged behind. This is delaying the progress of advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS), a suite of technologies that […]
The post How multi-sensory data enhances advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS) appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8월 여행 추천, 아름다운 배롱나무 명소 추천]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595747</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595747/8%ec%9b%94-%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89-%eb%b0%b0%eb%a1%b1%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4-%eb%aa%85%ec%86%8c-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T08:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조인트 까면서 좌파 대청소, 뭐가 달라졌나.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113098</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113098"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T07:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 한상진이 “차라리 김우룡이 그립다”고 말하는 이유. 이진숙(방송통신위원회 위원장 후보)의 청문회를 지켜보면서 많은 사람들이 불쾌한 기시감을 느끼고 있다. 이동관(전 방통위원장)이 가고 김홍일(전 방통위원장)이 가니 이진숙이 왔다. 지금까지 그랬듯이 청문보고서가 채택되거나 말거나 윤석열(대통령)은 이진숙을 임명할 거고, 이진숙이 가면 비슷한 누군가가 올 가능성이 크다. 이명박 정부 3년차인 2010년의 일이다. ‘방통대군’이라고 불렸던 최시중(당시 방통위원장)이 방통위를 장악하고 있었다. 최시중은...
The post 조인트 까면서 좌파 대청소, 뭐가 달라졌나. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set up a streams for Apache Kafka cluster with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>d924849e-4059-4a9a-8620-3258d7dfdbd9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/30/set-streams-apache-kafka-cluster-ansible"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the project Apache Kafka, streams for Apache Kafka is a powerful, innovative distributed event streaming platform. Using a fully distributed architecture, a streams for Apache Kafka cluster requires you to setup and deploy numerous services, ensure they are all properly configured and, even more importantly, that each component is functional and can communicate with each other. 
For all these reasons, applying an automation solution such as Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform to deploy and manage streams for Apache Kafka makes a lot of sense, especially as Ansible now has a collection dedicated for the product.
Overview
As mentioned, a typical implementation of streams for Apache Kafka includes several components, each deployed on numerous target systems. Depending on the organiza…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romain Pelisse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지리산 정상석 역사와 소회]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595740</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595740/%ec%a7%80%eb%a6%ac%ec%82%b0-%ec%a0%95%ec%83%81%ec%84%9d-%ec%97%ad%ec%82%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T06:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전기차 충전요금 인상 대응안]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595736</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595736/%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%b6%a9%ec%a0%84%ec%9a%94%ea%b8%88-%ec%9d%b8%ec%83%81"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T06:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[티메프 사태, 핵심은 금융과 비금융의 분리다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113075</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113075"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“…약간만 도와주시면은 다시 정상화시키고, 해결하고, 반드시 피해복구를 완전히 할 수 있다는 확신을 갖고 있습니다.” 구영배(큐텐그룹 대표), 국회정무위원회 티몬·위메프 미정산 사태 현안질의, 2024.07.30. 티몬과 위메프를 합쳐서 티메프, 인터파크까지 합쳐서 티메파크라고 부른다. 정부가 어제 긴급 자금 5600억 원을 투입하기로 했다. 사재를 털어 보상한다는 말이 나오더니 갑자기 법정 관리를 신청해서 피해자들이 분노하고 있는 상황이다. 이번 사건을 어떻게 보나....
The post 티메프 사태, 핵심은 금융과 비금융의 분리다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이진숙 청문회의 네 가지 문제: 2012년 MBC 총파업 해직기자의 출석 후기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113053</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113053"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 잘못된 프레임 지난주 이진숙 방통위원장 후보자 인사청문회 사흘 중 첫날과 이튿날 참고인으로 다녀왔습니다. 다들 보셨겠지만 첫날은 이진숙 검증이 아닌 MBC 청문회처럼 흘러갔죠. 전 MBC사장인 국민의힘 김장겸 의원이 후임 사장인 최승호 선배를 불러세워놓고 추궁하는 장면은 아찔했습니다. 김장겸 전 사장에 관해서는 서울고등법원이 ‘방송의 공정성·공익성 훼손, 보도 신뢰도 및 사회적 영향력 하락, 부당노동행위, 조직관리 및 운영 능력...
The post 이진숙 청문회의 네 가지 문제: 2012년 MBC 총파업 해직기자의 출석 후기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>박성호</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘영어 울렁증’ 사라지는데도 외국어 공부는 왜 해야 하냐 묻는다면]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79736</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/29/npsp_foreignlanguage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_foreignlanguage"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T03:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인공지능 기술이 얼마나 발전했는지 절감할 수 있는 분야 중 하나가 번역과 통역일 겁니다. 스마트폰의 번역기 앱을 이용하면 현지어를 한마디도 못 하는 곳에 가서도 여행하는 데 필요한 대화를 어느 정도 할 수 있을 정도입니다. 그러나 번역기가 많은 걸 해주는 세상에서도 번역기가 해줄 수 없는 것이 여전히 있기 때문에 외국어를 배울 이유와 의미는 충분히 많습니다. 비행기 조종사이자 작가인 마크 바노에네커의 칼럼을 번역하고, 해설을 덧붙였습니다. 전문 번역: 번역기가 다 번역해주는데… 외국어 공부는 이제 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/30, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595724</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595724/7-30-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T02:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[티메파크 사태, 경쟁의 룰을 다시 짜야 한다: 슬로우레터 7월30일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112999</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112999"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T22:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정치 진공상태. 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈, 왜 말이 달라졌나. 결국 제2부속실 만든다. “김민석 표가 왜 이렇게 안 나오나.” 더 깊게 읽기. 빅5 병원, 전공의 지원 0명. 이진숙 청문보고서 불발. 피해 금액 1조 원? ‘티메프’ 회생신청. 민간 기업의 실패를 왜 정부가 지원하나. 구영배의 야망. 다르게 읽기. 티메파크 사태, 공정위는 뭐했나. 트럼프의 밴스 리스크. 해법과 대안. 인구가 늘었다....
The post 티메파크 사태, 경쟁의 룰을 다시 짜야 한다: 슬로우레터 7월30일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.46.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983850/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983850/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T17:20:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.46.0 of the Git
source-code management system has been released.  This release seems to
consist of a long list of interface and performance improvements rather
than big new features; see the announcement for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an AI-powered service for detecting fraudulent card transactions]]></title>
        <id>8d98dd31-6c94-44f2-a54f-26d1452b6962</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/29/creating-ai-powered-service-detecting-fraudulent-card-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T14:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI and machine learning become integral to modern applications, developers need robust platforms that simplify the development and deployment process. Red Hat OpenShift AI offers a powerful and flexible environment tailored for these needs, making it easier for AI engineers and DevOps teams to collaborate and deliver high-quality AI solutions. In this blog post, we’ll explore how to set up a fraud detection system using Red Hat OpenShift AI, complete with a practical example and a demo API.
Developer experience with OpenShift
OpenShift AI simplifies the journey for teams working on AI applications. Utilizing OpenShift AI and Red Hat OpenShift, developers can enjoy a streamlined and efficient workflow. Let's take a look at an overview of the process:




  

Access Jupyter Notebook: Begi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an AI powered service for detecting fraudulant card transactions]]></title>
        <id>8d98dd31-6c94-44f2-a54f-26d1452b6962</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/29/creating-ai-powered-service-detecting-fraudulant-card-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T14:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI and machine learning become integral to modern applications, developers need robust platforms that simplify the development and deployment process. Red Hat OpenShift AI offers a powerful and flexible environment tailored for these needs, making it easier for AI engineers and DevOps teams to collaborate and deliver high-quality AI solutions. In this blog post, we’ll explore how to set up a fraud detection system using Red Hat OpenShift AI, complete with a practical example and a demo API.
Developer Experience with OpenShift
OpenShift AI simplifies the journey for teams working on AI applications. Utilising OpenShift AI and Red Hat OpenShift, developers can enjoy a streamlined and efficient workflow. Let's take a look  overview of the process:




  

Access Jupyter Notebook: Begin by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.11 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982605/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982605/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of 6.11-rc1
marked the end of the 6.11 merge window on July 28.  By that time,
12,102 non-merge changesets had been pulled into the mainline repository;
about 8,000 of those came in after the
first-half summary was written.  Quite a few significant changes were
to be found in those changesets; there is also one big change that did not
make it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983816/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983816/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (java-11-openjdk), Debian (bind9), Fedora (darkhttpd, mod_http2, and python-scrapy), Red Hat (python3.11, rhc-worker-script, and thunderbird), SUSE (assimp, gh, opera, python-Django, and python-nltk), and Ubuntu (edk2, linux, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux-oracle, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-nvidia-6.5, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, and lua5.4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[두산중공업에 녹색을! 기후위기 스프레이 액션은 무죄]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112977</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112977"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기후활동가들이 베트남 붕앙에 석탄화력발전소를 건설하기로 결정한 두산중공업(현 두산에너빌리티)의 행위를 고발하기 위한 ‘기후불복종’ 운동의 일환으로 조형물에 녹색 스프레이를 뿌리고 현수막을 펼쳤습니다. 1, 2심은 이 같은 직접행동에 책임을 물으며 벌금형을 선고했지만 대법원은 파기환송 했습니다. 이에 상현 기후활동가가 직접행동을 위축시키는 ‘과도한 벌금’에 대해 경고한 대법원의 선고의 의미를 비평했습니다. 기후정의를 위해 기후위기 시대, 우리 사회가 보호해야 할 가장 중요한...
The post 두산중공업에 녹색을! 기후위기 스프레이 액션은 무죄 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to classify Red Hat OpenShift audit logs]]></title>
        <id>8d7ad87c-7f2b-422c-a01d-dad505820806</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/29/how-classify-red-hat-openshift-audit-logs"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audit logs are a crucial component of any robust IT infrastructure, providing a detailed record of activities and changes within a system. In the context of Red Hat OpenShift, a comprehensive and highly scalable container platform, audit logs play a vital role in ensuring security, compliance, and operational transparency.
OpenShift audit logs track a wide range of actions performed by users and services. These logs capture data such as who accessed the system, what actions were taken, and when these actions occurred. By maintaining a detailed and chronological record of these activities, audit logs help administrators monitor the system for unauthorized access, detect potential security breaches, and ensure compliance with organizational and regulatory requirements.
Why use OpenShift audi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Filice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지리산 운해 시기와 운해 장소]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595720</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595720/%ec%a7%80%eb%a6%ac%ec%82%b0-%ec%9a%b4%ed%95%b4-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b8%b0%ec%99%80-%ec%9e%a5%ec%86%8c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T02:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] AI와 같이 살아도 ‘외로움’을 느낄 수밖에 없는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79462</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/28/npsp_aillmloneliness/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aillmloneliness"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 3일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 제가 정의하는 ‘연결’은 에너지입니다. 누군가가 나를 진심으로 봐주고, 들어주고, 가치 있게 여긴다고 느낄 때, 두 사람이 서로 아무런 가치판단 없이 무언가를 주고받을 수 있을 때, 그리고 그들이 그 관계에서 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rukahs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.11-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983760/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983760/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds has released 6.11-rc1 and closed the
merge window for this development cycle.  "The merge window felt pretty
normal, and the stats all look pretty normal too. I was expecting things to
be quieter because of summer vacations, but that (still) doesn't actually
seem to have been the case."

Note that the  extensible scheduler class
("sched_ext") was not merged, even though Torvalds had said he would back in June.  Sched_ext, it
seems, will need another development cycle out of tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘강제노동’ 빠졌는데 찬성? 어느 나라 정부냐는 말이 나온다: 슬로우레터 7월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112941</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112941"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[방통위가 ‘빵통위’가 됐다. 야당 추천은 왜 안 하나. 이진숙 법카 월 420만 원. “바보들의 행진 멈춰라.” 쟁점과 현안. 김건희가 장관 인사에 개입했나. “돌려주라” 했다더니 “맘에 안 드셨나요?” 의사 국가고시 11%만 접수. 윤석열 지지율 반등? 더 깊게 읽기. “저도 요새 거의 야당이라서요.” 국민의힘이 ‘배신자’를 선택한 이유. 상속세 인하, 민주당 동의가 관건. 다르게 읽기. 사도광산이 세계 유산?...
The post ‘강제노동’ 빠졌는데 찬성? 어느 나라 정부냐는 말이 나온다: 슬로우레터 7월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 update to my desktop system]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9248</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/07/28/the-2024-update-to-my-desktop-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have just upgraded my desktop system. As you can see from the picture below, it is a bespoke system; the third system built using the same chassis. The 11 drive bays on the right are configured for six 5.25-inch and five 3.5-inch disks/CD/DVD/tape drives, there is a drive cage that fits above the power […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning Gemma 2 with Keras - and an update from Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/fine-tuning-gemma-2-with-keras-hugging-face-update/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/fine-tuning-gemma-2-with-keras-hugging-face-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T20:14:21.277Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next generation of Gemma models is now available in KerasNLP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing the I/O magic to Berlin]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/bringing-the-io-magic-to-berlin/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/bringing-the-io-magic-to-berlin/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T20:14:16.687Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are some highlights from what we announced both on stage in Berlin and elsewhere in the world in celebration of this event!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro 2M context window, code execution capabilities, and Gemma 2 are available today]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/new-features-for-the-gemini-api-and-google-ai-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/new-features-for-the-gemini-api-and-google-ai-studio/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T20:14:16.669Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers will now be able to give Gemini 1.5 Flash a set of pre-trained data of their own and tune it to improve model performance significantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[태백여행, 바위굴로 흐르는 강물이 신비한 태백 구문소]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595706</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595706/%ed%83%9c%eb%b0%b1%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c-%ed%83%9c%eb%b0%b1-%ea%b5%ac%eb%ac%b8%ec%86%8c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T11:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>