<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2021-09-24T20:07:51.360Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 24, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9021</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-24-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T19:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are offloading too much to tech: The productivity boost that technology drove in the late 1990s and early 2000s has convinced a certain section of the population that software, chips, and data can solve many of the hard problems facing the world. Even my faith in IoT is driven in part by using technology […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 24, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Results from the 2021 Linux Foundation Technical Advisory Board election]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870403/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870403/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T19:55:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2021 election for the Linux Foundation's Technical Advisory board
resulted in all five incumbent members (Greg Kroah-Hartman, Jonathan
Corbet, Steven Rostedt, Ted Ts'o, and Sasha Levin) being re-elected. Of the
1,012 developers authorized to vote, 237 actually cast ballots.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Two security improvements for GCC]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870045/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870045/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T17:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has often been said that the competition between the GCC and LLVM
compilers is good for both of them.  One place where that competition 
shows up is in the area of security features; if one compiler adds a way to
harden programs, the other is likely to follow suit.  Qing
Zhao's session at the 2021
Linux Plumbers Conference told the story of how GCC successfully played
catch-up for two security-related features that were of special interest to
the kernel community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: first connected-bottle perfume fragrance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471044</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-first-connected-bottle-perfume-fragrance/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T15:53:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news, includes NFC connected perfume bottles, sensors news, and funding news in the world of embedded startups.
The post embedded news week: first connected-bottle perfume fragrance appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paco Rabanne perfume delivers connected experience with ST NFC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471055</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/paco-rabanne-perfume-delivers-connected-experience-with-st-nfc/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T15:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Paco Rabanne fragrance for men comes in perfume industry’s first-ever connected bottle powered by ST’s NFC contactless chip.
The post Paco Rabanne perfume delivers connected experience with ST NFC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[coreutils-9.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870372/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870372/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T15:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNU Core Utilities (coreutils) has announced the release of version 9.0 of "the basic file, shell and text manipulation utilities" used by the GNU operating system and various Linux distributions.  In the year and a half or so since the last major release (8.32), various new features were added, including:

cp has changed how it handles data

     
enables CoW [copy on write] by default (through FICLONE ioctl),
     
uses copy offload where available (through copy_file_range),
     
detects holes differently (though SEEK_HOLE)
     
This also applies to mv and install.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As More Workers Go Solo, the Software Stack Is the New Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1984</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/solo-workers-software-stack/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T15:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creator economy is a buzzy, often catchall term used to describe independent contractors. But in reality, most of the innovation has revolved around passion-project content (Substack for writing, Teachable for courses, etc.) and niche side projects. To date, “creator” tools have largely been quasi-horizontal, designed to serve broad categories of largely creative pursuits: writing, podcasting,... Read More
The post As More Workers Go Solo, the Software Stack Is the New Firm appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870365/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870365/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T14:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (mupdf), Fedora (ghostscript, gifsicle, and ntfs-3g), openSUSE (kernel and nodejs14), and SUSE (curl, ffmpeg, gd, hivex, kernel, nodejs14, python-reportlab, sqlite3, and xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blaize and LeiShen integrate lidar and AI for automotive and smart cities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471050</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/blaize-and-leishen-integrate-lidar-and-ai-for-automotive-and-smart-cities/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T13:29:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blaize and LeiShen will jointly promote autonomous driving and smart city projects based on lidar technology, using the Blaize Pathfinder P1600 AI accelerator integrated into LeiShen’s advanced auto grade lidar.
The post Blaize and LeiShen integrate lidar and AI for automotive and smart cities appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[그래프 데이터베이스, 시장 현황과 분석]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82043</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/i9dVC_uSiro/82043"/>
        <updated>2021-09-24T08:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 몇 년 동안 데이터 환경이 크게 바뀌었다. 다양한 소스에서 구조화된 데이터와 구조화되지 않은 데이터를 모두 생성하고 있다. 애플리케이션과 서비스를 그 어느 때보다 더 자주 애자일 방법론으로 개발하고 있으며 데이터 변경은 빠르고 중요하다. 또한, 확장성 요구 사항도 매우 중요한 데, 관계형 데이터베이스 관리 시스템(RDBMS)은 이러한 모든 문제를 처리하도록 설계되지 않았다. 따라서 기업들은 새로운 데이터 요구 사항에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘산업정책’의 귀환, 중국을 정조준해 산업정책을 꺼내 든 미국]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73414</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/09/23/industrial-policy-is-back/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=industrial-policy-is-back"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T22:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(월스트리트저널, Greg Ip) 미국은 오랫동안 정부 주도의 산업정책을 비효율의 전형이라며 비판해 왔습니다. 그러나 최근 반도체, 배터리를 포함한 전략적 산업을 지원하는 수단으로 산업정책을 주목하고 있습니다. 코로나19 팬데믹으로 글로벌 공급망이 무너지고 중국의 경제적 영향력이 높아지면서, 공화당인 트럼프 행정부와 민주당인 바이든 행정부를 막론하고 정부의 산업정책을 지지하는 목소리가 높아졌습니다. 미국 정부가 개입해 미국 산업을 육성하지 않으면 중국이 핵심적인 산업을 지배하게 될 것이라 우려합니다. 정책 전환의 배경과 전망을 설명한 월스트리트저널의 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 Coroutine Iterators]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/?p=3668</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/09/c20-coroutine-iterators/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T16:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my first blog post about C++20 Coroutines I introduced the concepts behind a synchronous or generator style coroutine and developed a template class to support coroutines for any data type.
In this post I’ll add an iterator to the template to support the range-for loop and iterative algorithms. You may want to review that post before reading this one but the following code should act as a reminder about how to write and use a coroutine to read two floating [...] 

The post C++20 Coroutine Iterators appeared first on Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poettering: Authenticated Boot and Disk Encryption on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870194/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870194/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T15:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a
lengthy missive from Lennart Poettering taking Linux distributors to
task for inadequately protecting systems from physical attacks.


	So, does the scheme so far implemented by generic Linux
	distributions protect us against the latter two scenarios?
	Unfortunately not at all. Because distributions set up disk
	encryption the way they do, and only bind it to a user password, an
	attacker can easily duplicate the disk, and then attempt to brute
	force your password. What's worse: since code authentication ends
	at the kernel — and the initrd is not authenticated anymore —,
	backdooring is trivially easy: an attacker can change the initrd
	any way they want, without having to fight any kind of protections.


The article contains a lot of suggestions for how to do things better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Improvements to GCC's -fanalyzer option]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869880/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869880/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T15:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the second year in a row, the GNU Tools Cauldron (the annual gathering
of GNU toolchain developers) has been held as a dedicated track at the
online Linux Plumbers
Conference.  For the 2021 event, that track started with a talk by
David Malcolm on his work with the GCC -fanalyzer option, which
provides access to a number of static-analysis features.  Quite a bit has
been happening with -fanalyzer and more is on the way with the
upcoming GCC 12 release, including, possibly, a set of checks that
have already found at least one vulnerability in the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870190/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870190/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T14:38:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ruby-kaminari and tomcat8), Mageia (389-ds-base, ansible, apache, apr, cpio, curl, firefox, ghostscript, gifsicle, gpac, libarchive, libgd, libssh, lynx, nextcloud-client, openssl, postgresql, proftpd, python3, thunderbird, tor, and vim), openSUSE (chromium, ffmpeg, grilo, hivex, linuxptp, and samba), Oracle (go-toolset:ol8, kernel, kernel-container, krb5, mysql:8.0, and nodejs:12), SUSE (ffmpeg, firefox, grilo, hivex, kernel, linuxptp, nodejs14, and samba), and Ubuntu (ca-certificates, edk2, sqlparse, and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Much ado about privacy and support]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9017</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-much-ado-about-privacy-and-support/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show kicks off with the news of the Raspberry Pi Trading company closing a new funding round of $45 million. We talk about what the Pi Trading company is, how it relates to the Foundation, and how companies are building Pis. We then dig into Apple’s plans for healthcare, including plans for tracking mental […]
The post Podcast: Much ado about privacy and support appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21세기의 질문]]></title>
        <id>http://wallflower.egloos.com/4201693</id>
        <link href="http://wallflower.egloos.com/4201693"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T11:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[추석 명절 연휴가 끝났다. 추석에 고향을 찾기보다 휴양지를 찾는 이들이 더 많아진 것이 요즘 세태이지만, 이제는 추석이 한국 고유의 명절이라는 사실을 알고 외국 친구들이 ‘해피 추석’이라는 메시지를 보내줄 정도로 한국에 대한 인지도도 높아졌다. 정작 한국인들 사이.... 글 전체보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이택광</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[외면당한 죽음, 주목받은 죽음: 택배업계 ‘을병 갈등’ 부추기는 조선·동아]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82025</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/zsF11waQDqg/82025"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T08:50:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CJ대한통운의 한 대리점주가 8월 30일 목숨을 끊었습니다. CJ대한통운 대리점연합회에 따르면 사망한 대리점주는 해당 대리점 소속 택배노조 조합원의 폭언으로 괴로워했고, 이들의 배송거부로 극심한 스트레스를 겪었다고 했습니다. 장례 기간 입장을 내지 않던 택배노조는 9월 2일 일부 조합원이 대리점주를 괴롭힌 정황을 확인했다며 사과했습니다. 다만, 해당 대리점은 지속적 수수료 삭감과 6년간 임금 지연 지급 등으로 조합원들과 갈등을 빚어왔으며, 이를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘택배’ 갈등의 진짜 구조: 누가 ‘을·병 갈등’을 부추기는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82016</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/RVnvfWk-CHw/82016"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T06:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[8월 30일 경기도 김포 CJ대한통운의 한 대리점주가 극단적인 선택을 한 안타까운 일이 벌어졌다. CJ대한통운 택배대리점연합회는 고인이 남긴 유서에 관해 이렇게 말했다: “유서를 확인한 결과 고인이 조합원들과의 갈등으로 극심한 스트레스를 받았으며 조합원 12명 이름을 구체적으로 지목하기도 했다.”(CJ대한통운 택배대리점연합회) 고인과 갈등을 빚었다는 조합원은 전국택배노동조합(이하 택배노조) 소속 노동자들이다. 언론부터 정치권까지, ‘을의 갈등’ 부추기기 주요 언론은 일제히 택배노조 상급단체인 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 23, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869381/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869381/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-23T00:35:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 23, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Roslyn API-based static analyzer for C#]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0867/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/294cUpY4MnU/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After you read this article, you'll have the knowledge to create your own static analyzer for C#. With the help of the analyzer, you can find potential errors and vulnerabilities in the source code of your own and other projects. Are you intrigued? Well, let's get started.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Courtès: What's in a package]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870047/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870047/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T20:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over at the Guix-HPC blog, Ludovic Courtès writes about trying to package the PyTorch machine-learning library for the Guix distribution.  Building from source in a user-verifiable manner is part of the philosophy behind Guix, but there were a number of problems that were encountered:

The first surprise when starting packaging PyTorch is that, despite being on PyPI, PyTorch is first and foremost a large C++ code base. It does have a setup.py as commonly found in pure Python packages, but that file delegates the bulk of the work to CMake.

The second surprise is that PyTorch bundles (or "vendors", as some would say) source code for no less than 41 dependencies, ranging from small Python and C++ helper libraries to large C++ neural network tools. Like other distributions such as Debian, Guix avoids bundling: we would rather have one Guix package for each of these dependencies. The rationale is manifold, but it boils down to keeping things auditable, reducing resource usage, and making security updates practical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A discussion on folios]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869942/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869942/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T18:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, Matthew Wilcox might have guessed that his session
at the 2021 Linux
Plumbers Conference would be focused rather differently.  But, as we reported earlier in September, his folio patch set ran into some, perhaps
unexpected, opposition and, ultimately, did not land in the mainline for
5.15.  Instead of discussing how to use folios as part
of the File
Systems microconference, he led a discussion that was, at least in part, on the
path forward for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME 41 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870031/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870031/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T18:11:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNOME project has announced the
release of GNOME 41.

The most notable changes this in release include an improved Software app, new multitasking settings, and enhanced power management features. With these changes, GNOME is smarter, more flexible, and offers a richer and more engaging experience than ever before.

The new release also comes with significant improvements for developers, including a new developer documentation website, a major new version of the Human Interface Guidelines, new features in the Builder IDE, GTK 4 enhancements, and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Beginner to Machine Learning Instructor In A Year]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/zMMLdXPR18o/from-beginner-to-machine-learning-expert.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/zMMLdXPR18o/from-beginner-to-machine-learning-expert.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:59:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Salim Abid, MENA Regional Lead, Developer Relations
     
Yara Elkady, Google Developer Student Club (GDSC) Lead, can trace her passion for tech all the way back to a single moment. She was sitting in computer class when her middle school teacher posed a question to the class: 

“Did you know that you can create apps and games like the ones that you spend so much time on?”

It was a simple question, but it was enough to plant the seed that would define the trajectory of Yara’s career. Following in the footsteps of so many beginners before her, Yara did a Google search to find out more about creating apps. She didn’t realize it at the time, but Yara had just taken her first steps down the path to becoming a developer. 
Knowing that she wanted to pursue tech further, Yara went to c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Postgres 14: It's The Little Things (Kerstiens)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870015/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870015/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Craig Kerstiens highlights
some of the "little things" featured in the upcoming PostgreSQL 14
release.


	And now in PostgreSQL 14 there is this seemingly small update,
	pipeline mode, which, according to the docs, allows applications to
	send a query without having to read the result of the previously
	sent query.  Taking advantage of the pipeline mode, a client will
	wait less for the server, since multiple queries/results can be
	sent/received in a single network transaction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update on Memory Safety in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870014/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870014/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T16:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google security blog provides
an overview of what is being done to address memory-safety problems in
the Chrome browser.


	In parallel, we’ll be exploring whether we can use a memory safe
	language for parts of Chrome in the future. The leading contender
	is Rust, invented by our friends at Mozilla. This is (largely)
	compile-time safe; that is, the Rust compiler spots mistakes with
	pointers before the code even gets to your device, and thus there’s
	no performance penalty. Yet there are open questions about whether
	we can make C++ and Rust work well enough together. Even if we
	started writing new large components in Rust tomorrow, we’d be
	unlikely to eliminate a significant proportion of security
	vulnerabilities for many years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A set of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870003/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870003/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.14.7, 5.10.68, 5.4.148, 4.19.207, 4.14.247, 4.9.283, and 4.4.284 have been released. They all contain
important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/870002/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/870002/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:15:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (grilo), Fedora (curl, firefox, mingw-python-pillow, python-pillow, python2-pillow, and webkit2gtk3), openSUSE (chromium, grafana-piechart-panel, kernel, libcroco, php-composer, and xen), Oracle (curl, kernel, and nss and nspr), Red Hat (nodejs:12), Slackware (alpine), SUSE (ghostscript, grafana-piechart-panel, kernel, and xen), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-hwe, linux-hwe-5.11, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, and linux-raspi2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Latin America’s Creator Economy: Rich in Influence, Poor in Cash]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1945</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/latin-america-creator-economy/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[14 hours and 40 minutes. That’s the average daily media consumption in Latin America—the highest in the world, according to a recent GWI survey. In addition, Latin America tops the charts for internet usage: the average Brazilian spends more than 10 hours a day online (three hours longer than the global average). And 88 percent... Read More
The post Inside Latin America’s Creator Economy: Rich in Influence, Poor in Cash appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Z-Wave, hello HomeKit smart garage door opener]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9006</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/goodbye-z-wave-hello-homekit-smart-garage-door-opener/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T13:52:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past four years, I’ve been using a GoControl Z-Wave smart garage door opener. Well, technically, I’ve been using it for about two years but it’s been installed since 2017. Once I moved away from smart home hubs that support Z-Wave, the GoControl has lain dormant. Since I’ve been transitioning over to HomeKit this […]
The post Goodbye Z-Wave, hello HomeKit smart garage door opener appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오구라 기조]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222513143087</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222513143087"/>
        <updated>2021-09-22T05:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222291932803 <2015년 8월 효고현의 '오다 마코토를 읽는 시민모임' 강연에서 김종철이 거론한 인물들은 그런 점에서 매우 흥미롭다. 그는 먼저 일본 근대, 메이지 유신의 선각자로 칭송받는 일본 최고액권 1만엔짜리 지폐의 얼굴 후쿠자와 유키치를 “조선이나 중국인의 입장에서는 엄청난 재앙과 비극과 불행의 사상적 씨앗을 뿌린 장본인”으로 비판하면서 “이 탈아입구론의 근저에 있는 사고구조가 여전히 일본 사회 속에 만만치 않게 살아 있다는 사실”을 지적한다. 그리고 등장시킨 인물이 오구라 기조(小倉紀蔵) 교토대 철학 교수다. 서울대 대학원에서 동양철학을 공부하고 박사학위를 받.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rosenzweig: Panfrost achieves OpenGL ES 3.1 conformance on Mali-G52]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869944/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869944/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T21:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alyssa Rosenzweig reports
that the open-source Panfrost driver for Mali GPUs has achieved official
conformance on Mali-G52 for OpenGL ES 3.1.

This important milestone is a step forward for the open source driver, as it now certifies Panfrost for use in commercial products containing Mali G52 and paves the way for further conformance submissions on other Mali GPUs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MISRA C: struggle for code quality and security]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0866/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/LUhbbJ-3UyE/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of years ago the PVS-Studio analyzer got its first diagnostic rules to check program code compliance with the MISRA C and MISRA C++ standards. We collected feedback and saw that our clients were interested in using the analyzer to check their projects for MISRA compliance. So, we decided to further develop the analyzer in this direction. The article covers the MISRA C/C++ standard and the MISRA Compliance report. It also shows what we already managed to do and what we plan to achieve by the end of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Weaponizing middleboxes]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869842/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869842/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T20:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Middleboxes are,
unfortunately in many ways, a big part of today's internet.  While middleboxes
inhabit the same physical niche as routers, they are not aimed at packet forwarding;
instead they are meant to monitor and manipulate the packets that they
see.  The effects of those devices on users of the networks they reign over may be
unfortunate as well, but the rest of the internet is only affected when
trying to communicate with those users—or so it was thought.  Based on some
recently reported research, it turns out that middleboxes can be abused to 
inflict denial-of-service (DoS) attacks elsewhere on the net.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Skip the setup— Run code directly from Google Cloud’s documentation]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/QS5xu3zyerY/run-code-directly-from-google-cloud-documentation.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/QS5xu3zyerY/run-code-directly-from-google-cloud-documentation.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T17:30:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Abby Carey, Developer Advocate
 
 Long gone are the days of looking for documentation, finding a how-to guide, and questioning whether the commands and code samples actually work. 
Google Cloud recently added a Cloud Shell integration within each and every documentation page. 
This new functionality lets you test code in a preprovisioned virtual machine instance while learning about Google Cloud services. Running commands and code from the documentation cuts down on context switching between the documentation and a terminal window to run the commands in a tutorial. 
This gif shows how Google Cloud’s documentation uses Cloud Shell, letting you run commands in a quickstart within your Cloud Shell environment. 
 
 If you’re new to developing on Google Cloud, this creates a low barri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Labs Pose Major Threat — Here’s What U.S. Should Do]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1928</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/global-labs-pose-major-threat-heres-what-u-s-should-do/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T15:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is an excerpt from the book UNCONTROLLED SPREAD by Scott Gottlieb, MD. Copyright © 2021 by Scott Gottlieb. Published on Future with permission by Harper, an imprint of HarperCollins Publishers. Establishing the odds that a lab might have played a role in expanding the COVID outbreak isn’t merely a curiosity, or a political... Read More
The post Global Labs Pose Major Threat — Here’s What U.S. Should Do appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869923/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869923/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T15:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (webkit2gtk, wpewebkit, and xen), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (curl, go-toolset:rhel8, krb5, mysql:8.0, nodejs:12, and nss and nspr), and Ubuntu (curl and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forget perimeters; for security, look at device behavior]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9000</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/forget-perimeters-for-security-look-at-device-behavior/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T13:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not a week goes by without some sort of vulnerability or breach associated with the IoT taking place. More devices, varied devices, and the rise of far more sophisticated attackers have led to big IT firms investing in their own security capabilities while our government issues executive orders trying to compel companies to invest in […]
The post Forget perimeters; for security, look at device behavior appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How containers improve the way we develop software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471040</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-containers-improve-the-way-we-develop-software/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T12:26:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To understand containers is to understand the future of software development. Here’s how to best leverage this software innovation. Containers are known as an amazing...
The post How containers improve the way we develop software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Hayzen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reaching the unreachable with satellite IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471034</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/reaching-the-unreachable-with-satellite-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-21T11:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It comes as no surprise that capturing data in some of the hardest to reach corners of the planet is a challenge any IoT player...
The post Reaching the unreachable with satellite IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anne van Gemert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hoyt: Structural pattern matching in Python 3.10]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869883/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869883/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T22:40:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ben Hoyt has published a critical
overview of the Python 3.10 pattern-matching feature.


	As shown above, there are cases where match really
	shines. But they are few and far between, mostly when handling
	syntax trees and writing parsers. A lot of code does have
	if ... elif chains, but these are often either
	plain switch-on-value, where elif works almost as well, or
	the conditions they’re testing are a more complex combination of
	tests that don’t fit into case patterns (unless you use awkward
	case _ if cond clauses, but that’s strictly worse than
	elif).


(Pattern matching has been covered here as
well).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mentoring future women Experts]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/ft4i4rBon40/mentoring-future-women-experts.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/ft4i4rBon40/mentoring-future-women-experts.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T17:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Justyna Politanska-Pyszko
 Google Developers Experts is a global community of developers, engineers and thought leaders who passionately share their technical knowledge with others.  
Becoming a Google Developers Expert is no easy task. First, you need to have strong skills in one of the technical areas - Android, Kotlin, Google Cloud, Machine Learning, Web Technologies, Angular, Firebase, Google Workspace, Flutter or other. You also need to have a track record of sharing your knowledge - be it via conference talks, your personal blog, youtube videos or in some other form. Finally, you need one more thing. The courage to approach an existing Expert or a Google employee and ask them to support your application. 
It’s not easy, but it’s worth it. Joining the Experts community comes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] More Rust concepts for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869428/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869428/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T16:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first day of the Kangrejos (Rust for Linux) conference
introduced the project and what it was trying to accomplish; day 2 covered a number of core Rust
concepts and their relevance to the kernel.  On the third and final day of
the conference, Wedson Almeida Filho delved deeper into how Rust can be
made to work in the Linux kernel, covered some of the lessons that have been
learned so far, and discussed next steps with a number of kernel
developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869863/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869863/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T15:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (gnutls28, nettle, nextcloud-desktop, and openssl1.0), Fedora (dovecot-fts-xapian, drupal7, ghostscript, haproxy, libtpms, lynx, wordpress, and xen), openSUSE (xen), Red Hat (rh-ruby27-ruby), and SUSE (openssl, openssl1, and xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony stacks SPAD sensor and logic in single chip for automotive lidar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471010</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/sony-stacks-spad-sensor-and-logic-in-single-chip-for-automotive-lidar/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T13:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony said its new IMX459 is the industry’s first stacked SPAD depth sensor for automotive lidar applications that includes SPAD pixels and distance measuring processing circuit on a single chip. 
The post Sony stacks SPAD sensor and logic in single chip for automotive lidar appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.15-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869838/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869838/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T13:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.15-rc2 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


So I've spent a fair amount of this week trying to sort out all the
odd warnings, and I want to particularly thank Guenter Roeck for his
work on tracking where the build failures due to -Werror come from.

Is it done? No. But on the whole I'm feeling fairly good about this
all, even if it has meant that I've been looking at some really odd
and grotty code. Who knew I'd still worry about some odd EISA driver
on alpha, after all these years? A slight change of pace ;)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 takeaways from this week’s Works With event]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8996</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/6-takeaways-from-this-weeks-works-with-event/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T13:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Silicon Labs held its annual Works With event, covering all aspects of the IoT. While many of the sessions were aimed at engineers trying to learn specific skills for product development, the event held a few panels with a larger focus that included elements worth noting. Silicon Labs also made three big news announcements […]
The post 6 takeaways from this week’s Works With event appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel materials could cool high-power devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471026</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/novel-materials-could-cool-high-power-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New substrates could be more effective than state-of-the-art thermal management materials in high-power density applications. Thermal management has quickly become one of the most significant...
The post Novel materials could cool high-power devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[워드프레스 테이블 플러그인 wpDataTables test]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583622</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583622/%ec%9b%8c%eb%93%9c%ed%94%84%eb%a0%88%ec%8a%a4-%ed%85%8c%ec%9d%b4%eb%b8%94-%ed%94%8c%eb%9f%ac%ea%b7%b8%ec%9d%b8-wpdatatables-test"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T08:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Return: std::any, std::optional, or std::variant?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/sphero-cpp-return/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/sphero-cpp-return/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-20T05:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What should happen when the data returned from a function is not valid? It might be an error or just how the system operates (embedded environment, a timeout). In this article, you’ll see a practical example from the robotics area where the vocabulary types from C++17 play important roles.
This is a guest post written by Rud Merriam:
Rud is a retired software engineer with interest in C++, embedded / robotic systems, and general hacking. He’s written about C++ for embedded systems for Hackaday and is currently working to catch up on C++20 capabilities and write about them. Reach him on Twitter at @r_merriam.
This text was initially published @Medium - see here.
Exploring C++ STL for Function Return Status
Sphero released the RVR robot above in 2019. Before its release, I worked to build a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncontrolled Spread: Science, Policy, Institutions, Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=1918</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/uncontrolled-spread-gottlieb-book-science-policy-institutions-technology-infrastructure-public-private-pandemic-emergency-beyond/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T23:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no question technology played a huge role in the recent/current pandemic, including especially in the plug-and-play engineering and incredibly fast development behind the mRNA vaccines… But is there an even bigger role for the private sector, not just government, to play (and partner) when it comes to key infrastructure for future such emergencies, and... Read More
The post Uncontrolled Spread: Science, Policy, Institutions, Infrastructure appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonal Chokshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutorial: GNU gcov Coverage with the NXP i.MX RT1064]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33275</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/09/19/tutorial-gnu-gcov-coverage-with-the-nxp-i-mx-rt1064/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T17:11:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial shows how to use and collect coverage data using the GNU gcov tool. As board and hardaware I’m using the NXP i.MX RT1064 EVK: While this tutorial uses this specific board, things are pretty generic and should be … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quext uses LoRa radios to connect smart appartments]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8954</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/quext-uses-lora-radios-to-connect-smart-appartments/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With Smart Rent going public last month, the acquisition last year of Stratis by RealPages, and an increased focus on implementing smart home features across a portfolio of rental units, multifamily IoT is having a moment. That is why I was intrigued to talk to Tray Johnson, VP of innovation at Quext, which has introduced an IoT product for multifamily […]
The post Quext uses LoRa radios to connect smart appartments appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[독보적 데이타 분석기업, 팔란티어 비즈니스 모델과 투자 포인트]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583589</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583589/%ed%8c%94%eb%9e%80%ed%8b%b0%ec%96%b4-%eb%b9%84%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88%ec%8a%a4-%eb%aa%a8%eb%8d%b8"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T07:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국철학에 대한 외경심]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222510733096</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222510733096"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T06:55:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[중국철학이나 동양철학에 대해서 외경심을 갖고 연구하라. 아마 서양 철학자들이 중국에 철학이 없다. 기껏해야 공자에서 볼 수 있듯이 삶의 지혜처럼 보이는 동네 늙은이의 인생에 대한 언명들이 있을 뿐이라는 혹독한 비판에 대한 대응이 이것일 것이다. 존경하라. 중국의 철학이란 그런 시시한 것이 아니다. 존경하고 공감하고 동정(同情)하면 어떤 보석을 발견할 것이다. 그러나 이러한 요구는 그렇게 바람직하지 못하다고 생각한다. 외경과 공감을 요구하기 전에, 외경하고 공감할 수밖에 없는 것을 보여주면 된다. 따라서 그것을 보고 존경하고 공감할 수밖에 없게 만들면 된다. 풍우란에 대한 한 글이 풍우란의 독창적 철학, 신리학(新理.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s how I juggle embedded projects (home office/workspace tour)]]></title>
        <id>https://jaycarlson.net/?p=1914</id>
        <link href="https://jaycarlson.net/2021/09/18/juggle-embedded-projects-home-office-workspace-tour/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-19T04:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My workspace has gone through a ton of changes over the years, but this year, I started making a concerted...
The post Here’s how I juggle embedded projects (home office/workspace tour) appeared first on Jay Carlson.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jay Carlson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시총 100조 기업을 만든 스노우플레이크 비전과 스노우플레이크 비즈니스 모델]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583463</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583463/%ec%8a%a4%eb%85%b8%ec%9a%b0%ed%94%8c%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac-%eb%b9%84%ec%a0%84%ea%b3%bc-%eb%b9%84%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88%ec%8a%a4-%eb%aa%a8%eb%8d%b8"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T16:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few weekend stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869746/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869746/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T15:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The relatively large
5.14.6,
5.13.19, and
5.10.67
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.  Note that this is the final update for the 5.13.x
series.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What local alternatives are there to cloud-based Nest Cams?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8988</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/what-local-alternatives-are-there-to-cloud-based-nest-cams/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Paul called in with a question about his smart home. He currently uses indoor Nest Cams pointing outside, along with Ubiquiti UniFi routers and they work fine, as expected. However, he’s thinking about replacing his Nest Cams with different devices so that he can keep his video files […]
The post What local alternatives are there to cloud-based Nest Cams? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8월 미국 소매판매 0.7% 증가, 델타변이 확산에도 불구 미국 경제의 견고함을 보여주다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583538</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583538/8%ec%9b%94-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%86%8c%eb%a7%a4%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4"/>
        <updated>2021-09-18T02:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 17, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8992</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-17-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T20:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Home Assistant tries with a new hub: The campaign for Home Assistant Amber is now live. For $149, customers can buy a Raspberry Pi computer that is pre-loaded with Home Assistant’s software and several radios including Wi-Fi, Bluetooth, and Zigbee. (The Zigbee radio will support Matter once that certification is out.) While some people are familiar […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 17, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schaller: Cool happenings in Fedora Workstation land]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869561/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869561/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T16:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a
post from Christian Schaller describing a number of the
desktop-oriented improvements that can be expected in the Fedora 35
release.


	And I know some people will wonder why we spent so much time
	working with NVidia around their binary driver, but the reality is
	that NVidia is the market leader, especially in the professional
	Linux workstation space, and there are lot of people who either
	would end up not using Linux or using Linux with X without it,
	including a lot of Red Hat customers and Fedora users. And that is
	what I and my team are here for at the end of the day, to make sure
	Red Hat customers are able to get their job done using their Linux
	systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conill: The long-term consequences of maintainers’ actions]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869557/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869557/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T16:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ariadne Conill looks
at the difficulties caused by the OpenSSL 3 transition in the
context of Alpine Linux.


	For distributions, however, the story is different:
	cryptography moved to using Rust, because they wanted to
	leverage all of the static analysis capabilities built into the
	language.  This, too, is a reasonable decision, from a development
	perspective.  From the ecosystem perspective, however, it is
	problematic, as the Rust ecosystem is still rapidly evolving, and
	so we cannot support a single branch of the Rust compiler for an
	entire 2 year lifecycle, which means it exists in community.  Our
	solution, historically, has been to hold cryptography at
	the latest version that did not require Rust to build.  However,
	that version is not compatible with OpenSSL 3, and so it will
	eventually need to be upgraded to a new version which is.  And so,
	since cryptography has to move to community, so does
	paramiko and Ansible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Key Rust concepts for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869317/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869317/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T15:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first day of the online Kangrejos conference was focused on
introducing the effort to bring the Rust programming language into the 
Linux kernel.  On the second day, conference organizer Miguel Ojeda shifted
to presenting the Rust language itself with an emphasis on what Rust can
provide for kernel development.  The result was a useful resource for
anybody who is curious about this project, but who has not yet had the time
to become familiar with Rust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: celebrating a visionary, and edge compute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471005</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-celebrating-a-visionary-and-edge-compute/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T15:23:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week's embedded news, includes a tribute to a visionary, plus the launch of new sever compute modules for the edge.
The post embedded news week: celebrating a visionary, and edge compute appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869521/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869521/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T13:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (firefox and thunderbird), Fedora (haproxy, wordpress, and xen), openSUSE (apache2-mod_auth_openidc, fail2ban, ghostscript, haserl, libcroco, nextcloud, and wireshark), Oracle (kernel and kernel-container), Slackware (httpd), SUSE (crmsh, gtk-vnc, libcroco, Mesa, postgresql12, postgresql13, and transfig), and Ubuntu (libgcrypt20, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-oem-5.13, python3.4, python3.5, and qtbase-opensource-src).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goodbye Sir Clive Sinclair]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470998</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/goodbye-sir-clive-sinclair/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T10:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A tribute to Sir Clive Sinclair, an electronics industry inventor and entrepreneur who was part of an era that created a whole new generation of programmers and gamers.  
The post Goodbye Sir Clive Sinclair appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국철학의 합법성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222509233834</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222509233834"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T10:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[풍우란 혹은 펑유란을 통해 중국철학의 철학 개념, 또는 철학성 혹은 <합법성>의 문제를 고찰하고 있는 글을 본다. 그런데 약간 미묘하고 복합적인 감정이 든다. 왜 중국철학자 펑유란인가? 오히려 우리 철학자를 탐구했어야 하는 것이 아닌가? 한국철학은 철학인가, 그것은 재료만 한국철학이었지 실제로 서양철학과 유사한 것이 아닌가, 아니면 철학이 아니라, 일종의 사상사가 아니었던가? 그래서 그것이 사학 논문인지, 철학 논문인지 별로 구분이 되는 않는 그런 것이었는가? 혹은 한국적 철학이 가능한가, ‘한국적’이란 무슨 의미인가? 그런데 이런 물음들에 대한 글을 중국학 혹은 중국철학 전공자에게 요구한다는 것은 과연 정당.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[검찰 고발 사주 의혹, 메시지 반박이 어려우면 메신저를 공격하라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81997</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/5kYka0bz7UE/81997"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T08:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인터넷매체 뉴스버스 단독보도로 시작된 ‘윤석열 검찰의 고발 사주 의혹’ 논란의 핵심은 지난해 4.15 총선을 앞둔 시점에서 검찰이 직접 작성한 고발장을 야당에 전달해 형사 고발을 사주했는지 여부입니다. 그러나 이번 사건의 본질인 ‘검찰 사유화’와 ‘검찰의 선거개입’ 여부에 대한 진상규명은 비껴간 채 언론은 오히려 ‘제보자 논란’, ‘제보 사주 의혹’에 집중하고 있습니다. 민주언론시민연합은 언론이 ‘제보자 조성은’을 어떻게 보도하고 있는지 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 시대, ‘영리병원’ 손들어준 시대착오적 판결]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81958</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/rUcByQe6TGw/81958"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T05:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지하철을 타고 문득 반대편에 앉아 있는 이들이 ‘마스크’를 벗고 있는 모습을 떠올려본다. 다시 누군가의 ‘생’얼굴을 보는 생경함을 떨치고 이내 익숙해 질 수 있을까. 코로나19는 끝이 보이지 않지만, 언젠가 ‘종식’이란 것이 된다면 그 이후의 사회는 이전과는 달라져 있을 것이다. 마스크를 쓰는 것이 오히려 자연스러운 일상이 될 것 같다고 할까. 코로나19가 새삼 일깨운 ‘공공의료 중요성’ 공공의료에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Two Cents #49] NFT, DAO, Metaverse; &#52285;&#50629;&#8202;-&#8202;&#49457;&#51109; &#51204;&#47029;, GTM; &#49884;&#51109;&#8202;-&#8202;BNPL, CRISPR, &#45367;&#54540;&#47533;&#49828; &#44172;&#51076;; &#49828;&#53440;&#53944;&#50629;&#8202;-&#8202;YC 2021, Airtable, Afterpay; &#51473;&#44397;&#8202;-&#8202;VC &#53804;&#51088;, &#48288;&#51060;&#51669; &#51613;&#49884;; FTX, SushiSwap; VC &#47784;&#45944; &#48320;&#54868;; &#49464;&#54028;&#54532;&#46993; (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-49-nft-dao-metaverse-gtm-56a</id>
        <link href="https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-49-nft-dao-metaverse-gtm-56a"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T01:10:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[9월16일 오후 실수로 편집 도중 Part 2가 먼저 발송되어 버렸습니다ㅠㅠ 원래 일정대로 Part 1, Part 2를 다시 보내 드립니다 - 허진호] [스타트업] Here are all the companies from Y Combinator’s Summer 2021 Demo Day, Part 1 | TechCrunch Here are all the companies from Day 2 of Y Combinator’s Summer 2021 Demo Day | TechCrunch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin Ho Hur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Two Cents #49] NFT, DAO, Metaverse; &#52285;&#50629;&#8202;-&#8202;&#49457;&#51109; &#51204;&#47029;, GTM; &#49884;&#51109;&#8202;-&#8202;BNPL, CRISPR, &#45367;&#54540;&#47533;&#49828; &#44172;&#51076;; &#49828;&#53440;&#53944;&#50629;&#8202;-&#8202;YC 2021, Airtable, Afterpay; &#51473;&#44397;&#8202;-&#8202;VC &#53804;&#51088;, &#48288;&#51060;&#51669; &#51613;&#49884;; FTX, SushiSwap; VC &#47784;&#45944; &#48320;&#54868;;&#160;&#49464;&#54028;&#54532;&#46993; (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-49-nft-dao-metaverse-gtm</id>
        <link href="https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-49-nft-dao-metaverse-gtm"/>
        <updated>2021-09-17T01:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[9월16일 오후 실수로 편집 도중 Part 2가 먼저 발송되어 버렸습니다ㅠㅠ 원래 일정대로 Part 1, Part 2를 다시 보내 드립니다 - 허진호] [Deep Dive] Vishal Kankani on Twitter: 1/ A long thread on why DAOs are the next logical step in our history and would bring incredible prosperity / Twitter Vishal Kankani on Twitter: 1/ Another long thread on DAOs. There would be millions of miniDAOs. They would come together to form composable and modularized bigDAOs that would have millions of people working for them. / Twitter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin Ho Hur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 도시의 모습은 어떻게 바뀔까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73371</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/09/16/globalcitiesafterpandemic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=globalcitiesafterpandemic"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이코노미스트 원문보기   코로나19 팬데믹으로 무너졌던 경제가 회복하는 양상은 국가별로, 지역별로, 또 산업이나 분야에 따라 천차만별입니다. 재빨리 백신을 보급, 접종한 덕분에 경제도 덩달아 빠르게 정상 궤도에 진입한 나라가 있는가 하면, 여러 가지 이유로 백신 접종률이 좀처럼 오르지 않아 고생인 나라도 많습니다. 팬데믹 상황에서, 또 팬데믹 이후 수요가 몰리는 분야도 있고, 반대로 수요가 뚝 끊겨 존립 자체가 위협받는 업종도 있습니다. 그동안 잘 눈에 띄지 않았던 또 한 가지 차이가 점점 더 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869403/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869403/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T17:49:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four new stable kernels, 5.14.5, 5.13.18, 5.10.66, and 5.4.147, have been released.

This, and the other stable kernels released today, consist of only some
reverts to solve some reported problems with the last round of stable
releases.  Upgrading is not required, but highly recommended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thread vs Bluetooth: the VHS vs Betamax of IoT connections?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470992</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/thread-vs-bluetooth-the-vhs-vs-betamax-of-iot-connections/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T17:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two low power radio internet protocols seek dominance in IoT, but is Thread vs Bluetooth looking like a similar battle to VHS vs Betamax in the 1980s?
The post Thread vs Bluetooth: the VHS vs Betamax of IoT connections? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carsten Rhod Gregersen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Travis CI flaw exposed secrets of thousands of open source projects (ars technica)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869388/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869388/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
ars technica article describes a problem with the Travis
continuous-integration service:


	A security flaw in Travis CI potentially exposed the secrets of
	thousands of open source projects that rely on the hosted
	continuous integration service. Travis CI is a software-testing
	solution used by over 900,000 open source projects and 600,000
	users. A vulnerability in the tool made it possible for secure
	environment variables—signing keys, access credentials, and API
	tokens of all public open source projects—to be exfiltrated.


Any project storing secrets in this service would be well advised to
replace them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The Rust for Linux project]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869145/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869145/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T15:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first ever Rust for Linux conference, known as Kangrejos, got underway on
September 13.  Organizer Miguel Ojeda used the opening session to give
an overview of why there is interest in using Rust in the kernel, where the
challenges are, and what the current status is.  The talk and following
discussion provided a good overview of what is driving this initiative and
where some of the sticking points might be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redefining firmware security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470980</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/redefining-firmware-security/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T14:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A review of potentially unaddressed vectors inherent in current platforms and a look at a potential solution for preventing firmware attacks and elevating platform security based on a trusted control/compute unit security processor.
The post Redefining firmware security appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Chamorro and Gopi Sirineni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 Coroutines]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/?p=3653</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/09/c20-coroutines/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 Coroutines
There seems to be a lot of confusion around the implementation of C++20 coroutines, which I think is due to the draft technical specification for C++20 stating that coroutines are a work in progress so we can’t expect full compiler and library support at this point in time.
A lot of the problems probably arise from the lack of official documentation about working with coroutines. We have been given C++ syntax support for coroutines (the co_yield and co_return) but without [...] 

The post C++20 Coroutines appeared first on Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869380/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869380/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T13:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (sssd), Fedora (libtpms and vim), openSUSE (kernel and php7-pear), Oracle (kernel), Slackware (curl), and Ubuntu (libgcrypt20 and squashfs-tools).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Wyze comes back from the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8982</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-wyze-comes-back-from-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T13:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I need to warn y’all in advance that we don’t discuss Apple news at all this week because nothing really jumped out at us for the IoT. But we did have a lot of other big news starting with Wyze raising $100 million and sharing the precariousness of its situation over the last 18 months. […]
The post Podcast: Wyze comes back from the edge appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인권단체 ‘휴먼라이츠워치’가 언론중재법 개정안을 반대하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81954</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/-CYnduE5nqU/81954"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T09:09:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2021년 9월 16일 오전 9시, 세계 최대 인권단체 중 하나인 휴먼라이츠워치(Human Rights Watch)는 문재인 대통령 및 국회의원 전원 그리고 8인 여야협의체에 3개 국내외 시민단체(사단법인 오픈넷, 진보네트워크센터, 아티클 19-ARTICLE 19-)가 참여하는 공동 서한을 보내 언론중재법 개정안에서 징벌적 손해배상 관련 조항 및 열람차단권 조항을 폐지할 것을 권고했습니다. 의견서에서 휴먼라이츠워치 등은 징벌적 손해배상을 언론에만 적용하고, 언론의 비판 및 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Two Cents #49] NFT, DAO, Metaverse; &#49884;&#51109;&#8202;-&#8202;&#49457;&#51109; &#51204;&#47029;, GTM; &#49884;&#51109;&#8202;-&#8202;BNPL, CRISPR, &#45367;&#54540;&#47533;&#49828; &#44172;&#51076;; &#49828;&#53440;&#53944;&#50629;&#8202;-&#8202;YC 2021, Airtable, Afterpay; &#51473;&#44397;&#8202;-&#8202;VC &#53804;&#51088;, &#48288;&#51060;&#51669; &#51613;&#49884;; FTX, SushiSwap; VC &#47784;&#45944; &#48320;&#54868;;&#160;&#49464;&#54028;&#54532;&#46993; (2/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-49-nft-dao-metaverse-gtm-dab</id>
        <link href="https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-49-nft-dao-metaverse-gtm-dab"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T07:53:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[스타트업] Here are all the companies from Y Combinator’s Summer 2021 Demo Day, Part 1 | TechCrunch Here are all the companies from Day 2 of Y Combinator’s Summer 2021 Demo Day | TechCrunch 요즘 새로 등장하는 스타트업 트렌드를 보기 위해 YC 데모데이는 빠지지 않고 보는 편인데, 이번 ’21 Summer batch에는 ‘아하’ 하는 스타트업이 거의 눈에 띄지 않는다. 아마 a16z, Benchmark, Sequoia 등의 주요 플레이어들이 모두 seed 단계까지 내려 오면서, 눈에 띄는 emerging 트렌드 회사는 모두 싹쓸이해 버려서인 듯. 최근 Clubhouse, BeReal, Poparazzi, YGG 등이 경쟁적으로 투자 받은 것 보면 알 수 있듯이.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin Ho Hur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언론중재법, 마지막 논의에 부쳐]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81943</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/ZFblmiWRwkY/81943"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T06:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[언론중재법 개정안이 여야 합의로 협의체를 구성해 9월 27일까지 처리하기로 결정되었다. 지난 7일 더불어민주당과 국민의힘이 언론중재법 개정안 논의를 위한 ‘8인 협의체’ 구성을 완료했다. 하지만 협의체 구성 이후에도 양당의 핵심 쟁점에 대한 첨예한 입장 차이에 우려를 표한다. 여야가 숙의를 위한 시간을 확보한 만큼 언론중재법 개정안에 대해 피해구제의 관점에서 적극적인 협의의 태도를 보여야 한다. 민주당 vs 국힘  은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 16, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868745/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868745/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-16T00:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 16, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[포스트 팬데믹 시대, 일터에서의 성별간 격차가 커질 수도 있다?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73337</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/09/15/men-dominated-offices-of-the-future/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=men-dominated-offices-of-the-future"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T22:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BBC 원문보기 코로나19 팬데믹으로 인해 재택근무가 일반화되었다가 또 폐쇄됐던 일터가 다시 열리면서 많은 변화가 생기게 되었습니다. 어떤 변화는 다시 적응하면 그만인 것들이지만, 일터의 구성이 근본적으로 달라질 수도 있다는 예측도 나옵니다. 회사가 재택근무를 어느 정도 허용하는 유연 근무제를 시행하게 되면, 여성과 남성의 선택이 달라질 수 있기 때문입니다. 2,300명을 대상으로 한 영국의 설문조사 결과에 따르면, 자녀를 둔 여성의 69%는 팬데믹이 끝나도 일주일에 최소 1회는 재택근무를 하고 싶다고 응답했습니다. 반면, 같은 답을 한 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Revisiting NaNs in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869231/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869231/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T22:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in January 2020, we looked at some
oddities in Python's handling of Not a Number (NaN) values in
its statistics
module.  The conversation went quiet after that, but it has been
revived recently with an eye toward fixing the problems that were reported.
As detailed in that earlier article, NaNs are rather strange beasts in the
floating-point universe, so figuring out how best to deal with their
presence is less straightforward than it might seem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SOAFEE architecture for embedded edge enables software defined cars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470975</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/soafee-architecture-for-embedded-edge-enables-software-defined-cars/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T20:40:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SOAFEE addresses software-defined needs of cars quickly and seamlessly, with a standardized framework enhancing proven cloud-native technologies that work at scale in real-time and with safety required for automotive.
The post SOAFEE architecture for embedded edge enables software defined cars appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADLINK brings Ampere Altra SoCs to embedded with COM-HPC modules]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470970</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/adlink-brings-ampere-altra-socs-to-embedded-with-com-hpc-modules/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T19:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADLINK said its new COM-HPC Ampere Altra is world’s first 80-core Arm based COM-HPC module that eliminates power-performance limitations. 
The post ADLINK brings Ampere Altra SoCs to embedded with COM-HPC modules appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869302/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869302/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T15:45:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.14.4, 5.13.17, 5.10.65, and 5.4.146 have been released.  There are
important fixes throughout the tree and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First flexible CPUs, now flexible RAM: Could this jumpstart truly smart clothing?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8972</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/first-flexible-cpus-now-flexible-ram-could-this-jumpstart-truly-smart-clothing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T15:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation in flexible computing components is arriving in wave after wave of late. In June, a report detailed a 32-bit ARM microprocessor that could bend, and this month, we learned that Stanford researchers demonstrated working bendable RAM. When discussing the pliable CPU news on our podcast, I suggested that this could help create smaller sensors […]
The post First flexible CPUs, now flexible RAM: Could this jumpstart truly smart clothing? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869301/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869301/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T15:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (chromium, element-desktop, element-web, firefox, ghostscript, and hedgedoc), Fedora (kernel and openssl), openSUSE (ghostscript, htmldoc, and openssl-1_0_0), Oracle (libtirpc), Red Hat (cyrus-imapd, kernel, and kernel-rt), SUSE (ghostscript), and Ubuntu (apport, curl, and squashfs-tools).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Average American Would Pay $242,000 For One Extra Year of Good Health]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1543</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/economic-case-for-curbing-aging/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T15:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From one of the oldest known works of literature, The Epic of Gilgamesh, which chronicles a mythical quest for immortality, to today’s media fascination with young blood-transfusing biohackers, the notion of conquering aging has long captured our imagination. Conspicuously missing from this narrative, however, is an economic perspective: the monetary implications of curbing aging.   In... Read More
The post The Average American Would Pay $242,000 For One Extra Year of Good Health appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[신입개발자를 뽑지 않는 이유]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=10863</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2021/09/15/why_dont_intern/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T13:26:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 개발자 학교에 있다보니,취업프로그램을 만들기 위해 여러 기업들을 만나게 됩니다. 꽤 많은 회사의 채용팀으로부터 들은 이야기인데, 한 번 정리 해볼까 합니다.이미 많은 친구들에게 이야기를 해준 내용이기도 합니다. 신입사원 A, B 씨 (1) 신입사원 A 씨. 김대리 : “A씨, 우리가 이렇게 저렇게 할건데, 이 모듈 좀 맡아서 다음주까지 만들어 주실래요?” A 씨 : “넵, 알겠습니다.” 그러고 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChipDNA PUF security co-processor provides 30x lower power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470962</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/chipdna-puf-security-co-processor-provides-30x-lower-power/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New PUF technology based cryptographic controller is suitable for securing IoT nodes including medical and wearable devices, as well as long-term deployments in security-critical harsh environments.
The post ChipDNA PUF security co-processor provides 30x lower power appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마음에 닿았던 이태원 클라쓰 명대사를 모아보다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583480</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583480/%ec%9d%b4%ed%83%9c%ec%9b%90-%ed%81%b4%eb%9d%bc%ec%93%b0-%eb%aa%85%eb%8c%80%ec%82%ac"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T10:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시세는 25억, 장부가는 1억? 장기전세주택과 ‘이상한 장부’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81936</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/WhdfrYlc8wc/81936"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T05:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[경실련 조사 결과 서울시와 SH공사가 보유하고 있는 장기전세주택의 자산 가치는 전체 33조 7천억, 호당 평균 10억으로 나타났다. 하지만 SH가 공개한 장기전세주택의 장부가는 7조 5천억, 호당 2.3억으로 시세의 1/5에 불과했다. 아크로리버파크, 래미안퍼스티지 등의 강남권 장기전세주택은 시세가 20~30억까지 형성되어 있지만 SH가 평가한 자산가치는 호당 1억 정도에 불과했다. 자산이 저평가되면 공공주택 사업이 적자사업으로 비춰지며 적극적인 공공주택 확대가 어려워질 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenBSD's pledge and unveil from Python]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/09/15/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/09/15/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-15T02:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was discussed on Hacker News.
Years ago, OpenBSD gained two new security system calls, pledge(2)
(originally tame(2)) and unveil. In both, an application
surrenders capabilities at run-time. The idea is to perform initialization
like usual, then drop capabilities before handling untrusted input,
limiting unwanted side effects. This feature is applicable even where type
safety isn’t an issue, such as Python, where a program might still get
tricked into accessing sensitive files or making network connections when
it shouldn’t. So how can a Python program access these system calls?
As discussed previously, it’s quite easy to access C APIs from
Python through its ctypes package, and this is no exception.
In this article I show how to do it. Here’s the full source if you want to
di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Roundup: managing issues for 20 years]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869118/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869118/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T22:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Roundup Issue Tracker
is a flexible tool for managing issues via the web or
email. However, Roundup is useful for more than
web-based bug tracking or help-desk ticketing; it can be used as a simple 
wiki or to manage tasks
with the Getting Things
Done (GTD) 
methodology. The 20th-anniversary
edition of
Roundup,
version 2.1.0, was
released in July; it is a maintenance release, but there have been a number
of larger improvements in the last year or so. Here we introduce 
Roundup's
features along with the
recent developments that have helped make Roundup even more useful for tracking
issues to their resolution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Billions of Code Name Permutations in 32 bits]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/09/14/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/09/14/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T21:06:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My friend over at Possibly Wrong created a code name generator. By
coincidence I happened to be thinking about code names myself while
recently replaying XCOM: Enemy Within (2012/2013). The game
generates a random code name for each mission, and I wondered how often it
repeats. The UFOpaedia page on the topic gives the word lists: 53
adjectives and 76 nouns, for a total of 4028 possible code names. A
typical game has around 60 missions, and if code names are generated
naively on the fly, then per the birthday paradox around half of all games
will see a repeated mission code name! Fortunately this is easy to avoid,
and the particular configuration here lends itself to an interesting
implementation.
Mission code names are built using “adjective noun”. Some examples
from the game’s word list:…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869221/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869221/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T14:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by openSUSE (libaom and nextcloud), Oracle (cyrus-imapd, firefox, and thunderbird), Red Hat (kernel and kpatch-patch), Scientific Linux (firefox and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (apport).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[복수의결권 주식, 누구를 위한 ‘계획’입니까?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81930</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/xz_kMr2fgc8/81930"/>
        <updated>2021-09-14T05:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 8월 26일 청와대, 문재인 대통령은 ‘K+벤처’(제2 벤처붐 성과와 미래) 성과보고회를 열고 비상장 벤처기업 복수의결권 주식을 발행토록 하는 법안이 조속히 통과 될 수 있도록 지시를 내렸습니다. 이와 더불어 스톡옵션 비과세 혜택과 주식 양도차익에 대해서도 각종 세제 혜택을 주겠다는 방침입니다. 복수의결권 주식이란? 복수의결권 주식이란 대주주 자기 출자지분을 초과하는 ‘무자본’ 의결권 주식입니다. 정부와 국회는 최대 1주10표를 비상장 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimum Viable Participation in Crypto: Games, Costs, & Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1878</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/minimum-viable-participation-in-crypto-games-costs-accessibility/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T21:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When people talk about the recent past and envision the distant future of crypto, conversation always comes back to the cycle of wealth creation and redistribution. Consciously or unconsciously, there’s an understanding that growing the network doesn’t just involve enriching the current members, it demands expanding the number of people who can afford to participate. ... Read More
The post Minimum Viable Participation in Crypto: Games, Costs, & Accessibility appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Whole-home audio and smart lighting: DIY or go pro?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8958</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/whole-home-audio-and-smart-lighting-diy-or-go-pro/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T21:13:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Dave called in to our voicemail hotline looking for advice. His brother-in-law has a Google TV and Nest Audio speakers but wants to invest in whole-home audio and smart lighting. Dave wonders what we would suggest and even gives us a virtual blank check: He says to consider […]
The post Whole-home audio and smart lighting: DIY or go pro? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A disagreement over the PostgreSQL trademark]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869108/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869108/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T17:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
release on PostgreSQL.org describes an ongoing disagreement over the
PostgreSQL trademark:


	In 2020, the PostgreSQL Core Team was made aware that an
	organization had filed applications to register the 'PostgreSQL'
	and 'PostgreSQL Community' trademarks in the European Union and the
	United States, and had already registered trademarks in Spain. The
	organization, a 3rd party not-for-profit corporation in Spain
	called 'Fundación PostgreSQL,' did not give any indication to the
	PostgreSQL Core Team or PGCAC that they would file these
	applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Drone control via gestures using MediaPipe Hands]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/U9xrEpogvM4/drone-control-via-gestures-using-mediapipe-hands.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/U9xrEpogvM4/drone-control-via-gestures-using-mediapipe-hands.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T17:00:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A guest post by Neurons Lab
  
Please note that the information, uses, and applications expressed in the below post are solely those of our guest author, Neurons Lab, and not necessarily those of Google. 
How the idea emerged
With the advancement of technology, drones have become not only smaller, but also have more compute. There are many examples of iPhone-sized quadcopters in the consumer drone market and the computing power to do live tracking while recording 4K video. However, the most important element has not changed much - the controller. It is still bulky and not intuitive for beginners to use. There is a smartphone with on-display control as an option; however, the control principle is still the same.  
That is how the idea for this project emerged: a more personalised approach t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 5.15 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868221/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868221/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T16:14:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released 5.15-rc1 and closed
the merge window for 
this release on September 12; at that point, 10,471 non-merge
changesets had found their way into the mainline repository.  Those
changesets contain a lot of significant changes and improvements.  Read on
for a summary of what came into the mainline in the roughly 7,000
changesets pulled since our first-half
summary was written.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869103/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869103/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T15:37:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (qemu and thunderbird), Fedora (chromium, firefox, and mosquitto), openSUSE (apache2-mod_auth_openidc, gifsicle, openssl-1_1, php7-pear, and wireshark), Oracle (oswatcher), Red Hat (cyrus-imapd, firefox, and thunderbird), SUSE (apache2-mod_auth_openidc, compat-openssl098, php7-pear, and wireshark), and Ubuntu (git and linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-snapdragon).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDB 11.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869060/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869060/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T13:32:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 11.1 of the GDB debugger is out.  There are a number of new
features, and somebody will surely be disappointed to see that support for
debugging Arm Symbian programs has been removed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why TinyML looks like a fit for the developing world]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8951</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-tinyml-looks-like-a-fit-for-the-developing-world/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T13:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Running small machine learning models on embedded devices has become a rich topic of research and investment, both at large tech companies and in academia. It’s not really mainstream yet, but it’s possible that the use cases where TinyML delivers the most value aren’t necessarily found in rich countries with robust infrastructure and bigger budgets […]
The post Why TinyML looks like a fit for the developing world appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[갤럭시워치4 Wi-Fi(와이파이) 기능]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222504426146</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222504426146"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T08:48:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[갤럭시워치4는 안드로이드 스마트폰과 연동하여 동작하며, 연동하는 방식에 따라 “Bluetooth 모델”과 “LTE 모델” 두 가지 종류가 있습니다. 갤럭시워치4는 전용 OS(Google의 안드로이드 기반 Wear OS)를 가진 모바일 디바이스이므로, 스마트폰과 연동없이 독립적으로 동작하는 기능도 제공하고 있습니다. 일반적인 모바일 디바이스처럼, 갤럭시워치4도 인터넷망과 연결하기 위해서는 Wi-Fi 또는 LTE(모바일 네트워크) 방식을 사용해야 합니다. “갤럭시워치4 Bluetooth 모델”에서는, 인터넷망에 직접 연결을 해야 하는 경우, Wi-Fi 기능을 통하여 인터넷에 연결을 해야 합니다. 따라서, “갤럭시워치4 Bluetooth 모델”에서 제공하고 있는 W.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aepkoreanet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘검찰 고발 사주 의혹’ 보도, 보수·경제지는 소극적이거나 논점 일탈]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81909</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/G_S-C6Ss2bY/81909"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T06:18:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인터넷매체 뉴스버스 [단독/윤석열 검찰, 총선 코앞 유시민·최강욱·황희석 등 국민의힘에 고발 사주] (전혁수 기자)는 9월 2일 지난해 4.15 총선을 앞둔 시점에 검찰이 미래통합당(현 ‘국민의힘’) 측에 범여권 정치인과 언론인 등 11명에 대한 형사 고발을 사주했다고 보도했습니다. 뉴스버스는 당시 손준성 대검 수사정보정책관이 검사 출신 미래통합당 국회의원 후보 김웅 의원(현 국민의힘)에게 두 차례 고발장을 작성해 전달했으며, 이는 미래통합당 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 Oxymoron: constexpr virtual]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/constexpr-virtual/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/constexpr-virtual/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two keywords, constexpr and virtual - can those two work together? Virtual implies runtime polymorphism, while constexpr suggests constant expression evaluation. It looks like we have a contradiction, does it?
Read on and see why those conflicting terms might help us get simpler code.
A basic example
Imagine that you work with some product list, and you want to check if a product fits in a given box size:
#include <cassert>

struct Box {
  double width{0.0};
  double height{0.0};
  double length{0.0};
};

struct Product {
  virtual ~Product() = default;

  virtual Box getBox() const noexcept = 0;
};

struct Notebook : public Product {
  Box getBox() const noexcept override {
    return {.width = 30.0, .height = 2.0, .length = 30.0};
  }
};

struct Flower : public Product {
  Box getBox() c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.15-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869031/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869031/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-13T02:53:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 5.15-rc1 and closed the
merge window for this development cycle.


	So 5.15 isn't shaping up to be a particularly large release, at
	least in number of commits. At only just over 10k non-merge
	commits, this is in fact the smallest rc1 we have had in the 5.x
	series. We're usually hovering in the 12-14k commit range.

	That said, counting commits isn't necessarily the best measure, and
	that might be particularly true this time around. We have a few new
	subsystems, with NTFSv3 and ksmbd standing out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels for Sunday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/869006/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/869006/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-12T20:30:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.14.3,
5.13.16,
5.10.64, and
5.4.145
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인간은 불확실성을 두려워한다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73357</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/09/10/uncertainty/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=uncertainty"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T22:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Elemental, Markham heid) 원문 보기 1927년 공포 소설의 아버지 H.P. 러브크래프트는 이렇게 썼습니다. “인간의 가장 오래되고 강력한 감정은 두려움이다. 그리고 가장 오래되고 강력한 두려움은 미지의 것에 대한 두려움이다.” 러브크래프트는 인간의 뇌가 불확실한 것에 대해 특별히 취약하다는 점을 알고 있었습니다. 이는 이후 이어진 수십 년 동안의 심리학 연구에서 사실로 밝혀졌습니다. 불확실한 것을 견디지 못하는 성격은 여러 불안증 증상과 관련이 있다는 증거가 있습니다. 불확실성이 공황 발작을 유발하는 “파국적 해석(catastrophic interpretations)”의 원인이 된다는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인간은 불확실성을 두려워한다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73357</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/09/10/%ec%9d%b8%ea%b0%84%ec%9d%80-%eb%b6%88%ed%99%95%ec%8b%a4%ec%84%b1%ec%9d%84-%eb%91%90%eb%a0%a4%ec%9b%8c%ed%95%9c%eb%8b%a4/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=%25ec%259d%25b8%25ea%25b0%2584%25ec%259d%2580-%25eb%25b6%2588%25ed%2599%2595%25ec%258b%25a4%25ec%2584%25b1%25ec%259d%2584-%25eb%2591%2590%25eb%25a0%25a4%25ec%259b%258c%25ed%2595%259c%25eb%258b%25a4"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T22:54:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Elemental, Markham heid) 원문 보기 1927년 공포소설의 아버지 H.P. 러브크래프트는 이렇게 썼습니다. “인간의 가장 오래되고 강력한 감정은 두려움이다. 그리고 가장 오래되고 강력한 두려움은 미지의 것에 대한 두려움이다.” 러브크래프트는 인간의 뇌가 불확실한 것에 대해 특별히 취약하다는 것을 알았던 것입니다. 이는 이후 이어진 수십 년 동안의 심리학 연구에서 사실로 밝혀졌습니다. 불확실한 것을 견디지 못하는 성격은 여러 불안증 증상과 관련이 있다는 증거가 있습니다. 불확실성이 공황 발작을 유발하는 “파국적 해석(catastrophic interpretations)”의 원인이 된다는 증거도 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 10, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8949</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-10-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T17:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Pis are pretty popular in industrial settings: Distributor Farnell recently surveyed 1,500 electronics engineers and discovered that 44% of them were using Raspberry Pis as their industrial single-board computer. Arduino boards came in second in popularity, at 28%, and Texas Instruments’ Beagleboards followed, with 6% of electronics engineers choosing them. Almost a quarter of the respondents used […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 10, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German Bundesliga extends AWS ML to broadcast player efficiency data]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470933</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/german-bundesliga-extends-aws-ml-to-broadcast-player-efficiency-data/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T16:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bundesliga uses AWS machine learning and analytics to give fans deeper insights into the game of football, now adding shot efficiency and passing profile to its match facts to be broadcast for the 2021-22 season.
The post German Bundesliga extends AWS ML to broadcast player efficiency data appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPDX Becomes Internationally Recognized Standard for Software Bill of Materials]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868882/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868882/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T16:31:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation has announced that  Software Package Data Exchange (SPDX) has become an international standard (ISO/IEC 5962:2021).  SPDX has been used in the kernel and other projects to identify the licenses and attach other metadata to  software components.

Between eighty and ninety percent (80%-90%) of a modern application is assembled from open source software components. An SBOM [software bill of materials] accounts for the software components contained in an application — open source, proprietary, or third-party — and details their provenance, license, and security attributes. SBOMs are used as a part of a foundational practice to track and trace components across software supply chains. SBOMs also help to proactively identify software issues and risks and establish a starting point for their remediation.

SPDX results from ten years of collaboration from representatives across industries, including the leading Software Composition Analysis (SCA) vendors – making it the most robust, mature, and adopted SBOM standard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The folio pull-request pushback]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868598/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868598/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T14:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we last caught up with the page folio patch set, it appeared to be on
track to be pulled into the mainline during the 5.15 merge window.  Matthew
Wilcox duly sent a pull
request in August to make that happen.  While it is possible that
folios could still end up in 5.15, that has not happened as of this writing
and appears increasingly unlikely.  What we got instead was a lengthy
discussion on the merits of the folio approach.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868863/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868863/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T14:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr, ghostscript, ntfs-3g, and postorius), Fedora (java-1.8.0-openjdk-aarch32, libtpms, and salt), openSUSE (libaom, libtpms, and openssl-1_0_0), Red Hat (openstack-neutron), SUSE (grilo, java-1_7_0-openjdk, libaom, libtpms, mariadb, openssl-1_0_0, openssl-1_1, and php74-pear), and Ubuntu (firefox and ghostscript).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: September kicks off event season]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470920</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-september-kicks-off-event-season/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T11:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of some of the embedded news we've seen this week, covering products, funding, events and people news.
The post embedded news week: September kicks off event season appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고통 불평등 시대: 권력 밀착형 발표 저널리즘과 인권]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81904</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/b63NWqZ1Ncw/81904"/>
        <updated>2021-09-10T05:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[감염병 위기 속에 재택근무를 할 수 있고, 이동을 스스로 통제하면서도, 소득에 지장이 없으며, 감염 위험으로부터도 보호될 수 있는 기득권 엘리트 계층과 재택근무 자체가 불가능한 필수 노동자, 고용 불안정에 신음하는 비정규직, 폐업이 걱정인 영세 자영업자 간에 ‘고통 불평등’이 뚜렷해 보인다. 최근 연구들에서도 제시되었지만, 장애인, 이주민, 홈리스, 빈곤층 노인과 아동, 시설 수용자, 난민, 성소수자 등 오랜 기간 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving full MCU partition isolation: Interrupts, debugging and hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470917</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/achieving-full-mcu-partition-isolation-interrupts-debugging-and-hardware/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T19:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving full microcontroller (MCU) partition isolation is essential for achieving high security for MCU-based systems. This article wraps up a series on this complex topic...
The post Achieving full MCU partition isolation: Interrupts, debugging and hardware appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[증권사 추천, 제2 테슬라 후보에 오른 유망 주식 7개 기업을 알아보자]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583450</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583450/%ec%a0%9c2-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%9c%a0%eb%a7%9d-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T19:31:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cro: Maintain it With Zig]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868781/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868781/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T19:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post by
Loris Cro makes the claim that the Zig
language  is
the solution to a lot of low-level programming problems:


	Freeing the art of systems programming from the grips of C/C++
	cruft is the only way to push for real change in our industry, but
	rewriting everything is not the answer. In the Zig project we’re
	making the C/C++ ecosystem more fun and productive. Today we have a
	compiler, a linker and a build system, and soon we’ll also have a
	package manager, making Zig a complete toolchain that can fetch
	dependencies and build C/C++/Zig projects from any target, for any
	target.


(LWN looked at Zig last year).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[룰루레몬 실적 분석과 월가의 룰루레몬 주가 전망(21년 9월 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583445</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583445/%eb%a3%b0%eb%a3%a8%eb%a0%88%eb%aa%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a3%b0%eb%a3%a8%eb%a0%88%eb%aa%ac-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T17:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arcane, complex vulnerability disclosure programs hinder security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470966</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/arcane-complex-vulnerability-disclosure-programs-hinder-security/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T16:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most product vulnerabilities are now discovered not by the affected vendor, but by outside sources like third-party researchers, and they’re all over the map. Vulnerabilities...
The post Arcane, complex vulnerability disclosure programs hinder security appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ann R. Thryft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 criteria for selecting a code coverage tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470900</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/10-criteria-for-selecting-a-code-coverage-tool/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T15:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code coverage is mandatory for safety-critical software development for good reason, but it is also a good method for anyone who wants to improve their...
The post 10 criteria for selecting a code coverage tool appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Klaus Lambertz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Green Hills Software delivers RTOS for military M-code GPS ASIC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470890</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/green-hills-software-delivers-rtos-for-military-m-code-gps-asic/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T15:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[M-code makes GPS signals resistant to spoofing, but GPS end user equipment needs to be able to receive it, hence the project to develop a next generation ASIC with safe and secure RTOS.
The post Green Hills Software delivers RTOS for military M-code GPS ASIC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기대 이상 2분기 룰루레몬 실적과  팬데믹 이후 수요 급증으로 룰루레몬 주가 상승하다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583435</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583435/21%eb%85%84-2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%a3%b0%eb%a3%a8%eb%a0%88%eb%aa%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T14:41:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Extended attributes for special files]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868505/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868505/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T14:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux extended-attribute mechanism allows the attachment of metadata to
files within a filesystem.  It tends to be little used — at least, in the
absence of a security module like SELinux.  There is interest in how these
attributes work, though, as evidenced by the discussions that have
followed the posting of revisions of this
patch by Vivek Goyal, which seeks to make a seemingly small change to
the rules regarding extended attributes and special files.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source Initiative's new executive director]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868744/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868744/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T14:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Open Source Initiative has announced the
appointment of Stefano Maffulli as its executive director.
"'Bringing Stefano Maffulli on board as OSI’s first Executive
Director is the culmination of a years-long march toward
professionalization, so that OSI can be a stronger and more responsive
advocate for open source,' says Joshua Simmons, Board Chair of OSI."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868743/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868743/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T14:03:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (lynx, matrix-synapse, and proftpd), openSUSE (ntfs-3g_ntfsprogs), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (RHV-H), Scientific Linux (kernel), and Ubuntu (libapache2-mod-auth-mellon, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.11, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.11, linux-gcp, linux-hwe-5.11, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.11, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, and linux-azure-5.8, linux-oem-5.10).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Blast off with IoT in space]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8944</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-blast-off-with-iot-in-space/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T13:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we kick off the show discussing several smart devices that might provide a modicum of security or comfort in case of weather disasters associated with climate change. After that, we start the long goodbye to 3G and discuss how companies are reacting. And for those who are keeping track of algorithmic accountability efforts, […]
The post Podcast: Blast off with IoT in space appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QuickLogic has new automatic eFPGA creation tool]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470887</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/quicklogic-has-new-automatic-efpga-creation-tool/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T10:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the OpenFPGA IP generator, Australis tool enables users to generate customized IP for any foundry or process node within days.
The post QuickLogic has new automatic eFPGA creation tool appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[탈감정 혹은 내 마음과 거리 두기: 설기문 박사 인터뷰]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81882</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/7OSj8hAVgxM/81882"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T09:25:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘무한도전’ 시절 노홍철 씨가 최면에 걸쳐 흘린 폭풍 눈물을 기억하는가? 노홍철 씨의 최면을 진행했던 심리학자 설기문 박사가 새 책을 냈다. 그 책에서 설 박사는 사회적 거리 두기만큼이나 자기 객관화를 통한 ‘내 마음과의 거리 두기’가 필요하다고 말한다. 그에게 부정적인 자기 감정에서 빠져나오는 방법, 탈감정 혹은 내 마음과 거리를 두고 자신을 객관화하는 방법과 노하우에 관해 물었다.   […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>좋은습관연구소</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 9, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868156/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868156/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-09T01:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 9, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Applying PEP 8]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868490/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868490/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T21:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two recent threads on the python-ideas mailing list have overlapped to a
certain extent; both referred to Python's style guide, but the discussion
indicates that the advice in it may have been stretched further than intended.   PEP 8
("Style Guide for Python Code") is the longstanding set of
guidelines and suggestions for code that is going into the standard
library, but the "rules" in the PEP have been applied in settings and tools well outside of that
realm.  There may be reasons to update the PEP—some unrelated work of that nature is
ongoing, in fact—but Pythonistas need to remember that the suggestions in
it are not carved in stone.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Toshiba Arm Cortex-M4 MCUs target high-speed data processing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470883</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-toshiba-arm-cortex-m4-mcus-target-high-speed-data-processing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T15:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toshiba has 20 new microcontroller devices available for high-speed data processing as part of the TXZ+ family M4G group products, suitable for applications like office equipment, audio/video equipment, IoT, home appliances, building automation and factory automation.
The post New Toshiba Arm Cortex-M4 MCUs target high-speed data processing appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868660/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868660/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T14:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.14.2, 5.13.15, and 5.10.63 have been released. As usual, there
are important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868659/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868659/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T14:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (haproxy), Fedora (libguestfs, ntfs-3g, ntfs-3g-system-compression, partclone, testdisk, vim, and wimlib), Mageia (kernel and kernel-linus), openSUSE (haproxy), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, and kpatch-patch), SUSE (haproxy), and Ubuntu (cpio, haproxy, libapache2-mod-auth-mellon, libgd2, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, openvswitch, python-pysaml2, and sssd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ship / Show / Ask: A modern branching strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/ship-show-ask.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/ship-show-ask.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've written a fair bit about how using pull requests can encourage a
      low integration frequency, increasing cycle time and discouraging
      refactoring. Rouan Wilsenach has had success using an approach that categorizes
      changes as Ship/Show/Ask - using this classification to decide whether and
      how to use pull requests.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart home devices to help prepare for climate change]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8939</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/smart-home-devices-to-help-prepare-for-climate-change/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This morning I awoke to pictures of flooding in the Northeast, tales from relatives about power outages in the South, and worries about wildfire smoke in my neck of the woods. It’s clear that we can’t stop climate change, and in all honesty, there’s little individuals can do to protect themselves. However, with some forethought […]
The post Smart home devices to help prepare for climate change appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존고 홀푸드 적용, 본격적인 아마존 오프라인 공략 시동의 시발점일까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583411</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583411/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4%ea%b3%a0-%ed%99%80%ed%91%b8%eb%93%9c-%ec%a0%81%ec%9a%a9"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T11:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Therapist Will See You Now. But Where?]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1519</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/virtual-therapy-distanced-intimacy/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T07:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For a century, when we’ve thought of therapy, many of us have thought of the places where it happens: the clinic, the ward, the institution. Most prominent among these spatial associations may be the so-called consulting room and its accoutrements: a box of tissues, a covert clock, chairs and perhaps a couch, the waiting room,... Read More
The post The Therapist Will See You Now. But Where? appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why California Burns: The Facts Behind the Flames]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1578</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/why-california-burns-the-facts-behind-the-flames/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T07:58:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“There is broad consensus in the scientific community that wildfire behavior is changing across the American West in general, and in California in particular. … All indicators shown—wildfire occurrence, total area burned, and average fire size—display an upward trend in the last several decades across the state.” The Costs of Wildfire in California, California Council... Read More
The post Why California Burns: The Facts Behind the Flames appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Case for ‘Developer Experience’]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1756</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-case-for-developer-experience/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T07:57:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a lot of buzz around APIs, “no code,” and “low code”: Developers can add new features more easily than ever before! While it’s true that this new wave of tools has helped developers build bigger systems, and build them faster, it turns out that developers are now spending their time worrying about an... Read More
The post The Case for ‘Developer Experience’ appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonal Chokshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Platform-Partnership Fit: A Guide to Business Development for Bio Startups]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1738</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/guide-to-business-development-for-bio-platform-startups/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T07:57:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As new biological technologies shift the way we make new medicines — from “bespoke craftsmanship to industrialized drug development” — we are seeing bio platforms truly deliver a dizzying array of novel discoveries, tools, and therapies, and across a variety of different business models. Before, virtually every company in biotech claimed to have a platform…... Read More
The post Platform-Partnership Fit: A Guide to Business Development for Bio Startups appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonal Chokshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s Time for Esports to Stop Idolizing Traditional Sports]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1524</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/esports-business-models/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T07:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, pundits and commenters debated whether esports qualified as “sports” at all; today, esports are leading sports entertainment into the digital age. Over the past decade, the monetization of esports has been heavily modeled after traditional sports leagues like the NBA, NFL, and NHL. Within the last few years, however, it has become increasingly... Read More
The post It’s Time for Esports to Stop Idolizing Traditional Sports appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월별 중국 수출 통계와 중국 무역수지 통계(21년 8월 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583402</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583402/%ec%a4%91%ea%b5%ad-%ec%88%98%ec%b6%9c-%ed%86%b5%ea%b3%84%ec%99%80-%ec%a4%91%ea%b5%ad-%eb%ac%b4%ec%97%ad%ec%88%98%ec%a7%80-%ed%86%b5%ea%b3%84"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T07:10:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘누구나집’과 중단된 ’10년 공공임대주택 사업’의 추억]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81873</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/4mDmU0op1O8/81873"/>
        <updated>2021-09-08T05:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 6일 국토부와 LH(한국토지주택공사), 인천도시공사는 ‘누구나집’(분양가 확정 분양전환형 공공지원 민간임대사업) 시범사업 택지공모를 8일부터 시행하겠다고 밝혔다. ‘누구나집’, 어떤 사업인가  정부나 집권 여당은 누구나집이 무주택자에게 저렴한 가격으로 내집 마련 기회를 제공할 수 있다고 밝혔다. 하지만 공기업이 강제수용한 택지를 민간업자에게 팔아서 진행되는 ‘누구나집’은 서민주거안정이 아닌 공기업과 민간업자의 이익추구 사업에 불과하다. 특히 문재인정부의 집값폭등으로 어느때보다 공공주택 확보가 절실한 상황에서 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10.0rc2 is available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/MNLSuW5j-cI/python-3100rc2-is-available.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/MNLSuW5j-cI/python-3100rc2-is-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T23:33:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10 is one month away, can you believe it? This snake is still trying to bite as it has been an interesting day of fighting fires, release blockers, and a bunch of late bugs but your friendly release team always delivers 
You can get this new release while is still fresh here:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3100rc2/
This release, 3.10.0rc2, is the last preview before the final release of Python 3.10.0 on 2021-10-04. Entering the release candidate phase, only reviewed code changes which are clear bug fixes are allowed between release candidates and the final release. There will be no ABI changes from this point forward in the 3.10 series and the goal is that there will be as few code changes as possible.
Call to action
     

The 3.10 branch is now accepting changes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 92.0 and Firefox ESR]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868603/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868603/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T20:29:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 92.0 has been released. In
this version Firefox can now automatically upgrade to HTTPS using HTTPS RR
as Alt-Svc headers, support full-range color levels for video playback on
many systems, and more.

Firefox
78.14.0 ESR and Firefox
91.1.0 have also been released.  ESR78 will reach end-of-life in
November.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] FOSS for amateur radio]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868309/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868309/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T19:07:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amateur ("ham") radio operators have been experimenting with ways to use
computers in their hobby since PCs became widely available—perhaps even
before then. While many
people picture hams either talking into a microphone or tapping a telegraph
key, many hams now type on a keyboard or even click buttons on a computer screen to make
contacts.  Even hams who still prefer to talk or use Morse code may still
use computers for some things, such as logging contacts or predicting
radio conditions. While most hams use Windows, there is no shortage of ham
radio software for Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868569/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868569/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T15:08:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by openSUSE (apache2, java-11-openjdk, libesmtp, nodejs10, ntfs-3g_ntfsprogs, openssl-1_1, xen, and xerces-c), Red Hat (kernel-rt and kpatch-patch), and SUSE (ntfs-3g_ntfsprogs and openssl-1_1).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSL 3.0.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868536/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868536/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T13:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 3.0 of the OpenSSL TLS library has been released; the large
version-number jump (from 1.1.1) reflects a new versioning scheme.


	Most applications that worked with OpenSSL 1.1.1 will still work
	unchanged and will simply need to be recompiled (although you may
	see numerous compilation warnings about using deprecated
	APIs). Some applications may need to make changes to compile and
	work correctly, and many applications will need to be changed to
	avoid the deprecations warnings. We have put together a migration 
	guide to describe the major differences in OpenSSL 3.0 compared to
	previous releases.


OpenSSL has also been relicensed to Apache 2.0, which should end the era of
"special exceptions" needed to use OpenSSL in GPL-licensed applications.
See this
blog entry and the changelog for
more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain 101: How distributed trusted data can boost the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8912</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/blockchain-101-how-distributed-trusted-data-can-boost-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T13:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past year or two, we’ve talked about blockchain in combination with the Internet of Things numerous times. But to really understand how the blockchain can help improve device security and the IoT experience, you first have to understand what the blockchain is. With that in mind, here’s a brief overview along with some examples, so […]
The post Blockchain 101: How distributed trusted data can boost the IoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 실업률 및 미국 고용지표 통계(21년 8월 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583391</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583391/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%8b%a4%ec%97%85%eb%a5%a0-%eb%b0%8f-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ea%b3%a0%ec%9a%a9%ec%a7%80%ed%91%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T12:37:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021년 유망 클라우드 컴퓨팅 스타트업 10선 (CRN 선정)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81858</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/YR9j7hA_kLQ/81858"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T05:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기술 전문 미디어인 CRN에서 2021년에 가장 핫한 클라우드컴퓨팅 분야 스타트업을 선정해서 소개했다.1) 모두 최근에 벤처 캐피털에서 투자를 받은 기업이고 인공지능 분야의 MLOps에서 하드웨어 개발자를 위한 사물인터넷 플랫폼 제공 기업, 클라우드 비용 관리 소프트웨어 기업 등 그 범주가 매우 다양하다. 이런 스타트업을 살펴봄으로써 국내에서도 새로운 혁신과 비즈니스 모델을 가진 클라우드컴퓨팅 스타트업이 나오기를 바라면서 CRN에서 선정한 기업에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Profiling newlib-nano's memcpy]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/memcpy-newlib-nano</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/memcpy-newlib-nano"/>
        <updated>2021-09-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article takes a look at one of the commonly used functions provided by the
Newlib C library: memcpy. We’ll examine the default nano implementation and
the performance implications, comparing it against the faster non-default
implementation.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10년 넘게 말 못 하던 환자, 뇌와 컴퓨터를 연결해 말하기에 성공하다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73322</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/09/06/brain-implant-lets-man-speak/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=brain-implant-lets-man-speak"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T22:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[말하는 능력을 잃어버린 사람들에게 희망을 주는 연구 결과가 발표됐습니다. 미국 캘리포니아대학 샌프란시스코 캠퍼스의 연구진은 사람의 뇌에 전극을 부착해 뇌 신호를 컴퓨터 화면에 표현하는 실험에 성공했다고 밝혔습니다. 연구진은 15년 전부터 말을 못 하게 된 참가자의 두뇌 활동을 컴퓨터에 기록해 이 남성이 말하려는 단어의 47%를 정확하게 식별할 수 있었습니다. 단어 자동 교정 기능과 비슷한 알고리듬을 활용하면 정확도가 76%까지 상승했습니다. 이번 연구에 자금을 지원한 페이스북은 모자나 옷과 같은 웨어러블 기기로 우리의 생각을 화면에 표현하는 최종 목표를 추구하고 있습니다. 과연 텔레파시의 꿈이 이뤄질까요? 월스트리트저널의 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio C#: what to do if project preparation takes too long or freezes?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0864/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/tCcQqQq56eE/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some users of the PVS-Studio C# analyzer faced a problem: the project preparing stage either took much time or even froze. This article covers how the problem manifested itself and how we fixed it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Visual Studio 2022 ate up 100 GB of memory and what XML bombs had to do with it]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0865/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/1nvZYQGOmv0/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April 2021 Microsoft announced a new version of its IDE – Visual Studio 2022 – while also announcing that the IDE would be 64-bit. We've been waiting for this for so long – no more 4 GB memory limitations! However, as it turned out, it's not all that simple...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing RTD temperature sensing systems: Wiring configurations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470864</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/optimizing-rtd-temperature-sensing-systems-wiring-configurations/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T20:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article on resistance temperature detector (RTD) sensing system optimization, we discuss the three RTD wiring configurations and how they impact accuracy. This...
The post Optimizing RTD temperature sensing systems: Wiring configurations appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jellenie Rodriguez and Mary McCarthy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reminder: linux.conf.au 2022 Call for Sessions open + Extended]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868500/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868500/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T19:24:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The linux.conf.au organizers have put out a second, extended call for
proposals for the 2022 event, which will be held online starting
January 14.


	Please submit a talk, join us in January. We have the "venue"
	sorted, sponsors organised, miniconfs chosen, keynotes ready, now
	all we need is a wonderful program of sessions for our community to
	listen and watch.


Proposals are due by September 12.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why smart home hubs are great… until they’re not]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8935</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-smart-home-hubs-are-great-until-theyre-not/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T16:02:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, David called in to our voicemail hotline with a question about smart home hubs. He has several in his home and has noticed that when he upgrades the hub, he often has to deal with some issues. These range from device integrations to previously configured automations. I know […]
The post Why smart home hubs are great… until they’re not appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] More IOPS with BIO caching]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868070/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868070/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T15:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once upon a time, block storage devices were slow, to the point that they
often limited the speed of the system as a whole.  A great deal of effort
went into carefully ordering requests to get the best performance out of
the storage device; achieving that goal was well worth expending some CPU
time.  But then storage devices got much faster and the equation changed.
Fancy I/O-scheduling mechanisms have fallen by the wayside and effort is now
focused on optimizing code so that the CPU can keep up with its storage.  A
block-layer change that was merged for the 5.15 kernel shows the kinds of
tradeoffs that must be made to get the best performance from current hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868464/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868464/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T14:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (btrbk, pywps, and squashfs-tools), Fedora (libguestfs, libss7, ntfs-3g, ntfs-3g-system-compression, partclone, testdisk, wimlib, and xen), Mageia (exiv2, golang, libspf2, and ruby-addressable), openSUSE (apache2, dovecot23, gstreamer-plugins-good, java-11-openjdk, libesmtp, mariadb, nodejs10, opera, python39, sssd, and xerces-c), and SUSE (apache2, java-11-openjdk, libesmtp, mariadb, nodejs10, python39, sssd, xen, and xerces-c).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are we there yet?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21277</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/are-we-there-yet/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T08:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to securing the Internet of Things “IoT”, the world cannot afford insanity, expecting different results from the same traditional ICT “cybersecurity”. No one can afford this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[구글 vs. 언론사 뉴스사용료 세계대전, 우리는?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81848</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/M0G9SSm4_24/81848"/>
        <updated>2021-09-06T05:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 국내외로 소셜미디어, 포털 등 디지털플랫폼 기업의 독점적 권리 남용이나 수수료율 인상으로 비판의 목소리가 높다. 구글 ‘인앱결제 강제 금지법’(일명 ‘구글 갑질방지법’) 논란이 사그라들기도 전에 구글, 페이스북, 인스타그램, 애플 등 글로벌 디지털플랫폼 뉴스 사용료 문제가 외국에서 쟁점이 되고 있다. 글로벌 디지털 플랫폼 기업이 그동안 전 세계에서 뉴스 서비스를 하면서 사용료나 저작권료를 제대로 지급하지 않은 문제가 드러난 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do you need the MISRA Compliance report and how to generate one in PVS-Studio?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0863/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/42resZeSa18/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are strongly interested in MISRA and would like to understand whether your project meets one of the MISRA association's standards, there is a solution. It's name is MISRA Compliance. PVS-Studio has recently learned how to generate the MISRA Compliance report. This article describes how you can use this feature. This can make somebody's life better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenWrt 21.02.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868406/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868406/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-05T20:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 21.02.0 of the OpenWrt router distribution is out.  "It
incorporates over 5800 commits since branching the previous OpenWrt 19.07
release and has been under development for about one and a half
year".  Significant changes include WPA3 support by default, TLS
support in opkg and in the LuCi interface, initial Distributed
Switch Architecture support, new hardware support, and more.  See the release
notes for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21년 7월 온라인쇼핑 동향, 성장세 지속 중 일부 델타변이 영향으로 증가세 둔화]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583387</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583387/21%eb%85%84-7%ec%9b%94-%ec%98%a8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8%ec%87%bc%ed%95%91-%eb%8f%99%ed%96%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-09-05T10:47:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[어느 중국 은행 강도와 은행원 이야기, 경력과 시스템의 중요성]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583375</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583375/%ec%96%b4%eb%8a%90-%ec%a4%91%ea%b5%ad-%ec%9d%80%ed%96%89-%ea%b0%95%eb%8f%84%ec%99%80-%ec%9d%80%ed%96%89%ec%9b%90-%ec%9d%b4%ec%95%bc%ea%b8%b0-%ea%b2%bd%eb%a0%a5%ea%b3%bc-%ec%8b%9c%ec%8a%a4%ed%85%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-09-05T08:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.7.12 and 3.6.15 security updates now available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/vI_S3Fb6-ks/python-3712-and-3615-security-updates.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/vI_S3Fb6-ks/python-3712-and-3615-security-updates.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-04T22:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.7.12 and 3.6.15,  the lastest security fix rollups for Python 3.7 and Python 3.6, are now available. You can find the release files, links to the changelogs, and more information here:
    https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3712/
    https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3615/
  

These releases are source code only; Windows and macOS binary installers are not provided for security fix releases.


Note that Python 3.9 is now the latest feature release series of Python 3. You should consider upgrading to 3.9 as soon as practical. Get the latest release of 3.9.x here.

Thanks to all of the many volunteers who help make Python Development and these releases possible!  Please consider supporting our efforts by volunteering yourself or through organization contributions to the Python Software Foundation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating some of the best indie games]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/NVhiXuG5O6w/celebrating-some-of-best-indie-games.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/NVhiXuG5O6w/celebrating-some-of-best-indie-games.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-04T15:35:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Patricia Correa, Director, Global Developer Marketing
  

     
In June this year we opened applications for our Indie Games Accelerator, a mentorship program to help top mobile game startups achieve their full potential, as well as for our Indie Games Festival, a competition open to small game studios who get the opportunity to win promotions and be featured on Google Play. These annual programs are part of our commitment to helping all developers thrive in the Google ecosystem. 
We received thousands of applications from developers across the world and we were truly amazed by the response. We’re impressed by the innovation and passion of the indie game community, and the unique and creative games they bring to players worldwide.  
Last month we announced the Festival finalists …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[맵의 미래는 게임의 현재를 따라간다 (번역)]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2641</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2021/09/04/mappings-future-looks-like-gamings/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-04T11:51:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지금 AR 게임에서 일어나고 있는 이 혁신들이, 상용 시장으로 넘어와 SaaS로 제공되고 일상에서도 쓰일 때가 되면, 아마 저는 할아버지가 되어있을지도 모릅니다. 요즘 애들이 뇌에 이식된 칩으로 세상의 지식을 너무 쉽게 접근하는 것에 대해 세상을 쉽게만 산다고 투덜거리는 그런 할아버지가요.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 3, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8933</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-3-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T17:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsara has confidentially filed for an IPO: This is big news for those of us who have been in the industry for a while. Samsara launched in 2015 as a connected sensor platform with an excellent pedigree. Its founders co-founded enterprise Wi-Fi company Meraki, and it has about 20,000 customers. Samsara’s history is a microcosm of the […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 3, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blending hardware and software for better audio]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470858</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/blending-hardware-and-software-for-better-audio/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T14:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing both hardware and software is essential to deliver quality sound systems but the complexity of state of the art audio systems makes implementation difficult....
The post Blending hardware and software for better audio appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Rathod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Not-so-anonymous virtual memory areas]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867818/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867818/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T14:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computing terminology can be counterintuitive at times, but even a
longtime participant in the industry may have to look twice at the notion
of named anonymous memory.  That, however, is just the concept that this
patch set posted by Suren Baghdasaryan proposes to add.  There are, it
seems, developers who find the idea useful enough to not only overcome the
initial cognitive dissonance that comes with it, but also to resurrect an
eight-year-old patch to get it into the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure coding skills are vital to address embedded software security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470848</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/secure-coding-skills-are-vital-to-address-embedded-software-security/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T14:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s not enough expertise out there in developing secure embedded software code for connected devices, but secure coding skills are essential in addressing software code vulnerabilities.
The post Secure coding skills are vital to address embedded software security appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868289/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868289/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T14:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5.14.1, 5.13.14, 5.10.62, 5.4.144, 4.19.206, 4.14.246, 4.9.282, and 4.4.283 stable kernels.  As usual, these updates
contain important fixes; users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868282/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868282/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T13:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (qemu), Fedora (condor, grilo, libopenmpt, opencryptoki, and php), openSUSE (xen), and SUSE (ffmpeg, file, php72, rubygem-addressable, and xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renesas teams with eProsima to port micro-ROS into RA MCUs for robotics]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470844</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/renesas-teams-with-eprosima-to-port-micro-ros-into-ra-mcus-for-robotics/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T09:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Renesas teams up with eProsima to port micro-ROS into the RA microcontrollers (MCUs), enabling easier development of professional robotics applications for IoT and industrial systems. 
The post Renesas teams with eProsima to port micro-ROS into RA MCUs for robotics appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘컴포저블 기업’이란 무엇인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81826</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/y_kyFNJHh2A/81826"/>
        <updated>2021-09-03T07:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘날의 기업이나 정부는 고객의 요구사항에 따라 제품과 서비스 방향을 신속하게 전환할 수 있어야 생존할 수 있다. 성공적인 비즈니스가 되려면, 세계의 지역과 산업에 상관없이 경쟁에 빠르게 대처하고 적응할 수 있으며, 핵심 역량을 활용하여 새로운 방식으로 자신을 확장할 수 있어야 한다. ‘컴포저블 기업’(Composable Enterprise: 구성 가능한 기업)이라는 키워드가 2021년 유행어처럼 번지고 있다. 클라우드, 개방형 API 및 데이터 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text broadcast of Cppcast 300: ABI stability]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0862/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/BymYkK6FpBc/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Episode 300 of CppCast with guest Marshall Clow recorded May 18th, 2021. In this episode, Rob Irving and Jason Turner are joined by Marshall Clow who talks about ABI stability. They also discuss Visual C++ and ASAN, Meeting C++ 2021 and the new RmlUI update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] 5.15 Merge window, part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867821/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867821/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T15:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of this writing, 3,440 non-merge changesets have been pulled into the
mainline repository for the 5.15 development cycle.  A mere 3,440 patches
may seem like a slow start, but those patches are densely populated with
significant new features.  Read on for a look at what the first part of the
5.15 merge window has brought.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuzzing 100+ open source projects with OSS-Fuzz - lessons learned (ADA Logics blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868165/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868165/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T14:48:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the ADA Logics blog, David Korczynski and Adam Korczynski write about their work integrating 115 open-source projects with Google's OSS-Fuzz project for doing continuous fuzz testing.    They describe the process of integrating a project into OSS-Fuzz, and discuss their findings, which include more than 2000 bugs (500+ security relevant), of which 1300+ have been fixed at this point:

Throughout the process we integrated projects written in C, C++, Python, Go and Rust and the types of bugs we found across the projects are a reflection of the language the project was written in. Typically, for managed languages the bugs are within the umbrella term of uncaught exceptions and denial of service bugs, whereas in native languages the bugs are mostly split between assert violations, NULL-dereferences, heap-out-of-bounds, stack-out-of-bounds, stack overflows, integer arithmetic, memory leaks, out-of-memory and timeout bugs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868155/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868155/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T13:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by openSUSE (ffmpeg and gstreamer-plugins-good), SUSE (apache2, apache2-mod_auth_mellon, ffmpeg, gstreamer-plugins-good, libesmtp, openexr, rubygem-puma, xen, and xerces-c), and Ubuntu (openssl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMake Part 4 – Windows 10 Host]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/?p=3635</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/09/cmake-part-4-windows-10-host/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T13:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous blog posts in this series (Part 1,  Part 2 and Part 3), I looked at using CMake on a Linux host to configure a build to cross compile to target hardware such as the STM32F4 Series. In this post, we’ll work with the GNU Arm Embedded Toolchain on a Windows 10 Host.
The first part of this blog discusses running the Windows hosted versions of CMake, GNU Arm Embedded Toolchain and GNU Make. An alternative approach, briefly discussed at [...] 

The post CMake Part 4 – Windows 10 Host appeared first on Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Bond</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Australia’s terrible, horrible, no good, very bad surveillance law]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8892</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-australias-terrible-horrible-no-good-very-bad-surveillance-law/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We start this week’s show with a look at a new surveillance law passed in Australia that seemingly obliterates a lot of protections about how law enforcement officials can access data and what they can do with it. We also talk about a survey conducted in the U.S. that shows how willing many Americans are to share their data […]
The post Podcast: Australia’s terrible, horrible, no good, very bad surveillance law appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연합뉴스, 과연 믿음을 회복할 수 있을까? (ft. 제평위)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81818</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/zrbhJQczgoU/81818"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T05:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난달 25일 포털의 뉴스제휴평가위(이하 ‘제평위’) 제재소위원회는 연합뉴스의 기사형 광고 전송 행위에 대하여 제재조치를 결정하는 회의를 열고 32일 동안 기사 노출 중단과 재평가 조치를 의결했다. 연합뉴스는 국가기간통신사로, 공적 책무를 가지고 있음에도 눈 앞의 이익을 취하기 위해 약 2,000여 건의 기사형 광고를 ‘기사’ 형태로 포털에 송고했고, 명백한 증거자료 앞에 제평위는 그들이 정한 규정대로 32일 노출중단과 재평가 결정을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 2, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867461/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867461/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T01:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 2, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[약자를 위한 언론은 없다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81814</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/H1GiH_AH90g/81814"/>
        <updated>2021-09-02T01:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2020년 새해 창궐한 코로나19가 벌써 1년 반이 지났다. 우리 정부와 언론은 하루도 빠지지 않고 신규 확진자와 사망자 현황을 상세히 알려주고 있고, 학생과 직장인뿐만 아니라 인터넷이 연결된 컴퓨터와 모바일을 가진 사람들은 기계를 중간에 두고 소통하는 일상에 익숙해졌다. 백신이 나오기도 전부터 포스트 코로나를 준비해야 한다고 주장하던 언론은 최근 ‘위드 코로나’(코로나19 완전한 종식을 기대하는 것보다 치명률을 낮추는 새로운 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Emacs discusses web-based development workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867956/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867956/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T22:41:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discussions on ways to  "modernize" the Emacs editor have come up in various guises over the past few
years.  Changes of that nature tend to be somewhat contentious in the Emacs
community, pitting the "old guard" that values the existing features (and
keybindings) against those who argue for changes to make Emacs more
approachable (and aesthetically pleasing) to newcomers.  Those discussions
tend toward mega-thread status, so it should be no surprise that a query
about possibly moving Emacs development to a "forge" (e.g. GitHub or GitLab) got
similar treatment.  As always in Emacs-land, there are multiple facets to
the discussion, including the desirability of moving away from an
email-based workflow, accommodating younger, forge-centric developers
without forcing existing developers into that model, and—naturally—licensing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Event: Let’s talk about RF Sensing]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8920</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/event-lets-talk-about-rf-sensing/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T20:04:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The internet of things needs more context. And to deliver that context, computers need more senses. This is why I’ve been really excited about the potential to use existing radios and new radios to give computers a better understanding of what’s going on without relying on cameras. Right now, Google is using radar to track […]
The post Event: Let’s talk about RF Sensing appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An easier way to move your App Engine apps to Cloud Run]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/S0pxH_mnWEM/an-easier-way-to-move-your-app-engine-to-cloud-run.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/S0pxH_mnWEM/an-easier-way-to-move-your-app-engine-to-cloud-run.html"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T17:00:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Wesley Chun (@wescpy), Developer Advocate, Google Cloud
 
 An easier yet still optional migration
  
In the previous episode of the Serverless Migration Station video series, developers learned how to containerize their App Engine code for Cloud Run using Docker. While Docker has gained popularity over the past decade, not everyone has containers integrated into their daily development workflow, and some prefer "containerless" solutions but know that containers can be beneficial. Well today's video is just for you, showing how you can still get your apps onto Cloud Run, even If you don't have much experience with Docker, containers, nor Dockerfiles. 
App Engine isn't going away as Google has expressed long-term support for legacy runtimes on the platform, so those who prefer sour…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing use of encryption poses network security risk]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470833</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/growing-use-of-encryption-poses-network-security-risk/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T16:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pervasive encryption may enhance network traffic security, but the use of encryption also exposes users to threats from malicious traffic.
The post Growing use of encryption poses network security risk appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/868015/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/868015/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T14:51:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (bind, GNOME, hivex, kernel, and sssd), Debian (gpac and squashfs-tools), Fedora (c-ares and openssl), openSUSE (dovecot23), Oracle (bind, hivex, kernel, and sssd), Red Hat (kernel), Scientific Linux (bind, hivex, kernel, libsndfile, libX11, and sssd), Slackware (ntfs), SUSE (dovecot23), and Ubuntu (ntfs-3g).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryo-CMOS IP enables qubit control chips at cryogenic temperatures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470828</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/cryo-cmos-ip-enables-qubit-control-chips-at-cryogenic-temperatures/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T10:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[sureCore is developing a CMOS IP library suitable for operation at extremely low temperatures required for quantum computing applications, enabling design of cryo-CMOS control chips co-located with qubits in a cryostat.
The post Cryo-CMOS IP enables qubit control chips at cryogenic temperatures appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino ESP32 support version 2.0.0 is out!]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1b4de762228e</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/arduino-esp32-support-version-2-0-0-is-out-1b4de762228e?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T10:16:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino is definitely one of the most popular embedded development frameworks, and this popularity is mostly due to its simplicity and huge…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Minatel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xilinx and Motovis offer complete automotive forward camera solution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470825</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/xilinx-and-motovis-offer-complete-automotive-forward-camera-solution/"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T09:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xilinx and Motovis collaborate to pair Zynq SoC with Motovis’ CNN IP for automotive vision, to provide a complete hardware and software solution for forward camera systems in vehicles.
The post Xilinx and Motovis offer complete automotive forward camera solution appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[수술실 CCTV 설치법 통과에 부쳐: 일부 후퇴에도 환자 인권 개선]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81807</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/ef7XnwFZkzY/81807"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T07:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[수술실에 CCTV를 의무적으로 설치하도록 하는 의료법 개정안이 지난 8월 31일 국회 본회의를 통과했다. 다수 국민의 의견을 반영한 의료법 개정을 환영하며 불법 의료, 중대 범죄 등으로부터 방치됐던 환자 인권을 보호하기 위한 실질적인 제도로 정착하길 기대한다. 수술실 CCTV 설치 의무화는 의료 현장에서 절대적 약자인 환자를 보호하기 위해 제기됐지만, 사생활 침해나 진료 위축을 이유로 의료계 등의 반대가 극명했던 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대법원까지 가서 3년 만에 받은 자료 (사진)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81802</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/_RzUCf6VoF8/81802"/>
        <updated>2021-09-01T06:18:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3년 넘게 기다려 받은 자료입니다. 결과가 나오고도 물질명 등을 지운다며 한 달은 더 기다리게 했습니다. 고등법원까지였으면 모두 가려졌을 텐데, 대법원까지 갔기에 겨우 공정명을 얻었습니다. 일일이 손으로 지운다고 애쓴 이도 딱합니다만… 무엇보다 노동자의 생명과 안전에 관한 정보를 모두 가리면 무엇으로 책임을 입증하여 산업재해로 인정받을 수 있을까요. *사진 설명: 대법원 판결과 중앙행심위 결정에 따라 고용노동부 경기지청 산재예방지도과가 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>반올림</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FSF copyright handling: A basis for distribution, licensing and enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867944/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867944/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T21:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Free Software Foundation (FSF) clarifies
the purpose of its copyright policies and examines the impact of
potential alternatives. 

For some GNU packages, the ones that are FSF-copyrighted, we ask contributors for two kinds of legal papers: copyright assignments, and employer copyright disclaimers. We drew up these policies working with lawyers in the 1980s, and they make possible our steady and continuing enforcement of the GNU General Public License (GPL).

These papers serve four different but related legal purposes, all of which help ensure that the GNU Project's goals of freedom for the community are met.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technical support: what it's for and how to avoid burnout?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0861/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/YOh7SD9IJ-M/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Not everyone enjoys working in support. Many people who work there experience burnout. So maybe companies shouldn't have any support at all? How do they benefit from it? Is there a way to prevent burnout while working in support? Let's try to find the answers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Cooperative package management for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867657/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867657/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T19:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A longstanding tug-of-war between system package managers and Python's own
installation mechanisms (primarily pip, but there are others) looks
on its way to being resolved—or at least regularized.  PEP 668
("Graceful cooperation between external and Python package
managers") has been created to provide ways for the two types of package installation
to
work together, rather than at cross-purposes at times.
Since many operating systems depend on Python tools, with package versions
that may differ from those of users' Python applications, making them play together
nicely should result in more stable systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iconic processor emerges in flexible form]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470877</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/iconic-processor-emerges-in-flexible-form/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T16:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6502 design is still supported by Western Design Center, which estimates licensees have shipped over 6 billion embedded 65xx processors, a total that grows...
The post Iconic processor emerges in flexible form appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to design a better pulse oximeter: Implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470802</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-design-a-better-pulse-oximeter-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T15:18:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is more important than ever to design medical devices that are more convenient to use and consume less power. This article discusses design and...
The post How to design a better pulse oximeter: Implementation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Finnerty</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Realtime preemption locking core merged]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867919/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867919/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T15:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.15 merge window is off to a fast start; stay tuned for our usual full
summary.  It is worth mentioning, though, that the realtime preemption
locking code has been pulled into the
mainline with little fanfare.  This 
work began in 2004 and has fundamentally
changed many parts of the core kernel.  With this pull, the sleepable locks
that make deterministic realtime response possible have finally joined all
of that other work (though the kernel must be built with the
REALTIME configuration option to use them).

Congratulations are due to all of the realtime developers who pushed this
project forward for nearly two decades.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867917/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867917/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T15:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (libsndfile and libX11), Debian (ledgersmb, libssh, and postgresql-9.6), Fedora (squashfs-tools), openSUSE (389-ds, nodejs12, php7, spectre-meltdown-checker, and thunderbird), Oracle (kernel, libsndfile, and libX11), Red Hat (bind, cloud-init, edk2, glibc, hivex, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, microcode_ctl, python3, and sssd), SUSE (bind, mysql-connector-java, nodejs12, sssd, and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (apr, squashfs-tools, thunderbird, and uwsgi).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Air quality is a great use case for interoperable smart homes]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8902</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/air-quality-is-a-great-use-case-for-interoperable-smart-homes/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T13:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This summer was a pretty weird one for the Pacific Northwest, where I live. Most summers it’s cool in the mornings and warm in the afternoons. People leave their windows open more than they use AC. But thanks to heatwaves and fire, HVAC systems are becoming more common and more necessary. As are air purifiers. […]
The post Air quality is a great use case for interoperable smart homes appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시빅 해커와 백신 예약 대란의 교훈]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81779</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/Wd9bvrik_Uo/81779"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T07:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[플랫폼으로서의 정부(GaaP: Government as a Platform)가 국가 디지털 전략의 주요 화두가 되고 있다. 본 칼럼에서는 GaaP의 배경과 개념을 소개한 1편에 이어 성공적인 GaaP을 위한 기본적인 “가이드”를 소개하고자 한다. 이 얘기를 이어가기 전에 최근 발생한 사건을 우선 주목해 보자. 우리나라는 코로나 판데믹 한가운데에서 디지털 경쟁력을 바탕으로 위기를 극복해 나아가며 전 세계의 주목을 받았다. 이런 성과를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in July and August]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/august-2021-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/august-2021-roundup"/>
        <updated>2021-08-31T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may have noticed there was no July roundup. We’ve been busy improving Memfault, building out our partnerships with Nordic Semiconductor and Laird, and enjoying the summer months. Thanks for understanding.
Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
July and August.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[센서스 결과와 선거구 재획정]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73298</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/08/30/censusredistricting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=censusredistricting"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T22:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[워싱턴포스트 멍키케이지 / Rowan McGarry-Williams, Noah Kim, Deanna Han, Sarah Sadhwani 원문보기   지난 12일, 미국 인구총조사국(U.S. Census Bureau)이 2020년 센서스 최종 결과를 발표했습니다. (이용자가 궁금한 데이터를 쉽게 찾아볼 수 있는, 해설이 포함된 버전은 9월 30일에 발표됩니다.) 이번 센서스는 코로나19 팬데믹 때문에 조사 과정에서 적잖은 차질을 빚었습니다. 트럼프 행정부가 막판에 조사 기한을 급히 바꾸거나 예산 지원을 끊었고, 불법 이민자를 조사에서 배제하려 하는 등 방해한 탓에 우여곡절을 겪은 끝에 예년보다 4개월 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.7 and 3.8.12 are now available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/FQQRx2G9O4s/python-397-and-3812-are-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/FQQRx2G9O4s/python-397-and-3812-are-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T22:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.7

Get it here: https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-397/

    
    
  


  


Python 3.9.7 is the newest major stable release of 
the Python programming language, and it contains many new features and 
optimizations. There’s been 187 commits since 3.9.6 which is a similar 
amount compared to 3.8 at the same stage of the release cycle. See the change log for details.

On macOS, we encourage you to use the universal2 binary installer variant whenever possible. The legacy 10.9+ Intel-only variant will not be provided for Python 3.10 and the universal2 variant will become the default download for 3.9.8. You may need to upgrade third-party components, like pip,
 to later versions. You may experience differences in behavior in IDLE 
and other Tk-based applic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some 5.14 development statistics]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867540/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867540/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T19:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.14 kernel was released on August 29
after a nine-week 
development period.  This cycle was not as active as its predecessor, which
set a record for the number of developers involved, but there was still a
lot going on and a number of long-awaited features were merged.  Now that
the release is out, the time has come for our 
traditional look at where the code in 5.14 came from and how it got there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s the perfect situation for a smart button in your home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8897</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/heres-the-perfect-situation-for-a-smart-button-in-your-home/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T17:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Brent called in with a question to make life a little easier in his smart home. He has a reading lamp in his bedroom that he can control with either a switch or a digital assistant. But he’s looking for a solution to quietly control it while he’s […]
The post Here’s the perfect situation for a smart button in your home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동영상 플랫폼 비메오 혁신 사례, 비메오 CEO 안잘리 수드가 말하는 비메오 전략]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583316</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583316/%eb%b9%84%eb%a9%94%ec%98%a4-%ed%98%81%ec%8b%a0-%ec%82%ac%eb%a1%80"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T16:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Startup packs 1000 RISC-V cores into AI accelerator chip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470874</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/startup-packs-1000-risc-v-cores-into-ai-accelerator-chip/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The startup’s energy-efficient chip targets M.2 accelerator sockets for speeding recommendation models in data centers. Coinciding with the Hot Chips conference, startup Esperanto emerged from...
The post Startup packs 1000 RISC-V cores into AI accelerator chip appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Ward-Foxton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867791/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867791/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T14:54:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (exiv2, grilo, gthumb, and redis), Fedora (krb5, nbdkit, and rubygem-addressable), Mageia (libass and opencontainers-runc), openSUSE (cacti, cacti-spine, go1.15, opera, qemu, and spectre-meltdown-checker), Red Hat (java-1.7.1-ibm, java-1.8.0-ibm, libsndfile, and libX11), SUSE (389-ds, qemu, and spectre-meltdown-checker), and Ubuntu (grilo).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How should governments hold AI accountable?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8841</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-should-governments-hold-ai-accountable/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T14:12:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Look, we all know that algorithms are biased. What matters is how they are biased. What data helped train the algorithm? Is that data representative? What weights and preferences did the data scientist ascribe to different features when designing the algorithm? As an end user, it’s often impossible to know. But when we blame the […]
The post How should governments hold AI accountable? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[constexpr vector and string in C++20 and One Big Limitation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/constexpr-vecstr-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/constexpr-vecstr-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[constexpr started small in C++11 but then, with each Standard revision, improved considerably. In C++20, we can say that there’s a culmination point as you can even use std::vector and std::string in constant expressions!
Let’s look at use cases, required features to make it work, and finally, one significant limitation that we might want to solve in the future.
Sidenote: is my code run at constexpr?
Before we dive into fun stuff with vectors, it would be good to set some background.
In short: even if your function is marked with constexpr, it doesn’t mean it will always be executed at compile-time.
constexpr function can be both executed at compile-time and runtime.
For example:
constexpr int sum(unsigned int n) {
    return (n*(n+1))/2;
}

int main(int argc, const char**argv) {    
    i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘강철부대’ 시즌2를 기다리며: 시즌1의 네 가지 아쉬움]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81754</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/0LJ8D71GOsA/81754"/>
        <updated>2021-08-30T03:33:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[강철부대]는 대한민국 최정예 특수부대 출신 예비역들이 팀을 이뤄 각 부대의 명예를 걸고 경쟁하는 ‘밀리터리 서바이벌 예능’으로 채널A와 SKY채널이 공동 제작해 2021년 3월 23일부터 6월 22일까지 매주 화요일마다 방영했습니다. [강철부대]는 제707대테러특수임무단(707), 군사경찰특임대(SDT), 육군특수전사령부(특전사), 해군특수전전단(UDT), 해군해난구조전대(SSU), 해병대특수수색대(해병대) 등 모두 6개 특수부대 출신 예비역들이 참여해 대한민국 최고 특수부대를 가려내는 콘셉트 프로그램입니다. 기존 군대식 예능과 달리 각 부대 출신 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내수용 감각(interoception): 행복감을 주는 숨겨진 감각]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73293</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/08/29/m-interoception/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-interoception"/>
        <updated>2021-08-29T22:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(가디언, David Robson) 원문 보기   편한 자세로 앉아 눈을 감고 심장이 뛰는 것을 느껴봅시다. 손으로 맥을 짚지 않고도 심장의 움직임이 느껴지나요? 아니면 아무것도 느껴지지 않나요? 이 간단한 테스트는 뇌가 내부 장기의 신호로부터 신체 상태를 파악하는 능력을 말하는 “내수용 감각(interoception)” 능력을 확인하는 테스트입니다. 내수용 감각은 시각, 청각, 미각, 촉각, 후각과 같은 “외향적” 감각에 비해 잘 알려지지 않지만, 한 사람의 기분에 매우 큰 영향을 미치는 감각입니다. 과학자들은 내수용 감각이 우리의 우울증이나 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.14 kernel has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867706/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867706/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-29T22:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released the 5.14 kernel.


	So I realize you must all still be busy with all the galas and
	fancy balls and all the other 30th anniversary events, but at some
	point you must be getting tired of the constant glitz, the
	fireworks, and the champagne. That ball gown or tailcoat isn't the
	most comfortable thing, either. The celebrations will go on for a
	few more weeks yet, but you all may just need a breather from them.

	And when that happens, I have just the thing for you - a new kernel
	release to test and enjoy.


Headline features in 5.14 include:
core scheduling (at last),
the burstable CFS bandwidth controller,
some initial infrastructure for BPF program
loaders,
the rq_qos
I/O priority policy,
some improvements to the
SO_REUSEPORT networking option,
the control-group "kill" button,
the memfd_secret() system call,
the quotactl_fd() system call,
and much more.  See the LWN merge-window summaries (part 1, part 2) for more details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in C# 9: overview]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0860/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/V_EtDcRfo8I/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although C# 9 came out over half a year ago, the community is still processing its immense list of changes and has yet to discover best practices for the new features. It's a great excuse to go over C# 9 features one more time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plugins in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/plugins-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/plugins-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-28T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Several years ago I started writing a <a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/tag/plugins">series of posts</a> on <em>plugins</em>: how they are
designed and implemented in various systems and programming languages. In this,
I'll extend the series by providing some examples of plugins in Go.</p>
<p>As a reminder, <a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2012/08/07/fundamental-concepts-of-plugin-infrastructures">the original post</a>
in this series identifies four fundamental …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[August 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/155ab81b311d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/august-2021-155ab81b311d?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-08-28T05:55:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for August 27, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8887</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-august-27-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T21:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Foghorn gets a big win with Saudi Arabia’s Aramco: Foghorn, a startup providing data processing and analytics at the edge for industrial IoT clients, has signed a deal with Aramco, the oil and gas giant. Aramco will use Foghorn’s software for analyzing camera input in its plants and on its rigs. Specifically, Aramco will use it […]
The post IoT news of the week for August 27, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Nftables reaches 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867185/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867185/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T14:49:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux kernel is a fast-moving project, but change can still be
surprisingly slow to come at times.  The nftables project to replace the kernel's
packet-filtering subsystem has its origins in 2008, but is still not being
used by most (or perhaps even many) production firewalls.  The transition
may be getting closer, though, as highlighted by the release of nftables 1.0.0 on
August 19.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867636/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867636/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T12:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (haproxy and libopenmpt), openSUSE (aws-cli, python-boto3, python-botocore,, dbus-1, and qemu), Oracle (rh-postgresql10-postgresql), Red Hat (compat-exiv2-023, compat-exiv2-026, exiv2, libsndfile, microcode_ctl, python27, rh-nodejs12-nodejs and rh-nodejs12-nodejs-nodemon, rh-nodejs14-nodejs and rh-nodejs14-nodejs-nodemon, and rh-python38), Scientific Linux (compat-exiv2-023 and compat-exiv2-026), SUSE (compat-openssl098), and Ubuntu (libssh, openssl, and openssl1.0).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[정부와 기업의 ‘집게손’ 삭제, 어처구니 없다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81750</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/LsWFlp2T2AY/81750"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T10:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 최근 집게손가락 표현을 ‘남성 혐오’라 우기는 억지 주장을 여과없이 수용해 유사 표현들을 자체검열하고 있는 대기업과 정부기관이 여성혐오에 동조하는 블랙리스팅을 중단할 것을 요구한다. 공적 가치를 생산하는 정부기관과, 그와 유사한 정도의 영향력을 갖고 있는 대기업은 공적 가치 생산과 사회적 자원 배분에 중요한 역할을 하므로 이들의 의견 표명은 사회 질서와 균형을 잡는 데에 큰 무게감을 가진다. 그렇기에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존 투자로 살펴보는 아마존 전망, 현재의 엄청난 투자는 아마존 성장을 가속시킬 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583294</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583294/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%99%80-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T08:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오프라인 유통의 반격이 시작되다. 생각보다 비관적인 아마존 전망을 제시한 짐 크레이머]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=583288</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/583288/%ec%a7%90-%ed%81%ac%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b4%eb%a8%b8-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T02:23:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some reasons to measure]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/why-benchmark/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/why-benchmark/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A question I get asked with some frequency is: why bother measuring X, why not build something instead? More bluntly, in a recent conversation with a newsletter author, his comment on some future measurement projects I wanted to do (in the same vein as other projects like keyboard vs. mouse, keyboard, terminal and end-to-end latency measurements) was, "so you just want to get to the top of Hacker News?"
The implication for the former is that measuring is less valuable than building and for the latter that measuring isn't valuable at all (perhaps other than for fame), but I don't see measuring as lesser let alone worthless. If anything, because measurement is, like writing, not generally valued, it's much easier to find high ROI measurement projects than high ROI building projects.
Let's st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Luu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text broadcast of CppCast 285: Clang Power Tools and C++ myths]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0859/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/95T8nbCMi24/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Episode 285 CppCast was recorded on February 3rd, 2020. Hosts Rob Irving and Jason Turner are joined by Victor Ciura. They first talk about different ways to filter a C++ container and a blog post on the Visual C++ blog from the Diablo 4 development team. They then talk to Victor about the Clang Power Tools plugin for Visual Studio which has recently been made free for both open source and commercial use. They also talk about C++ myths.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Not-a-GPU accelerator drivers cross the line]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867168/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867168/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T16:23:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a general rule, the kernel community is happy to merge working device
drivers without much concern for the availability of any associated
user-space code.  What happens in user space is beyond the kernel's concern
and unaffected by the kernel's license.  There is an exception, though, in
the form of drivers for graphical processors (GPUs), which cannot be merged
in the absence of a working, freely-licensed user-space component.  The
question of which drivers are subject to that rule has come up a few times
in recent years; that discussion has now come to a decision point with an
effort to block some
Habana Labs driver updates from entry into the 5.15 kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What I'm up to now]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/202107-what-doing-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/202107-what-doing-now.html"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A couple of months ago I announced that I was stepping back from
      speaking. A few people wondered whether I would still be writing. I did
      indicate in that article that I am, but I felt it may be worth saying a
      bit more about what I’m concentrating on these days.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which achieves better security: Ad hoc testing or certification?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470786</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/which-achieves-better-security-ad-hoc-testing-or-certification/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T13:59:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to security within embedded systems there are several approaches one can take. Which one is right for your project is a matter...
The post Which achieves better security: Ad hoc testing or certification? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Jakob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867495/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867495/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T13:58:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sasha Levin has announced the release of the 5.13.13, 5.10.61, 5.4.143, 4.19.205, 4.14.245, 4.9.281, and 4.4.282 stable kernels.  As usual, they
contain important fixes throughout the tree.  Users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/867492/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/867492/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T13:30:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (community-mysql, containerd, dotnet3.1, dotnet5.0, perl-Encode, and tor), Mageia (gpsd), openSUSE (cacti, cacti-spine, go1.16, jetty-minimal, libmspack, mariadb, openexr, and tor), SUSE (aspell, jetty-minimal, libesmtp, mariadb, and unrar), and Ubuntu (firefox and mongodb).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Is this robot an INTJ?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8884</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-is-this-robot-an-intj/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T13:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show starts off with old news that I forgot to tell y’all about last week: The Matter interoperability standard for the smart home is delayed until 2022. We talk about what that means and then turn to Google’s confusing fitness wearable strategy and the new Fitbit Charge 5 device. After that, we discuss […]
The post Podcast: Is this robot an INTJ? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT device security still neglected despite $1.5 trillion market by 2027]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470780</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/iot-device-security-still-neglected-despite-1-5-trillion-market-by-2027/"/>
        <updated>2021-08-26T11:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite huge growth projections, IoT device security is often neglected in the development process, says Sequitur Labs' CEO.
The post IoT device security still neglected despite $1.5 trillion market by 2027 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>