<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2021-06-14T20:07:33.108Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.10.2</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's fully homomorphic encryption package]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859688/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859688/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:34:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Developers Blog has this
announcement describing the release of a fully
homomorphic encryption project under the Apache license.
"With FHE, encrypted data can travel across the Internet to a server,
where it can be processed without being decrypted. Google’s transpiler will
enable developers to write code for any type of basic computation such as
simple string processing or math, and run it on encrypted data. The
transpiler will transform that code into a version that can run on
encrypted data. This then allows developers to create new programming
applications that don’t need unencrypted data."  See this
white paper for more details on how it all works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling telemetry for custom models in Intel DevCloud for the Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470131</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/enabling-telemetry-for-custom-models-in-intel-devcloud-for-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While edge computing has seen an exponential growth in the last few years, developers are experiencing issues in implementing AI and edge software solutions. Here’s...
The post Enabling telemetry for custom models in Intel DevCloud for the Edge appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daya Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our latest updates on Fully Homomorphic Encryption]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/9T13AYszQNQ/our-latest-updates-on-fully-homomorphic-encryption.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/9T13AYszQNQ/our-latest-updates-on-fully-homomorphic-encryption.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:00:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Miguel Guevara, Product Manager, Privacy and Data Protection Office.
   

 As developers, it’s our responsibility to help keep our users safe online and protect their data. This starts with building products that are secure by default, private by design, and put users in control. Everything we make at Google is underpinned by these principles, and we’re proud to be an industry leader  in developing, deploying, and scaling new privacy-preserving technologies that make it possible to learn valuable insights and create helpful experiences while protecting our users’ privacy.  
That’s why today, we are excited to announce that we’re open-sourcing a first-of-its-kind, general-purpose transpiler for Fully Homomorphic Encryption (FHE), which will enable developers to compute on encrypte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859669/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859669/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T15:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (apache, gitlab, inetutils, isync, kube-apiserver, nettle, polkit, python-urllib3, python-websockets, thunderbird, and wireshark-cli), Debian (squid3), Fedora (glibc, libxml2, mingw-openjpeg2, and openjpeg2), Mageia (djvulibre, docker-containerd, exif, gnuchess, irssi, jasper, kernel, kernel-linus, microcode, python-lxml, python-pygments, rust, slurm, and wpa_supplicant, hostapd), openSUSE (389-ds and pam_radius), Oracle (.NET Core 3.1, container-tools:3.0, container-tools:ol8, krb5, microcode_ctl, postgresql:12, postgresql:13, and runc), Red Hat (dhcp, postgresql, postgresql:10, postgresql:12, postgresql:9.6, rh-postgresql10-postgresql, rh-postgresql12-postgresql, and rh-postgresql13-postgresql), Scientific Linux (dhcp and microcode_ctl), SUSE (ardana-neutron, ardana-swift, cassandra, crowbar-openstack, grafana, kibana, openstack-dashboard, openstack-ironic, openstack-neutron, openstack-neutron-gbp, openstack-nova, python-Django1, python-py, python-pysaml2, python-xmlschema, rubygem-activerecord-session_store, venv-openstack-keystone, crowbar-openstack, grafana, kibana, monasca-installer, python-Django, python-py, rubygem-activerecord-session_store, freeradius-server, libjpeg-turbo, spice, and squid), and Ubuntu (rpcbind).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We now know what we don’t know about Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8465</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/we-now-know-what-we-dont-know-about-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are still a lot of unknowns with regard to the new Matter interoperability standard, but we have a much better sense of what we don’t know in the wake of a panel hosted this week by Silicon Labs. During the event, which I moderated (and was paid by Silicon Labs to both create and moderate), we heard from product […]
The post We now know what we don’t know about Matter appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[근래 두드러진 아마존, 월마트 등 유통업체 광고사업 강화 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581156</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581156/%ec%9c%a0%ed%86%b5%ec%97%85%ec%b2%b4-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0%ec%82%ac%ec%97%85-%ea%b0%95%ed%99%94"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[루시드 전기차가 거실같은 미래 컨셉의 루시드 전시장을 만든 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581141</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581141/%eb%a3%a8%ec%8b%9c%eb%93%9c-%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8%ec%9d%98-%eb%af%b8%eb%9e%98-%ec%bb%a8%ec%85%89-%eb%a3%a8%ec%8b%9c%eb%93%9c-%ec%a0%84%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TREs and the IoT – Enabling a Trusted Connected Future]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21182</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/tres-and-the-iot-enabling-a-trusted-connected-future/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T08:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Trusted Connectivity Alliance (TCA) and IoT Security Foundation share a common vision: to secure the IoT and drive sustained growth through trusted connectivity. In this article, Claus Dietze, Chair of the TCA Board, explains how Tamper Resistant Elements (TRE) can help the IoT achieve its potential.  The IoT landscape is notoriously under-secured. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘방송법 개정’ 공약, 잊으셨습니까!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80997</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/9HR_mzhYkHc/80997"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T02:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[물 건너가는 걸까? 오는 8월 KBS 이사회와 MBC 관리·감독기구인 방송문화진흥회, 9월 EBS 이사회, 12월 KBS 사장 선임이 예정돼 있다. 6월까지 방송법 개정이 이뤄져야만 새 법에 따라 공영방송 이사와 사장 선임이 가능하다는데 벌써 6월 중순이다. 올해 들어 많은 사람들이 공영방송 지배구조를 바꾸기 위한 방송법 개정을 적극 주장해왔고, 최근 그 목소리가 더 커지고 있다. 6월 7일부터 언론·시민사회단체들이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.13-rc6]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859536/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859536/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T23:27:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.13-rc6 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Nothing particularly special to say about this - rc6 is
certainly smaller than rc5 was, so we're moving in the right
direction".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1분기 츄이 실적으로 살펴본 팬데믹 이후 츄이 비즈니스 전망과 츄이 주가 향방?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581127</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581127/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%b8%84%ec%9d%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%ec%b8%84%ec%9d%b4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T09:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국제자본주의인터내셔널은 테크자이언트를 길들일 수 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=81895</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Economic_View/~3/zv4ZLxelFEI/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T07:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[G7 국가들이 이번 주 콘월의 정상회담에서 서명할 협정은 두 가지 부문으로 나뉜다. 첫째, 여러 나라에서 영업하는 다국적 기업들은 그들이 어디에서 상품을 팔거나 서비스를 제공하든 더 많은 세금을 내야 할 것이다. 지금까지는 특정 국가에서 어떤 기업이 수십억 달러를 벌지라도 그들은 그곳에서 매우 적은 세금만을 내곤 했다. 이것은 그들이 더 낮은 세율로 더 많은 이윤을 취하는 곳에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[올 여름 SPAC 상장이 지고 전통 IPO 시장 활성화는  성장주 상승으로 이어질까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581123</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581123/%ec%97%ac%eb%a6%84-ipo-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-13T03:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why it’s time for 2FA on all smart home devices]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8471</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-its-time-for-2fa-on-all-smart-home-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Thomas called in to the voicemail hotline with a question. Technically, it was more of a plea, but it’s an important one. So we decided to help amplify Thomas’s concern with the lack of 2FA, or two-factor authentication, on smart home devices. In Thomas’s case, it’s the Flo by […]
The post Why it’s time for 2FA on all smart home devices appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국 차량공유 플랫폼 디디추싱 상장, 디디추싱 실적과 향후 전망을 보자]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581103</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581103/%eb%94%94%eb%94%94%ec%b6%94%ec%8b%b1-%ec%83%81%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T16:43:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개발자 교육에 대한 생각]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=10430</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2021/06/12/think-about-education/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T12:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[반대 “개발자 100 만명 양성” 나는 단순 개발자를 양성하는 이런 정책에 명백히 반대한다.단순 개발자란, 시장의 목소리에 귀기울이지 않고 단순 기술 교육만 하는 걸 말한다.솔직히 말하면, 개발자라는 이름으로 벌어지는 많은 무개념들을 반대한다. 이런 일에 데였기도 하지만,더 큰 이유가 있다. 선순환 나는 개발자가 돈을 많이 벌어야 한다고 생각한다.그건 높은 월급을 의미하는 게 아니다.높은 부가가치를 만들 수 있어야 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[트렌드 차트] 세계 게임 시장 규모 추이 및 게임 시장 전망( ~ 23년)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581073</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581073/%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84-%ea%b2%8c%ec%9e%84-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5-%ea%b7%9c%eb%aa%a8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T06:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[플랫폼 노동자의 ‘노동자성 제거 시도’에 대한 투쟁]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=81872</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Economic_View/~3/cwavrhCJEYc/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T03:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자본가는 노동일을 될수록 연장해서 가능하다면 1노동일을 2노동일로 만들려고 할 때, 그는 구매자로서의 자기의 권리를 주장하는 것이다. 다른 한편, 판매된 이 상품의 특수한 성질은 구매자에 의한 이 상품의 소비에 일정한 한계가 있음을 암시하고 있는데, 노동자가 노동일을 일정한 표준적인 길이로 제한하려고 할 때 그는 판매자로서의 자기의 권리를 주장하는 것이다. 따라서 여기에는 하나의 이율배반이 일어나고 있다. 즉, 쌍방이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 세계 최대 기업 아마존이 현실화 될 듯, JP모건 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581058</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581058/2022%eb%85%84-%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84-%ec%b5%9c%eb%8c%80-%ea%b8%b0%ec%97%85-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4%ec%9d%b4-%ed%98%84%ec%8b%a4%ed%99%94-%eb%90%a0-%eb%93%af-jp%eb%aa%a8%ea%b1%b4-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T03:28:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[게임업계 넷플릭스가 되려는 마이크로소프트 게임 스트리밍 야망이 현실화되고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581047</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581047/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%9c%ec%86%8c%ed%94%84%ed%8a%b8-%ea%b2%8c%ec%9e%84-%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%a6%ac%eb%b0%8d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-12T01:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Code humor and inclusiveness]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857765/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857765/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T22:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Free-software development is meant to be fun, at least some of the time.
Even developers of database-management systems seem to think that it is
fun; there is no accounting for taste, it seems.  Part of having fun is
certainly allowing the occasional exercise of one's sense of humor while
working on the code.  But, as some recent "fix" attempts show, humor does
not always carry through to developers all over the planet.  Balancing
humor and inclusiveness is always going to be a challenge for our community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privacy analysis of FLoC (Mozilla blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859246/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859246/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T22:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Mozilla blog, Eric Rescorla looks
into some of the privacy implications of the Federated Learning of Cohorts
(FLoC), which is a Google effort to replace
third-party cookies with a different type of identifier that is less
trackable. But less tracking does not equal no tracking. "People's
interests aren't constant and neither are their FLoC IDs. Currently, FLoC
IDs seem to be recomputed every week or so. This means that if a tracker is
able to use other information to link up user visits over time, they can
use the combination of FLoC IDs in week 1, week 2, etc. to distinguish
individual users. This is a particular concern because it works even with
modern anti-tracking mechanisms such as Firefox's Total
Cookie Protection 
(TCP). TCP is intended to prevent trackers from correlating visits across
sites but not multiple visits to one site. FLoC restores cross-site
tracking even if users have TCP enabled."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poettering: The Wondrous World of Discoverable GPT Disk Images]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859240/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859240/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T22:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a lengthy
blog post, Lennart Poettering describes the advantages of using the
unique IDs (UUIDs) and flags from the discoverable partitions
specification to label the entries in a GUID Partition
Table (GPT).  That information can be used to tag disk images if a
self-descriptive way, so that external configuration files (such as
/etc/fstab) are not needed to assemble the filesystems for the
running system.  Systemd can use this information in a variety of ways,
including for running the image in a container: "If a disk image
follows the Discoverable Partition Specification then systemd-nspawn has
all it needs to just boot it up. Specifically, if you have a GPT disk image
in a file foobar.raw and you want to boot it up in a container, just run
systemd-nspawn -i foobar.raw -b, and that's it (you can specify a block
device like /dev/sdb too if you like). It becomes easy and natural to
prepare disk images that can be booted either on a physical machine, inside
a virtual machine manager or inside such a container manager: the necessary
meta-information is included in the image, easily accessible before
actually looking into its file systems."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for June 11, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8463</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-june-11-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T16:03:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bosch opened a fully connected chip-making plant: Bosch, an industrial giant that also makes specialty sensors and chips for automotive and industrial use cases, has opened a new 300 millimeter chip-making plant in Dresden, Germany. Bosch made a big deal of it being a 300 mm wafer plant, which means the chips are made on top of […]
The post IoT news of the week for June 11, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859192/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859192/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T14:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libwebp), Fedora (firefox, lasso, mod_auth_openidc, nginx, redis, and squid), Oracle (.NET 5.0, container-tools:2.0, dhcp, gupnp, hivex, kernel, krb5, libwebp, nginx:1.16, postgresql:10, and postgresql:9.6), SUSE (containerd, docker, runc, csync2, and salt), and Ubuntu (libimage-exiftool-perl, libwebp, and rpcbind).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전기차 판매 증가, 전기차 소음과 안전 이슈가 부각되다, 전기차 시대의 법과 제도의 정비]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581044</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581044/%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4-%ec%a6%9d%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T11:32:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[클릭 저널리즘 vs. 진짜 저널리즘]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80976</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/eY8D8-K0CzQ/80976"/>
        <updated>2021-06-11T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 프랑스의 프리랜서 기자, 소피 유스타쉬(Sophie Eustache)의 최근 저서, [기사 베끼기, 어떻게 돈이 저널리즘을 파괴하는가] (원제: Batonner, comment l’argent detruit le journalisme)라는 책을 접했다. 유스타쉬는 이 책에서 언론이 ‘덜’ 벌기 위해 ‘더’ 많은 기사를 쓰고 있다고 주장한다. 언론의 ‘우라까이’(베껴 쓰기), 즉 타 언론사의 기사 일부를 대충 바꾸거나 조합해 마치 새로운 기사처럼 표절하는 행위는 우리만의 문제는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NCAA에서 뛰는 ‘아마추어’ 대학생 스포츠 선수들의 처우가 달린 대법원 판결]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72875</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/10/ncaavalston/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=ncaavalston"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국에서 미식축구 선수들은 NFL에 프로 선수로 등록하려면 최소 3년을 대학교에서 아마추어 선수로 뛰어야 합니다. 선수들은 대학교 팀에서 뛰는 동안 아마추어 규정에 따라 급여를 받을 수 없습니다. 선수들은 대신에 제대로 된 교육이라도 받을 수 있도록 지원해달라며 NCAA를 상대로 소송을 냈고, 대법원이 곧 이에 대한 최종 판결을 내립니다. NPR 플래닛 머니에서 다룬 방송을 요약했습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Implementing eBPF for Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857215/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857215/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Extended BPF (eBPF), the general-purpose
execution 
engine inside of the Linux kernel, has proved helpful for tracing and
monitoring the system, for processing network packets, or generally for
extending the behavior of the kernel. So helpful, in fact, that developers
working on other operating systems have been watching it. Dave Thaler and
Poorna Gaddehosur, on behalf of Microsoft, recently
published an implementation of eBPF for Windows. A Linux feature making
its way to Windows, in itself, deserves attention. Even more so when that
feature has brought new degrees of programmability to the Linux kernel over
the last few years. This makes it especially interesting to look at what the
new project can do, and to ponder how the current ecosystem might evolve as
eBPF begins its journey toward Windows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Privilege escalation with polkit: How to get root on Linux with a seven-year-old bug (GitHub blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859064/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859064/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T22:01:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the GitHub blog, Kevin Backhouse writes
about a privilege escalation vulnerability in polkit, which
"enables an unprivileged local user to get a root shell on the
system"  CVE-2021-3560
"is triggered by starting a dbus-send command but killing it while
polkit is still in the middle of processing the request. [...] Why does
killing the dbus-send command cause an authentication bypass? The
vulnerability is in step four of the sequence of events listed above. What
happens if polkit asks dbus-daemon for the UID of connection :1.96, but
connection :1.96 no longer exists? dbus-daemon handles that situation
correctly and returns an error. But it turns out that polkit does not
handle that error correctly. In fact, polkit mishandles the error in a
particularly unfortunate way: rather than rejecting the request, it treats
the request as though it came from a process with UID 0. In other words, it
immediately authorizes the request because it thinks the request has come
from a root process."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why You Should Check Values of Public Methods' Parameters]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0835/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/f_zuV3CiWSc/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This note will answer the question - why PVS-Studio considers parameters of public methods potential sources of tainted data. The analyzer can issue warnings if such parameters haven't been checked before use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[온라인쇼핑에 맞선 오프라인 매장 생존 방법 4가지 by BCG]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581030</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581030/%ec%98%a4%ed%94%84%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8-%eb%a7%a4%ec%9e%a5-%ec%83%9d%ec%a1%b4-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T18:29:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Josue Gutierrez]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/TQ33k_62590/iamagde-josue-gutierrez.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/TQ33k_62590/iamagde-josue-gutierrez.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T17:05:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alicja Heisig  
#IamaGDE series presents: Google Maps 
The Google Developers Experts program is a global network of highly experienced technology experts, influencers, and thought leaders who actively support developers, companies, and tech communities by speaking at events and publishing content. 
Meet Josue Gutierrez — Maps, Web, Identity and Angular Google Developer Expert. 
Josue currently works at the German company Boehringer Ingelheim and lives near Frankfurt. Before moving to Germany, Josue was working as a software engineer in Mexico, and before that, he spent almost a year in San Francisco as a senior front-end developer at Sutter Health.
 
Josue Gutierrez
 Josue studied computer science and engineering as an undergraduate and learned algorithms and programming. His fir…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another batch of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859020/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859020/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T16:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.12.10, 5.10.43, 5.4.125, 4.19.194, 4.14.236, 4.9.272, and 4.4.272 stable kernels have been released.  As
usual, they contain fixes all over the kernel tree and users of those
series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859008/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859008/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (htmldoc, lasso, and rails), Fedora (exiv2, firefox, and microcode_ctl), openSUSE (python-HyperKitty), Oracle (389-ds-base, qemu-kvm, qt5-qtimageformats, and samba), Red Hat (container-tools:3.0, container-tools:rhel8, postgresql:12, and postgresql:13), Scientific Linux (389-ds-base, hivex, libwebp, qemu-kvm, qt5-qtimageformats, samba, and thunderbird), SUSE (caribou, djvulibre, firefox, gstreamer-plugins-bad, kernel, libopenmpt, libxml2, python-Pillow, qemu, spice, spice-gtk, and ucode-intel), and Ubuntu (rpcbind).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silicon Labs SoCs add Wirepas for IoT asset tracking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470120</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/silicon-labs-socs-add-wirepas-for-iot-asset-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T14:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Silicon Labs and Wirepas partnership provides hardware-software solution for large-scale IoT mesh networks for asset tracking and building automation.
The post Silicon Labs SoCs add Wirepas for IoT asset tracking appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: HomeKit and Home Assistant embrace Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8453</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-homekit-and-home-assistant-embrace-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We start this week’s show with a quick update on Amazon’s Sidewalk and then focused on the smart home news from Apple’s WWDC event earlier this week. We’re excited about third-party devices getting Siri support. We then cover the EU’s thoughts on anticompetitive behavior by IoT device companies, as well as the launch of a […]
The post Podcast: HomeKit and Home Assistant embrace Matter appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWDC 2021에서 공개된 애플 개인정보보호 정책 3가지, 디지탈 광고 업계에 악몽이 될듯]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581012</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581012/wwdc-2021-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ea%b0%9c%ec%9d%b8%ec%a0%95%eb%b3%b4%eb%b3%b4%ed%98%b8-%ec%a0%95%ec%b1%85"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T12:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제4회 페미니즘 연극제: 다른 곳, 누군가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80962</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/JDOuCmHypxc/80962"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T04:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제4회 페미니즘 연극제가 7월 1일부터 8월 1일까지 연극실험실 혜화동 1번지에서 열립니다. 연극제는 총 7편의 공연과 2개의 부대 프로그램을 마련했습니다. 듣지 못한 이야기들 ‘연극계에 돋아난 페미니즘의 싹을 쑥쑥 키우기 위해’ 2018년 첫 발을 내디딘 페미니즘 연극제가 올해로 4회를 맞았습니다. 대학로 한 가운데서 페미니즘을 외친 제1회 연극제, 서로를 위한 연대의 손길을 내민 제2회 연극제, 페미니스트로서의 삶을 이야기한 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[REST Servers in Go: Part 7 - GraphQL]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-7-graphql/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-7-graphql/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T02:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is the seventh post in a series about writing REST servers in Go. Here is
a list of posts in the series:</p>
<ul class="simple">
<li><a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-1-standard-library/">Part 1 - standard library</a></li>
<li><a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-2-using-a-router-package/">Part 2 - using a router package</a></li>
<li><a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-3-using-a-web-framework/">Part 3 - using a web framework</a></li>
<li><a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-4-using-openapi-and-swagger/">Part 4 - using OpenAPI and Swagger</a></li>
<li><a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-5-middleware/">Part 5 - middleware</a></li>
<li><a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rest-servers-in-go-part-6-authentication/">Part 6 …</a></li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[애플 광고 사업은 미래 애플 전략 핵심이 될지도 모른다 by Evans]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581007</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581007/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0-%ec%82%ac%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T00:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 10, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858155/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858155/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-10T00:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 10, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 사람들은 자신을 피해자라 생각할까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72863</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/09/victimhood/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=victimhood"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T22:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(마크 맥나마라, Nautilus) 원문 보기 양극화된 세상에서 피해자 행세(victimhood)는 명예 훈장과 같습니다. 이를 통해 사람들은 권력을 얻습니다. “오늘날 미국 정치에서 피해자는 가장 중요한 정체성이 되었다.” UC샌디에고의 언론정보학 교수인 로버트 B.호르위츠의 말입니다. 호르위츠는 2018년 “피해자 행세의 정치, 정치에서의 피해자 행세”라는 제목의 연구결과를 발표했습니다. 그는 미국 정치에서 피해자 행세가 가장 중요해지도록 만든 사회적 흐름에 주목했으며, 그 기원이 “1960년대의 시민운동 등으로 인해 불안했던 정치상황”에 있다고 말했습니다. 그럼 심리학적으로는 피해자 행세가 어떤 의미가 있을까요? → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] When and how to evaluate Python annotations]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858576/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858576/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T16:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Annotations in Python came late to the party; they were introduced in
Python 3 as a way to attach information to functions describing their arguments and
return values.  While that mechanism had obvious applications for adding
type information to Python functions, standardized interpretations for the
annotations came later with type hints.
But evaluating the annotations at function-definition time caused some
difficulties, especially with respect to forward references to type names,
so a Python Enhancement Proposal (PEP) was created to postpone their
evaluation until they were needed. The PEP-described behavior was set to
become the default in the upcoming Python 3.10 release, but that is
not to be; the postponement of evaluation by default has itself been postponed in the
hopes of unwinding things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858832/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858832/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T15:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (eterm, mrxvt, and rxvt), Mageia (cgal, curl, exiv2, polkit, squid, thunderbird, and upx), openSUSE (firefox and libX11), Oracle (libwebp, nginx:1.18, and thunderbird), Red Hat (.NET 5.0, .NET Core 3.1, 389-ds-base, dhcp, gupnp, hivex, kernel, kernel-rt, libldb, libwebp, microcode_ctl, nettle, postgresql:10, postgresql:9.6, qemu-kvm, qt5-qtimageformats, rh-dotnet50-dotnet, and samba), SUSE (apache2-mod_auth_openidc, firefox, gstreamer-plugins-bad, kernel, libX11, pam_radius, qemu, runc, spice, and spice-gtk), and Ubuntu (intel-microcode and rpcbind).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino for ESP32-S2 and ESP32-C3 is coming!]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/f36d79967eb8</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/the-esp-journal/arduino-for-esp32-s2-and-esp32-c3-is-coming-f36d79967eb8?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T12:54:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial was created based on the Arduino for ESP32 version 2.0.0-alpha1 (preview version) on April 30th, 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Minatel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESP-IDF Development Tools Guide — Part I]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/89af441585b</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/the-esp-journal/esp-idf-development-tools-guide-part-i-89af441585b?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T12:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guide will introduce some tools that are not commonly used and could help you on specific tasks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pedro Minatel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LH 혁신, 그 핵심 과제는 무엇인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80952</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/YO_teD3ykew/80952"/>
        <updated>2021-06-09T04:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 월요일(6.7.) 정부가 ‘LH 혁신방안’을 발표했다. 그 주요 내용은 다음과 같다. 20% 이상 단계적 인력축소  재산등록 대상 전 직원 확대 고위직 취업제한 확대 등 통제장치 마련 공공택지 입지조사의 국토부 이관  내용은 많았지만, 택지개발·주택건설·주거복지 등 핵심 기능을 모두 존치하되 신도시 입지조사 업무를 국토부로 이관하는 등의 미봉책 나열에 그쳐 국민이 요구하는 해체수준의 쇄신안과는 거리가 멀다. LH 투기사태의 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rewriting the GNU Coreutils in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857599/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857599/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T21:48:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As movement toward memory-safe languages, and Rust in particular, continues to
grow, it is worth looking at
one of the larger scale efforts to port C code that has existed for decades
to Rust. The uutils project aims to
rewrite all of the individual utilities included in the GNU Coreutils project in
Rust. Originally created by Jordi
Boggiano in 2013, the project aims to provide drop-in
replacements for the Coreutils programs, adding
the data-race protection and memory safety that Rust provides.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unity Projects Analysis: The solution file has two projects named &quot;UnityEngine.UI&quot;]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0834/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/YEelnflJ17c/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While PVS-Studio analyses a Unity project, one may stumble upon such an error: Error was encountered while trying to open solution file '...': The solution file has two projects named "UnityEngine.UI". This note discusses the reasons for this error and how to eliminate it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WWDC 2021: What Apple’s HomeKit strategy means for the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8436</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/wwdc-2021-what-apples-homekit-strategy-means-for-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T17:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many others, I watched Apple’s WWDC 2021 keynote on Monday. Unlike most of those viewers though, I was impatient for any HomeKit news. It was worth the wait until late in the keynote to hear about HomeKit because Apple is pushing forward with the new Matter standard and opening up HomeKit in a big […]
The post WWDC 2021: What Apple’s HomeKit strategy means for the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858644/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858644/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T15:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (nginx), Fedora (musl), Mageia (dnsmasq, firefox, graphviz, libebml, libpano13, librsvg, libxml2, lz4, mpv, tar, and vlc), openSUSE (csync2, python-py, and snakeyaml), Oracle (qemu), Red Hat (container-tools:2.0, kernel, kpatch-patch, nettle, nginx:1.16, and rh-nginx116-nginx), Slackware (httpd and polkit), SUSE (389-ds, gstreamer-plugins-bad, shim, and snakeyaml), and Ubuntu (gnome-autoar and isc-dhcp).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How audio edge processors enable voice integration in IoT devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470102</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-audio-edge-processors-enable-voice-integration-in-iot-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T13:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dedicated audio edge processors with a focus on audio fidelity and with machine learning optimized cores are the key to providing IoT devices with voice user interfaces without the need for a high bandwidth internet connection.
The post How audio edge processors enable voice integration in IoT devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Choi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연도별 전기차 판매량 및 전기차 비중 추이( ~20년 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580982</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580982/%ec%97%b0%eb%8f%84%eb%b3%84-%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T12:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[클라우드 전문업체 탐방: 디딤365, 솔비텍]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80929</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/5PTG5jKPLf0/80929"/>
        <updated>2021-06-08T05:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[클라우드 전문업체 디딤365와 솔비텍을 찾아 이들 회사의 대표와 임원으로부터 디딤365와 솔비텍의 주요 서비스와 미래 비전을 들었다. 순서대로 정리해보자.       디딤365    “공공과 게임 분야에서 고객들의 인정을 받아온 걸 바탕으로 기술개발과 고객지원, 파트너들과의 상생에 더 무게를 두고 성장하는 기업을 만들고 있습니다. 2019년 매출 100억 원을 돌파했고, 올해 200억 원 매출도 넘길 만큼 클라우드 성장세는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역사가 말해주는 포스트 팬데믹 경제 호황의 교훈]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72868</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/07/what-history-tells-you-about-post-pandemic-booms/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-history-tells-you-about-post-pandemic-booms"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T22:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이코노미스트) 선진국을 중심으로 백신 보급률이 높아지면서 코로나바이러스 환자와 사망자가 줄어들고 있습니다. 일부 전문가들은 보복 소비와 보복 여행을 비롯한 포스트 팬데믹 경제 호황을 전망하기도 합니다. 과연 대유행 이후에는 어떤 경제가 펼쳐질까요? 미래를 예상하기 위해서는 과거의 역사를 살펴볼 필요가 있습니다. 대유행과 경제 호황의 역사적 사례를 분석한 이코노미스트의 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The runtime verification subsystem]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857862/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857862/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T19:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The realtime project has been the source of many of the
innovations that have found their way into the core kernel in the last
fifteen years or so.  There is more to it than that, though; the wider realtime
community is also doing 
interesting work in a number of areas that go beyond ensuring deterministic
response.  One example is Daniel Bristot de Oliveira's runtime
verification patch set, which can monitor the kernel to ensure that it
is behaving the way one thinks it should.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A more effective approach for developing AC-AC automatic voltage regulators]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470098</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/a-more-effective-approach-for-developing-ac-ac-automatic-voltage-regulators/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T17:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Development of AVRs has moved to digitally controlled systems built with 8-bit microcontrollers, but programmable mixed-signal ASICs offer advantages in reducing cost and size —...
The post A more effective approach for developing AC-AC automatic voltage regulators appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aamir Hussain Chughtai and Muhammad Saqib</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Starting your Google Career in IT | Kate Grant]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/sUinRPw0fNI/starting-your-google-career-in-it-kate-grant.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/sUinRPw0fNI/starting-your-google-career-in-it-kate-grant.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T17:00:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Max Saltonstall
 A little over 10 years ago, we launched the IT Residency Program (ITRP) at Google with a twofold mission: to provide exceptional tech support for Googlers and to empower the next generation of IT pioneers.  
ITRP’s founding principle is learning and development. In addition to formal on-the-job IT support training, the program takes its residents through a focused career development path, including a hands-on rotation in a specific Google function in their chosen specialty. For their part, the residents, who come from a wide spectrum of often non-traditional backgrounds, bring with them a passion for learning. ITRP converts that passion into real-world experience and equips them for a lifelong career in tech. 
Today, hundreds of Googlers are ITRP alums, working i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Q&A: How do you Select Thread Priorities to Improve Performance?]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=13799</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/06/07/qa-how-do-you-select-thread-priorities-to-improve-performance/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[7 June 2021 by Phillip JohnstonIntended Audience: People who are interested in adjusting thread priorities to improve their system’s performance and/or responsiveness. We’ve fielded multiple questions recently that follow this general pattern: The number of threads in my system are growing, and finding the best priority settings to optimize performance using trial and error is … 
Continue reading "Q&A: How do you Select Thread Priorities to Improve Performance?"
The post Q&A: How do you Select Thread Priorities to Improve Performance? appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858561/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858561/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T14:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libwebp, python-django, ruby-nokogiri, and thunderbird), Fedora (dhcp, polkit, transfig, and wireshark), openSUSE (chromium, inn, kernel, redis, and umoci), Oracle (pki-core:10.6), Red Hat (libwebp, nginx:1.18, rh-nginx118-nginx, and thunderbird), SUSE (gstreamer-plugins-bad), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-hwe-5.8, linux-kvm, linux-oracle).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Element Analytics is making middleware for the IIoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8430</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/element-analytics-is-making-middleware-for-the-iiot/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Getting data from the operations network to the IT network isn’t easy. The demands of each network are different. The protocols are different. The data formats are different. And for organizations, that means getting operational data into the formats and applications used by the business team can be a challenge. With digital transformation on every […]
The post Element Analytics is making middleware for the IIoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[포털 뉴스, 알고리즘와 저널리즘의 이분법을 넘어서]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80931</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/ce7MkIPihvw/80931"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T04:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 4월 29일 전국언론노동조합은 4·7 서울시장 보궐선거 기간 중 네이버를 통해 이용자가 가장 많이 본 선거 관련 뉴스를 분석하여 결과를 공개했다. 50만 회가 넘는 조회수 1위 기사는 중앙일보의 [中동포는 민주당 찍는다?···오세훈 발언에 거세진 투표권 논란]이었다. 자칫 중국동포에 대한 선입견을 심고 차별을 조장할 수 있는 기사를 이용자가 많이 보았다는 사실은 “많이 보는 기사가 좋은 기사”라는 포털 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.13-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858512/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858512/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T02:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.13-rc5 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Hmm. Things haven't really started to calm down very much yet, but rc5
seems to be fairly average in size. I'm hoping things will start
shrinking now."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to generate a Bode plot with LTspice]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470079</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-generate-a-bode-plot-with-ltspice/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-07T01:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the development of dynamic systems in electrical engineering, control engineering, and even mechatronics, engineers must know the system’s frequency response, represented by the Bode...
The post How to generate a Bode plot with LTspice appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Brand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Position-Independent Code with GCC for ARM Cortex-M]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=28612</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/06/05/position-independent-code-with-gcc-for-arm-cortex-m/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-05T18:31:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to ‘Alice in Wonderland‘! For a university research project using an ARM Cortex-M33 we are evaluating position-independent code as way to load applications or part of it with a bootloader. It sounds simple: just add -fPIC to the compiler … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Planning to reject Amazon Sidewalk? Do it for the right reasons]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8427</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/planning-to-reject-amazon-sidewalk-do-it-for-the-right-reasons/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T18:30:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow. This week, the media went after Amazon’s distributed IoT network with a vengeance. Both the mainstream news and the tech press came out in force to recommend that people opt out of Amazon’s Sidewalk Network before June 9th, when Amazon is due to turn it on. I, on the other hand, recommend that you […]
The post Planning to reject Amazon Sidewalk? Do it for the right reasons appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with Smart Home Notifications and Follow-up Responses]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/hz4XKC0_y3Q/getting-started-with-smart-home-notifications-and-follow-up-responses.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/hz4XKC0_y3Q/getting-started-with-smart-home-notifications-and-follow-up-responses.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Toni Klopfenstein, Developer Advocate 
 Alerts for important device events, such as a delivery person arriving or the back door failing to lock, create a more beneficial and reassuring experience for your smart home device users. 
As we announced at I/O, you can now add proactive notifications and follow-up responses to your Smart Home Action to alert users to events in a timely, relevant and helpful fashion and better engage with your end users.  
 
 Notifications can either alert a user to an event that has occurred without them proactively issuing a request through the Assistant, or as a follow-up to verify that the user's request has been fulfilled.  Each device event that triggers one of these notifications has a unique event id, which helps the Assistant route it to the app…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week forJune 4, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8425</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-forjune-4-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T16:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft buys ReFirm Labs for more secure firmware: Microsoft is continuing with its attempts to make enterprise and industrial IoT more integrated with IT security. After purchasing industrial security firm CyberX last year, it has now bought ReFirm, a company that scans and analyzes device firmware. Firmware controls how device hardware runs, and keeping it […]
The post IoT news of the week forJune 4, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fedora contemplates the driverless printing future]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857502/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857502/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T14:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in a distant time — longer ago than he cares to admit — your editor
managed a system-administration group.  At that time, most of the day-to-day
pain reliably came from two types of devices: modems and printers.  Modems
are more 
plentiful than ever now, but they have disappeared into interface
controllers and (usually) manage to behave themselves.  Printers, instead,
are still entirely capable of creating problems and forcing a
reconsideration of one's life choices.
Behind the scenes, though, the situation has been getting better but, as a
recent conversation within the Fedora project made clear, taking advantage
of those improvements will require some changes and a bit of a leap of faith.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CentOS Linux 8	(2105) released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858348/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858348/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T14:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a new release of CentOS Linux 8.  
"Effectively immediately, this is the current release for CentOS
Linux 8 and is tagged as 2105, derived from Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8.4
Source Code."  See the
release notes for the changes in this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858331/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858331/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T14:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (lasso), Fedora (mingw-djvulibre, mingw-exiv2, python-lxml, and singularity), openSUSE (ceph, dhcp, inn, nginx, opera, polkit, upx, and xstream), Oracle (firefox, perl, and polkit), Scientific Linux (firefox), SUSE (avahi, csync2, djvulibre, libwebp, polkit, python-py, slurm, slurm_18_08, thunderbird, and umoci), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-oem-5.10, and squid, squid3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is the AI of things (AIoT)?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470057</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/what-is-the-ai-of-things-aiot/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T12:27:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the growing trend for intelligent connected devices enabling the AI of things (AIoT), the technologies and some of the applications that benefit from AIoT.
The post What is the AI of things (AIoT)? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kavita Char</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A comparison of SRAM vs quantum-derived semiconductor PUFs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470053</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/a-comparison-of-sram-vs-quantum-derived-semiconductor-pufs/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T12:24:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores the relative performance of SRAM PUF and quantum-derived semiconductor PUF technologies for IoT security. 
The post A comparison of SRAM vs quantum-derived semiconductor PUFs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leonardo Machado</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why We Need Build Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/06/why-we-need-build-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/06/why-we-need-build-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T06:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Build systems were developed to simplify and automate running the compiler and linker and are an essential part of modern software development. This blog post is a precursor to future posts discussing our experiences refactoring the training projects to use the CMake build generator.</p>
<p>Using Build Systems</p>
<p>Build systems can be standalone command line applications such as  Make, Scons and Ninja; or part of an (Integrated Development Environment IDE) like Visual Studio , XCode or IAR Workbench.</p>
<p>Configuring build systems for a project [...] </p>
<div class="clearfix"></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/06/why-we-need-build-systems/">Why We Need Build Systems</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blog.feabhas.com">Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sticky Bits – Powered by Feabhas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민식이법 놀이 ‘홍보’하는 언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80908</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/wSndkhqvzU4/80908"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T05:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[6월 1일 정세균 전 국무총리가 자신의 사회관계망 서비스(SNS)에 도로교통법 및 특정범죄 가중처벌 등에 관한 법률 일명 ‘민식이법’을 언급했다. 총리 시절 보행자 보호를 강조했던 것과는 반대되는 내용으로, “스쿨존서 ‘민식이법 놀이’하는 아이들”(아시아투데이)이라는 기사를 인용하며 “스쿨존 내 어린이의 안전은 그 무엇보다 중요합니다. 그러나, 본래의 입법 취지와는 다른 문제들이 있다면 과감하게 뜯어고칠 필요도 있습니다”라고 말했다. 정세균 전 국무총리의 ‘민식이법’ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘이투스’ 클라우드 전환 사례: 문의선 CTO 인터뷰]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80915</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/uXKDOQ8JcMw/80915"/>
        <updated>2021-06-04T04:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 1년 동안 클라우드 전환을 직접 실행한 이투스교육 문의선 CTO와의 인터뷰를 정리했다. 전통적인 컴퓨팅 환경을 가진 기업이 클라우드 전환 과정 겪었던 경험을 공유함으로써 향후 국내 기업이 클라우드 전환을 고려할 때 어떤 문제를 준비하고 계획해야 하는 가를 검토하는 데 도움이 되고자 한다. 문의선 CTO는 서울대에서 컴퓨터공학을 전공하고 박사 학위를 받았으며, 두 번의 창업 경험이 있다. 이투스가 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빅데이타가 알려주는 팬데믹 이후 줌 주가 전망, 사용자 증가 둔화와 화상회의 급감]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580935</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580935/%ed%8c%ac%eb%8d%b0%eb%af%b9-%ec%9d%b4%ed%9b%84-%ec%a4%8c-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T23:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘코로나19 바이러스 우한 연구소 기원설’ 시간표 총정리]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72824</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/03/covid19originwivtimeline/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=covid19originwivtimeline"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T22:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 바이러스로 전 세계에서 300만 명 이상이 목숨을 잃었습니다. 그러나 바이러스의 기원은 여전히 정확히 알려지지 않았습니다. 중국 우한에 있는 바이러스 연구소에서 코로나19 바이러스가 처음 생겼다는 주장은 한동안 말도 안 되는 음모론으로 치부됐지만, 최근 조금씩 지지를 얻고 있습니다. 워싱턴포스트가 이 주장을 둘러싼 논쟁을 총정리했습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[트렌드 차트] 세계 펫푸드 시장규모 추이 및 중국 펫푸드 시장 성장 가능성]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580927</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580927/%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84-%ed%8e%ab%ed%91%b8%eb%93%9c-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5%ea%b7%9c%eb%aa%a8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T22:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio's New Website: How We Designed It]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0833/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/pD6kYfglUQ4/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PVS-Studio website turns 15 this year. This is quite significant for any internet resource. Back then, when our website was born, Russia announced 2006 as a year of humanities. That same year, in June, Denis Kryuchkov established a new platform, "Habrhabr" (now known as Habr). In November, Microsoft officially completed OS Windows Vista. That same month we registered the viva64.com domain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nanoleaf’s new lights are a Scandinavian design dream]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8409</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/nanoleafs-new-lights-are-a-scandinavian-design-dream/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T17:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I make no secret of my love for Nanoleaf light panels. Sure, they don’t solve a problem or add convenience like much of my smart home gear. They also aren’t cheap. And yet, I still want to cover my walls in them as tech-inspired wall decor. The company’s new Elements lights that are covered in […]
The post Nanoleaf’s new lights are a Scandinavian design dream appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning GDEs: Q1 2021 highlights, projects and achievements]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/h6H8xf-9WP8/machine-learning-gdes.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/h6H8xf-9WP8/machine-learning-gdes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T17:00:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by HyeJung Lee and MJ You, Google ML Ecosystem Community Managers. Reviewed by Soonson Kwon, Developer Relations Program Manager.
 Google Developers Experts is a community of passionate developers who love to share their knowledge with others. Many of them specialize in Machine Learning (ML). Despite many unexpected changes over the last months and reduced opportunities for various in person activities during the ongoing pandemic, their enthusiasm did not stop. 
Here are some highlights of the ML GDE’s hard work during the Q1 2021 which contributed to the global ML ecosystem. 
 ML GDE YouTube channel
 
 With the initiative and lead of US-based GDE Margaret Maynard-Reid, we launched the ML GDEs YouTube channel. It is a great way for GDEs to reach global audiences, collaborate as a co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assessing IoT and the impact of 5G]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470074</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/assessing-iot-and-the-impact-of-5g/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T15:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where are we with IoT? While billions of devices are already connected and enhancing many aspects of modern living, is the IoT fulfilling its true...
The post Assessing IoT and the impact of 5G appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Auditing io_uring]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858023/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858023/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T14:34:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The io_uring subsystem, first introduced in
2019, has quickly become the leading way to perform high-bandwidth,
asynchronous I/O.  It has drawn the attention of many developers, including,
more recently,
those who are focused more on security than performance.  Now some members
of the security 
community are lamenting a perceived lack of thought about security support in
io_uring, and are trying to remedy that shortcoming by adding audit and
Linux security module support there.  That process is proving difficult,
and has raised the prospect of an unpleasant fallback solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858145/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858145/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T13:22:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 5.12.9, 5.10.42, 5.4.124, 4.19.193, 4.14.235, 4.9.271, and 4.4.271 stable kernels.  As usual, these
contain fixes throughout the kernel tree; users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858144/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858144/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T13:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (chromium, curl, dhclient, dhcp, firefox, keycloak, lib32-curl, lib32-libcurl-compat, lib32-libcurl-gnutls, libcurl-compat, libcurl-gnutls, opera, packagekit, pam-u2f, postgresql, rabbitmq, redis, ruby-bundler, and zint), Debian (caribou, firefox-esr, imagemagick, and isc-dhcp), Fedora (mapserver, mingw-python-pillow, and python-pillow), openSUSE (chromium), Red Hat (firefox, glib2, pki-core:10.6, polkit, rh-ruby26-ruby, and rh-ruby27-ruby), SUSE (ceph, dhcp, libwebp, nginx, qemu, squid, and xstream), and Ubuntu (firefox, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-snapdragon, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, and policykit-1).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Stick with Sidewalk, y’all]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8406</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-stick-with-sidewalk-yall/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T13:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show is going to get controversial with a discussion of Amazon’s Sidewalk. Kevin is out on vacation this week, so my friend Chris Albrect of The Spoon is here to co-host.   We start with a rundown on why I think you should participate in Amazon’s Sidewalk network but also explain how to opt […]
The post Podcast: Stick with Sidewalk, y’all appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMBA ATP Engine 3.1: programmable traffic generation]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:71d34f36-09ae-4876-98b4-12ab3043937e</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/developer/ip-products/system/b/soc-design-blog/posts/amba-atp-engine-3-1-programmable-traffic-generation"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T12:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog, read about the AMBA ATP 3.1 release for programmable traffic generation.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adrian Herrera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategies for extending battery life]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470109</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/strategies-for-extending-battery-life/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T11:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Battery life is one of the core challenges in IoT. It relies on almost every specification of the device (hardware and firmware architecture, size, environment…)....
The post Strategies for extending battery life appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wilfried Dron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CALL FOR PAPERS LAUNCHED: IoTSF Virtual Conference 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21156</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/call-for-papers-launched-iotsf-virtual-conference-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T08:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IoT Security Foundation is delighted to announce the launch its 7th Annual IoT Security Conference. 2020 presented us with an opportunity to deliver a virtual IoTSF conference to an international audience of members and stakeholders, this was so well received that we will deliver the 2021 conference virtually to bring]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>-</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[젠더 갈등 부추기는 클릭 저널리즘]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80901</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/n4B5-lb7CJY/80901"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T05:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[온라인 커뮤니티 게시물을 검증이나 취재 없이 그대로 받아쓰는 언론 보도 행태가 계속되고 있다. 커뮤니티 게시물은 작성자의 신원을 전혀 알 수 없으며, 정확성도 검증되지 않은 이용자의 의견이다. 기자는 정보 검증과 게시자의 동의를 받는 등의 절차를 거쳐야 하지만 현 보도 행태는 전혀 그렇지 않다. 특히 여초, 남초로 나뉜 커뮤니티 인용 보도는 마치 성별의 의견을 대표하는 것처럼 언급되어 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 3, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857462/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857462/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-03T01:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 3, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글로벌 거인들이 눈독들이는 베트남 온라인쇼핑 성장 가능성과 기회]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580914</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580914/%eb%b2%a0%ed%8a%b8%eb%82%a8-%ec%98%a8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8%ec%87%bc%ed%95%91-%ec%84%b1%ec%9e%a5-%ea%b0%80%eb%8a%a5%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T23:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Growing pains for Fedora CoreOS]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857933/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857933/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When last we looked in on Fedora CoreOS back in December,
it was under consideration to become an official Fedora edition.  That has
not happened, yet at least, but it would seem that the CoreOS "emerging edition"
is still undergoing some difficulties trying to fit in with the rest of
Fedora.  There are differences between the needs of a container operating
system and those of more general-purpose distributions, which still need to
be worked out if Fedora CoreOS is going to "graduate".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code for C/C++ with ARM Cortex-M: Part 7 – FreeRTOS]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32665</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/06/02/visual-studio-code-for-c-c-with-arm-cortex-m-part-7-freertos/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a new article in my series about using Microsoft Visual Studio Code: After installation, project setup, building, debugging, setting up a kit and IntelliSense. This one is about setting using FreeRTOS: Outline FreeRTOS is probably the most used … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ?. Operator in foreach Will Not Protect From NullReferenceException]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0832/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/FwjQoDvDN1c/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you like the ?. operator? Well, who doesn't? Many people like these concise null checks. However, today's article shows that the ?. operator may be tricky sometimes. That is, it can create an illusion of safety when used in the foreach loop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you integrate a Wyze Home Monitoring System and Nest x Yale lock?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8388</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/can-you-integrate-a-wyze-home-monitoring-system-and-nest-x-yale-lock/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T18:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Noah called in to our voicemail hotline with a smart home integration question. Noah uses a Wyze Home Monitory System and a Nest x Yale lock in his smart home. He wants to disarm the Wyze alarm system when typing in the numeric code on the Nest x […]
The post Can you integrate a Wyze Home Monitoring System and Nest x Yale lock? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McQueen: Next steps for the GNOME Foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/858001/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/858001/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T17:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert McQueen takes
a look at the state of the GNOME Foundation.

[We’ve] got a larger staff team than GNOME has ever had before. We’ve widened the GNOME software ecosystem to include related apps and projects under the GNOME Circle banner, we’ve helped get GTK 4 out of the door, run a wider-reaching program in the Community Engagement Challenge, and consistently supported better infrastructure for both GNOME and the Linux app community in Flathub.

Aside from another grant from Endless (note: my employer), our fundraising hasn’t caught up with this pace of activities. As a result, the Board recently approved a budget for this financial year which will spend more funds from our reserves than we expect to raise in income. Due to our reserves policy, this is essentially the last time we can do this: over the next 6-12 months we need to either raise more money, or start spending less.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[게이밍과 암호화폐 덕분 급증한 1분기 엔비디아 실적과 긍정적인 엔비디아 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580900</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580900/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T16:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On the Diverse And Fantastical Shapes of Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2021-test-shapes.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2021-test-shapes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T15:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are arguments about whether a testing portfolio should be a
      pyramid or more like honeycomb. My second biggest issue with this argument
      is that it's rendered opaque by the fact that it's not clear what people
      see as the difference between unit and integration tests.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857978/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857978/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T15:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (squid), Fedora (dhcp), openSUSE (gstreamer, gstreamer-plugins-bad, gstreamer-plugins-base, gstreamer-plugins-good, gstreamer-plugins-ugly and slurm), Oracle (glib2 and kernel), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, perl, and tcpdump), Scientific Linux (glib2), SUSE (bind, dhcp, lz4, and shim), and Ubuntu (dnsmasq, lasso, and python-django).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Google’s Fuchsia OS and its role in IoT?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8400</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/what-is-googles-fuchsia-os-and-its-role-in-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T15:02:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Google Home Hub, now known as the Google Nest Hub, is getting a software update. You won’t see any difference after the update, but it’s still a big deal. Why? Because Google’s original smart display from 2018 will have a completely new operating system. After years of quiet development, Google’s Fuchsia OS has arrived. […]
The post What is Google’s Fuchsia OS and its role in IoT? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[openSUSE Leap 15.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857957/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857957/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T14:58:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSUSE
Leap 15.3 has been released.  "There is one huge change from the
previous Leap versions. openSUSE Leap 15.3 is built not just from SUSE
Linux Enterprise source code like in previous versions, but built with the
exact same binary packages, which strengthens the flow between Leap and SLE
like a yin yang."  There are a lot of new features as well, see the
announcement for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garrett: Producing a trustworthy x86-based Linux appliance]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857935/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857935/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T13:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matthew Garrett has written up the long,
complex series of steps required to build an x86 device that only boots
code that the creator wants to run there.  "At this point everything
in the boot process is cryptographically verified, and so should be
difficult to tamper with. Unfortunately this isn't really sufficient - on
x86 systems there's typically no verification of the integrity of the
secure boot database. An attacker with physical access to the system could
attach a programmer directly to the firmware flash and rewrite the secure
boot database to include keys they control. They could then replace the
boot image with one that they've signed, and the machine would happily boot
code that the attacker controlled. We need to be able to demonstrate that
the system booted using the correct secure boot keys, and the only way we
can do that is to use the TPM."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사용자 증가 둔화에도 폭발적인 이익 증가, 1분기 줌 실적 및 향후 줌 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580872</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580872/21%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%a4%8c-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T12:05:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efforts target multiple automotive cybersecurity threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470113</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/efforts-target-multiple-automotive-cybersecurity-threats/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T11:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The good news is that there is a growing number of automotive cybersecurity activities to secure in-vehicle hardware and software and cloud platforms. The automotive...
The post Efforts target multiple automotive cybersecurity threats appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Egil Juliussen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제조업, 클라우드 전환의 방법론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80887</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/7n3L5d6IieU/80887"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T05:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2020년 초 제조 산업은 이미 매우 어려운 전망에 직면했다. 세계 경기 침체와 생산의 현저한 감소로 인해 매출 성장과 수익성은 이미 둔화하고 있었고, 많은 기업이 광범위한 인력 감축과 해외 생산 거점을 줄이고 닫는 등 효율성 개선과 구조조정에 주력하고 있었다. 같은 맥락에서 디지털 전환이 강력하게 요구되었고, 클라우드의 도입과 전환은 그중 최우선순위가 되었다. 그 후 코로나19로 산업 가치 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[추천 영상] 강방천의 인플레이션 예측과 주식투자 성공법칙 4가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580864</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580864/%ea%b0%95%eb%b0%a9%ec%b2%9c%ec%9d%98-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%ec%84%b1%ea%b3%b5%eb%b2%95%ec%b9%99-4%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80"/>
        <updated>2021-06-02T00:16:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Making CPython faster]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857754/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857754/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T21:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last month or so, there has been a good bit of news
surrounding the idea of increasing the performance of the CPython
interpreter.  At the 2021
Python Language Summit in mid-May, Guido van Rossum announced
that he and a small team are being funded by Microsoft to work with the
community on getting performance improvements upstream into the
interpreter—crucially, without breaking the C API so that the ecosystem of
Python extensions (e.g. NumPy) continue to
work.  Another talk at 
the summit looked
at Cinder, which is a performance-oriented CPython fork that is used in
production at Instagram.  Cinder was recently released as open-source
software, as was another
project to speed up CPython that originated at Dropbox: Pyston.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Flip-Dot Clock using Used Bus Parts]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32701</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/06/01/flip-dot-clock-using-used-bus-parts/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T21:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I always have been fascinated by electromechanical stuff like these Flip-Dot Displays. I received my flip-dot 20×16 module as a donation by surprise from the UK (thanks James!). It seems that they are especially available in the UK (search on … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 영업이익은 적자일까? 탄소배출권과 비트코인으로 버티고 있다는 주장에 대해]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580855</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580855/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%98%81%ec%97%85%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5-%eb%b6%84%ec%84%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T16:30:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grow your indie game with help from Google Play]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/QC5D4BYQHRQ/grow-your-indie-game-with-help-from-google-play.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/QC5D4BYQHRQ/grow-your-indie-game-with-help-from-google-play.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Patricia Correa, Director, Global Developer Marketing
 
 At Google Play we’re committed to helping all developers thrive, whether these are large multinational companies or small startups and indie game studios. They are all critical to providing the services and experiences that people around the world look for on their Android devices. The indie game developer community, in particular, constantly pushes the boundaries with their creativity and passion, and bring unique and diverse content to players everywhere.  
To continue supporting indies, today we’re opening submissions for two of our annual developer programs - the Indie Games Accelerator and the Indie Games Festival. These programs are designed to help small games studios grow on Google Play, no matter what stage they ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 89]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857831/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857831/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T15:26:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 89 has been released. The
changes in this version focus on the look and feel. "We’ve redesigned
and modernized the core experience to be cleaner, more inviting, and easier
to use. " This release also includes enhancements to the privacy
offerings. "We’ve
enhanced the privacy of the Firefox Browser’s Private Browsing mode
with Total Cookie Protection, which confines cookies to the site where they
were created, preventing companies from using cookies to track your browsing across sites. This feature was originally launched in Firefox’s ETP Strict mode."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857830/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857830/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (cflow, chromium, eterm, gnutls, and kernel), Mageia (kernel and kernel-linus), Oracle (glib2), Red Hat (glib2, kernel, kernel-rt, and kpatch-patch), SUSE (curl, djvulibre, gstreamer, gstreamer-plugins-bad, gstreamer-plugins-base, gstreamer-plugins-good, gstreamer-plugins-ugly, nginx, python-httplib2, and slurm), and Ubuntu (gupnp, libwebp, postgresql-10, postgresql-12, postgresql-13, and python3.8).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC drops its copyright-assignment requirement]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857791/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857791/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T14:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GCC compiler, like other GNU projects, has long required contributors
to complete paperwork assigning the copyrights on their work to the Free
Software Foundation.  That requirement has just been dropped, and
contributors can now attach a Signed-off-by tag indicating use of the
Developers Certificate of
Origin instead.  "This change is consistent with
the practices of many other major Free Software projects, such as the
Linux kernel."  Initial discussion
suggests that some developers 
were surprised by this change and are yet to be convinced that it is a good
idea.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s talk about 6G, because it’s never too early for hype]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8397</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/lets-talk-about-6g-because-its-never-too-early-for-hype/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T13:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roughly every 10 years, we get a new cellular communication standard. In 2000, we got 3G. In 2010, we got 4G (LTE). And in 2019, we had 5G shoved down our collective throats (indeed, demand for the 5G transition has been nothing like the demand for the 4G transition). But already the industry is looking […]
The post Let’s talk about 6G, because it’s never too early for hype appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 새로운 스포츠 미래를 제안한 나이키 Play New 캠페인, 폭력아닌 자발적인 즐거움 회복]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580810</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580810/%eb%82%98%ec%9d%b4%ed%82%a4-play-new-%ec%ba%a0%ed%8e%98%ec%9d%b8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T12:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Powering smart buildings with Power over Ethernet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470117</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/powering-smart-buildings-with-power-over-ethernet/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T12:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The convenience of delivering power and data over the same cable is compelling, and just as USB has become a ubiquitous source of power for...
The post Powering smart buildings with Power over Ethernet appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Card</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[형이상학 혹은 철학의 실질적 효과]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222379444736</id>
        <link href="http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222379444736"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T11:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 살아야 하는가? 공자나 맹자, 나아가 순자가 이렇게 살라고 말해준다. 인간은 적어도 그러한 행위를 할 수 있는 자유 존재이다. 아마 그들은 이것을 구체적으로 거론할 수 없었지만, 전제하고 있었을 것이다. 그렇지 않다면 그들의 윤리적 명령, 충고, 권고가 성립되지 않았을 것이다. 자유론과 결정론의 문제는 중요한 철학적 문제이다. 그러나 나는 이 문제에 대해서 별로 관심이 없다. 따라서 이 문제를 다루고 있는 철학서적들이나 논문들을 자발적으로 거의 읽지 않는다. 그렇지만 이런 문제를 다루는 철학적 작업이 가치가 없거나 중요성이 없다고 말할 수 없을 것이다. 나아가 이 문제에 대한 철학적 사유들이 ‘어떻게 살아가야 하.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>내 마음의 풍경</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10.0b2 is available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/ZAtqT2lu_Es/python-3100b2-is-available.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/ZAtqT2lu_Es/python-3100b2-is-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T11:04:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After fighting with some release blockers, implementing a bunch of GC traversal functions, and fixing some pending reference leaks, we finally have Python 3.10.0 beta 2 ready for you! Thanks to everyone that helped to unblock the release!
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3100b2/
This is a beta preview of Python 3.10
Python 3.10 is still in development. 3.10.0b2 is the second of four planned beta release previews. Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their projects to support the new feature release.
We **strongly encourage** maintainers of third-party Python projects to **test with 3.10** during the beta phase and report issues found to [the Python bug tracker](https://bugs.python.org…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia business unit revenue, Test]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580819</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580819/nvidia-business-unit-revenue-test"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T09:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Size Matters – Using emCompress to Accelerate Firmware Updates via CAN Bus]]></title>
        <id>https://casestudies.segger.com/size-matters-using-emcompress-to-accelerate-firmware-updates-via-can-bus/</id>
        <link href="https://casestudies.segger.com/size-matters-using-emcompress-to-accelerate-firmware-updates-via-can-bus/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T07:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the increasing complexity of today’s embedded devices, customers may expect multiple firmware updates over the life of an embedded device. SEGGER’s compression software emCompress is an ideal solution for reducing the update time dramatically.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEGGER Microcontroller RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서울 구청장 25명, 부동산 재산은 얼마나 될까?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80875</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/dg5JNRQd6ew/80875"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T05:40:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[경실련이 2021년도 공개된 서울시 구청장 25명이 공개한 재산을 분석한 결과 올해도 부동산재산이 시세보다 낮게 축소신고 된 것으로 나타났다. 서울시 구청장 25명이 공개한 총 재산은 477억이며, 그중 부동산 재산은 429억으로 확인됐다. 특히 부동산재산은 20년 공개 때 358억보다 71억, 1인당 평균 2.8억 증가한 것으로 나타났다. 이도 신고가액 기준의 상승액으로 시세대로 신고했다면 더 많이 증가했을 것이다. 반면 같은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in May]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/may-2021-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/may-2021-roundup"/>
        <updated>2021-06-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
May.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아시아 유통기업 순위 및 아시아 온라인쇼핑 기업 순위 by 유로모니터]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580806</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580806/%ec%95%84%ec%8b%9c%ec%95%84-%ec%9c%a0%ed%86%b5%ea%b8%b0%ec%97%85-%ec%88%9c%ec%9c%84"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T23:18:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP, Vulnerabilities, and Taint Analysis in PVS-Studio for C#. Stir, but Don't Shake]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0831/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/Y_bMsfJgq0A/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We continue to develop PVS-Studio as a SAST solution. Thus, one of our major goals is expanding OWASP coverage. You might ask, what's the use when there's no taint analysis? That's exactly what we thought - and decided to implement taint analysis in the C# analyzer. Curious about what we accomplished? Read on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve Your Project Management Skills by Applying a Land Navigation Lesson]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=13657</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/05/31/improve-your-project-management-skills-by-applying-a-land-navigation-lesson/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[31 May 2021 by Phillip Johnston
The post Improve Your Project Management Skills by Applying a Land Navigation Lesson appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] eBPF seccomp() filters]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857228/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857228/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T15:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The seccomp()
mechanism allows a process to load a BPF program to restrict its future use
of system calls; it is a simple but flexible sandboxing mechanism that is
widely used.  Those filter programs, though, run on the "classic" BPF virtual
machine, rather than the extended BPF
(eBPF) machine used elsewhere in the 
kernel.  Moving seccomp() to eBPF has been an often-requested
change, but security concerns have prevented that from happening.  The
latest attempt to enable eBPF is this patch
set from YiFei Zhu; whether it will succeed where others have failed
remains to be seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857737/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857737/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T15:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (hyperkitty, libxml2, nginx, openjdk-11-jre-dcevm, rxvt-unicode, samba, and webkit2gtk), Fedora (exiv2, java-1.8.0-openjdk-aarch32, mingw-python-pillow, opendmarc, php-symfony3, php-symfony4, python-pillow, runc, rust-cranelift-codegen-shared, rust-cranelift-entity, and rxvt-unicode), openSUSE (curl, hivex, libu2f-host, libX11, libxls, singularity, and upx), Oracle (dotnet3.1 and dotnet5.0), Red Hat (docker, glib2, and runc), and Ubuntu (lz4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언어활동에 의해 짜여진 욕망의 주체인 그것 1]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222377531181</id>
        <link href="http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222377531181"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T12:08:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[라캉이 분석한 거울단계 이론은 진짜 맞는 이론인가? 내가 진짜 아기일 때, 나를 산산이 찢어지고 깨어진 존재로 간주했고 거울을 통해 통일적 존재로 인식했는가? 그 아기 시절을 기억할 수 있는가? 아기가 이런 경험을 한다는 것을 어떻게 입증할 수 있는가? 그러나 내가 읽은 라캉을 소개한 책들은 이런 의문을 보여주고 있지 않다. 거울 단계에 대한 라캉의 이야기를 자상하게 소개하고 설명해 주고 있다. 아기는 거울에 비친 영상을 자기로 간주한다. 자기와 동일화한다. <주체성의 동일성 작업>이 이런 방식으로 진행된다. ‘동일성’과 ‘정체성’은 동일한 단어의 번역이다. 그런데 정확하게 분석할 수 없지만, 두 개념에 차이가 있.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>내 마음의 풍경</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠버네티스를 품다: 클라우드 파운드리의 미래]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80863</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/M-pSWn76AGg/80863"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T04:33:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[클라우드 파운드리(Cloud Foundry, 이하 ‘CF’)는 멀티클라우드를 지원하는 오픈소스 기반의 PaaS(Platform as a Service)이다. 일반적인 클라우드서비스인 IaaS(Infra as a Service)에서는 필요한 만큼 컴퓨팅 자원과 인프라가 제공되지만, 애플리케이션을 포장하고 배포하는 것은 모두 고객(개발자)이 알아서 수행해야 한다. 참고로, PaaS는 애플리케이션 패키징, 배포, 실행을 모두 클라우드에서 ‘알아서’ 해주는 것을 말한다. IaaS가 초기 단계의 클라우드서비스를 대표한다면, PaaS는 다음 단계의 진화된 클라우드서비스로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build and use DLLs on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/05/31/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/05/31/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T02:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve recently been involved with a couple of discussions about Windows’
dynamic linking. One was Joe Nelson in considering how to make
libderp accessible on Windows, and the other was about w64devkit,
my Mingw-w64 distribution. I use these techniques so infrequently that I
need to figure it all out again each time I need it. Unfortunately there’s
a whole lot of outdated and incorrect information online which gets in the
way every time this happens. While it’s all fresh in my head, I will now
document what I know works.
In this article, all commands and examples are being run in the context of
w64devkit (1.7.0).
Mingw-w64
If all you care about is the GNU toolchain then DLLs are straightforward,
working mostly like shared objects on other platforms. To illustrate,
let’s build a “square” libr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.13-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857680/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857680/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T01:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth 5.13 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "So after two small rc releases, the other shoe finally
dropped, and rc4 is fairly sizable."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded design with FPGAs: Implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469955</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-design-with-fpgas-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-31T01:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The availability of more powerful FPGAs and more effective programming environments has made FPGA implementation broadly accessible but using FPGAs can seem daunting. Editor’s Note:...
The post Embedded design with FPGAs: Implementation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Ledin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vapor chamber cooling finds growing role in hot products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470035</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/vapor-chamber-cooling-finds-growing-role-in-hot-products/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-30T23:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing vapor chamber cooling technology could pay off for particular applications such as embedded systems with critical thermal management concerns.
The post Vapor chamber cooling finds growing role in hot products appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding Memory Bugs with Google Address Sanitizer (ASAN) on Microcontrollers]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=28077</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/31/finding-memory-bugs-with-google-address-sanitizer-asan-on-microcontrollers/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-30T22:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dangling pointers and memory corruption problems are nasty issues for any developer, and usually hard to find and locate in the code. Luckily Google has developed an open source tool to solve such issues: the Address Sanitizer (ASAN). The tool … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.13: SQL Injections, Blame Notifier, .NET 5]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0829/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/_aGqUw5Mj7s/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The newest PVS-Studio static analyzer version will please you with these features: tainted data analysis, .NET 5 support. The Blame Notifier utility can now sort warnings by commit date.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio Team: Switching to Clang Improved PVS-Studio C++ Analyzer's Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0830/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/0_q-4cDYQHc/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the earliest days, we used MSVC to compile the PVS-Studio C++ analyzer for Windows - then, in 2006, known as Viva64, version 1.00. With new releases, the analyzer's C++ core learned to work on Linux and macOS, and we modified the project's structure to support CMake. However, we kept using the MSVC compiler to build the analyzer's version for Windows. Then, in 2019, on April 29th, Visual Studio developers announced they had included the LLVM utilities and Clang compiler in the IDE. And just recently we've gotten around to try it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[View to the South]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32653</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/30/view-to-the-south/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-30T15:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fantastic view to the South today on a hike around the ‘Engelstock’: The snow covered Swiss Alps in the background with Ingenbohl-Brunnen and Lake Lucerne in the middle and Lake Lauerz on the right. If you want to see the … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미래의 전기차 경쟁에서 뒤처지는 우버와 리프트]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72818</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/05/28/how-uber-and-lyft-are-losing-the-race-to-the-electric-future/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-uber-and-lyft-are-losing-the-race-to-the-electric-future"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T22:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(블룸버그, Ben Elgin & Lizette Champman) 차량호출 업계의 글로벌 공룡 기업인 우버(Uber)와 리프트(Lyft)의 전기차 활용률은 매우 낮은 수준입니다. 미국의 평균 전기차 비율보다 더 낮습니다. 과연 두 기업이 공격적인 기후대응 목표를 달성할 수 있을까요? 그간의 노력과 평가, 향후 과제에 대해 분석한 블룸버그의 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux 8.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857614/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857614/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T20:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux 8.4, a clone of RHEL filling the role that CentOS used to
play, has been released.  Changes include full support for secure boot, a
developer repository with packages not found in RHEL, and more; see the release
notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for May 28, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8386</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-may-28-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T16:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is this an easier way to build digital twins? Digital twins are digital simulations of the physical world and a physical process. By applying real-world data to a virtual model people can understand how forces or stresses might affect an individual machine or building — or even see it writ large over the scale of an […]
The post IoT news of the week for May 28, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[May 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/92bd7d6767de</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/the-esp-journal/may-2021-92bd7d6767de?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T16:13:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Top-tier memory management]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857133/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857133/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T15:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern computing systems can feature multiple types of memory that differ in
their performance characteristics.  The most common example is NUMA
architectures, where memory attached to the local node is faster to access
than memory on other nodes.  Recently, persistent memory has
started appearing in deployed systems as well; this type of memory is
byte-addressable like DRAM, but it is available in larger sizes and is slower to
access, especially for 
writes. This new memory type makes memory allocation even more complicated
for the kernel, driving the need for a method to better manage multiple types of
memory in one system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.12.8, 5.10.41, and 5.4.123]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857582/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857582/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T15:05:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.12.8, 5.10.41, and 5.4.123 stable kernels have been released.
These contain only a small handful of changes, including fixes to the BPF
verifier to address a privilege
escalation vulnerability.  Users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857581/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857581/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T14:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (nginx), Fedora (chromium, curl, kernel, php-symfony3, php-symfony4, python-lxml, python-pip, and runc), Mageia (ceph and wireshark), openSUSE (mpv), Oracle (bind, idm:DL1, redis:6, slapi-nis, squid:4, and xorg-x11-server), SUSE (curl, nginx, postgresql10, postgresql12, postgresql13, slurm, slurm_18_08, and slurm_20_11), and Ubuntu (nginx).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The realities of developing embedded neural networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470029</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-realities-of-developing-embedded-neural-networks/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T14:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For most embedded software, freezing functionality is necessary to enable a rigorous verification methodology, but when embedding neural networks, that can be a major problem....
The post The realities of developing embedded neural networks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tony King-Smith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘주거 약자’는 없는 세계: 한국경제 ‘세금폭탄론’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80836</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/at1ukmrt674/80836"/>
        <updated>2021-05-28T04:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[6월 재산세 납부와 종합부동산세 과세기준일이 다가오자 ‘종부세 폭탄론’, ‘징벌적 세금’을 꺼내든 보도가 또다시 등장했습니다. 한국경제는 5월 10일부터 13일까지 “부동산 세금폭탄 째깍째깍”이라는 제목으로 관련 보도를 잇달아 냈는데요. 정부 부동산 세금 정책으로 많은 시민이 피해를 입게 될 것이라고 주장하는 내용입니다. 민주언론시민연합은 한국경제 보도처럼 정부 부동산 세금 정책으로 대다수 시민이 피해를 입게 되는지 사실관계를 확인했습니다. 팩트체크 1. 종합부동산세 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국가 주도 디지탈화폐 발행이 암호화폐 가격을 올리는 계기가 될까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580724</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580724/%eb%94%94%ec%a7%80%ed%83%88%ed%99%94%ed%8f%90-%eb%b0%9c%ed%96%89%ea%b3%bc-%ec%95%94%ed%98%b8%ed%99%94%ed%8f%90-%ea%b0%80%ea%b2%a9"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tech Camp introduces Georgia high schoolers to technology careers]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/zPjgACGLlkc/tech-camp-introduces-georgia-high.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/zPjgACGLlkc/tech-camp-introduces-georgia-high.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T23:05:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Posted by Erica Hanson, Senior Program Manager, Google Developer Student Clubs 
   
Tamta Kapanadze wishes that she had learned sooner about careers in technology. By the time that the Georgian citizen learned about them, she was already a university student. 
As Kapanadze continued her studies and her interest in technology grew, she wanted to spread the word about the growing field to high-school students in Georgia, a country where the industry is still small. 
To do this, Kapanadze called in the support of Google Developer Student Clubs (GDSCs), community groups for college and university students interested in Google's developer technology. After Kapanadze graduated from university, she continued her work by organizing a chapter of Google Developer Groups (GDGs) for Kutaisi.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the scenes: How the Google I/O photo booth was made]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/gs2QECafc3s/behind-scenes-how-google-io-photo-booth-was-made.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/gs2QECafc3s/behind-scenes-how-google-io-photo-booth-was-made.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T17:00:00.011Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by the Google Developers team
 A closer look at building a Flutter web app with Google Developer products
  
If you attended Google I/O this year, you probably stopped by the Google I/O photo booth for a selfie with our Google Developer mascots: Flutter’s Dash, Android Jetpack, Chrome’s Dino, and Firebase’s Sparky. If you didn’t, it’s not too late to jump in, take a selfie, and share it on social media! We loved seeing all of the pictures you posted and your favorite props! Want to learn more about building a camera plugin, layouts, and gestures used in a photo booth for Flutter on the web? 
 
 It took a combination of Google developer products to make the photo booth successful. The Flutter and Firebase teams joined forces to build a best in class example of Flutter on the web that used Firebase for hosting, auth, performance monitoring, and social sharing. Take a closer look at how the photo booth was built here and then grab the open source code on Github! 
 
Flutter team members having fun in the photo booth!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reports from the 2021 Python Language Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857490/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857490/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T15:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Python Software Foundation blog, the reports from day 1 of the Python Language Summit are available.  At the time of this writing, a few from day 2 are ready as well.  There are lots of interesting topics discussed at the summit, including a talk on making CPython faster from Python creator Guido van Rossum. "Seven months ago, Guido van Rossum left a brief retirement to work at Microsoft. He was given the freedom to pick a project and decided to work on making CPython faster. Microsoft will be funding a small team consisting of Guido van Rossum, Mark Shannon, Eric Snow, and possibly others. [...] The team is optimistic about doubling CPython's speed for 3.11. They plan to try an adaptive, specializing byte code interpreter, which is a bit like the existing inline cache and a bit like the shadow byte code covered in Dino Viehland's talk."  Some of the ideas go back to Shannon's thoughts on speeding up the interpreter that we looked at back in December.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] printk() indexing]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857148/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857148/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When kernel developers want to communicate something about the state of a
running kernel, they tend to use printk(); that results in a log
entry that is intended — with varying success — to be human-readable.  As it
happens, though, the
consumers of that information are often not human; the kernel's log output
is also read by automated monitoring systems that are looking for
problems.  The result is an impedance mismatch that often ends with the
monitoring system missing important messages.  The printk()
format indexing patch set is the latest of many attempts to improve
this situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lack of scrutiny sinks AV safety scores]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470041</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/lack-of-scrutiny-sinks-av-safety-scores/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do regulators — and the public — have reason to trust the safety and reliability of the AVs that are already on the public streets...
The post Lack of scrutiny sinks AV safety scores appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Junko Yoshida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857460/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857460/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (djvulibre), Fedora (slapi-nis and upx), Gentoo (ceph and nginx), openSUSE (python-httplib2 and rubygem-actionpack-5_1), Slackware (curl), SUSE (curl, libX11, and python-httplib2), and Ubuntu (isc-dhcp, lz4, and nginx).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Google’s Fuchsia looks promising for the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8378</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-googles-fuchsia-looks-promising-for-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T13:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that Roku aims to get into the smart home game? We discuss that along with a new set of vulnerabilities in Bluetooth during the first part of the show, before moving onto Google’s new Fuchsia OS and some updates from Google I/O. After that, we discuss surveillance technology from China and the […]
The post Podcast: Google’s Fuchsia looks promising for the IoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LTE Cat-M1 IoT module connects directly to global cellular networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470011</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/lte-cat-m1-iot-module-connects-directly-to-global-cellular-networks/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T09:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Renesas cellular IoT module uses Sequans hardware to support LTE Cat-M1 and enable direct connection to existing global mobile network infrastructure.
The post LTE Cat-M1 IoT module connects directly to global cellular networks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이스라엘-팔레스타인, ‘충돌’인가 ‘학살’인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80828</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/TffntJSU-MQ/80828"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T05:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2014년 7월 7일, 이스라엘과 팔레스타인 간 “50일 전쟁”이 있었다. 당시 팔레스타인 쪽에서는 2,143명의 사망자가, 이스라엘에서는 70명의 사망자가 나왔다. 특히 팔레스타인 사망자 중 약 1,460명이 민간인이고(이스라엘은 6명) 47만 명이 넘는 난민이 발생했다. 이 시기 우리나라에서는 이스라엘-팔레스타인 사이를 ‘전쟁’으로 보도하는 언론에 대한 비판(전쟁이 아니라 ‘사실상’ 일방적인 대학살이므로. -편집자)이 터져 나왔다. [KBS] 언론은 왜 ‘팔레스타인’을 외면할까? (2014.08.03) [PD 저널] […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 27, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856789/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856789/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-27T01:44:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 27, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국제 규범 무시한 벨라루스 독재 정권, 실질적으로 규제할 수 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72808</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/05/26/belarusryanair/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=belarusryanair"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기술의 발달로 독재 정권이 해외에 있는 반정부 인사를 체포하거나 납치하는 등 마수를 뻗칠 방법은 많아졌지만, 이를 효과적으로 예방하거나 사후에 제재하기는 갈수록 어려워지고 있습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text Broadcast of CppCast 278: SerenityOS]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0828/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/ZMpfn-vb95I/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Episode 278 of CppCast is an inspiring story how guest Andreas Kling overcame his drug addiction by creating and developing a new open-source operating system in C++. He named it after the Serenity Prayer he learned in rehab – SerenityOS. In this episode, hosts Rob Irving and Jason Turner interview Andreas Kling about his operating system and also discuss QT6 and new C++ podcasts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Turmoil at the freenode IRC network]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857140/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857140/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T20:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet Relay
Chat (IRC) is a longstanding protocol—or series of protocols—for
creating online,
text-based chat rooms.
While many of the "channels" (as chat rooms are usually called) are highly useful to
a wide variety of projects and organizations, including much of the
free-software world,
IRC seems to have a community that suffers from
more than its fair share of disagreements, hostile forks, vitriol, and other types of
divisiveness.  It is perhaps no huge surprise, then, that the IRC
world is currently undergoing another of its periodic upheavals.  The
largest IRC network, freenode, is
embroiled in a messy dispute that has led
to the mass resignation
of many of its volunteer staff, the founding of a competitor network (run by the former staff),
and its abandonment by multiple high-profile projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Control your Mirru prosthesis with MediaPipe hand tracking]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/tPszlMM-K-k/control-your-mirru-prosthesis-with-mediapipe-hand-tracking.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/tPszlMM-K-k/control-your-mirru-prosthesis-with-mediapipe-hand-tracking.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guest post by the Engineering teams at Mirru and Tweag  
 What is the Mirru App?
 

 
Mirru is a free and open source Android app under development with which one can control robotic prosthetic hands via hand tracking. With our app, a user can instantly mirror grips from their sound hand onto a robotic one, which could be 3D-printed and self-assembled at low cost. With Mirru, we want to provide a cheap, intuitive and open end-to-end alternative to existing, costly, cumbersome and proprietary technology. 
 

Figure 1: A demonstration of using MediaPipe hand tracking to move a robotic hand’s fingers with the Mirru app.
   
The Mirru team is a collaboration between Violeta López and Vladimir Hermand, two independent designers and technologists currently based in Paris. To kickstart the projec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알리바바 사용자를 추월, 최다 사용 공동구매 쇼핑앱, 판둬둬 성공요인 7가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580673</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580673/%ed%8c%90%eb%91%ac%eb%91%ac-%ec%84%b1%ea%b3%b5%ec%9a%94%ec%9d%b8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T16:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A set of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857353/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857353/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T15:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.12.7, 5.10.40, 5.4.122, 4.19.192, 4.14.234, 4.9.270, and 4.4.270 have been released. As usual, they
contain important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857352/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857352/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T14:55:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (djvulibre, dotnet-runtime, dotnet-runtime-3.1, dotnet-sdk, dotnet-sdk-3.1, gupnp, hivex, lz4, matrix-synapse, prometheus, python-pydantic, runc, thunderbird, and websvn), Fedora (composer, moodle, and wordpress), Gentoo (bash, boost, busybox, containerd, curl, dnsmasq, ffmpeg, firejail, gnome-autoar, gptfdisk, icu, lcms, libX11, mariadb, mumble, mupdf, mutt, mysql, nettle, nextcloud-client, opensmtpd, openssh, openvpn, php, postgresql, prosody, rxvt-unicode, samba, screen, smarty, spamassassin, squid, stunnel, tar, tcpreplay, and telegram-desktop), openSUSE (Botan), Red Hat (kernel), Slackware (gnutls), SUSE (hivex, libu2f-host, and rubygem-actionpack-5_1), and Ubuntu (apport, exiv2, and libx11).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NB-IoT achieves statis after years of hype]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470038</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nb-iot-achieves-statis-after-years-of-hype/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The hype around NB-IoT led to three years’ worth of breathless press releases and articles, mostly from vendors. What happened to NB-IoT? It’s a classic...
The post NB-IoT achieves statis after years of hype appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Matter (previously ‘CHIP’) on ESP32]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/84164316c0e3</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/the-esp-journal/announcing-matter-previously-chip-on-esp32-84164316c0e3?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T12:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrishikesh Dhayagude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Placing Code in Sections with managed GNU Linker Scripts]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32592</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/26/placing-code-in-sections-with-managed-gnu-linker-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T07:36:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managed linker scripts are great on one side: the simplify the otherwise complex GNU linker script handling. On the other side it requires knowledge how to tweak them in case ‘non-standard’ behavior is needed. I described the context in Putting … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEGGER’s emRun Runtime Library Licensed by SiFive for Superior Code Size and Performance Improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.segger.com/news/seggers-emrun-runtime-library-licensed-by-sifive-for-superior-code-size-and-performance-improvements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.segger.com/news/seggers-emrun-runtime-library-licensed-by-sifive-for-superior-code-size-and-performance-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T07:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEGGER emRun runtime library is available as part of the recently announced SiFive 21G1 release. SiFive’s focus on toolchain and library support enables key market requirements, including reduced code size and lower memory footprints. To support this goal, SiFive has licensed emRun as part of the SiFive Freedom Tools and Freedom-E-SDK packages. This integration enables chip designers to easily achieve optimum performance, while reducing code size by up to 25 % [1] [2].]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEGGER Microcontroller RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[관평원 ‘특공’ 공무원의 특혜 3종 세트]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80823</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/gQRWQNVQ9JI/80823"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T05:35:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 17일 권영세 의원실을 통해 대전에 위치한 관세청 산하 관세평가분류원(‘관평원’)이 이전 대상도 아닌데 세종시에 신청사를 짓고 상당수 직원이 특별공급(‘특공’)으로 세종시 아파트를 분양받아 수억원의 시세차익을 남긴 사실이 밝혀졌다. 혈세로 지은 신청사는 현재 빈 건물로 방치돼 있다. 애초에 세종시 이전 대상도 아닌 관평원이 특별공급 아파트를 노리고 청사 신축을 강행했다는 의혹이 제기되면서 특공 제도에 대한 논란이 일고 있다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존 MGM 인수, 아마존이 한물간 MGM과  제임스 본드에 90억 달러를 투자하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580694</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580694/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-mgm-%ec%9d%b8%ec%88%98"/>
        <updated>2021-05-26T04:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magit 3.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857218/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857218/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 3.0 of
Magit, a Git interface that runs inside emacs, has been released. 
"The big change are the completely reworked menus used to select
arguments and invoke suffix commands. Magit now uses the Transient package to
implement these menus." See the release
notes for more details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Julia 1.6 addresses latency issues]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856819/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856819/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T16:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On March 24, version 1.6.0 of the Julia
programming language was released. This is the
first feature release since 1.0 came out in 2018. The new release
significantly reduces the "time to first plot", which is a common source of
dissatisfaction for newcomers to the language, by parallelizing
pre-compilation, downloading packages more efficiently, and reducing the
frequency of just-in-time re-compilations at run time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857212/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857212/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:52:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (python-eventlet), openSUSE (grub2 and mpv), and Red Hat (kpatch-patch and rh-ruby25-ruby).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding threshold hysteresis for smooth undervoltage/overvoltage lockout]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469996</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/adding-threshold-hysteresis-for-smooth-undervoltage-overvoltage-lockout/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T14:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Resistive dividers help set up power supply undervoltage and overvoltage lockout thresholds, but threshold hysteresis is needed to obtain a smooth and chatter-free lockout function...
The post Adding threshold hysteresis for smooth undervoltage/overvoltage lockout appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pinkesh Sachdev</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting critical infrastructure through application performance monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469984</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/protecting-critical-infrastructure-through-application-performance-monitoring/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given recent attacks on existing infrastructure, the cybersecurity of embedded systems built into critical infrastructure is perhaps even more crucial than their physical security. As...
The post Protecting critical infrastructure through application performance monitoring appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ludovic Rembert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Wi-Fi chips in short supply, Minim finds a way]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8363</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/with-wi-fi-chips-in-short-supply-minim-finds-a-way/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chip shortage shows no sign of letting up, and while we may be looking forward to innovation in chip design and better software as a result of the shortage, companies also have to deal with the here and now. So I spoke with Minim, a software company that last year merged with a modem-maker to find […]
The post With Wi-Fi chips in short supply, Minim finds a way appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI chips soaring, AI software gaining spotlight]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470022</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ai-chips-soaring-ai-software-gaining-spotlight/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T12:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the tech industry continues to tout a “renaissance” of artificial intelligence, the number of AI chip startups has begun to plateau as major players...
The post AI chips soaring, AI software gaining spotlight appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Junko Yoshida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden’s Executive Order on Improving U.S. Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21149</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/president-bidens-executive-order-on-improving-u-s-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T08:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you think your software is secure, get ready to prove it. This is a guest blog authored by Eric Greenwald, General Counsel at Finite State, and Matt Wyckhouse, Founder and CEO at Finite State A perspective on President Biden’s Executive Order on Improving U.S. cybersecurity. President Joe Biden has just released an Executive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인공지능 공동선언문]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80808</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/PRo0O7SyKiM/80808"/>
        <updated>2021-05-25T07:54:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어제(5월 24일) 오후 2시 우리(120개 시민사회단체)는 참여연대 아름드리홀에서 기자회견을 열고 정부와 국회에 인권과 안전, 민주주의가 보장되는 인공지능 정책을 요구하는 선언을 발표했습니다. 우리는 ♦인공지능의 인권과 법률 준수 ♦인공지능 규율법의 마련을 촉구하며, 규율법에 담겨야 할 내용으로 다음 네 가지 사항을 제안했습니다. 인공지능 국가 감독 체계 마련 정보 공개와 참여 인공지능 평가 및 위험성 통제 권리구제 절차 보장 산업계 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should you sell all of your smart home gear to get ready for Matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8358</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/should-you-sell-all-of-your-smart-home-gear-to-get-ready-for-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T22:49:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Josh called in to the voicemail hotline with a Matter question. He’s moving to a new home soon and has already packed up his smart home gear. That includes Insteon lighting products, Z-Wave devices, and a Samsung SmartThings hub. He’s wondering if he should just sell his “hodgepodge […]
The post Should you sell all of your smart home gear to get ready for Matter? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inkscape 1.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857151/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857151/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T22:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.1 of the Inkscape vector image editor has been released.
"Among the highlights in Inkscape 1.1 are a Welcome dialog, a Command
Palette, a revamped Dialog Docking System, and searchable preference
options, along with new formats for exporting your work."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code for C/C++ with ARM Cortex-M: Part 6]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32532</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/24/visual-studio-code-for-c-c-with-arm-cortex-m-part-6/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T19:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The previous parts were about installation, project setup, building, debugging and setting up a kit. This one is about setting up IntelliSense for Cross Development in Visual Studio Code which allows for browsing symbols or code completion: Outline The powerful … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A conversation with Hebe He, a developer from Guangzhou]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/nIWqMzA1STQ/a-conversation-with-hebe-he-developer.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/nIWqMzA1STQ/a-conversation-with-hebe-he-developer.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Shen, Program Manager, Google Developers 
    
Google Developer Groups are one of the largest community networks of developers in the world. Every group has an organizer that helps curate events based on the interests of their local developer community.  
As we continue to explore how different Google Developer Groups build their communities, we interviewed Hebe He, an organizer of Google Developer Group Guangzhou in China. Learn more about how she is building the developer scene in China, thinking up new events for her community, and more below.  
    
 Hebe He, an organizer of Google Developer Group Guangzhou in China. 
     
Tell us about yourself. 
I am Hebe from China and I'm a native of Guangzhou. I'm the organizer of GDG Guangzhou, as well as an ambassador for Women …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another Valuable Practice from the Kitchen: Clean as You Go]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=13654</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/05/24/another-valuable-practice-from-the-kitchen-clean-as-you-go/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[24 May 2021 by Phillip JohnstonToday I want to explore another example of a valuable practice I picked up from a non-engineering field. This is another kitchen lesson: clean as you go. This kitchen principle is essential to me, especially now that I’m a parent. I definitely don’t want to spend what little free time … 
Continue reading "Another Valuable Practice from the Kitchen: Clean as You Go"
The post Another Valuable Practice from the Kitchen: Clean as You Go appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking down misconceptions about driver monitoring systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470017</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/breaking-down-misconceptions-about-driver-monitoring-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Awareness of the importance of robust driver monitoring systems has risen significantly in recent weeks. I will explore some of the most common misconceptions I’ve...
The post Breaking down misconceptions about driver monitoring systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Barnden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join us for Google for Games Developer Summit 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/2zrVU4HsGUg/join-us-for-google-for-games-developer-summit-2021.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/2zrVU4HsGUg/join-us-for-google-for-games-developer-summit-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T16:00:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Greg Hartrell, Head of Product Management, Games on Android & Google Play
 
 With a surge of new gamers and an increase in time spent playing games in the last year, it’s more important than ever for game developers to delight and engage players. To help developers with this opportunity, the games teams at Google are back to announce the return of the Google for Games Developer Summit 2021 on July 12th-13th. 
Hear from experts across Google about new game solutions they’re building to make it easier for you to continue creating great games, connecting with players, and scaling your business.  Registration is free and open to all game developers. 
Register for the free online event at g.co/gamedevsummit to get more details in the coming weeks.  We can’t wait to share our latest innovations with the developer community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm launches 5G modem optimized for industrial IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469975</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/qualcomm-launches-5g-modem-optimized-for-industrial-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:53:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm hopes to make fully reconfigurable flexible wireless factories possible with the launch of a new 5G modem chip optimized for industrial IoT.
The post Qualcomm launches 5G modem optimized for industrial IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Multi-generational LRU: the next generation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856931/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856931/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The multi-generational LRU patch set is a significant reworking of the
kernel's memory-management subsystem that promises better performance for a
number of workloads; it was covered here in
April.  Since then, two new versions of that work have been released by
developer Yu Zhao, with
version 3
being posted on May 20.  Some significant changes have been made since
the original post, so another look is in order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857132/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857132/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libx11, prosody, and ring), Fedora (ceph, glibc, kernel, libxml2, python-pip, slurm, and tpm2-tss), Mageia (bind, libx11, mediawiki, openjpeg2, postgresql, and thunderbird), openSUSE (Botan, cacti, cacti-spine, chromium, djvulibre, fribidi, graphviz, java-1_8_0-openj9, kernel, libass, libxml2, lz4, and python-httplib2), and Slackware (expat).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A deep dive into Google I/O’s smart home news]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8360</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/a-deep-dive-into-google-i-os-smart-home-news/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T15:02:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google’s developer conference this week largely focused on cool machine learning demos, and for the most part, the various presentations felt a little disjointed from any cohesive whole. But for people who care about the smart home, Google’s smart home keynote had a compelling core theme: cleaning up the mess the smart home has become. […]
The post A deep dive into Google I/O’s smart home news appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[찻잔속 태풍에 그친 아마존 오프라인 공략, 그럼에도 아마존 잠재력이 무궁무진한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580666</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580666/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%98%a4%ed%94%84%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8-%ea%b3%b5%eb%9e%b5-%ea%b2%b0%ea%b3%bc"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T14:12:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’15자’만 공개된 한국군의 민간인학살]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80788</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/c3glrRBmPtI/80788"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T04:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[중앙정보부가 베트남전에서 한국군의 민간인학살 사건을 조사했다는 것은 공공연한 사실이었다. 1969년 11월, 월남전에 참전한 해병 1대대 1중대 소속 소대장 3인은 줄줄이 호출을 받고 남산으로 갔다. 이들을 포함해 같은 부대 장교와 하사관 10여명이 조사를 받았다. “월남에서의 작전을 기억하십니까?” 수사관이 물었다. 조사받은 때로부터 1년 9개월 전인 1968년 2월 12일, 베트남 퐁니퐁넛마을에서 일어난 민간인 집단 살인 사건에 대한 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.13-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/857060/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/857060/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-24T02:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third 5.13 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "It's been a very calm rc3 week, and at least in pure
number of commits this is the smallest rc3 we've had in the 5.x
series.

Considering that the merge window was not in any way small, this is a
bit surprising, but I suspect it's one of those 'not everybody sent in
fixes this week' things that will rectify itself next week."
This prepatch does include reverts and fixes for a long series of broken
patches identified in the TAB report on the UMN
mess.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[온라인쇼핑 성장에 대처하는 오프라인 유통전략 5가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580658</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580658/%ec%98%a4%ed%94%84%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8-%ec%9c%a0%ed%86%b5%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5-5%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T21:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentecost 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32553</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/23/pentecost-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T14:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weather in Switzerland is changing fast and frequently over this long weekend: with hours pouring rain followed by hours of beautiful sunshine. The traffic jams on the roads to the South are nearly back to ‘normal’. The pandemic is still … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 트렌드, 온라인 브랜드들이 앞다퉈  오프라인 매장을 여는 이유는? 무신사, 구글, 올버즈 등등]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580648</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580648/%ec%98%a8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8-%eb%b8%8c%eb%9e%9c%eb%93%9c-%ec%98%a4%ed%94%84%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8-%eb%a7%a4%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T11:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동남아 클라우드 시장을 두고 격화되는 미중  클라우드 전쟁]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580640</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580640/%eb%8f%99%eb%82%a8%ec%95%84-%ed%81%b4%eb%9d%bc%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T09:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[트렌드 차트] 연도별 세계 국방비 순위 Top 50, 21년 보고서 업뎃]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580626</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580626/%ec%97%b0%eb%8f%84%eb%b3%84-%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84-%ea%b5%ad%eb%b0%a9%eb%b9%84-%ec%88%9c%ec%9c%84"/>
        <updated>2021-05-23T01:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday Stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856996/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856996/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T23:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.12.6,
5.10.39,
5.4.121,
4.19.191,
4.14.233,
4.9.269, and
4.4.269
stable kernels have all been released; each contains yet another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SWO with ARM Cortex-M33]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32464</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/22/swo-with-arm-cortex-m33/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T18:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One major concern of embedded system development is performance. Microcontroller have more MHz than in the past, but embedded applications are all about timing and real-time aspects. The challenge is: how to get data off the target in realtime? SWO … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[리기론, 실체, 속성]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222361806543</id>
        <link href="http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222361806543"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T12:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이기론, 혹은 리기론이 진짜 중요한 철학적 의미를 갖고 있는 것인가? 개인적으로 나는 리기론의 주장을 수용하지 않는다. <태극도설>에 있는 주장은 웅장하지만, 거의 거짓말이라고 생각한다. 그 이유는 그것을 주장하는 근거가 분명하지 않기 때문이다. 그저 골방에 앉아서 우주에 대해서 자기 주관적 생각을 표현한 것이라고 여긴다. 따라서 그에게는 매우 중요하겠지만, 나에게는 별로 중요치 않다. 리기론에 대한 몇몇 논문들은 주자, 즉 주희의 리기론에 대한 소개가 거의 전부이다. 주자의 저술로부터 리와 기에 대한 구절을 인용하면서 리가 무엇이고, 기가 무엇이며, 그들의 관계가 어떤 것인지 해설해 주고 있다. 이것도 중요하.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[트렌드 차트] 연도별 국방비 증가율 및  GDP 대비 국방비 비중 추이]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580585</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580585/%ec%97%b0%eb%8f%84%eb%b3%84-%ea%b5%ad%eb%b0%a9%eb%b9%84-%ec%a6%9d%ea%b0%80%ec%9c%a8-gdp-%eb%8c%80%eb%b9%84-%ea%b5%ad%eb%b0%a9%eb%b9%84-%eb%b9%84%ec%a4%91"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T11:11:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[트렌드 차트] 분기별 PC 출하량 및 PC 점유율 추이(1Q21 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580590</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580590/%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0%eb%b3%84-pc-%ec%b6%9c%ed%95%98%eb%9f%89"/>
        <updated>2021-05-22T02:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for May 21, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8355</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-may-21-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T18:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Span releases a second-generation smart electrical panel: As we electrify our homes and add electric vehicles to our garages we’re either going to need a lot more juice or a better way to manage the electricity coming into the home. Span’s a startup that adds computing and connectivity to electrical panels to help optimize how our […]
The post IoT news of the week for May 21, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efabless chipIgnite enables SoC for $9,750 in Skywater CMOS node]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469963</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/efabless-chipignite-enables-soc-for-9750-in-skywater-cmos-node/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T17:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Community chip creation platform Efabless has launched chipIgnite, a program enabling low-cost fabrication of initial prototypes of intellectual property (IP) blocks or full systems on...
The post Efabless chipIgnite enables SoC for $9,750 in Skywater CMOS node appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSIRO's seL4 project shut down]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856934/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856934/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T17:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2018, LWN covered a talk by Gernot
Heiser about the seL4 project, which has developed an open-source
operating system for safety-critical applications and gone to the trouble
of proving its correctness.  Much of that work has been done at CSIRO in
Australia.  Heiser has announced
via Twitter that CSIRO's support for this project is being shut down, with
the staff being 
redirected to artificial-intelligence projects.  Hopefully the seL4 Foundation, established in
2020, will be able to carry on this inter…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perl 5.34.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856926/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856926/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T15:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 5.34.0 of the Perl language has been released.
"Perl 5.34.0 represents approximately 11 months of development since
Perl 5.32.0 and contains approximately 280,000 lines of changes across
2,100 files from 78 authors."  See this
page for a list of changes; they include a new try/catch syntax, a new
octal syntax, and many improvements to various modules.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Control-flow integrity in 5.13]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856514/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856514/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:36:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the many changes merged for the 5.13 kernel is support for the LLVM
control-flow integrity (CFI) mechanism.  CFI defends against exploits by
ensuring that indirect function calls have not been redirected by an
attacker.  Quite a bit of work was needed to make this feature work well
for the kernel, but the result appears to be production-ready and able to
defend Linux systems from a range of attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856902/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856902/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T14:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (ceph, chromium, firefox, gitlab, hedgedoc, keycloak, libx11, mariadb, opendmarc, prosody, python-babel, python-flask-security-too, redmine, squid, and vivaldi), Debian (lz4), Fedora (ceph and python-pydantic), and openSUSE (cacti, cacti-spine).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[학자로서 정직함]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222360201724</id>
        <link href="http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222360201724"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T07:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[데란다의 책을 번역한 역자들이 다음처럼 말한다. 알랭 소칼이라는 시대적 사기꾼, 혹은 깡패가 등장해 지식계를 뒤집어 놓았다. 이 사악한 물리학자에 동조해서 무책임한 언사를 뱉어냈던 사람이 이 책을 읽었으면 좋겠다. 자신의 경솔함을 되돌아보고 학자로서 정직함을 진지하게 생각해 볼 기회를 가졌으면 좋겠다. 나는 소칼이 사기꾼이라고 생각하지 않는다. 그러나 깡패이기는 할 것이다. 그는 그들에게 지적 깡패이다. 소칼은 지적으로 또 학적으로 정직하지 않은 사상가들을 고발하고 혼내 주고 있다. 그들이 바로 엉터리이고 사기꾼이다. 그런데 역자들은 그렇게 생각하지 않는다. 오히려 소칼이 엉터리이며, 그에 동조하는 자가 학문적.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KTX 열차의 ‘사소한’ 결투]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80774</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/7ZVQAajTpxk/80774"/>
        <updated>2021-05-21T04:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[좀 전에 KTX에서 어떤 외국인 남자랑 싸웠다. 전모는 이렇다. 열차를 탔는데, 탄 지 얼마 안 되어 어디선가 자꾸만 큰 소리가 나는 것이다. 참다못해 “누구야! 누가 공공장소에서 자꾸 큰 소리를 내는 거야!” 하면서 쳐다봤는데 내 자리 맞은편 쪽에 앉은 백인 남성이 전화 통화를 하고 있었다. 뭐 거기까진 그러려니. 문제는 남자가 마스크까지 벗고 그러고 있었다는 것이다. 너무나 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한승혜</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new for Android developers at Google I/O]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/C-tG8-Xcm9M/whats-new-for-android-developers-at.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/C-tG8-Xcm9M/whats-new-for-android-developers-at.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T23:53:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cross-posted on the Android Developers blog by Karen Ng, Director, Product Management & Jacob Lehrbaum, Director of Developer Relations, Android & Play 
  
As Android developers, we are all driven by building experiences that delight people around the world. And with people depending on your apps more than ever, expectations are higher and your jobs as developers aren’t getting easier. Today, at Google I/O, we covered a few ways that we’re trying to help out, whether it be through Android 12 - one of the bi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[누구나 알지만 아무나 흉내낼 수 없는 파타고니아의 성공 비결]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72776</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/05/20/patagoniacorporateactivism/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=patagoniacorporateactivism"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T22:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정치적인 논쟁에 휘말리는 건 무조건 피하는 게 상책이라는 통념을 거스르고도 파타고니아는 존경받는 브랜드이자 돈도 잘 버는 기업으로 확고히 자리 잡았습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering Cortex-M Microcontroller with a Power Glitch]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32438</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/20/recovering-cortex-m-microcontroller-with-a-power-glitch/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T18:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If a Cortex microcontroller is unresponsive to a debug connection for various reasons, then this trick might help to recover that device for you. All you need is a debug probe from PEMICRO and a utility. Many NXP Kinetis and … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Why RISC-V doesn't (yet) support KVM]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856685/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856685/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T17:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RISC-V CPU architecture has been
gaining prominence for some years; its relatively open nature makes it an
attractive platform on which a number of companies have built products.
Linux supports
RISC-V well, but there is one gaping hole: there is no support for
virtualization with KVM,
despite the fact that a high-quality 
implementation exists.  A recent attempt to add that support is shining
some light on a part of the ecosystem that, it seems, does not work quite
as well
as one would like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856775/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856775/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T14:08:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (cacti, cacti-spine, exif, firefox, kernel, mariadb, and thunderbird), Mageia (kernel, kernel-linus, and libxml2), openSUSE (exim and jhead), Oracle (slapi-nis and xorg-x11-server), Scientific Linux (slapi-nis and xorg-x11-server), Slackware (libX11), SUSE (djvulibre, fribidi, graphviz, grub2, libass, libxml2, lz4, python-httplib2, redis, rubygem-actionpack-4_2, and xen), and Ubuntu (pillow and python-babel).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global standardization efforts foster machine vision adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470003</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/global-standardization-efforts-foster-machine-vision-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T13:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In many technologies, standardization is the technological gateway to a barrier-free world. For machine vision as a still relatively young technology, the global, joint standardization efforts of the past 15 years have been key to adoption.
The post Global standardization efforts foster machine vision adoption appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Werner Feith</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple TV 4K: An amazing content experience with a side of HomeKit and Thread]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8329</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/apple-tv-4k-2021-review-homekit-thread/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T13:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Apple TV 4K arrives soon in stores with a starting price of $179. I’ve been using an Apple-loaned $199 model, which doubles the internal storage to 64 GB, for the past week. Mostly, I’ve been interested in what new smart home features Apple will deliver, but I’ll admit it: I watched a lot […]
The post Apple TV 4K: An amazing content experience with a side of HomeKit and Thread appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Google decides Matter matters]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8343</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-google-decides-matter-matters/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T12:58:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show focuses on news from Google I/O 2021 where it’s clear the search giant is trying to build out a fairly open ecosystem based on the Matter protocol and WebRTC for audio and video streaming. Google also said it would use Wear OS for Fitbit and combine Wear OS with Samsung’s Tizen OS. […]
The post Podcast: Google decides Matter matters appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가정상비약, 무엇을 준비하고 어떻게 사용할까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80766</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/TrXn40rgAzE/80766"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T05:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[누구나 살면서 갑자기 아프거나 열이 나거나 다친 경험이 있을 것이다. 더구나 아이를 키워본 분이라면, 밤에 아이가 열이 나서 발을 동동 구른 경험을 갖고 있을 것이다. 단순한 감기로 열이 나는 것을 알면서도 밤에 응급실을 가면 여러 검사에 시달리기 일쑤이고, 시간과 돈을 낭비하고 있다는 생각이 들기도 할 것이다. 찰과상 정도라면 간단한 소독만으로도 가 치료할 수 있는데 가정상비약이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 20, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856148/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856148/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-20T01:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 20, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[피터글릭의 비판에 대한 마이클 셀렌버거의 반박(2/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72784</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/05/19/m-shellenberger2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-shellenberger2"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(마이클 셀렌버거, environmentalprogress) 원문 보기 4. 1970년대 인구 증가율이 높아지면서 인구 폭발에 대한 두려움은 더 커졌습니다. 하지민 1972년 네이처의 편집장은 미래를 이렇게 예측했습니다. “1970, 80년대에는 기근이나 기아가 아니라 남은 음식을 어떻게 처리해야 하는지가 문제가 될 것이다.” 그는 또 공포를 조장하는 것은 “신식민주의를 옹호하는 셈이다”라 말했고, 다른 이들도 여기에 동의했습니다. 한 인구학자는 인구 폭발이 문제가 아니라 “폭발이라는 단어가 헛소리”라고 말했습니다. FAO에서 일하는 덴마크의 경제학자 에스터 보스럽은 역사적으로 인구가 증가할 때마다 사람들은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[피터 글릭의 비판에 대한 마이클 셀렌버거의 반박(1/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72782</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/05/19/m-shellenberger1/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-shellenberger1"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(마이클 셀렌버거, environmentalprogress) 원문 보기 피터 글릭의 비판   1. 피터 글릭은 예일기후대응모임(Yale Climate Connections)에 올린 내 책에 대한 서평에서 내가 환경주의와 기후과학을 오해하고 있다고 말합니다. 그는 내가 허수아비를 공격할 뿐 아니라, 원자력 에너지를 다른 에너지보다 옹호하고, 인신공격을 저질렀다고 썼습니다. 그러나 오해는 글릭이 내 책에 대해 하고 있습니다. 내 책은 최신 과학 연구 결과와 에너지 기술을 바탕으로 했으며, 이를 근거로 원자력을 에너지원에서 배제하지 말 것을, 그리고 원자력 기술을 옹호하는 이들을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A bunch of releases from the Pallets projects]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856518/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856518/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T22:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[May 11 marked a new major release for the Python-based Flask web
microframework project, but Flask 2.0
was only part of the story.  While the framework may be the most visible
piece, it is one of a small handful of cooperating libraries that provide
solutions for various web-development tasks;  all are incorporated into the Pallets projects organization.  For
the first time, all
six libraries that make up Pallets were released at the same time and
each had a new major version number.  In part, that new majo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pay introduces a Flutter plugin for payments]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/Zet2fcbSst0/google-pay-introduces-flutter-plugin-for-payments.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/Zet2fcbSst0/google-pay-introduces-flutter-plugin-for-payments.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T18:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jose Ugia, Developer Programs Engineer, Google Pay and Anthony Panissidi, Technical Writer, Google Developer Studio
 
 We made it easier than ever to integrate Google Pay in Flutter apps! 
Our open source Flutter plugin simplifies the addition of payments to Flutter apps on iOS and Android. 
The plugin gives you the ability to add functionality to your apps across platforms with a single and familiar codebase written in Dart.  
It adapts common steps required to facilitate payments that adhere to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new open source content library from Google]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/GzFH4RTVGy0/a-new-open-source-content-library-from-google.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/GzFH4RTVGy0/a-new-open-source-content-library-from-google.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sebastian Trzcinski-Clément, Program Manager, Developer Relations
 Developers around the world are constantly creating open source tools and tutorials but have a hard time getting them discovered. The content published often spanned many different sites - from GitHub to Medium.  Therefore we decided to create a space where we can highlight the best projects related to Google technologies in one place - introducing the Developer Library.  
 
 The platform showcases blog posts and open source tools …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[트렌드 차트] 동남아 온라인쇼핑 시장규모 추이 – 싱가폴, 인도네시아, 필리핀, 태국]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580576</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580576/%eb%8f%99%eb%82%a8%ec%95%84-%ec%98%a8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8%ec%87%bc%ed%95%91-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5%ea%b7%9c%eb%aa%a8"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T16:45:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856650/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856650/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.12.5, 5.11.22, 5.10.38, and 5.4.120 have been released. This is the last
5.11.y kernel and users should move to 5.12.y at this time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856649/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856649/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:43:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (cacti, cacti-spine, exif, and hivex), Red Hat (bash, bind, bluez, brotli, container-tools:rhel8, cpio, curl, dotnet3.1, dotnet5.0, dovecot, evolution, exiv2, freerdp, ghostscript, glibc, GNOME, go-toolset:rhel8, grafana, gssdp and gupnp, httpd:2.4, idm:DL1, idm:DL1 and idm:client, ipa, kernel, kernel-rt, krb5, libdb, libvncserver, libxml2, linux-firmware, mailman:2.1, mingw packages, NetworkManager and libnma, opensc, p11-kit, pandoc, perl, pki-core:10.6 and pki-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윈도우 생산성 앱, 윈도우에서 구글 킵(Google keep) 사용법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580078</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580078/%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80-%ed%82%b5google-keep-%ec%82%ac%ec%9a%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T14:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upheaval at freenode]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856543/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856543/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several readers have alerted us to some serious problems at freenode, which runs an IRC network that
is popular in the free-software world.  Evidently there has been a change
of control within the volunteer-run organization that has led to the
resignations of multiple different volunteers, at least in part due
to a concern about the personal information of freenode users under the new
management. "The
freenode resignation FAQ" has collected a bunch of information (and
links to even more resignation letters)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[매출 이익 모두 완벽했던 1분기 타겟 실적과 향후 타겟 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580556</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580556/21%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%83%80%ea%b2%9f-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T13:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TCP/IP stacks vulnerabilities are a wake-up call for embedded software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469947</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/tcp-ip-stacks-vulnerabilities-are-a-wake-up-call-for-embedded-software/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T12:08:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[URGENT/11 and other recent vulnerabilities such as AMNESIA:33 related to embedded TCP/IP stacks indicate a deficiency in vetting and auditing software supply chains. The blame...
The post TCP/IP stacks vulnerabilities are a wake-up call for embedded software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Hermeling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[철학적 미학]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222357623270</id>
        <link href="http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222357623270"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T11:48:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(가) <그가 말하는 미학은 미적 예술을 잘 하도록 도와주는 미적 학문이다.> 내가 가진 그의 책은 2001년에 간행된 두 권짜리인데, 책의 앞부분을 읽어보아도 그가 <미학>을 이렇게 생각한다는 구절을 찾을 수 없었다. 이런 경우, 그의 책에서 (가)를 보여주는 구절들을 인용해 주면 좋을 것이다. <미학>이 미에 대한 학문이다. 그리고 칸트는 그러한 학문이 존재할 수 없다고 이야기한다. 칸트의 이런 주장은 이미 <순수이성비판>에 나타나 있다. 그런데 이런 칸트 주장의 정당성은 <학문>이라는 개념의 의미에 달려 있다. 칸트는 미에 대한 객관적이고 체계적이며 그 규칙과 법칙을 보여주는 학문이 불가능하다.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경제가 열리는 미국을 잘 보여준 1분기 홈데포 실적과 향후 홈데포 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580545</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580545/21%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%99%88%eb%8d%b0%ed%8f%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T10:40:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 성장성이 의문스런 1분기 월마트 실적 및 그럼에도 오르는 월마트 주가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580529</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580529/21%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9b%94%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T07:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firmware Static Analysis with CodeChecker]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/static-analysis-with-codechecker</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/static-analysis-with-codechecker"/>
        <updated>2021-05-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post, I go over how to set up CodeChecker on a
firmware project to reap the benefits of static analysis. I’ll also cover ways
to deal with false positives, and configure your assert functions to be
analysis-friendly.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The misc control group]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856438/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856438/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T21:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Control groups (cgroups) are meant to limit access to a shared resource among
processes in the system.  One such resource is the values used to specify
an encrypted-memory region for a virtual machine, such as the address-space
identifiers (ASIDs) used by the AMD Secure
Encrypted Virtualization (SEV) feature.  Vipin Sharma set
out to add a 
control group for these ASIDs back in September; based on the feedback,
though, he expanded the idea into a controller to track and limit any countable resource.
The pat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New for I/O: Assistant tools and features for Android apps and Smart Displays]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/HWd67lvvpwQ/new-for-io-assistant-tools-and-features.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/HWd67lvvpwQ/new-for-io-assistant-tools-and-features.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T20:00:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rebecca Nathenson, Director of Product for the Google Assistant Developer Platform
 
 Today at I/O, we shared some exciting new product announcements to help you more easily bring Google Assistant to your Android apps and create more engaging content on smart displays. 
Assistant development made easy with new Android APIs
App Actions helps you easily bring Google Assistant to your Android app and complete user queries of all kinds, from booking a ride to posting a message on social media. Compani…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock new use cases and increase developer velocity with the latest ARCore updates]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/foS6QQINJBM/unlock-use-cases-and-increase-developer-velocity-with-new-capabilities-in-arcore.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/foS6QQINJBM/unlock-use-cases-and-increase-developer-velocity-with-new-capabilities-in-arcore.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T20:00:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ian Zhang, Product Manager, AR & Zeina Oweis, Product Manager, AR
 
 ARCore was created to provide developers with simple yet powerful tools to seamlessly blend the digital and physical worlds. Over the last few years, we’ve seen developers create apps that entertain, engage, and help people in different ways–from letting fans interact with their favorite characters, to placing virtual electronics and furniture for the perfect home setup and beyond. 
At I/O this year, we continue on the mission of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pay integration patterns that drive conversions on Android]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/r2hxTcMn794/google-pay-integration-patterns-that-drive-conversions-on-android.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/r2hxTcMn794/google-pay-integration-patterns-that-drive-conversions-on-android.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T18:30:00.010Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jose Ugia, Developer Relations Engineer, Google Pay & Anthony Panissidi, Technical Writer, Google Developer Studio
 
 What do Gilt, MTS, Panera Bread, and SpotHero have in common? 
At first glance, you probably only see four totally different businesses: 
 
Gilt is an online shopping and lifestyle website.  
MTS is a mobile network operator with 80 million users in Armenia, Belarus, and Russia.  
Panera Bread is a chain of more than 2,000 fast-casual bakery-cafe restaurants in the US and Canada.  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updated Google Pay app offers more consumer touchpoints]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/xR4xJcssKCQ/updated-google-pay-app-offers-more-consumer-touchpoints.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/xR4xJcssKCQ/updated-google-pay-app-offers-more-consumer-touchpoints.html"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T17:30:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Soc Sieng, Developer Advocate, Payments & Ola Ben Har, Payments DevRel Lead
    

 We redesigned the Google Pay app to boost user engagement with your business. 
The redesigned app makes it easy for users to find your business and provides you with a branded surface that lets you build relationships with your customers at scale. 
The app is available in the App Store and Google Play Store in the US, India, and Singapore with availability in more markets on the way. In this blog post, we focus on f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Site Isolation in Firefox (Mozilla security blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856506/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856506/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T16:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mozilla Security Blog announces
that there is a new site-isolation mechanism available for testing in the
Firefox browser.  It's a defense against Meltdown and Spectre exploits.


This fundamental redesign of Firefox's Security architecture extends
current security mechanisms by creating operating system process-level
boundaries for all sites loaded in Firefox for Desktop. Isolating each site
into a separate operating system process makes it even harder for malicious
sites to read another site’s secret …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon, Google, Apple, and Assa Abloy are working on a smart lock standard]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8321</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/amazon-google-apple-and-assa-abloy-are-working-on-a-smart-lock-standard/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T15:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, the Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA) — formerly known as the Zigbee Alliance — showed off new branding for what used to be known as Project Connected Home over IP. Now called Matter, the protocol is designed to ensure interoperability between many common smart home devices and various related ecosystems. Along with the branding, […]
The post Amazon, Google, Apple, and Assa Abloy are working on a smart lock standard appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856496/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856496/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium, curl, prosody, and ruby-rack-cors), Fedora (dotnet3.1 and dotnet5.0), openSUSE (ibsim and prosody), SUSE (kernel and python3), and Ubuntu (caribou and djvulibre).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 세계 광고 시장 전망, ’21년 15%로 사상 최대 성장, 디지탈 광고도 20% 성장할 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580495</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580495/%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84-%eb%94%94%ec%a7%80%ed%83%88-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T14:47:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[탄소중립 위한 아디다스 올버즈 협업에서 읽어보는 트렌드 변화와 시사점]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580479</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580479/%ec%95%84%eb%94%94%eb%8b%a4%ec%8a%a4-%ec%98%ac%eb%b2%84%ec%a6%88-%ed%98%91%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T12:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attention could bring needed context to vision applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469970</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/attention-could-bring-needed-context-to-vision-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded vision technologies are giving machines the power of sight, but today’s systems still fall short of understanding all the nuances of an image. An...
The post Attention could bring needed context to vision applications appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Ward-Foxton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will phones and tablets eventually have Thread radios?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8317</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/will-phones-and-tablets-eventually-have-thread-radios/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T11:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Ian called in to the podcast hotline with a curious question. He wants to know if future mobile devices might include Thread radios to assist with local control of Thread products in the smart home. Ian wonders if Thread will replace Bluetooth for device provisioning. In theory, it […]
The post Will phones and tablets eventually have Thread radios? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[산재를 바라보는 두 시선: 기업범죄 vs. 달라질 거 없다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80750</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/9274PcsoKzc/80750"/>
        <updated>2021-05-18T07:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[문재인 정부의 ‘임기 내 산재 사망사고 절반 감축’ 공약 이행은 물 건너간 듯하다. 고용노동부가 4월 14일 발표한 ‘2020년 산업재해 사고사망 통계’를 보면 지난 한 해만 업무상 사고 재해로 882명이 사망했다. 2019년(855명)보다 27명(3.2%)이 되레 증가했다. 사망사고 81%(714명)는 주로 50인 미만 사업장에서 발생했다. 5인 미만 사업장에서 35.4%(312명), 5인 이상 29인 사업장이 45.6%(402명)로 나타났다. 노동자 1만 명당 산재사고 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글로벌 인공지능 규제를 선도하려는 유럽연합]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72745</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/05/17/the-eu-wants-to-become-the-worlds-super-regulator-in-ai/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=the-eu-wants-to-become-the-worlds-super-regulator-in-ai"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T22:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 4월 21일 유럽연합 집행위원회가 발표한 인공지능 규제 법안에 전 세계의 이목이 쏠렸습니다. 이번 규제안은 인공지능에 대한 광범위한 규정을 마련하는 첫 번째 시도였습니다. 과연 이 규정이 과거 유럽에서 제정해 전 세계로 퍼진 개인정보보호법처럼 널리 채택될까요? 법안의 내용, 평가, 전망에 대한 이코노미스트의 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio New Features for Notifying Developers About Errors Found]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0827/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/K9JFgPgbot4/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio user support often receives clients' suggestions on product improvement. We are happy to implement many of them. Recently one of the users suggested refining the automatic notification utility for developers (Blame Notifier). They asked us to make Blame Notifier extract the date/the code revision to which the analyzer issued a message using blame information from the version control system. This feature allowed us to expand the utility capabilities, which we'll discuss in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Exported-symbol changes in 5.13]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856312/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856312/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T20:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been many disagreements over the years in the kernel community
concerning the exporting of internal kernel symbols to loadable modules.
Exporting a symbol often exposes implementation decisions to outside code,
makes it possible to use (or abuse) kernel functionality in unintended
ways, and makes future changes harder.  That said, there is no authority
overseeing the exporting of symbols and no process for approving exports;
discussions only tend to arise 
when somebody notices a change that they…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사상최대 수주잔고 등 비전을 보여준 1분기  인텍플러스 실적과 인텍플러스 주가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580468</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580468/21%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%8d%ed%94%8c%eb%9f%ac%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T19:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[T2 Linux 21.5 "Because we can" for 18 architectures]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856447/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856447/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T18:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The T2 System Development Environment Linux 21.5 was released with 18 pre-
and cross-compiled architectures. "The 21.5 release received updates
across the board, while a major point of work was the GCC 11 update as well
as re-basing and fixing upstream regressions for the Sony PS3 support as
well as various small improvements, including an up to 15 seconds faster
system shutdown when using sysvinit."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build better UX for IoT devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469918</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-build-better-ux-for-iot-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:30:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphones have created an interesting challenge for internet of things (IoT) development teams as consumers, industrial workers, medical professionals, and more desire a sophisticated mobile...
The post How to build better UX for IoT devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Clarke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fighting Feelings of Overwhelm with an Attitude Shift]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=13699</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/05/17/fighting-feelings-of-overwhelm-with-an-attitude-shift/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[17 May 2021 by Phillip Johnston
The post Fighting Feelings of Overwhelm with an Attitude Shift appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기대 미달 1분기 파크시스템스 실적이나 향후  기대감이 충만한 파크시스템스 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=580453</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/580453/21%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%8c%8c%ed%81%ac%ec%8b%9c%ec%8a%a4%ed%85%9c%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:46:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded design with FPGAs: Building a project]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469926</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-design-with-fpgas-building-a-project/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor’s Note: As advanced algorithms continue to emerge for smart product designs, developers often find themselves struggling to implement embedded systems able to meet the...
The post Embedded design with FPGAs: Building a project appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jim Ledin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An FAQ on the Matter protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8319</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/an-faq-on-the-matter-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:14:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, Project Connected Home over IP became Matter, and with the new name came new information about how it will provide interoperability between certain classes of smart home devices. Now that the protocol is back in the spotlight, I’m getting a lot of questions from readers around what will happen to their existing gear, what […]
The post An FAQ on the Matter protocol appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856437/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856437/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T15:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libimage-exiftool-perl and postgresql-9.6), Fedora (chromium, exiv2, firefox, kernel, kernel-headers, kernel-tools, mariadb, and python-impacket), Mageia (avahi), openSUSE (chromium, drbd-utils, dtc, ipvsadm, jhead, nagios, netdata, openvpn, opera, prosody, and virtualbox), Slackware (libxml2), SUSE (kernel and lz4), and Ubuntu (intel-microcode, python-eventlet, and rust-pleaser).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[철학의 외부 1]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222355057876</id>
        <link href="http://blog.naver.com/sellars/222355057876"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<맑스주의의 외부를 통해 맑스주의를 사유하고 있다. 즉 모든 것을 설명하고 이해하게 해주었던 하나의 사상에 외부가 존재했다.> 이때 <외부>는 맑스주의와 다른 사유를 의미할 것이다. 따라서 맑스주의와 다른 사유, 혹은 다른 철학적 사유가 존재한다. 이것이 의미하는 것이 하나의 철학이나 사상이 세계의 모든 것을 설명하고 이해하게 만들어 줄 수 없다는 것이다. 나는 이 점에서 맑스주의자들이 싫어하는 포퍼의 생각이 적절하다고 여긴다. 모든 것을 설명하고 이해하게 만들어주는 철학적, 사상적 만병통치약에 조심하라. 그것은 반증이나 반박이 되지 않는 그런 신념일 것이다. <외부, 그것은 그것을 상대하는 자가 자신.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name/>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Addressing design challenges in precision DC energy metering]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4469843</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/addressing-design-challenges-in-precision-dc-energy-metering/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T13:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to development of efficient power conversion technology based on wide band gap semiconductors, precision dc energy metering is becoming relevant, especially where energy billing...
The post Addressing design challenges in precision DC energy metering appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luca Martini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.13-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/856386/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/856386/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T12:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.13-rc2 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "The fixes here are all over the place - drivers, arch updates,
documentation, tooling.. Nothing particularly stands out".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["제 다음 생 후배들은 비정규직 설움 못 느꼈으면" 어느 피디의 유언]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80738</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/5EiH8UDtq5U/80738"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T05:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[청주지방법원은 5월 13일 CJB청주방송 고 이재학 PD가 제기한 근로자지위확인소송 2심에서 이 PD 손을 들어주었습니다. 13년간 프리랜서로 고용돼 정규직보다 더 많이 일하고도 적은 임금을 받았던 이 PD가 청주방송 노동자로 인정된다는 판결입니다. 재판부는 청주방송이 이 PD가 비정규직 임금 인상을 요구한 것을 이유로 프로그램 하차 후 해고한 결정이 위법하다고 봤습니다. 따라서 청주방송에게 이 PD 해고기간 임금 6,300만 원과 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 포털에선 중앙일보가 더 많이 노출되나]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80724</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/YRpyI6FussU/80724"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T04:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이명박 대통령 후보 캠프에서 뉴미디어 간사를 지낸 진성호 씨가 “네이버는 평정됐고 다음은 손봐야 한다”고 말했던 게 2007년 일이다. 네이버는 상대적으로 보수적인 편집을 하고 다음은 좀 더 진보적인 성향을 보인다는 평가가 많지만 지난해 9월 더불어민주당 윤영찬 의원의 “카카오 들어오라 하세요” 메시지 논란에서 보듯 서 있는 자리에 따라 풍경이 다를 수밖에 없다. 플랫폼 공정성 이슈는 여전히 뜨겁고 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7년간 잠잠하던 이스라엘-팔레스타인, 왜 지금 다시 충돌했나?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72764</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/05/16/israelpalestineconflict/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=israelpalestineconflict"/>
        <updated>2021-05-17T01:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이슬람력의 아홉 번째 달로 신성한 달인 라마단의 첫 번째 밤이었던 4월 13일은 공교롭게도 이스라엘의 현충일이기도 했습니다. 이날 이스라엘 경찰이 알 아크사 사원에서 강행한 작전이 7년 만에 촉발된 충돌에 적잖은 원인을 제공합니다. 뉴욕타임스가 지난 한 달간 무슨 일이 있었는지 심층 분석한 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to speed up building ang analyzing of your project with IncrediBuild?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0826/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/Qs_NPObuNBk/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["How much longer are you going to build it?" - a phrase that every developer has uttered at least once in the middle of the night. Yes, a build can be long and there is no escaping it. One does not simply redistribute the whole thing among 100+ cores, instead of some pathetic 8-12 ones. Or is it possible?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Full Bathroom Remodeling (with the Help of a 3D Printer)]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=31457</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/05/16/full-bathroom-remodeling-with-the-help-of-a-3d-printer/"/>
        <updated>2021-05-16T16:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is about one of my ‘long running projects’: I happily can report that the missing last piece has been installed after 16 months from the start of the project: the ‘3D-Printed-Supported-Driftwood-Bath-Tub-Shower-Gel-Holder’ 🙂 : This is the ‘official finish’ of … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>