<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2022-01-10T20:17:23.443Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.12.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some 5.16 kernel development statistics]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880699/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880699/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T19:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16 kernel was released
on January 9, as expected.  This development cycle incorporated 14,190
changesets from 1,988 developers; it was thus quite a bit busier than its 
predecessor, and fairly typical for recent kernel releases in general.  A
new release means that the time has come to have a look at where those
changes came from.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“Disapproved Ads Auditor” tool]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/01/disapproved-ads-auditor-tool.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/01/disapproved-ads-auditor-tool.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T18:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nir Kalush, Dvir Kalev, Chen Yoveg, Elad Ben-David
  
Ads Review Tool
   
This tool flags (and optionally deletes) policy violating ads across your accounts. Advertisers can learn from the output to ensure their ads are compliant with Google Ads Policies at all times. 
Business Challenge:
Advertisers operating at scale need a solution to holistically review policy violating ads across their accounts so they can ensure compliance with Google’s Ad Policies. As Google introduces more policies and enforcement mechanisms, advertisers need to continue checking their accounts to ensure they comply with Google’s Ads Policies.
Solution Overview:  
“Disapproved Ads Auditor” is a tool  that enables advertisers to review at scale all disapproved ads across their  Google Ads accounts. This view  allows advertisers to proactively audit their accounts , analyze the ad disapprovals holistically and identify  learnings to minimize and  reduce submission of potentially policy violating ads. 
The tool is based on a Python script, which can be run in either of the following modes: 
 
“Audit Mode”- export an output of disapproved ads across your accounts 
“Remove Mode” - delete currently disapproved ads and log details.
 
There are a few output files (see here) which are saved locally under the “output” folder and there is an optional feature to export on BigQuery for further data analysis (“Disapproved Ads Auditor” dataset). 
Skills Required:   
 
 Python 3.9+ 
 BigQuery API 
 Google Ads API 
 OAuth 2.0
 
Google Products Used:
 
Google Ads  
BigQuery
 
Estimated time to implement the solution: ~2h 
Implementation instructions: View on github
Impact:
“Disapproved Ads Auditor” tool automates auditing ads across your accounts to provide you insights into non compliant ads. You can take the learnings from the output to ensure ads are compliant with Google Ads Policies and avoid creating non compliant ads. Moreover, you can optionally remove disapproved ads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remember to lock around all std::condition_variable “variables”]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=18563</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2022/01/10/remember-to-lock-around-all-stdcondition_variable-variables/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 January 2022 by Phillip JohnstonI recently received a question regarding our dispatch queue implementation: I had a question concerning the locking of the mutex in the destructor to set the boolean quit_ variable. The way I see it, the mutex protects the queue access and does not really refer to the quit_ variable. When … 
Continue reading "Remember to lock around all std::condition_variable “variables”"
The post Remember to lock around all std::condition_variable “variables” appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What NPM Should Do Today To Stop A New Colors Attack Tomorrow]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/npm-colors</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/npm-colors"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T16:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stop blindly installing the latest version of all transitive dependencies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Address digital baseband to unlock THz communications for 6G]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472112</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/address-digital-baseband-to-unlock-thz-communications-for-6g/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T16:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To unlock the ultra-high data rates and high-frequency radio communications integral to future 6G technologies, we need ultra-fast encoding and decoding for the baseband chipset, also known as channel coding, or forward-error-correction.
The post Address digital baseband to unlock THz communications for 6G appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Looking back at 2021, looking forward at 2022 (Libre Arts)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880811/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880811/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T15:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is a
comprehensive look on the Libre Arts site at the current state of free
software for creative 
artists.


	The other reason is that, with a project like GIMP, it’s hard to do
	just one thing. The team is constantly bombarded with requests that
	are mostly doable once you have a team of 10 to 20 full-time
	developers, which is light years away from where GIMP is now. Which
	results in a lot of running around between under-the-hood work, UX
	fixes, featurettes, better file formats support etc. So you give
	everyone a little of what they want but you end up delaying an
	actual release because the big stuff still needs to happen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev corrupts NPM libs 'colors' and 'faker' breaking thousands of apps
(Bleeping Computer)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880809/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880809/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T15:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bleeping Computer reports
on the latest NPM mess: the developer of the "faker" module deleted the
code and it's development history from GitHub (with a force push), replaced
it with a malicious alternative, and broke dependencies for numerous
applications. 


	The reason behind this mischief on the developer's part appears to
	be retaliation—against mega-corporations and commercial consumers
	of open-source projects who extensively rely on cost-free and
	community-powered software but do not, according to the developer,
	give back to the community.


GitHub has evidently called this action a violation of its terms of
service and disabled the owner's account; NPM has restored a previous
version of the code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880807/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880807/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T14:37:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ghostscript and roundcube), Fedora (gegl04, mbedtls, and mediawiki), openSUSE (kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-operator-container), SUSE (kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-operator-container and libvirt), and Ubuntu (apache2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[멕시코 마약 전쟁: 마크 스티븐슨의 기록]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83520</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83520"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T10:06:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[9·11 이후 미국이 해상과 공중의 경계를 강화하면서, 콜롬비아 등 남아메리카에서 생산되는 마약을 미국으로 밀수하는 해상·공중 통로가 모두 막히고 말았다. 이로써 남미에서 생산되는 마약은 모두 멕시코를 통해서만 들어가게 되었는데, 이로써 미국과 접경 지역을 중심으로 마약 밀수를 전문적으로 하는 갱단이 곳곳에서 생겨나기 시작한다. 마약 밀수를 통해 벌어들인 엄청난 돈으로 이들 갱은 조직을 키우고, 값비싼 무기로 무장하며, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20 Smaller yet Handy C++20 Features]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/20-smaller-cpp20-features/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/20-smaller-cpp20-features/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 is huge and filled with lots of large features. Just to mention a few: Modules, Coroutines, Concepts, Ranges, Calendar & Timezone, Formatting library.
But, as you know, that’s not all.
Depending on how we count, C++20 brought around 80 Library features and 70 language changes, so there’s a lot to cover :)
In this article, I’ll show you 20 smaller C++20 things that are very handy and good to know. Ten language elements, and ten more for the Standard Library. Most of them with a cool example.
Let’s jump right into the text!



     
    


You can find the whole C++20 draft here:
https://timsong-cpp.github.io/cppwp/n4861/ (post Prague 2020 draft)
And here’s a great summary page with the compiler support at C++ Reference:
https://en.cppreference.com/w/cpp/compiler_support#cpp20
Here’s a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비호감 대선: 선거제 개혁이 필요한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83505</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83505"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T03:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대통령 선거가 이제 두 달 앞으로 다가왔다. 주요 후보들은 지지율을 끌어올리기 위해 선거 운동에 한창이지만, 정작 유권자들은 ‘비호감 대선’이란 오명까지 붙은 이번 대선에서 마음 줄 곳을 쉽사리 찾지 못한 채 스트레스를 받고 있다. 과거 여느 대통령 선거처럼 거대 양당의 두 후보가 여론 지지율에서 양강 구도를 형성하고 있지만, 아이러니하게도 두 후보의 비호감도 또한 1, 2 위를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[박근혜 사면 관련 보도 정리: ’17년 3월 31일 구속 ~ ’21년 12월 31일 석방까지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83474</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83474"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T02:24:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[초지일관 동아와 조선, 한겨레의 ‘따로 또 같이’   국정농단 사건 등으로 구속된 지 4년 9개월 만에 박근혜 씨가 석방됐습니다. 언론은 이번 사면에 큰 공로를 세웠다고 할 수 있을 만큼 꾸준히 박근혜 씨 구속 동정 보도와 함께 사면 주장을 이어왔는데요. 민주언론시민연합은 박근혜 대통령이 수감된 2017년 3월 31일 이후에 언론의 박근혜 씨 사면 보도를 정리했습니다. ‘박근혜 사면’ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16 kernel has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880775/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880775/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-09T23:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds has released the 5.16
kernel, as expected.  Significant changes in 5.16 include
the futex_waitv() system call,
cluster-aware CPU scheduling,
some internal memcpy() hardening,
memory folios,
the DAMON operating schemes
user-space memory-management mechanism,
and much more.  See the LWN merge-window summaries
(part 1,
part 2) and the KernelNewbies 5.16 page for
details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIY Split-Flap Display]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33198</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/01/09/diy-split-flap-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-09T16:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Split-flap displays are electromechanical display devices, which were common in airports or railway stations a few years ago.Unfortunately, most of them are gone and replaced by LED displays. Why not create a DIY version of it? As mechanical devices they … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[벤 에반스의 2022년 테크 주요 이슈 (번역)]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2982</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2022/01/09/2022-questions/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-09T12:52:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뭐가 어떻게 될지 대충 보이는 분야도 있습니다. PC, 웹, 스마트폰 기기에 대한 것들은 그런 편이죠. 하지만 2022년을 맞이하는 지금, 실체를 갖추기보다는 무언가 뿌연 물음표로만 가득한 분야 역시 있습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: software-defined vehicles, open lidar, biowearables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472098</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-software-defined-vehicles-open-lidar-biowearables/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T22:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes more coverage from CES 2022, including a look at software-defined vehicles, open lidar API, and biowearables.
The post embedded news: software-defined vehicles, open lidar, biowearables appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Jan. 7, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9554</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-jan-7-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T20:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s Sidewalk network is getting larger: We caught wind of a new Sidewalk outdoor radio back in December and figured it was meant to be used by Amazon to broaden its LoRaWAN footprint. Turns out, we were correct. Amazon will use professional installers to add the new Sidewalk Bridge Pro by Ring around the U.S. It plans to trial the […]
The post IoT news of the week for Jan. 7, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New AI/ML processor supports SoCs and chiplets for smart edge devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472092</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-ai-ml-processor-supports-socs-and-chiplets-for-smart-edge-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T20:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CEVA’s latest NeuPro-M supports both system-on-chip and heterogeneous SoC scalability, targeting edge AI/ML and edge compute.
The post New AI/ML processor supports SoCs and chiplets for smart edge devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CES 2022: A year of catching up for the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9533</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/ces-2022-a-year-of-catching-up-for-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T18:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2022 Consumer Electronics Show is nearly half over, but the more impactful news is already out. Thanks to the pandemic, it feels as though last year’s CES let the industry take a breath and this year’s show is about catching up. There’s also much to look forward to in 2022 based on some of […]
The post CES 2022: A year of catching up for the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint 20.3 "Una" released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880696/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880696/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T17:56:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint has announced its 20.3 ("Una")  release for three different desktop environments: the Cinnamon, MATE, and Xfce editions. Mint 20.3 is a long-term support release, with support lasting until 2025. Each edition comes with a long list of new features (Cinnamon, MATE, and Xfce) and detailed release notes (Cinnamon, MATE, and Xfce).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fixing a corner case in asymmetric CPU packing]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880367/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880367/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T17:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux supports processor architectures where CPUs in the same system
might have 
different processing capacities; for example, the Arm big.LITTLE
systems combine fast, power-hungry CPUs with slower, more efficient
ones. Linux has also run for years on simultaneous
multithreading (SMT) architectures, where one CPU executes multiple
independent execution threads and is seen as if it were multiple cores.
There are architectures that mix both approaches. A recent discussion
on a patch
set submitted by Ricardo Neri shows that, on these systems, the
scheduler might distribute tasks in an inefficient way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880672/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880672/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T14:41:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (sphinxsearch), Fedora (chromium and vim), Red Hat (rh-nodejs14-nodejs and rh-nodejs14-nodejs-nodemon), and Ubuntu (apache2 and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sequans LTE-M/NB-IoT powers AMI network in Taiwan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472084</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/sequans-lte-m-nb-iot-powers-ami-network-in-taiwan/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T14:14:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sequans’ LTE-M/NB-IoT module provides connectivity in Ubiik’s advanced metering infrastructure (AMI) network for Taiwan Power Company.
The post Sequans LTE-M/NB-IoT powers AMI network in Taiwan appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[버킷리스트 쓰기 연습: 하루 5분 종이 위에 써보기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83476</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83476"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T08:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이 글은 전 편인 ‘버킷리스트는 인생의 내비게이션’에서 이어집니다.)   안드레스 에릭슨은 『1만 시간의 재발견』에서 우리가 어떤 일에 무조건 1만 시간을 투여한다고 해서 전문가가 되는 것이 아니라 의식적인 노력과 훈련이 수반되어야 전문가 수준에 이를 수 있다고 말했다. 그러면서 상투적인 연습만 하는 1만 시간은 무의미하다고 했다. 이는 비단 전문가에게만 국한되지는 않는다. 일정 수준 이상의 성과를 내기 위해서는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최호진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아이 생존권보다 나쁜 아빠 명예가 우선? ‘배드파더스’ 항소심 유감]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83462</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83462"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T01:02:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[수원고법 형사1부(부장판사 윤성식)는 2021년 12월 23일 정보통신망 이용촉진 및 정보보호 등에 관한 법률 위반(명예훼손) 혐의로 기소된 ‘배드파더스’ (양육비 미지급 부모 신상공개 사이트) 대표 구본창 씨에게 무죄를 선고한 원심을 파기하고 벌금 100만 원의 선고유예 판결을 내렸다(수원고등법원 2021.12.23. 선고 2020노70). 오픈넷은 이번 판결이 ‘사실적시 명예훼손죄’의 과잉성, 위헌성을 드러내는 판결이자, 타인의 비위사실을 고발하는 모든 활동을 형사범죄화하여 표현의 자유를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving LLVM Infrastructure - Part 1: Mailing lists]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2022-01-07-moving-to-discourse/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2022-01-07-moving-to-discourse/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the LLVM Project was open sourced in 2003, it was a small project with a small community. The tools selected to support the project were chosen during a different time and a different situation.
Now, almost 18 years later, the project has grown tremendously and those infrastructure choices are not necessarily the right choices today. According to a recent article, the LLVM community experienced record growth in 2021 with 1400 contributors to the LLVM Project. This is incredible growth! While there is a very real cost to change, it is clear that we need to invest in modernizing these tools to support the current and further growth of LLVM.
Recently, the LLVM Project moved its source code repository and bug tracker to GitHub in an effort to grow the LLVM community and make contributing …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The LLVM Project Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] VSTATUS, with or without SIGINFO]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880498/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880498/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T19:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unix signal
interface is complex and hard to work with; some developers 
have argued that its design is
"unfixable".  So when Walt Drummond proposed
increasing the number of signals that Linux systems could manage, eyebrows
could be observed at increased altitude across the Internet.  The proposed
increase seems unlikely to happen, but the underlying goal — to support a
decades-old feature from other operating systems — may yet become a
reality.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CES 2022: Green Hills Software safety solution for BMW iX, plus eSync OTA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472071</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ces-2022-green-hills-software-safety-solution-for-bmw-ix-plus-esync-ota/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T18:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Green Hills Software’s RTOS and IDE is being used in BMW’s 2022 iX EV, and eSync-compliant OTA is now available with Excelfore, for secure OTA software and data services in automotive electronics.
The post CES 2022: Green Hills Software safety solution for BMW iX, plus eSync OTA appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880564/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880564/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T14:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (log4j and quaternion), Mageia (gnome-shell and singularity), SUSE (libsndfile, libvirt, net-snmp, and python-Babel), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.11, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.11, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.11, linux-hwe-5.11, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.11, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, linux-oem-5.10, and linux-oem-5.14).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software-defined vehicles drive next-gen connected EV development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472058</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/software-defined-vehicles-drive-next-gen-connected-ev-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T14:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software-defined vehicles, software-based simulation and neural processors in EVs and connected cars, with a look at developments from General Motors, Mercedes-Benz and Blackberry.
The post Software-defined vehicles drive next-gen connected EV development appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Virtual CES extravaganza]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9537</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-virtual-ces-extravaganza/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s CES week, and neither Kevin nor I are physically there for the second year running. That makes it really tough to get a macro sense of cool tech and upcoming trends outside of press releases and product launches. Normally, we spend so much time trawling for the weird or futuristic in the demos and […]
The post Podcast: Virtual CES extravaganza appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 지지하면 박근혜가 ‘대인배’된다는 MBN 김주하 앵커]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83444</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83444"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T01:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[전직 대통령 박근혜 씨가 2021년 12월 31일 특별사면됐습니다. 언론은 특별사면 결정 직후부터 박근혜 씨가 내놓을 정치적 메시지에 주목했습니다. 이른바 ‘박근혜 메시지’에 주목하는 보도는 지금까지도 이어지고 있는데요. 특히 박근혜 씨 법률대리인 유영하 변호사가 출연한 1월 3일 MBN 저녁종합뉴스 대담은 김주하 앵커가 사실관계가 틀린 질문까지 동원해 자극적 답변을 유도하려는 진행으로 눈살을 찌푸리게 했습니다. 김주하 앵커의 ‘집착성 질문’ […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 6, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879697/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879697/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-06T01:15:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 6, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Restricting SSH agent keys]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880458/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880458/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T22:01:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OpenSSH suite of tools for
secure remote logins is used widely within our communities; it also
underlies things like remote Git repository access.
A recent experimental feature for the upcoming OpenSSH 8.9 release
will help close a security hole 
that can be exploited by attacker-controlled SSH servers (e.g. sshd) when the user is forwarding
authentication to a local ssh-agent.  Instead
of allowing the keys held in the agent to be used for authenticating to any
host where they might work, SSH agent 
restriction will allow users to specify where and how those keys can be
used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The most interesting C# / .NET blogs and websites]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0907/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0907/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's take a look at the list of information sources that can be useful for the C# / .NET developers. Our list includes blogs, repositories with source code, standards and accounts of developers who covers the deep aspects of the C# and .NET.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paxos: using two consensus-building phases to handle unreliable                nodes]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/paxos.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/paxos.html"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T15:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unmesh Joshi is ready to start the New Year with a few
      more of his Patterns of Distributed Systems. With this one he attempts the
      tricky task of explaining Paxos. This is a well-known
      protocol developed by Leslie Lamport, for nodes to reach a reliable
      consensus when both they, and the network, are prone to unexpected
      failure. Although it's well-known, it's also notoriously difficult to
      understand, indeed we had considerable difficulty getting our heads around
      it. We hope this description makes it a bit easier for those who follow
      us.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The latest set of stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880462/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880462/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T15:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.15.13,
5.10.90,
5.4.170,
4.19.224,
4.14.261,
4.9.296, and
4.4.298
stable kernel updates have all been released.  These medium-size updates
all contain another set of important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880454/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880454/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T15:04:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (xorg-x11-server), Debian (apache2), openSUSE (libvirt), Oracle (grafana, qemu, and xorg-x11-server), Red Hat (idm:DL1, samba, and telnet), SUSE (libvirt), and Ubuntu (python-django).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open lidar API aims to accelerate software-defined lidar adoption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472031</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/open-lidar-api-aims-to-accelerate-software-defined-lidar-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lumotive has defined an open lidar API to allow application developers, perception software developers, and lidar hardware developers to use a common and future-proof interface for software-defined lidar.
The post Open lidar API aims to accelerate software-defined lidar adoption appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CES 2022: NXP first secure tri-radio device and 4D imaging radar for L2+]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472040</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ces-2022-nxp-first-secure-tri-radio-device-and-4d-imaging-radar-for-l2/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T14:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NXP Semiconductors launches tri-radio devices supporting Wi-Fi 6, Bluetooth 5.2 and 802.15.4 protocols, and updates automotive 4D imaging radar portfolio.
The post CES 2022: NXP first secure tri-radio device and 4D imaging radar for L2+ appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021년 회고]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/2021-retrospective/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/2021-retrospective/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T13:32:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정말 바쁘게 2021년을 보냈다. 수업 하나가 정말 힘들었는데 기말까지 다 끝내고 나서도 점수 걱정에 스트레스가 많았다.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CES 2022: Infineon has new AURIX 28nm MCU and AIROC BLE SoC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472035</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ces-2022-infineon-has-new-aurix-28nm-mcu-and-airoc-ble-soc/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T13:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infineon launches new AURIX microcontroller (MCU) for automotive and AIROC BLE system on chip (SoC) which is Bluetooth 5.3 core spec-compliant.
The post CES 2022: Infineon has new AURIX 28nm MCU and AIROC BLE SoC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter: Thread Border Router in Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/240838dc4779</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-thread-border-router-in-matter-240838dc4779?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T08:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #5]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shu Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제다이(JEDI) 프로젝트를 대체한 ‘JWCC’ 현황]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83434</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83434"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T00:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제다이(JEDI; Joint Enterprise Defence Infrastructure) 프로젝트는 미국 국방부의 기본 인프라를 기업에서 활용하는 수준의 클라우드로 전환하는 것을 목표로 하는 것으로, 오바마 정부부터 시작된 ‘클라우드 퍼스트’ 전략을 상징하는 프로젝트로 간주된다. 제다이 프로젝트: 시작부터 취소까지  2018년 3월 RFP 드래프트가 공개되며 단일 벤더가 10년간 독점하는 100억 달러짜리 초대형 프로젝트로 알려지며 시장의 관심이 매우 뜨거웠고, 2019년 10월 아마존을 따돌리고 마이크로소프트가 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Another Fedora integrity-management proposal]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880263/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880263/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T23:47:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File-integrity management for the Fedora distribution
has been the overarching theme of a number of different feature proposals
over the last year or so.  In general, they have been met with skepticism,
particularly with regard to how well the features mesh with Fedora's
goals, but also in how they will change the process of building RPM
packages.  A new proposal that would allow systems to (optionally) perform remote
attestation is likewise encountering headwinds; there are several
different concerns being raised in the discussion of it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인간이 가장 쉽게 빠지는 생각의 오류 (ft. 비판적 상상력)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83410</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83410"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T23:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[앞에서 살펴본 논증의 핵심은 다음과 같다. 이 세 가지 요소만으로도 상대방을 설득하는 데 성공하는 경우도 있겠지만, 비판적으로 사고하는 사려 깊은 독자를 설득하기는 어렵다. 특히 ‘글’까지 써서 해결해야 하는 문제라면 그 자체로 복잡하고 찬반이 치열하게 엇갈리는 주제인 경우가 많기 때문에, 이 세 요소만으로 설득하는 것은 거의 불가능하다. 독자의 시선으로, 독자의 관점으로  이 때 필요한 것이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will a new standard for smart appliances matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9522</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/will-a-new-standard-for-smart-appliances-matter/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T17:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several big names in the appliance industry, including Samsung, Haier (GE Appliances), American Standard, Electrolux, Trane, and Arcelink, have banded together to create a standards organization to build a common language for smart features that will work across the participating brands. The organization is called the Home Connectivity Alliance and it hopes to have something […]
The post Will a new standard for smart appliances matter? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gentoo Linux 2021 retrospective]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880334/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880334/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T15:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gentoo Linux project looks back at
2021.



	The number of commits to the main ::gentoo repository has once more
	clearly grown in 2021, from 104507 to 126920, i.e., by 21%. While
	the number of commits by external contributors, 11775, has remained
	roughly constant, this number now distributes across 435 unique
	external authors compared to 391 last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NumPy 1.22.0 has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880332/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880332/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T14:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 1.22.0 of the NumPy scientific computing module is out.
"NumPy 1.22.0 is a big release featuring the work of 153
contributors spread over 609 pull requests. There have been many
improvements".  Those improvements include the "essentially
complete" annotation of the main namespace, a preliminary version of
the proposed Array API, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880327/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880327/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T14:31:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (salt and thunderbird), Red Hat (xorg-x11-server), and Scientific Linux (xorg-x11-server).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mimik aims to create a decentralized platform for the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9517</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/mimik-aims-to-create-a-decentralized-platform-for-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T14:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Where is the edge? If you ask different people you get very different responses. Telco executives will tell you the edge lives in their data centers at the base of cell towers or in local central offices. Factory operations folks will cite gateways inside their plants. And people like me will look to cellphones or […]
The post Mimik aims to create a decentralized platform for the edge appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[네티즌에게 보낸 JTBC ‘협박문’: ‘설강화’ 논란에 부쳐]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83400</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83400"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T09:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[낭패다. JTBC 드라마 [설강화] 논란을 두고 JTBC 측이 또 다시 입장문을 발표했다. 세 번째다. 드라마에 대한 허위사실 유포에 강력히 대응하겠다는 내용이다. 첫 방송이 끝나자마자 드라마 방영중지 국민청원과 협찬취소 불매운동에 이어 방송금지 가처분 신청까지 진행된 논란은 법원의 기각 결정으로 일단은 지켜보자는 기류로 흘러가는 듯했다. 20여 개 온라인 커뮤니티에 보낸 JTBC ‘협박문’ 그러나 방송사 측은 곧바로 “드라마 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제20대 대선과 지방 소멸의 위기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83383</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83383"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T02:23:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제20대 대통령 선거가 약 두 달 앞으로 다가왔다. 이번 선거는 팬데믹 이후 한국사회의 미래 비전을 마련해야 하는 시점에 치러지는 선거라는 점에서 어느 때보다 큰 중요성을 지닌다. 우리 사회가 직면한 위기에 대한 진단을 바탕으로 대안을 위한 치열한 토론과 논의가 본격적으로 필요한 시간이다. 더 이상 미룰 수 없는 과제 우리 사회의 긴급한 문제들의 중심에는 지방의 소멸을 초래하는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in December]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/december-2021-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/december-2021-roundup"/>
        <updated>2022-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Happy 2022 everyone! 🎉
Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
December.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN's unreliable predictions for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878573/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878573/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T23:37:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is 2022 already, and that can only mean one thing: it's time for your
editor to make a (bigger) fool of himself by posting a set of
predictions for what may come in the new year.  One should never pass up an
opportunity for a humbling experience, after all.  There can be no doubt
that interesting things will happen this year; let's see how many random
darts thrown in that direction can hit close to the mark.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[성큼 다가온 큰 정부 시대]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73980</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/01/03/biggovernment/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=biggovernment"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T22:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이코노미스트) 원문보기   작은 정부를 지향하는 고전적 자유주의자의 바람직한 자세 “정부가 얼마를 쓰고 있는지 두눈 똑바로 뜨고 지켜봅시다.” 작은 정부를 강조하는 경제학자 밀턴 프리드먼의 말입니다. 만약 프리드먼 교수가 최근 상황을 본다면 눈이 튀어나올 정도로 놀랄 것입니다. 세계 각국 정부는 코로나19 팬데믹 이후 대출과 보조금 등을 망라해 17조 달러(2경 원)나 되는 막대한 예산을 지출했습니다. 전 세계 GDP의 16%나 되는 엄청난 금액입니다. 최근 발표된 전망에 따르면, 모든 주요 선진국의 2026년 GDP 대비 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[성큼 다가온 큰 정부 시대]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73980</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/01/03/%ec%84%b1%ed%81%bc-%eb%8b%a4%ea%b0%80%ec%98%a8-%ed%81%b0-%ec%a0%95%eb%b6%80-%ec%8b%9c%eb%8c%80/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=%25ec%2584%25b1%25ed%2581%25bc-%25eb%258b%25a4%25ea%25b0%2580%25ec%2598%25a8-%25ed%2581%25b0-%25ec%25a0%2595%25eb%25b6%2580-%25ec%258b%259c%25eb%258c%2580"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T22:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이코노미스트) 원문보기   작은 정부를 지향하는 고전적 자유주의자의 바람직한 자세 “정부가 얼마를 쓰고 있는지 두 눈을 똑바로 뜨고 지켜봅시다.” 작은 정부를 강조하는 경제학자 밀턴 프리드먼의 말입니다. 만약 프리드먼 교수가 최근 상황을 본다면 눈이 튀어나올 정도로 놀랄 것입니다. 세계 각국 정부는 코로나19 팬데믹 이후 대출과 보조금 등을 망라해 17조 달러(2경 원)나 되는 막대한 예산을 지출했습니다. 전 세계 GDP의 16%나 되는 엄청난 금액입니다. 최근 발표된 전망에 따르면, 모든 주요 선진국의 2026년 GDP → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The most interesting blogs and websites for C++ developers]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0906/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0906/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Readers surely have favorite websites and blogs about C++. Hopefully, today your collection will grow.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Just Develop FOR Docker]]></title>
        <id>https://jameshunt.us/?p=431</id>
        <link href="https://jameshunt.us/writings/dont-just-develop-for-docker/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T20:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of words get written about how Docker revolutionizes delivery of the output of the software development process.  This post is not about that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Koch: A New Future for GnuPG]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880248/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880248/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T16:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Longtime GnuPG maintainer Werner Koch has posted an update on the project,
mostly focused on the new associated "GnuPG VS-Desktop" business that is,
it seems, going quite well:


  For many years our work was mainly financed by donations and smaller
  projects.  Now we have reached a point where we can benefit from a
  continuous revenue stream to maintain and extend the software without
  asking for donations or grants.  This is quite a new experience to us
  and I am actually a bit proud to lead one of the few self-sustaining
  free software projects who had not to sacrifice the goals of the
  movement.


He concludes with a request for individuals who have been donating to GnuPG
to redirect their generosity toward another deserving project.  This is
good news; GnuPG ran on a shoestring for far too long.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GIMP 2021 annual report]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880241/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880241/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T15:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GIMP project has put out a
report summarizing a year of development on this image-manipulation
application.


	With 4 development versions released already, you know that we are
	working very hard on the future: GIMP 3.0.

	Some features took a lot of time, mostly when we changed core
	logics. I am thinking in particular about the code for
	multi-selection of layers. It’s not that selecting multiple items
	in a list is hard to implement, it’s that any feature in the whole
	application has been forever expecting just one layer or one
	channel selected. So what happens when there are 2, 3 or any number
	of items selected? Every feature, every tool, every plug-in and
	filter has to be rethought for this new use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just give me buttons! Flic buttons are convenient, fun.]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9512</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/just-give-me-buttons-flic-buttons-are-convenient-fun/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T15:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early in December, I took advantage of a holiday sale to pick up a Flic hub and three accompanying buttons, for a total of $149.99 plus tax, so I could cluster some of my smart home devices into a routine that could be triggered without using my voice. Instead, I would use the Flic buttons […]
The post Just give me buttons! Flic buttons are convenient, fun. appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880232/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880232/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T13:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (thunderbird), Fedora (kernel, libopenmpt, and xorg-x11-server), Mageia (gegl, libgda5.0, log4j, ntfs-3g, and wireshark), openSUSE (log4j), and Red Hat (grafana).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which smart smoke detectors are good choices for you?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9465</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/which-smart-smoke-detectors-are-good-choices-for-you/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our most recent IoT Podcast, Duncan called in to the voicemail hotline with a question about smart smoke detectors. He’s wondering which connected detectors we would recommend. To be honest, this is an easy question. That’s mainly because there are fewer choices when it comes to smart smoke detectors compared to bulbs, switches, locks, […]
The post Which smart smoke detectors are good choices for you? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify template code with fewer typename in C++20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/less-typename-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/less-typename-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++ not only grows with cool features but also improves and makes code simpler and readable. It’s evident in template code. For example, typename inside dependent names is now much easier (not) to use.
If you have an expression like X<T>::name, should you always put typename in front?
See the full details below.



     


A few weeks ago, I experimented with a code kata and implemented a container and an iterator for “vectors of vectors.” I set the C++20 flag in Compiler Explorer wrote the code. But then I tried the C++17 flag, and I was surprised to see how much I had to add to compile it!
To simplify things, let’s look at a simple wrapper for a container class. It uses std::vector as internal storage and only exposes some essential functionality.
template <typename T>
class MyVec {
publ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Dec. 31, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9520</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-dec-31-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T04:43:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Editor’s note: This missed its scheduled publication date, so I’m publishing Sunday instead of Friday. Apologies.  Why IoT ExpressLink was the big news from AWS Re:Invent: This is a story I wanted to write based on conversations with a few IoT platform folks who build on AWS, but I never got around to it leading into […]
The post IoT news of the week for Dec. 31, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[현대전 역사상 가장 긴 포위전: 사라예보 포위전 (’92-’96)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83360</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83360"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T01:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[무슬림 인구가 많은 보스니아가 유고슬라비아로부터 독립을 선언하자 이 지역에 거주하는 기독교도 세르비아인들이 민병대를 조직하여 사라예보 주변 산악지역을 점령하고 소총, 기관총, 박격포, 대포, 로켓발사기 등을 배치한 뒤 도심을 공격하기 시작하였다. 세르비아 민병대는 군인은 물론 민간인도 보이는 대로 사살하였다. 1992년 5월 2일 시작되어 1996년 2월 29일 끝난 이 포위전은 현대전 역사상 가장 긴 포위전으로 기록되었다. 보스니아군은 끝내 세르비아 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fast kernel headers tree]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880175/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880175/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-02T23:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel developer Ingo Molnar has been quiet for a while; now we know why.
He has just announced a massive
set of patches (touching over half of the files in the kernel tree)
reworking how header files are handled.


	The fast-headers tree offers a +50-80% improvement in absolute
	kernel build performance on supported architectures, depending on
	the config. This is a major step forward in terms of Linux kernel
	build efficiency & performance.

	A justified question would be: why on Earth 2,200 commits??


It seems likely that interesting conversations will follow; stay tuned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc8]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880174/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880174/rss"/>
        <updated>2022-01-02T22:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eighth and final 5.16 kernel prepatch
is out for testing.  "Please, as you emerge from your holiday-induced
food coma, do give it a quick test so that we can all be happy about the
final release next weekend".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년]]></title>
        <id>http://wallflower.egloos.com/4204399</id>
        <link href="http://wallflower.egloos.com/4204399"/>
        <updated>2022-01-02T10:17:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다보니 2022년을 베니스에서 맞이하게 되었다. 베니스 비엔날레 전시 때문에 온 김에 쓰던 책을 마저 완성할 생각으로 볼로냐 대학에 적을 두고 1월까지 체류하기로 했다. 팬데믹 심화로 볼로냐 대학 역시 별로 갈 일이 없기에 계속 베니스에서 지내고 있다. 사실 .... 글 전체보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이택광</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spilling the Beans: storage class and linkage in C, including static locals]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33664</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/01/01/spilling-the-beans-storage-class-and-linkage-in-c-including-static-locals/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-01T19:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Spilling the Beans: C/C++ Header Files, I touched on interfaces and the difference between external and internal linkage. This article has a focus on internal linkage with using the static keyword in C. So this might be a programming language … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of reading: October - December 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/summary-of-reading-october-december-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/summary-of-reading-october-december-2021/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-01T05:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<ul class="simple">
<li>&quot;Chasing New Horizons: Inside the Epic First Mission to Pluto&quot; by Alan Stern
and David Grinspoon - a fascinating account of the New Horizons mission, told
by its principal investigator. Lots of interesting scientific and engineering
details about the mission. A good portion of the book is spent on NASA
politics …</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new protocol and tool for PNG file attachments]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/31/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/31/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T22:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When my articles include diagrams to illustrate a concept, such as a
state machine, I will check the Graphviz, gnuplot, or SVG
source into source control alongside the image in case I need to make
changes in the future. Sometimes I even make the image itself a link to
its source file. I’ve thought it would be convenient if the raster image
somehow contained its own source as metadata so that they don’t get
separated. I looked around and wasn’t satisfied with the solutions I
found, so I wrote one: pngattach.
My approach introduces a new private chunk type atCh (“attachment”)
which contains a file name, a flag to indicate if the attachment is
compressed, and an optionally DEFLATE-compressed blob of file contents. I
tried to follow the spirit of PNG chunk formatting, but without the
constrain…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME libadwaita 1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880110/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880110/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T18:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.0 of the GNOME libadwaita library is out; this will be of interest to
GNOME application developers.  "Libadwaita is a library implementing
the GNOME HIG, complementing GTK. For GTK 3 this role has increasingly been
played by Libhandy, and so Libadwaita is a direct Libhandy
successor."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: CES 2022, quantum security and lidar]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472012</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-ces-2022-quantum-security-and-lidar/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T16:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes some of the preview announcements CES 2022, plus quantum security, lidar, and our top 10 articles of 2021, plus other news and products.
The post embedded news: CES 2022, quantum security and lidar appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880100/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880100/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T14:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (agg, aria2, fort-validator, and lxml), Fedora (libgda, pgbouncer, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Mageia (calibre, e2guardian, eclipse, libtpms/swtpm, nodejs, python-lxml, and toxcore), openSUSE (c-toxcore, gegl, getdata, kernel-firmware, log4j, postrsd, and privoxy), and SUSE (gegl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantum-enhanced keys on demand add security against cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4472007</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/quantum-enhanced-keys-on-demand-add-security-against-cyberattacks/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T13:56:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new Quantum Origin platform uses the unpredictable nature of quantum mechanics to generate cryptographic keys seeded with verifiable quantum randomness.
The post Quantum-enhanced keys on demand add security against cyberattacks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silicon photonics is key to ubiquitous 3D sensing with lidar on chip]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471999</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/silicon-photonics-is-key-to-ubiquitous-3d-sensing-with-lidar-on-chip/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T12:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voyant Photonics has developed a complete lidar system in a field-deployable package, using patented techniques for on-chip digital beam steering, optical signal processing, and laser control.
The post Silicon photonics is key to ubiquitous 3D sensing with lidar on chip appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국민 76% 찬성한 언론중재법 합의도 못 이룬 미디어특위]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83355</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83355"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T08:49:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘(2021년 12월 31일, 금) 여야의 ‘언론미디어제도개선특별위원회’(이하 ‘미디어특위’)의 기존 일정이 끝난다. 미디어특위는 언론중재법 개정안, 포털 개혁 방안, 공영방송 지배구조 문제 등을 두고 논의를 이어갔으나, 촉박한 일정과 여야 정쟁구도로 인해 빈손으로 기존 종료일을 앞두고 있다. 여야가 합의를 통해 내년 5월 말까지로 활동 기한을 연장했으나, 지금과 같은 상황이라면 활동기한이 연장되었다 하더라도 제대로 된 성과도 내지 못할 것이 분명하다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ at the end of 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cpp-status-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cpp-status-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to present the 10th edition of “C++ at the end”! See what happened this year in the C++ World!
New features, plans for the language, updated tools and compilers, conferences, books, and more!
What was the most important event this year? The pandemic? C++20 adoption? Ongoing work for C++23 or something else?
Let’s have a look.
Reports from previous years: 2020,
2019,
2018,
2017,
2016,
2015,
2014,
2013,
2012.
The following companies support this year’s report:
 

 
 
 


Disclaimer: the view presented here is mine and does not represent the opinion of the ISO C++ committee, companies I work for, or sponsors.
A Brief Introduction
2021 was the full pandemic year, and we all seem to be tired, frightened, bored, or even divided (in various proportions). It looks like we have already ac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[버킷리스트는 인생의 내비게이션]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83345</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83345"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T00:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이 글은 전 편인 ‘회사 생활이 힘든 이유를 알았다’에서 이어집니다.) 휴직 기간 동안 버킷리스트 워크숍 활동 외에 캐나다 여행을 70일 동안 아이들과 함께 다녀왔다. 아이 엄마는 일 때문에 함께 할 수 없었고, 오로지 아빠와 아이들만 함께 하는 여행이었다. 코로나가 유행인 지금은 상상도 할 수 없는 일이지만 다행히 코로나가 시작되기 전이라 문제 없이 떠날 수 있었다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최호진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some sanity for C and C++ development on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/30/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/30/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T23:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hard reality of C and C++ software development on Windows is that there
has never been a good, native C or C++ standard library implementation for
the platform. A standard library should abstract over the underlying host
facilities in order to ease portable software development. On Windows, C
and C++ is so poorly hooked up to operating system interfaces that most
portable or mostly-portable software — programs which work perfectly
elsewhere — are subtly broken on Windows, particularly outside of the
English-speaking world. The reasons are almost certainly political,
originally motivated by vendor lock-in, than technical, which adds insult
to injury. This article is about what’s wrong, how it’s wrong, and some
easy techniques to deal with it in portable software.
There are multiple C impl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in PVS-Studio in 2021?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0905/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0905/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2021 is coming to an end, which means it's time to sum up the year! Today we'll tell you about the new features we added to PVS-Studio in the past year. Buckle up and let's go!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xcode의 기기 USB 연결 문제 해결하기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/how-to-fix-usb-connectivity-issue-with-xcode/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/how-to-fix-usb-connectivity-issue-with-xcode/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T19:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[iOS 앱을 개발하다보면 Xcode에서 기기를 제대로 인식하지 못해서 연결이 되었다 말았다 하는 증상을 보일 때가 있다. Xcode…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technology trends enabling demand for mass customization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471985</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/technology-trends-enabling-demand-for-mass-customization/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T17:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How will the desire for mass consumer customization impact product development and go-to-market strategies? Here are some of the trends likely to emerge in 2022 to help address this demand.
The post Technology trends enabling demand for mass customization appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LoRaWAN with NXP LPC55S16 and ARM Cortex-M33]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=34182</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/12/30/lorawan-with-nxp-lpc55s16-and-arm-cortex-m33/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T17:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LoRaWAN is getting more an more popular, both for terrestrial and increasingly with low-orbit satellite systems. The ‘Long Range’ in ‘LoRa’ makes it an ideal solution for low-power and low data rate applications. For a university research project we selected … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Zero-copy network transmission with io_uring]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879724/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879724/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T17:15:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the goal is to push bits over the network as fast as the hardware can
go, any overhead hurts.  The cost of copying data to be transmitted
from user space into the kernel can be especially painful; it adds latency,
takes
valuable CPU time, and can be hard on cache performance.  So it is
unsurprising that the developers working with io_uring, which is all about performance, have
turned their attention to zero-copy network transmission.  This
patch set from Pavel Begunkov, now in its second revision, looks to be
significantly faster than the MSG_ZEROCOPY option supported by current
kernels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3D lidar sensors deliver remote mobile surveillance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471981</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3d-lidar-sensors-deliver-remote-mobile-surveillance/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T15:38:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collaboration between Quanergy Systems and Securitas France to enable mobile remote surveillance in locations with limited infrastructure using 3D lidar technology.
The post 3D lidar sensors deliver remote mobile surveillance appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Large 3D Printed Artwork]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=12065</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2021/12/30/how-to-create-a-large-3d-printed-artwork/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T15:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently built a relatively large (100cm × 80cm) 3D printed artwork, which features a painted relief of mathematical functions. Read how I prepared the data, converted it into 3D printable tiles and converted them into printable gcode. All the images and previews are from the proof of concept I created. The final artwork is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/880039/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/880039/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T14:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (advancecomp, apache-log4j2, postgis, spip, uw-imap, and xorg-server), Mageia (kernel and kernel-linus), Scientific Linux (log4j), and SUSE (kernel-firmware and mariadb).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: As Alexa goes, so does the smart home?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9506</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-as-alexa-goes-so-does-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re back after a one-week break in the Internet of Things Podcast, and we didn’t miss too much. The biggest stories of this show are the slow collapse of CES 2022 and a Bloomberg article that uses internal Amazon documents to show how Alexa growth has stagnated and illustrates the hopes Amazon has for its […]
The post Podcast: As Alexa goes, so does the smart home? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MIPI M-PHY v5.0 doubles peak data for latest flash memory storage]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471976</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mipi-m-phy-v5-0-doubles-peak-data-for-latest-flash-memory-storage/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T12:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Latest version of MIPI M-PHY doubles potential data rate compared with previous specification to 23.32 Gbps, and is optimized for applications needing high data rates, low pin counts, lane scalability and power efficiency. 
The post MIPI M-PHY v5.0 doubles peak data for latest flash memory storage appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘포털 뉴스 편집 금지법’은 위헌이다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83339</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83339"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T10:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 12월 26일 더불어민주당과 열린민주당이 합당 선언을 하며 포털의 뉴스 편집·추천·배열 서비스를 금지하는 일명 ‘포털 뉴스 편집 금지법’을 적극 추진하기로 합의했다고 알려졌다. 사업자의 영업의 자유, 이용자의 이용권 제한  그러나 이처럼 포털의 뉴스 배열·추천 서비스를 금지하거나, 뉴스 콘텐츠는 아웃링크나 이용자 구독 형태로만 제공하도록 강제하는 내용 등, 포털 뉴스 서비스에 대한 강제 규제는 합리적 이유없이 포털과 언론사의 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대선 3분 가이드: 꼭 확인해야 할 세 가지 공약]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83323</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83323"/>
        <updated>2021-12-30T00:48:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유권자(有權者). 투표를 할 수 있는 즉 선거권을 가진 사람을 우리는 유권자로 부른다. 얼마 전 선거권이 없는 무권자(無權者)가 되었다. 이번 연재 칼럼의 명칭은 ‘유권자의 스케치북’이지만, 유권자 섭외에 실패하여 번외편으로 무권자의 대선 공약 관전기를 올린다. 비전과 공약이 중요하다 이번 대선이 70여일 앞으로 다가왔다. 하지만 한국 사회의 비전이나 정책에 대한 논의나 논쟁보다는 주요 후보자와 그 가족에 대한 의혹제기, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prediction Framework, a time saver for Data Science prediction projects]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/prediction-framework-a-time-saver-for-data-science-prediction-projects.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/prediction-framework-a-time-saver-for-data-science-prediction-projects.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T20:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Álvaro Lamas, Héctor Parra, Jaime Martínez, Julia Hernández, Miguel Fernandes, Pablo Gil
 Acquiring high value customers using predicted Lifetime Value, taking specific actions on high propensity of churn users, generating and activating audiences based on machine learning processed signals…All of those marketing scenarios require of analyzing first party data, performing predictions on the data and activating the results into the different marketing platforms like Google Ads as frequently as possible to keep the data fresh. 
Feeding marketing platforms like Google Ads on a regular and frequent basis, requires a robust, report oriented and cost reduced ETL & prediction pipeline. These pipelines are very similar regardless of the use case and it’s very easy to fall into reinventin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are fewer people chatting with Alexa?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9494</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-are-fewer-people-chatting-with-alexa/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T16:22:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart speakers with voice assistants have accomplished one key goal. At a low cost, consumers were able to bring some smarts into their homes on the cheap. And that has led to a surge in the sales of other connected devices to actually control by voice. Think how many more smart outlets, light bulbs, switches, […]
The post Why are fewer people chatting with Alexa? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last stable kernels for 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879996/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879996/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T15:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.15.12,
5.10.89,
5.4.169,
4.19.223,
4.14.260,
4.9.295, and
4.4.297
stable kernel updates have all been released.  These should be the last
updates for this year; as usual, they all contain more important fixes and
updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879995/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879995/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T14:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr, python-gnupg, resiprocate, and ruby-haml), Fedora (mod_auth_mellon), openSUSE (thunderbird), Slackware (wpa_supplicant), and SUSE (gegl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[박근혜 특별사면, ‘평가’ 대신 ‘셈법’만 가득]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83309</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83309"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T09:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정부는 12월 24일 2022년 신년 특별사면을 발표했습니다. 2021년 12월 31일 자로 중소기업인·소상공인 등 서민생계형 형사범, 특별배려 수형자, 전직 대통령 등 주요 인사, 선거사범, 사회적 갈등 사범 등 3,094명에 대한 특별사면·복권·감형을 단행한다는 내용인데요. 주요 대상자에 전직 대통령 박근혜 씨와 한명숙 전 총리 등이 올랐습니다. 가장 큰 관심을 모은 건 단연 박근혜 씨입니다. 대통령 선거를 75일 남겨둔 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이바닥늬우스의 2021년 이슈 탑10]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2863</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2021/12/29/ebadak-best-of-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T06:36:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이거 이번주면 올해가 끝나더라구요? 바쁘다는 핑계로 하라는 번역은 안하고.. 오리지널 포스트도 안쓰고.. 하다가 올해가 넘어갈 것 같아서요. 연말 이슈를 빌려 미뤄왔던 뉴스도 좀 찾아보고..? 해봤습니다. 좀 길어요?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존의 재발명, ‘AWS’ 15년 (ft. 리:인벤트 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83297</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83297"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T00:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AWS(Amazon Web Services)는 한마디로 말해서 아마존의 재발명(ReInvent)이다. 이유는 2006년 아마존의 한 부서에서 아마존 자체 웹 서비스를 사용하기 위해 아마존 S3(AWS Simple Storage Service)나 EC2(Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud)와 같은 다양한 표준 컴퓨팅 서비스를 재발명했기 때문이다. 이렇듯 클라우드 컴퓨팅의 여명으로 재발명된 AWS는 컴퓨터에 의존하는 비즈니스 경제를 근본적으로 바꿔 놓았다. 초기 인터넷 기업가들은 엔지니어링 시간과 노력의 70%를 데이터 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 bugs found in C# projects in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0904/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0904/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2021 we published several articles and showed you errors found in open-source projects. The year 2021 ends, which means it's time to present you the traditional top 10 of the most interesting bugs. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] User-managed concurrency groups]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879398/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879398/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-28T15:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's thread model is relatively straightforward and performs
reasonably well, but that's not enough for all users.  Specifically, there
are use cases out there that benefit from a lightweight threading model
that gives user space control over scheduling decisions.  Back in May 2021,
Peter Oskolkov posted a patch set implementing an abstraction known as user-managed
concurrency groups, or UMCG.  Several revisions later, many observers
still lack a clear idea of what this patch is supposed to do, much less
whether it is a good idea for the kernel.  Things have taken a turn,
though, with Peter Zijlstra's reimplementation
of UMCG.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879952/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879952/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-28T15:44:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (djvulibre, libzip, monit, novnc, okular, paramiko, postgis, rdflib, ruby2.3, and zziplib), openSUSE (chromium, kafka, and permissions), and SUSE (net-snmp and permissions).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 ‘실언’을 대하는 언론의 태도 (ft. 한경의 모른 척)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83288</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83288"/>
        <updated>2021-12-28T10:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 국민의힘 대선 후보가 잇단 실언으로 비판을 받고 있습니다. 12월 22일 전북 지역 청년과 만난 자리에서는 “극빈의 생활을 하고 배운 것이 없는 사람은 자유가 뭔지도 모를 뿐 아니라, 자유가 왜 개인에게 필요한지 필요성 자체를 느끼지를 못한다”고 했고, 다음날인 12월 23일 전남지역 선거대책위원회 출범식에선 “민주화운동 중에는, 외국에서 수입해온 이념에 사로잡혀 운동을 한 분도 있다”고 했습니다. 일부 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가치 있는 주장을 위한 세 가지 조건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83272</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83272"/>
        <updated>2021-12-28T00:35:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[모든 논증의 심장은 주장이다. 그래서 주장이 독자에게 호기심을 끌지 못한다면, 아무리 꼼꼼한 논증이라도 아무도 주목하지 않을 것이다. ‘무엇이 어떠하다’고 주장하는 것은 동시에 ‘내 주장에 관한 논증에 귀 기울일 시간을 투자하라’고 독자에게 요구하는 것이다. 따라서 주장은 독자가 동의해주기를 바라는 진술인 동시에 독자가 관심을 가질 만한, 또 관심을 가져야 한다고 생각하는 문제에 대한 해법이 되어야 한다. 서둘러 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc7]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879901/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879901/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T17:27:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc7 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Obviously the holidays are a big reason it's all small, so
it's not like this is a sign of us having found all bugs, and we'll keep at
this for at least two more weeks".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879891/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879891/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T15:20:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache-log4j2, libextractor, libpcap, and wireshark), Fedora (grub2, kernel, libopenmpt, log4j, mingw-binutils, mingw-python-lxml, and seamonkey), Mageia (golang, lapack/openblas, and samba), and openSUSE (go1.16, libaom, log4j12, logback, and runc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js 서버에서 PKCS#11 API 사용하기]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222605981842</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222605981842"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T09:04:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이번 강좌의 목적은 당사가 공급하는 HSM장비인 KeyperPlus를 가지고, Node.js 서버 환경에서, ECDSA Key를 어떤 방식으로 생성하는 지, 그리고 어떻게 Signing 하는 지를 보여 주고자 하는 것입니다. Node.js Node.js 공식 사이트에서의 설명에 의하면, Node.js는 Chrome V8 JavaScript 엔진으로 빌드된 JavaScript 런타임 이라고 합니다. JavaScript 기반으로 구성된 Server Side 서비스를 JavaScript로 구현할 수 있게 만든 런타임 입니다. pkcs11js pkcs11js는 Node.js 에서 PKCS#11 API를 사용할 수 있도록 구현한 Node.js package입니다. MIT 라이센스로 사용할 수 있는 open source 입니다. pkcs11js 는 PKCS#11 2.3 사양을 기준으로 개발.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aepkoreanet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언론의 권위는 현장에서 생긴다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83237</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83237"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T02:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“어딘가에서 수천 명에 달하는 평범한 사람이 모두 빠져나오려고 애쓰고 있는데, 정신 나간 몇몇 사람이 그곳으로 들어가려고 애쓰고 있다면, 그들은 틀림없이 기자일 것이다.” (모트 로젠블럼, Mort Rosenblum) AP 특파원은 직접 눈으로 보는 것이 직업 윤리의 핵심이고, 그렇게 기사를 써야만 정확성을 담보할 수 있으며, 그렇게 쓴 기사가 영향력을 발휘한다고 믿는다. 역사적으로 언론이 권위를 갖게 된 것은, 기자가 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded’s Top 10 Articles of 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471918</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embeddeds-top-10-articles-of-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T01:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We continue our annual look back at the year’s most-read articles. This year, articles on coding practices and the UART communications protocol share the spotlight...
The post Embedded’s Top 10 Articles of 2021 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Errors and suspicious code fragments in .NET 6 sources]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0903/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0903/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The .NET 6 turned out to be much-awaited and major release. If you write for .NET, you could hardly miss such an event. We also couldn't pass by the new version of this platform. We decided to check what interesting things we can find in the sources of .NET libraries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite musical discoveries of 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2021-music.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2021-music.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-26T16:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I listen to a lot of interesting music, so picked out my six favorite
      new-to-me albums this year. I hope you find something interesting to
      groove to in there.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McuOnEclipse Components: 26-Dec-2021 Release]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=34176</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/12/26/mcuoneclipse-components-26-dec-2021-release/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-26T10:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pleased to announce a new release of the McuOnEclipse components, available on SourceForge. This release includes several bug fixes, support for more devices, and updated components like FreeRTOS, MinINI, Percepio Tracealyzer and SEGGER SystemView. SourceForge 💡 Not using Processor … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한계 개념과 선험철학]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222605128061</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222605128061"/>
        <updated>2021-12-26T10:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[칸트에 의하면, 합리론은 독단주의이다. 그들은 경험에 의해 정당화될 수 없거나 혹은 경험과 관련을 맺지 않은 그런 주장을 한다. 비경험적, 순수이성적인, 혹은 사변적 이성에 의존하여 형이상학적 주장을 하지만, 그것은 결국 우리가 그 진리성을 믿어야 할지 의심스러운 독단적 주장에 지나지 않는다. 가령 신의 존재에 대한 데카르트의 증명이 바로 그것이다. 반면에 흄의 회의주의는 우리가 반드시 의존해야 할 어떤 선제(presupposition)들에 대해서 의심하고 부정한다. 세계에 대해 인과 관계를 주장하기 위해 우리는 인과 범주를 반드시 선제해야 하지만, 또 마찬가지로 지성 범주를 선제해야만 비로소 경험적 주장이 가능할 수 있지만.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1 동서철학의 회통(會通) 가능성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222604147443</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222604147443"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T21:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[강의한 내용을 녹음하여 그것을 책으로 만들었기 때문에, 모종삼의 <동서철학의 회통>은 약간 산만하다. 1장의 제목이 <동서철학의 회통 가능성, 철학적 진리의 보편성과 특수성>인데, 동서철학이 회통 가능하다는 것이 그의 주장이다. 그것이 서로 회통 가능한 것은 철학적 진리의 두 차원, 즉 보편성과 특수성이 있기 때문이다. 철학적 진리는 보편성으로만 성립될 수도 없고, 마찬가지로 특수성으로만 성립되지 않는다. 어떤 보편적 진리도 개인의, 혹은 문화의 생명을 통해 표현되어야 한다. 생명을 통해 표현되는 것에 바로 철학적 진리가 갖고 있는 특수성이 있다. 따라서 동일한 보편적 진리도 중국적으로 표현될 수 있고, 그.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jami "Taranis" released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879792/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879792/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T15:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Jami communication tool has released a major new stable version called "Taranis"; the blog post announcement explains: "Taranis, the Gallic and Celtic god of the sky, lightning and thunder, will be the baptismal name of this new version of Jami."  The mailing-list announcement describes the tool this way:

Jami is a GNU package for universal communication that respects the
freedom and privacy of its users.  Jami is an end-to-end encrypted
secure and distributed voice, video, and chat communication platform
that requires no central server, and leaves the power of privacy and
freedom in the hands of users.


Another recent blog post gives an overview of Jami for video conferences. The new release has improvements throughout the system, including the first phase of Swarm support, which are "fully distributed, peer-to-peer chats with conversation
    histories synchronized across your devices, and the potential to
    be expanded into group chats in upcoming future releases of Jami".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879791/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879791/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T15:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (webkit2gtk and wpewebkit), Fedora (httpd and singularity), Mageia (ldns, netcdf, php, ruby, thrift/golang-github-apache-thrift, thunderbird, and webkit2), openSUSE (go1.16, go1.17, libaom, and p11-kit), and SUSE (go1.16, go1.17, htmldoc, libaom, libvpx, logstash, openssh-openssl1, python3, and runc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darktable 3.8.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879765/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879765/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T15:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
3.8.0 of the Darktable photo-processing application has been released.
Significant changes include a new keyboard shortcut system, a new
diffuse-or-sharpen module, a new "scene-referred" blurs module "to
synthesize motion and lens blurs in a parametric and physically accurate
way", support for the Canon CR3 raw format, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: DAC and EDA trends, RISC-V reaches adolescence]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471961</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-dac-and-eda-trends-risc-v-reaches-adolescence/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T13:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes podcasts featuring interviews with Joe Sawicki of Siemens post- DAC, and a report on the RISC-V Summit plus news of products, funding and people.
The post embedded news: DAC and EDA trends, RISC-V reaches adolescence appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination NNA powers UNISOC 5G smartphone chips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471954</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/imagination-nna-powers-unisoc-5g-smartphone-chips/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T10:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination Technologies Series3NX neural network accelerator (NNA) is being used for advanced AI in UNISOC Tanggula T770 and T760 5G smartphone chips.
The post Imagination NNA powers UNISOC 5G smartphone chips appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge IoT devices will provide easier entry point for cyberattacks in 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471950</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/edge-iot-devices-will-provide-easier-entry-point-for-cyberattacks-in-2022/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T09:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More edge IoT devices gives more opportunity for cyberattacks as cybercriminals infiltrate connected systems, and devices built on legacy technology without proper security are soft targets ripe for exploitation.
The post Edge IoT devices will provide easier entry point for cyberattacks in 2022 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부당해고 피해자가 말하는 ‘싸움이 가장 힘들었을 때’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83226</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83226"/>
        <updated>2021-12-24T00:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[부당해고를 당하고 중앙노동위원회에서 (부당해고를 인정하지 않은) 서울지방노동위원회의 초심을 취소하는 판정을 받기까지 저에게는 참 기나긴 1년이었습니다. 중앙노동위원회에 재심을 청구할 지 고심할 때 거의 모든 사람이 이길 가능성이 희박하다고 저에게 말했습니다. 지난하고 고단한 싸움이 이어져 왔기에 저도 지쳐 있는 상황이었습니다. 그런데도 결국 저는 중앙노동위원회에 재심을 청구했습니다. ‘싸움’을 이어간 이유  저도 초심 취소 판정을 확신하고 재심을 청구한 것은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>청년유니온</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 250 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879739/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879739/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T23:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 250 has been released.  To say that the list of new features is
long would be a severe understatement; the developers have clearly been
busy.



	systemd-homed now makes use of UID mapped mounts for the home areas.
          If the kernel and used file system support it, files are now
          internally owned by the "nobody" user (i.e. the user typically used
          for indicating "this ownership is not mapped"), and dynamically
          mapped to the UID used locally on the system via the UID mapping
          mount logic of recent kernels. This makes migrating home areas
          between different systems cheaper because recursively chown()ing file
          system trees is no longer necessary.


(See this article for a description of
ID-mapped mounts).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How MCUs will advance endpoint intelligence over the next decade]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471946</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-mcus-will-advance-endpoint-intelligence-over-the-next-decade/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T20:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microcontrollers (MCUs) are only at the beginning of a new trend toward lower-cost, lower-power devices with AI and ML built in. Here are seven predictions of more sophisticated MCU applications in the next decade.
The post How MCUs will advance endpoint intelligence over the next decade appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carmelo Sansone, Renesas Electronics</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Krita 5.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879679/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879679/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T15:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 5.0 of
the Krita painting program has been released.
"This is a huge release, with a lot of new features and
improvements". 
Changes include a reworked
resource system, dithered gradients, faster color management, a reworked
animation subsystem, and more; see the release notes
for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chip-integrated FMCW lidar sensors deliver coherent 3D vision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471938</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/chip-integrated-fmcw-lidar-sensors-deliver-coherent-3d-vision/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T15:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New sensors are FMCW lidar transceivers featuring SiLC Technologies’ silicon photonics chip which integrates lidar functionality into a single chip.
The post Chip-integrated FMCW lidar sensors deliver coherent 3D vision appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879675/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879675/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T14:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (openjdk-11), Fedora (keepalived and tang), openSUSE (openssh, p11-kit, runc, and thunderbird), Oracle (postgresql:12, postgresql:13, and virt:ol and virt-devel:ol), Red Hat (rh-maven36-log4j12), and SUSE (ansible, chrony, logstash, elasticsearch, kafka, zookeeper, openstack-monasca-agent, openstack-monasca-persister-java, openstack-monasca-thresh, openssh, p11-kit, python-Babel, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 차별에 찬성합니다.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222602870799</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222602870799"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T07:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이미 읽었던 책인데, 요사이 오찬호의 <우리는 차별에 찬성합니다.>(2013)가 생각나서 다시 읽는다. 차별에 찬성하는 우리는 누구인가? 그들이 바로 그 당시의 20대 대학생들이다. 아마 자신이 차별 당하는 것에 찬동하지 않을 것이다. 그러나 자신보다 낮은 곳에 있는 자, 실력이 떨어지는 자, 그렇게 좋은 대학에 다니지 못하는 자, 이들에게 가해지는 차별은 당연한 것이다. 그들은 노력이 부족한 존재이며, 자기 계발을 하지 않은 존재이기에 당연하게 그 차별을 감수해야 한다. 궁금한 것이 이 진단이 여전히 지금에도 들어맞는가 하는 것이다. 소위 2030이 보여주는 정치적 경향의 밑바닥에 이 책이 진단하는 그런 모습이 존재하는 것.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 23, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878856/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878856/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T00:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 23, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[회사 생활이 힘든 이유를 알았다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83218</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83218"/>
        <updated>2021-12-23T00:36:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1편에서 이어집니다)   휴직을 하고 2019년을 시작하면서 두 명의 지인과 2박 3일의 짧은 제주 여행을 떠났다. 비장한 마음을 품고 떠난 여행이었다. 어떻게 하면 휴직 기간을 알차고 보람차게 보낼 수 있을지, 제주에서 그 답을 얻고 돌아오고 싶었다. 그래서 2박 3일 일정 안에 한라산 등반을 포함시켰다. 힘들게 산을 오르고 나면 생각도 정리되고 좋은 계획도 떠오를 것 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최호진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an app to help your community during the pandemic with Gaston Saillen #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/creating-app-to-help-your-community.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/creating-app-to-help-your-community.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T23:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
Gaston Saillen started coding for fun, making apps for his friends. About seven years ago, he began working full-time as an Android developer for startups. He built a bunch of apps—and then someone gave him an idea for an app that has had a broad social impact in his local community. Now, he is a senior Android developer at Distillery. 
 Meet Gaston Saillen, Google Developer Expert in Android and Firebase.
 

 
Building the Uh-LaLa! app
 After seven years of building apps for startups, Gaston visited a local food delivery truck to pick up dinner, and the server asked him, “Why don’t you do a food delivery ap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio checks the code of Flipper Zero dolphin]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0902/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0902/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Flipper Zero is an open-source multi-tool for geeks and penetration testers. It so happened that the Flipper Zero project and the PVS-Studio analyzer crossed paths. A philosophical question: should we check the project, if the project developers have already started fixing errors? Let's try to do this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN's 2021 retrospective]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879053/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879053/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T19:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It may have seemed questionable at times, but we have indeed survived yet
another year — LWN's 22nd year of publication.  That can only mean one
thing: it is time to take a look back at our
ill-advised attempt to make predictions in January and see how it all
worked out.  Shockingly, some of those predictions were at least partially
on the mark.  Others were ... not quite so good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A farewell to LWN]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879072/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879072/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T16:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back at the beginning of 2020, it was predicted that retirements would increase
during this decade.  In 2021, the prediction
was that retirements would increase over the next couple of years. It is
happening and LWN is no exception.  I am retiring at the end of this year
after more than 20 years with LWN.

So who am I and how did I get here?  To some, I'm a name at the bottom of
some LWN page. To a few, I'm the one that reminds them when their LWN group
subscription is about to expire. You might have even met me at a
conference. Not that I have been to very many.  Mostly I tend to be quietly
in the background watching the LWN mailbox, looking for brief items and
quotes of the week (sorry I haven't found much lately), proofreading
articles, managing subscriptions, and more. But I'm older than most of you
and this is my last LWN weekly edition.  Getting here is a bit of story.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A set of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879495/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879495/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T14:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today's stable kernel updates are
5.15.11,
5.10.88,
5.4.168,
4.19.222,
4.14.259,
4.9.294, and
4.4.296.
Each contains another set of important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879492/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879492/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T14:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (firefox, ipa, log4j, and samba), Debian (sogo, spip, and xorg-server), Fedora (jansi and log4j), Mageia (apache, apache-mod_security, kernel, kernel-linus, and x11-server), openSUSE (log4j and xorg-x11-server), Oracle (kernel, log4j, and openssl), and SUSE (libqt4 and xorg-x11-server).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT questions: multi-zone smart LED light strips, digital assistant options and Home Assistant]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9482</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-questions-multi-zone-smart-led-light-strips-digital-assistant-options-and-home-assistant/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T14:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Ken called in to our IoT voicemail hotline with three smart home questions. He wants to know what multi-zone color LED light strips we’d recommend for his house, which digital assistant he should consider, and if he should consider looking into a DIY smart home with Home Assistant. […]
The post IoT questions: multi-zone smart LED light strips, digital assistant options and Home Assistant appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CAES developing 16-core RISC-V based microprocessor for space]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471909</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/caes-developing-16-core-risc-v-based-microprocessor-for-space/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T13:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European Space Agency awards CAES project to develop the first RISC-V-based ASIC for space applications.
The post CAES developing 16-core RISC-V based microprocessor for space appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공적 의혹 vs. 사생활 루머: 김건희 씨 보도 분석]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83201</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83201"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T09:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘허위 경력’ 논란으로 윤석열 국민의힘 대선후보 배우자 김건희 씨가 연일 언론에 오르내리면서 후보 배우자 검증을 더 철저히 해야 한다는 목소리도 커지고 있습니다. 김 씨가 받고 있는 의혹을 정리하면 다음과 같습니다. 허위 경력 기재 주가조작 연루 (김 씨가 대표인 회사의) 대가성 협찬 논문 표절 모친이자 윤 후보 장모인 최 모 씨의 사문서 위조 공모 의혹  제1야당 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Locked root and rescue mode]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879272/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879272/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-22T01:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora is among the group of Linux distributions that, by default, lock
out the root account such that it does not have a password and cannot be
logged into.  But, traditionally, "rescue mode" boots the system into
single-user
mode, which requires a root password—difficult to provide if it 
does not exist.  A Fedora proposal to remove the need for the password in
that case, and just drop into a root shell, does not seem likely to go far
in that form,
but it would seem to have pointed toward some better solutions for the
underlying problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국의 ‘제한 정부’, 유럽의 ‘50%+1’ 원칙이 주는 교훈]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83185</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83185"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T23:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국은 1948년 건국 이래 1960~1961년 제2공화국을 제외하고는 대통령제를 채택해 왔다. 그동안 한국 대통령 중 다수는 비극적으로 생을 마감해 왔다. 특히 1987년 민주화 이후에도 대통령제는 큰 변화 없이 유지되었고, 역대 대통령들은 재임 이후 평안한 삶을 영위하지 못하였다. 왜 그랬으며, 앞으로는 어떨까? 지금 두 명의 주요 후보가 대권을 위해 경쟁하고 있는데, 문재인 대통령과 다음 대통령의 말로는 과연 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adopting a zero trust security model]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471895</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/adopting-a-zero-trust-security-model/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T18:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We dive into the concept of zero-trust security and discuss how you can implement it in your organization. (Source: rawpixel.com @ freepik.com) The reality of...
The post Adopting a zero trust security model appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ludovic Rembert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental problems with “traditional” power transmission]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471891</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-fundamental-problems-with-traditional-power-transmission/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T18:06:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The growth of touchless wireless power transfer is ushering in a disruptive technology for medium-range and long-range transmission. (Source: WiGL) Electrical power as we know...
The post The fundamental problems with “traditional” power transmission appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dr. Ahmad Glover and Cherif Chibane</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get started in cloud computing]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/how-to-get-started-in-cloud-computing.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/how-to-get-started-in-cloud-computing.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Google Cloud training & certifications team
 
   Validated cloud skills are in demand. With Google Cloud certifications, employers know that certified individuals have proven knowledge of various professional roles within the cloud industry.  Google Cloud certifications have also been recognized as some of the highest-paying IT certifications for the past several years. This year, the Google Cloud Certified Professional Data Engineer topped the list with an average salary of $171,749, while the Google Cloud Certified Professional Cloud Architect came in second place, with an average salary of $169,029.  
    You may be wondering what sort of background you need to take advantage of these opportunities: What sort of classes should you take? How exactly do you get started in the cl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation's report on diversity, equity, and inclusion
in open source]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879379/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879379/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T17:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux Foundation has announced
the posting of a report on its research into diversity, equity, and
inclusion in open-source communities.


The research shows that while
a majority of respondents feel welcome in open source, many in
underrepresented communities do not. We hope that the data and insights
that this project provides will be a catalyst for strengthening existing
DEI initiatives and creating new ones.


The full report can be downloaded from this page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879360/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879360/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T15:42:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (log4j), openSUSE (chromium, log4j, netdata, and nextcloud), Oracle (kernel and kernel-container), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, log4j, openssl, postgresql:12, postgresql:13, and virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel), Slackware (httpd), SUSE (xorg-x11-server), and Ubuntu (firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avular debuts modular mobile robotics hardware and software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471882</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/avular-debuts-modular-mobile-robotics-hardware-and-software/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T15:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile robotics company offers modular hardware and software solution providing the building blocks for a robot’s core functionalities, to simplify robot development.
The post Avular debuts modular mobile robotics hardware and software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fi collar is what you get the dog who has everything]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9490</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/the-fi-collar-is-what-you-get-the-dog-who-has-everything/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T14:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve spent the last few weeks testing a connected dog collar called Fi, and have found it more fun than necessary for my senior dog, but I could easily imagine paying for the collar and the $99 annual subscription fee back when she was young and prone to escape. The collar costs $149 and tracks […]
The post The Fi collar is what you get the dog who has everything appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memfault partners with Silicon Labs for IoT device diagnostics in cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471875</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/memfault-partners-with-silicon-labs-for-iot-device-diagnostics-in-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T13:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memfault and Silicon Labs improve IoT development and operations with embedded observability, debugging and device diagnostics in the cloud.
The post Memfault partners with Silicon Labs for IoT device diagnostics in cloud appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[냉소적인 방관자 ‘독자’ 설득하기: 실용 논증과 개념 논증]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83173</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83173"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T11:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[글을 쓸 시간이 없거나 직접 만나서 이야기해야 할 때는 얼굴을 마주보며 논증할 수 있을 것이다. 하지만 설득하고자 하는 상대를 직접 만날 수 없을 때, 논증을 펼치기 위해 먼저 설계하고 검토할 시간이 필요할 때, 상대방이 논증을 검토할 시간을 요구할 때는 글로써 논증해야 한다. 하지만 논증 ‘글’이 제공하는 효용은 이보다 훨씬 크다. 논증 글을 쓰는 것은 비판적 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[석궁과 죽창]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222601097601</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222601097601"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T08:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘광주 민주화 운동’이지만, 나는 ‘광주 사태’라는 명칭으로 그 소식을 처음 들었다. 그 당시 대통령이었던 최규화의 사진이 근엄한 표정으로 TV 화면에서 같은 소리만 반복하고 있었다. 대학은 폐쇄되고, 대학에 탱크 혹은 장갑차가 진주했고, 학교 정문에는 총을 든 공수부대인가 하여튼 군인들이 지키고 있었다. 그러나 그들이 이렇게 할 수 있는 정당성이 있는가? 신문은 검열을 당해 허옇게 나온 부분도 있었지만, 박정희 치하를 겪은 사람들에게 군인들이 전면에 나선다는 것 자체가 무엇을 의미하는지 아주 분명했다. 광주 시민들이 심심해서 총을 들었겠는가? 세월이 흘러 이 시대를 경험하지 못한 어떤 밥통들은 그들을 폭도라고 조.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[올해 가장 잘한 일]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=82214</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/82214/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T03:11:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[별로 성과도 없이 바쁜 한해였기에 블로그에 글을 많이 남길 수 없었다. 비즈니스적으로는 그저 그런 한 해였지만, 올해 그나마 성과가 있다면 칼맑스의 자본론을 3권까지 완독한 것, 그리고 그에 이어서 루돌프힐퍼딩의 금융자본을 읽고 있다는 것(자본론을 다 읽고 나면 당연히 논리의 흐름이 금융자본주의로 이어져야 할 것 같기에 읽고 있는데 그런 심증이 더 깊어진다), 비틀즈 모든 앨범을 들은 것, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Content blockers and Chrome's Manifest V3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879063/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879063/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-21T01:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A clarion call from the Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) warning about upcoming changes to the Chrome
browser's extension API was not the first such—from the EFF or from
others.  The time of the switch to Manifest
V3, as the new API is known, is growing closer; privacy advocates are
concerned that it will preclude a number of techniques that browser
extensions use for features like ad and tracker blocking.  Part of the
concern stems from the fact that Google is both the developer of a popular
web browser and the operator of an enormous advertising network so its
incentives seem, at least, plausibly misaligned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto at Congress: ‘Watershed’ Moment for Regulation and Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2835</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/crypto-at-congress-watershed-moment-for-regulation-and-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T21:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to 16 Minutes, our podcast where we discuss tech trends in the news and their impact on the long arc of innovation. Today’s topic is crypto regulation, and specifically, two recent federal government hearings in the news that were focused on crypto and therefore the related trend of web3. In contrast to the model... Read More
The post Crypto at Congress: ‘Watershed’ Moment for Regulation and Web3 appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomicah Tillemann and Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 bugs found in C++ projects in 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0901/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0901/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's freezing outside, everyone has already decorated the Christmas tree and bought tangerines. New Year is coming! So, it's time to meet the Top 10 interesting bugs found by the PVS-Studio C++ analyzer in 2021.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware The CopyLEFT Trolls (Techdirt)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879263/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879263/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T20:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Techdirt looks
at the problem of copyleft trolls, and those who target users of
Creative Commons materials in particular.


	However, in the end, they are still licenses, and those licenses
	are still backed by copyright -- which means that if you don't
	abide by the specifics of the Creative Commons license, you could
	very much be liable for copyright infringement. Enter the copyleft
	trolls. They search for those using CC-licensed works, but not
	following the exact terms of the license, and then resort to the
	typical copyright troll shakedown game.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doubling the performance of NXP LPC845 with improved Flash Access Time]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33724</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/12/20/doubling-the-performance-of-nxp-lpc845-with-improved-flash-access-time/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For more than two years I’m using the NXP LPC845 in my university courses. Beside of that it is used in many projects. First, because the LPC845-BRK board is small, breadboard friendly and inexpensive. Second, for many small projects that … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Growing as a Technologist in Shanghai with Google Developer Groups]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/growing-with-gdg-in-shanghai.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/growing-with-gdg-in-shanghai.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Shen, Regional Lead for Mainland China Developer Communities
          
Every developer’s path to pursuing a career in tech can be traced back to a single moment. Such is the case for Ning Zhang, a developer from China, who found his early interest in web development as a high schooler at the age of fifteen. Ning built his first website for his English class to help his classmates succeed with their studies. He didn’t realize it at the time, but he was only just getting started. Throughout high school, he played with Google Webmaster Tools (now Google Search Console) and Google Adsense to create and manage numerous other websites for fun. Like so many aspiring developers before him, Ning knew he’d found his passion, but the path ahead remained unclear. 

Enter Google Develo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resiliency and electrification will drive smart energy]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9487</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/resiliency-and-electrification-will-drive-smart-energy/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T14:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After years of lackluster starts in what I think of as the internet of electricity, we might be at an inflection point thanks to the very real perils of climate change. For at least a decade, companies and energy experts have envisioned a future where the electrical grid responds to market and demand signals to ultimately […]
The post Resiliency and electrification will drive smart energy appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879228/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879228/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T14:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache-log4j2, firefox-esr, libssh2, modsecurity-apache, and tang), Fedora (lapack, log4j, rust-libsqlite3-sys, rust-rusqlite, xorg-x11-server, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Mageia (bind, botan2, chromium-browser-stable, dovecot, hiredis, keepalived, log4j, matio, mediawiki, olm, openssh, pjproject, privoxy, vim, and watchdog), openSUSE (barrier, nim, and python-pip), Oracle (ipa and samba), Scientific Linux (ipa and samba), SUSE (log4j), and Ubuntu (apache-log4j2, htmldoc, python3.6, python3.7, python3.8, and python3.8, python3.9).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[실용적 인간학과 도덕 형이상학]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222600220738</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222600220738"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T09:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 공자는 충서(忠恕) 혹은 서(恕)에 대해서 말한다. 나는 서(恕)를 ‘배려의 명령’이라고 이해한다. 네가 하기 싫은 것은 남에게 강요하지 말라. 나는 공자가 강조한 이 명령이 도덕적으로 당연한 명령이라고 생각하지만, 그것에 대한 비판도 있다. 가령 내가 도덕적으로 사는 것이 싫은 경우, 그것을 남에게 강요하지 않아야 한다. 그러나 이러한 비판은 서(恕)를 문맥에서 떨어 뜨린 채 글자 그대로 이해한 것이라고 생각한다. 진정한 인간 혹은 인(仁)에 대해서 말하고 있는 공자의 관점에서 서(恕)는 도덕적, 인간적 관점에서 네가 하기 싫은 것은 남에게 강요하지 말아야 한다는 도덕적 명령이다. (2) 박이문은 <<논어>의 논리.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ in 2021 - Survey]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cpp21-survey/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cpp21-survey/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s almost the end of the year! As usual, I started writing my “year” summary that I will publish on the 31st of December.
Yet, this article won’t be possible without your input!
I have a survey with just nine questions about C++ and your experience in 2021.
Questions:
C++ Standard used
Your experience with C++17, C++20
Compiler used
IDE and tools
Best thing that happened
It should take no more than 5 minutes :)
Please note that this survey is not an official ISO C++ survey. It’s solely for the blog.
Giveaway
There’s also a giveaway for those of you who take part in the survey! I have 5x Amazon.com gift cards, 10$ Each, selected randomly. See at the end of the survey how to enter and get a chance to win.
The Survey
Here’s the link to Google Forms: C++ in 2021 Survey.
Or click below:

It’s valid till 28th December (I need a couple of days to process it and publish the final blog post).
Thank you!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[취재원의 여섯 가지 유형]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83151</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83151"/>
        <updated>2021-12-20T01:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[많은 기자들이 취재 능력은 ‘취재원’에 의해 결정된다고 말한다. 좋은 취재원을 확보할 수 있는 힘은 바로 ‘근성’이라고 AP 특파원 캐시 개넌(Cathy Ganon)은 말한다. 정부의 최고지도자에서 부족 마을에 사는 아이들까지, 로마 교황청에서, 탈레반까지, 세계 곳곳에 개넌의 취재원이 있다. “나는 집요하게 물고 늘어져요. 늘 현장에 있죠. 사람들을 만나 상황이 어떤지, 어떻게 생각하는지 물어보죠. 별다른 취재거리가 없을 때도 그래요. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc6]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879158/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879158/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-19T23:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc6 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	Regardless of what happens, I will be making an rc8 - not because
	this release looks particularly problematic, but simply due to the
	seasonal holidays. There's no point in releasing a final 5.16 and
	opening the merge window when people are still on holiday or just
	coming back. So we'll have at least one extra week of rc this
	release, even if no nasty issues appear.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[매년 안 맞아도 되는 독감 백신 만들 수 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73949</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/12/19/npc_fluvaccine/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_fluvaccine"/>
        <updated>2021-12-19T20:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 백신 이전에도 현대 의학과 공중보건에서 백신은 수많은 목숨을 구했습니다. 대표적인 것이 매년 추워지기 전에 맞는 독감(influenza) 백신이죠.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key-Value pairs in FLASH Memory: file-system-less minINI]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=34100</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/12/19/key-value-pairs-in-flash-memory-file-system-less-minini/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-19T11:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many embedded systems application need to store some kind of data in a persistent way: calibration values, settings or log information. For a smaller amount of data, using an external memory or file system is an overkill. In many system … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대단한 철학자 모종삼]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598995619</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598995619"/>
        <updated>2021-12-18T19:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[모종삼이 대단한 철학자이다. 아마 그는 근현대 중국철학의 최고봉일 것이다. 내가 묻는다. 무엇이 그렇게 대단한가? 그가 모종삼의 학문적 이력에 대해서 쭉 설명해 준다. 그러나 그런 발생적, 학술적 배경이 중요한 것이 아니다. 그의 개인적 학술적 과거가 중요한 것이 아니다. 그가 <논리철학논고>를 번역했고, 칸트의 저술을 번역했다는 것은 그의 번역적 공헌을 말하는 것이지, 그의 철학적이며 학문적 성취에 대해서 이야기해 주는 것이 아니다. 내가 듣고 싶은 것은 다음과 같은 것이다. 도대체 그가 무엇을 주장했는가? 그리고 그 주장이 가진 철학적 의의에 대해서 이야기해야 그의 철학적 독창성이나 가치에 대해서 말할 수 있.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전기 하이데거의 언어철학 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598578169</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598578169"/>
        <updated>2021-12-18T06:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[게오르크 W. 베르트람의 <언어, 의미, 그리고 철학>은 <언어철학에서 해석학적 전회>라는 제목으로 헤르더와 하이데거의 언어철학을 이야기하고 있다. 베르트람에 의하면 ‘해석학적 전회’의 가장 분명한 특성이 반심리주의이다. 베르트람에 의하면, 정신은 언어와 상관없이 구성되어 있다는 주장이 심리주의의 주장이다. 해석학적 전회가 주장하는 반심리주의는 언어와 정신 사이에 근본적 연관이 있다는 주장이다. 즉 <화자의 정신에 들어 있는 표상들이 곧 언어적 표현의 의미가 아니다.> 베르트람은 콩디약에 대한 헤르더의 비판에서 볼 수 있는 반심리주의를 다음처럼 요약한다. <콩디약은 언어는 정신적 방식으로 세.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The container throttling problem]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/cgroup-throttling/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/cgroup-throttling/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an excerpt from an internal document David Mackey and I co-authored in April 2019. The document is excerpted since much of the original doc was about comparing possible approaches to increasing efficency at Twitter, which is mostly information that's meaningless outside of Twitter without a large amount of additional explanation/context.
At Twitter, most  CPU bound services start falling over at around 50% reserved container CPU utilization and almost all services start falling over at not much more CPU utilization even though CPU bound services should, theoretically, be able to get higher CPU utilizations. Because load isn't, in general, evenly balanced across shards and the shard-level degradation in performance is so severe when we exceed 50% CPU utilization, this makes the prac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[뉴욕타임스 올해의 인물 이름 맞히기 퀴즈]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73931</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/12/17/nyt2021notablepeople/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nyt2021notablepeople"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T22:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 주로 글을 쓰느라 하반기에는 뉴스페퍼민트에 많은 글을 올리지 못했습니다. 그와 관련해서는 조만간 새로운 글 업로드 방침을 공지할 계획입니다. 조금만 기다려주시기를 부탁드리며, 연말을 맞아 뉴욕타임스가 꼽은 올해의 인물 이름 맞히기 퀴즈 함께 풀어보시죠. 퀴즈 풀기 점수가 너무 낮을까봐 걱정하시는 분들을 위해 부끄럽지만, 제 점수를 공개합니다. (퀴즈를 푸실 분은 먼저 퀴즈부터 풀고 봐주세요!)         저는 특히 문화예술계 유명인을 거의 못 맞혔습니다. 정치 뉴스만 주로 보는 편식이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for December 17, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9480</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-december-17-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T21:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Radar-based health monitoring startup scores $10M: Toronto-based Xandar Kardian has closed a $10 million Series A funding round led by Phoenix Venture Partners, Portfolia Active Aging & Longevity Fund, and Taronga Ventures after a busy year for the startup. Xandar Kardian, which I profiled back in February, makes a device that uses radar to monitor patients’ breathing rates and heartbeats, […]
The post IoT news of the week for December 17, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCompris Releases Version 2.0 (KDE.news)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879058/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879058/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T19:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time for the upcoming holidays, "KDE's educational suite of more than 170 activities and pedagogical games", GCompris, has released version 2.0.  It includes new and updated games and activities, including:

Getting back to numeracy activities, GCompris 2.0 includes a wide range of activities that mimic basic manipulation math games, allowing young players to experiment with elements, grouping them in sets of up to ten items. This helps them build a clear concept of the decimal system, and, as with many GCompris activities, an educator can gradually increase the difficulty level, allowing the activities to be used with children of ages between 3 and 10. Once they grasp the concept of the decimal system, the addition and subtraction activities, also based on math manipulation, help practice arithmetic.

Along with other classics, like chess, align four, and checkers, fans of strategy games will enjoy Oware, a game that requires forethought and, again, numeracy skills. Oware is originally a traditional African pastime and can be played against a friend or against Tux, offering unlimited hours of fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Impact of Apache Log4j Vulnerability (Google)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879052/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879052/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Security Blog looks
into the ripple effects of the Log4j vulnerability.


	Most artifacts that depend on log4j do so indirectly. The deeper
	the vulnerability is in a dependency chain, the more steps are
	required for it to be fixed. The following diagram shows a
	histogram of how deeply an affected log4j package (core or api)
	first appears in consumers dependency graphs. For greater than 80%
	of the packages, the vulnerability is more than one level deep,
	with a majority affected five levels down (and some as many as nine
	levels down). These packages will require fixes throughout all
	parts of the tree, starting from the deepest dependencies first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] SA_IMMUTABLE and the hazards of messing with signals]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878768/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878768/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some parts of the kernel where even the most experienced and
capable developers fear to tread; one of those is surely the code that
implements signals.  The nature of the signal API almost guarantees that
any implementation will be full of subtle interactions and complexities,
and the version in Linux doesn't disappoint.  So the inclusion of a
signal-handling change late in the 5.16 merge window might have been
expected to have the potential for difficulties; it didn't disappoint
either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Work is Not Corporate — It’s DAOs and Crypto Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2769</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-future-of-work-daos-crypto-networks/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T16:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the future, it’s likely that the average person will not work for a company. Instead, people will earn income in non-traditional ways by taking actions such as playing games, learning new skills, creating art, or curating content. This kind of shift in how we work is not unusual or unexpected — the idea that... Read More
The post The Future of Work is Not Corporate — It’s DAOs and Crypto Networks appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schecter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.15.10, 5.10.87, and 5.4.167]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879022/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879022/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T15:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 5.15.10, 5.10.87, and 5.4.167 stable kernels.  These are fairly
small updates, but, unlike yesterday's single
self-test bug fix updates, do contain important fixes throughout the tree; users
should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879020/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879020/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T14:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel), Fedora (dr_libs, libsndfile, and podman), openSUSE (fetchmail, log4j, log4j12, logback, python3, and seamonkey), Oracle (go-toolset:ol8, idm:DL1, and nodejs:16), Red Hat (go-toolset-1.16 and go-toolset-1.16-golang, ipa, rh-postgresql12-postgresql, rh-postgresql13-postgresql, and samba), Slackware (xorg), SUSE (log4j, log4j12, and python3), and Ubuntu (apache-log4j2 and openjdk-8, openjdk-lts).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXPLIoT Named IoT Security Champion Award Winner 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21439</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/expliot-named-iot-security-champion-award-winner-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T09:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pictured (left to right): Tom White Paratus People, Jenny Devoy IoTSF, John Moor IoTSF & Piers Linney, Guest Speaker  EXPLIoT has been announced as the 2021 IoT Security Champion of the Year by the IoT Security Foundation The award was presented by business entrepreneur and "Dragon's Den" star Piers Linney at the TechWorks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>-</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[차별금지법 제안 14년, 무슨 논의가 더 필요한가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83145</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83145"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T08:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“충분한 논의와 국민적 합의에 이르러야 한다는데 전적으로 동의한다. 우리사회가 앞으로 가야 할 방향을 잡는 지침 같은 것이라서 일방통행식의 처리는 바람직하지 않다. 이 문제는 우리 사회구성원들의 높은 시민의식에 기초해 왜곡되거나 잘못된 적용을 배제하고, 이 문제에 대해서 충분한 논의와 토론을 통해 얼마든지 사회적 합의에 이를 수 있다.” “헌법 정신에 따라 모든 영역에 있어서 차별이 없어야 한다는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[하고 싶은 일 100가지 쓰기, 버킷리스트를 만나다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83129</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83129"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T00:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“과장님은 왜 그렇게 회사 생활을 힘들어하세요?”  지금으로부터 6, 7년 전, 직장 생활에서 큰 고비를 마주한다는 10년 차 때의 일이다. 막 과장으로 진급했을 때였다. 오랜 대리 딱지를 떼고, 바라던 승진도 했는데 마냥 기쁘지만 않았다. 누군가에게는 배부른 소리처럼 들릴 수도 있겠지만, 당시 나는 회사 생활이 너무 힘겨웠다. 입사 후 처음으로 맛본 승진의 기쁨이었는데 허무하다는 생각밖에 들지 않았다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최호진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1000 eyes that don't want to check open-source code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0900/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0900/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a myth that open-source software is better and safer that the closed one. This was reasonably questioned many times. People regularly find epic vulnerabilities in the open source code. These vulnerabilities have been there for a long time. I think the project quality depends on how the development managers arrange the process and what methodologies/tools are used. It has nothing to do with the project being open source or closed source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fostering an inclusive tech community with Evelyn Mendes #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/iamagde-evelyn-mendes.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/iamagde-evelyn-mendes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T19:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
  
Evelyn Mendes, the first transgender Google Developer Expert, is based in Porto Alegre, Brazil, and has worked in technology since 2002. “I've always loved technology!” she exclaims, flashing a dazzling smile. As a transgender woman, Evelyn faced discrimination in the tech world in Brazil and relied on her friends for emotional support and even housing and food, as she fought for a job in technology. Her excruciating journey has made her a tireless advocate for diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI), as she works toward her vision of a world of empathy, acceptance, and love. 
Meet Evelyn Mendes, Google De…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878897/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878897/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T18:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.15.9, 5.10.86, and 5.4.166 stable kernels have been
released. "Only change here is a permission setting of a netfilter
selftest file. 
No need to upgrade if this problem is not bothering you."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Assistant Recap]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/2021-assistant-recap.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/2021-assistant-recap.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jessica Dene Earley-Cha, Mike Bifulco and Toni Klopfenstein, Developer Relations Engineers for Google Assistant
 We've reached the end of the year - and what a year it's been! Between all of our live (virtual) events including I/O, developer summits, meetups and more, there are a lot of highlights for App Actions, Smart Home Actions and Conversational Actions. Let's dive in and take a look.  

App Actions
 App Actions allows developers to extend their Android App to Google Assistant. App Actions integrates more cleanly with Android using new Android platform features. With the introduction of the beta shortcuts.xml configuration resource, expanding existing Android features and our latest Google Assistant Plug App Actions is moving closer to the Android platform. 
App Actions Ben…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Lessons from Log4j]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878570/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878570/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T16:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, most readers will likely have seen something about the Log4j 
vulnerability that has been making life miserable for system administrators
since its disclosure on December 9.  This bug is relatively easy to
exploit, results in remote code execution, and lurks on servers all across
the net; it is not hyperbolic to call it one of the worst vulnerabilities
that has been disclosed in some years.  In a sense, the lessons from Log4j
have little new to teach us, but this bug does highlight some problems in
the free-software ecosystem in an unambiguous way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come for the Tool, Stay for the Exchange: Bootstrapping Liquidity in the Private Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2742</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/liquidity-private-market-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 20 years, there has been a dramatic shift in capital flow from the public to private markets. Since 2000, private market assets have grown over 10 times, representing over $6 trillion globally. This trend has been driven by a variety of factors, including low interest rates, companies staying private longer, the need... Read More
The post Come for the Tool, Stay for the Exchange: Bootstrapping Liquidity in the Private Markets appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Haber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878844/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878844/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T14:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache-log4j2 and mediawiki), Fedora (libmysofa, libolm, and vim), Oracle (httpd), Red Hat (go-toolset:rhel8), and Ubuntu (apache-log4j2 and mumble).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Smart homes in the metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9476</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-smart-homes-in-the-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T14:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when the smart home meets the metaverse? We talk about the potential for better user interfaces and home mapping if we build digital twins of the home in a metaverse, while also discussing the potential of UWB to expand the amount of information contained in that digital twin. Then we discuss an excellent […]
The post Podcast: Smart homes in the metaverse appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 16, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878143/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878143/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T01:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 16, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크로소프트의 메타버스 전략 (ft. 팀즈용 메시)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83113</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83113"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T01:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나 대유행 이후에 새로운 트렌드를 이끌어 가기 위해 요즘 빅테크 IT 기업들은 너나 할 것 없이 ‘메타버스’를 각자 관점으로 바라보고 있다. 마이크로소프트 역시 어느 기업 못지 않게 메타버스에 투자하고 있다. 특히, 지난 10월에 진행했던 마이크로소프트 이그나이트 개발자 행사에서 ‘위드 코로나’ 시대에 사람들이 어떻게 업무 생산성에 재미있게 높일 수 있을지 보여줬다. 이것은 페이스북이 메타버스에 대한 미래를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Wrangling the typing PEPs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878675/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878675/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T00:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When last we looked in on the great typing PEP
debate for Python, back in August, two PEPs were still being
discussed as alternatives for handling annotations in the language.
The steering council was considering the issue after deferring on a
decision for the Python 3.10 release, but the question has been
deferred again for Python 3.11.  More study is needed and the council
is looking for help from the Python community to guide its
decision.  In the meantime, though, discussion about the deferral has led
to the understanding that annotations are not a general-purpose feature,
but are only meant for typing information.  In addition, there is a growing
realization that typing information is effectively becoming mandatory
for Python libraries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹이 테크 산업을 어떻게 바꾸고 있는가?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73915</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/12/15/how-the-pandemic-has-changed-the-weather-in-the-technology-industry/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-the-pandemic-has-changed-the-weather-in-the-technology-industry"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T22:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이코노미스트) 원문보기   클라우드, 하드웨어, 경쟁이라는 세 가지 변화가 테크 산업을 강타했습니다. 최근 테크 업계가 연일 호황입니다. 지난 2분기 실적 하락에 따른 우려는 3분기 실적 발표를 계기로 사라졌습니다. 구글(Google)의 모회사인 알파벳(Alphabet), 아마존(Amazon), 페이스북(Facebook), 애플(Apple), 마이크로소프트(Microsoft) 등 서부의 5대 빅테크의 실적이 급증했습니다. GAFAM이라 불리는 다섯 기업의 매출은 지난 해 3분기보다 40% 증가했고, 이익은 90%나 뛰었습니다. S&P 500 정보통신(IT) 지수는 연일 신고가를 기록하며 상승하고 있습니다. 그러나 최근 실적이 정점이라고 보는 전문가들도 많습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹이 테크 산업을 어떻게 바꾸고 있는가?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73915</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/12/15/%ed%8c%ac%eb%8d%b0%eb%af%b9%ec%9d%b4-%ed%85%8c%ed%81%ac-%ec%82%b0%ec%97%85%ec%9d%84-%ec%96%b4%eb%96%bb%ea%b2%8c-%eb%b0%94%ea%be%b8%ea%b3%a0-%ec%9e%88%eb%8a%94%ea%b0%80/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=%25ed%258c%25ac%25eb%258d%25b0%25eb%25af%25b9%25ec%259d%25b4-%25ed%2585%258c%25ed%2581%25ac-%25ec%2582%25b0%25ec%2597%2585%25ec%259d%2584-%25ec%2596%25b4%25eb%2596%25bb%25ea%25b2%258c-%25eb%25b0%2594%25ea%25be%25b8%25ea%25b3%25a0-%25ec%259e%2588%25eb%258a%2594%25ea%25b0%2580"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T22:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이코노미스트) 원문보기   클라우드, 하드웨어, 경쟁이라는 세 가지 변화가 테크 산업을 강타했습니다. 최근 테크 업계가 연일 호황입니다. 지난 2분기 실적 하락에 따른 우려는 3분기 실적 발표를 계기로 사라졌습니다. 구글(Google)의 모회사인 알파벳(Alphabet), 아마존(Amazon), 페이스북(Facebook), 애플(Apple), 마이크로소프트(Microsoft) 등 서부의 5대 빅테크의 실적이 급증했습니다. GAFAM이라 불리는 다섯 기업의 매출은 지난 해 3분기보다 40% 증가했고, 이익은 90%나 뛰었습니다. S&P 500 정보통신(IT) 지수는 연일 신고가를 기록하며 상승하고 있습니다. 그러나 최근 실적이 정점이라고 보는 전문가들도 많습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20: linker surprised by four lines of code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0899/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0899/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you are a student learning modern C++ features. And you have to complete a task concerning concepts/constraints. The teacher, of course, knows the proper way to do it – but you don't. You've already written spaghetti code that does not work. (And you keep adding more and more overloads and templates specializations to solve escalating compiler claims).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mold (linker) 1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878759/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878759/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.0 of the mold linker has been released.


	mold 1.0 is the first stable and production-ready release of the
	high-speed linker. On Linux-based systems, it should "just work" as
	a faster drop-in replacement for the default GNU linker for most
	user-land programs. If you are building a large executable which
	takes a long time to link, mold is worth a try to see if it can
	shorten your build time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve seen the future of the UWB smart home and I want it now]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9468</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/ive-seen-the-future-of-the-uwb-smart-home-and-i-want-it-now/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine using a single app to control everything in your smart home. I don’t mean the apps of today which show your devices in groups or rooms. I’m talking about a context-aware interface that intelligently surfaces a specific device, and its controls when you point your phone at it. That’s the future of the smart […]
The post I’ve seen the future of the UWB smart home and I want it now appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Idea to Impact: How a team from Solution Challenge launched an environmentally-focused social enterprise]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/from-idea-to-impact-how-a-team-from-solution-challenge.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/from-idea-to-impact-how-a-team-from-solution-challenge.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T16:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Merve Isler, Regional Developer Relations Community Manager, Turkey
                
Some challenges affect everyone regardless of borders or nationality, and combating climate issues is no different. Aysu Keçeci, a student in Turkey with an avowed reverence for the sea, found herself increasingly distressed by the growing amount of plastic in the world’s oceans. She notes, “As an Aegean, the seas are a big part of my life, Unfortunately, I have grown up observing that our waters are polluted daily, and I know that plastics now make up 80% of marine garbage, and if we don't take precautions, there will be more plastic in our seas than fish in 2050. That's why plastic pollution has always been a problem I wanted to address.” 
As part of a global community, Google Developer Student…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878749/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878749/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T16:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (libopenmpt), openSUSE (icu.691, log4j, nim, postgresql10, and xorg-x11-server), Red Hat (idm:DL1), SUSE (gettext-runtime, icu.691, runc, storm, storm-kit, and xorg-x11-server), and Ubuntu (xorg-server, xorg-server-hwe-18.04, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the advice process works in practice]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#HowThisTypicallyWorksInPractice</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#HowThisTypicallyWorksInPractice"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew finishes his article on how to scale software architecture by
      looking at how this technique works in practice, and also outlines how
      things can go wrong.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selecting the right software defined radio solution for your application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471871</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/selecting-the-right-software-defined-radio-solution-for-your-application/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T13:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SDRs are available in a wide range of performance, form factor and cost, so choosing the right SDR for your application can be a challenge....
The post Selecting the right software defined radio solution for your application appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon McHugh and Kaue Morcelles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘승무원 룩북’ 성상품화가 문제? 편승하는 언론이 더 문제!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83108</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83108"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T10:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국경제가 12월 13일 오전 [“속옷부터 보정 없이…” 승무원 룩북 영상, 성상품화 논란[영상] ] (김소연 기자)을 보도했습니다. 한 유튜버가 채널에 승무원 유니폼을 착용하는 영상을 올렸는데, 선정적이라 성상품화 논란이 일고 있다는 기사입니다. 한국경제 보도 이후, 다른 언론도 앞다퉈 ‘승무원 룩북 영상으로 성상품화 논란이 일고 있다’는 기사를 내놨습니다. 그런데 이런 언론보도가 오히려 해당 유튜브 영상을 더욱 확산시키고 있습니다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["충청의 아들" "강릉의 외손" 지역주의 조장 그만하시라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83101</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83101"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T09:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제20대 대통령선거가 90일도 채 남지 않았습니다. 그러나 후보별 정책을 집중 조명하고 평가하는 보도는 찾아보기 힘듭니다. 대신 후보들이 유권자 표심을 잡기 위해 전국 각지를 방문해 내놓는 발언을 보도의 주된 내용으로 삼고 있습니다. 그중에서도 선거철만 다가오면 어김없이 등장하는 보도가 있습니다. 바로 후보 연고와 지연을 강조하는 보도입니다. ‘지연 강조’ 보도가 늘고 있다 민주언론시민연합은 대통령선거 D-100인 11월 29일부터 12월 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter: Bridge for Non-Matter Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d3b7f003a004</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-bridge-for-non-matter-devices-d3b7f003a004?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T06:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shu Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kdenlive 21.12 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878696/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878696/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T23:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
21.12 of the Kdenlive video editor is out.


	The last and most exciting release of Kdenlive this year is out and
	brings long awaited features like Multicam Editing and Slip
	trimming mode, all of which drastically improve your editing
	workflow.  This version also comes with a new deep-learning based
	tracking algorithm, an auto-magical noise reduction filter and
	support for multiple Project Bins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Adding fs-verity support for Fedora 36?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878281/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878281/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T22:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding fs-verity file-integrity information
to RPM packages for Fedora 36 is the 
topic of a recent discussion on the Fedora devel mailing list.  The feature
would provide a means to install files from RPM packages as read-only files
that cannot be read or otherwise operated on if the data in the files changes
at any point.  The proposal is mostly about making the plumbing available
for use cases that are not particularly clear—which has led to some
questions and skepticism among those participating in the thread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving accurate low-power validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471900</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/achieving-accurate-low-power-validation/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T19:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing the right tool to measure low power leads to more accurate power validation, which, in turn, enhances product performance. In an increasingly connected world, electronic devices are becoming...
The post Achieving accurate low-power validation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Hall, Macarena Calderon, Mike Denton and Paul Ulezko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promote your Google Workspace Marketplace apps with the new badge for developers]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/promote-your-google-workspace-marketplace-apps.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/promote-your-google-workspace-marketplace-apps.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Elena Kingbo, Program Manager
 Recently, Google Workspace Marketplace launched new features for developers to improve the application search and evaluation experience in the Marketplace for our Google Workspace admins and end users.  
Continuing with updates to further improve the developer experience, we are excited to announce Google Workspace Marketplace badges.  
The new badges will allow developers to promote their published Google Workspace Marketplace applications on their own websites. Users will be taken directly to the Marketplace application listing, where they can review application details, privacy policy, terms of service, and more. These users will then be able to securely install applications directly from the Google Workspace Marketplace. 
This promotional tool c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878630/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878630/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T15:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.15.8, 5.10.85, 5.4.165, 4.19.221, 4.14.258, 4.9.293, and 4.4.295 have been released.  As usual there
are important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878629/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878629/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T15:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libsamplerate and raptor2), Fedora (pam-u2f and python-markdown2), openSUSE (chromium, fetchmail, ImageMagick, and postgresql10), Oracle (samba), SUSE (fetchmail, postgresql10, python-pip, python3, and sles12sp2-docker-image), and Ubuntu (apache-log4j2, flatpak, glib, and samba).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treat integration as strategic to your business]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#TreatIntegrationAsStrategicToYourBusiness</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#TreatIntegrationAsStrategicToYourBusiness"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T14:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brandon finishes his article on how we should look at
      integration by arguing that it is a strategic element of an enterprise's
      infrastructure. You can buy the best products in the world but "none of it
      will make you competitive in a digital world if you continue to treat
      integration as a tactical nuisance to overcome so you take advantage of
      those new systems."
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This chipmaker could change the air quality monitoring game]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9460</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/this-chipmaker-could-change-the-air-quality-monitoring-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are y’all sick of me writing about air quality yet? I view the monitoring of indoor air quality and management of in-home energy as the two biggest trends to emerge from the last year or so, so I’m very focused on them these days. To that end, this week I met a startup called Piera Systems, which […]
The post This chipmaker could change the air quality monitoring game appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[양심적 병역거부과 십자가 밟기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83094</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83094"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T09:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2018년, 양심적 병역거부자에 대한 대체복무제를 규정하지 않은 병역종류 조항은 양심의 자유를 침해한다는 취지의 헌법재판소 결정과 진정한 양심에 따른 병역거부는 병역법 제88조(입영의 기피) 제1항에 정한 ‘정당한 사유’에 해당한다는 대법원의 전원합의체 판결이 나오며 우리 사회에 존재했던 또 하나의 뒤틀린 정의가 바로잡혔다. 하지만 기존 논의가 ‘여호와의 증인’을 중심으로 이루어진 결과, 종교적 신념이 아닌 비폭력·평화주의 신념에 따른 양심적 병역거부자들은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선험주의와 본래적 자기]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222595435215</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222595435215"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T09:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기농이 그렇게 자세하게 분석하고 있지 않지만, 로티와 테일러의 논의가 두 가지 논점에서 대립하고 있다고 본다. 첫째, 선험주의, 혹은 선험적 논증의 문제이다. 둘째, 자아의 본래성의 문제이다. 비트겐슈타인이나 하이데거를 충분히 실행적 혹은 실천적 선험주의로 이해할 수 있다고 생각한다. 그런데 이 입장이 논리적이고 문법적이며 개념적인 것이 실행적인 것을 통해 구성될 수 있다는 주장을 의미한다면, 그것은 문제가 있다고 생각한다. https://blog.naver.com/sellars/221100870499 https://blog.naver.com/sellars/220763474930 https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222240665508 분명히 비트겐슈타인이나 하이데거에게서 본래성이 문제.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논증의 다섯 가지 요소: 일상 대화에서 찾는 논증의 원리]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83078</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83078"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T08:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 다른 사람과 대화하는 과정에서 아이디어를 떠올리는 경험을 자주 한다. 질문하고 대답하는 과정에서 자신도 미처 깨닫지 못하고 있던 가치있는 주장을 발견하기도 하고, 주장을 뒷받침하는 이유와 근거를 즉흥적으로 떠올리기도 한다. 관심 있는 주제를 놓고 대화하다 보면 누구나 경험할 수 있는 일이다. 논증이란 무엇인가  글을 쓸 때도 마찬가지다. 글을 쓴다는 것은 혼자 자신이 아는 것을 쏟아내는 것이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘몰카’가 아니라 ‘불법 촬영 범죄’다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83069</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83069"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T07:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[12월 8일 MBC가 [단독/‘골프장’·‘기독교 언론사’ 대표 아들‥불법 촬영물 62개] (이문현 기자)를 보도했습니다. “유명 골프장 리조트와 언론사를 운영하는 기업 회장의 아들이 여러 여성과 성관계하는 장면을 불법 촬영”했고 이를 여성 이름과 나이순으로 정리해둔 것이 수백 개에 달한다는 내용입니다. 취재진은 “확보한 모든 자료와 증언을 서울지방경찰청 여성청소년범죄수사대에 제출”했다면서, 경찰은 보도 당일 저녁 “미국 LA로 출국하려던 (피의자) 권 씨를 공항 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio checks Umbraco code for the third time]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0898/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0898/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six years ago, we first checked Umbraco with the PVS-Studio static analyzer for C#. Today, we decided to go where it all started and analyze the Umbraco CMS source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Digging into the community's lore with lei]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878205/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878205/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T18:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email is often seen as a technology with a dim future; it is slow, easily
faked, and buried in spam.  Kids These Days want nothing to do with it, and
email has lost its charm with many others as well.
But many development projects are still dependent on it, and even
non-developers still cope with large volumes of mail.  While development
forges show one possible path away from email, they are not the only one.
What if new structures could be built on top of email to address some of
its worst problems while keeping the good parts that many projects depend
on?  The "lei" system recently launched by Konstantin Ryabitsev is a hint
of how such a future might look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878520/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878520/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T15:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (chromium, firefox, gitlab, grafana, grafana-agent, thunderbird, and vivaldi), Debian (apache-log4j2, privoxy, and wireshark), Fedora (firefox, grub2, mariadb, mod_auth_openidc, rust-drg, rust-tiny_http, and rust-tiny_http0.6), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, curaengine, fetchmail, firefox, libvirt, log4j, opencontainers-runc, python-django, speex, and thunderbird), openSUSE (clamav, firefox, glib-networking, glibc, gmp, ImageMagick, log4j, nodejs12, nodejs14, php7, python-Babel, python-pip, webkit2gtk3, and wireshark), Red Hat (mailman:2.1 and samba), and SUSE (bcm43xx-firmware, firefox, glib-networking, ImageMagick, kernel-rt, and python-pip).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EFF: Chrome Users Beware: Manifest V3 is Deceitful and Threatening]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878454/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878454/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T15:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Electronic Frontier Foundation warns
against Manifest V3, a set of changes coming to a Chrome browser near
you.


	Manifest V3, or Mv3 for short, is outright harmful to privacy
	efforts. It will restrict the capabilities of web
	extensions—especially those that are designed to monitor, modify,
	and compute alongside the conversation your browser has with the
	websites you visit. Under the new specifications, extensions like
	these– like some privacy-protective tracker blockers– will have
	greatly reduced capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A tech landscape and current climate sensing tool - Your own Tech Radar]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#4.ATechLandscapeAndCurrentClimateSensingTool-YourOwnTechRadar</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#4.ATechLandscapeAndCurrentClimateSensingTool-YourOwnTechRadar"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew's fourth supporting element for the Advice Process is using a
      tech radar to capture and map out your local version of the technology
      trends you see across your organization. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing a smart home with multiple digital assistants isn’t bad]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9458</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/sharing-a-smart-home-with-multiple-digital-assistants-isnt-bad/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T14:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re finally approaching the end of 2021! I don’t know about you, but perhaps the biggest change I made to my smart home this past year was transitioning to Apple HomeKit. When I started out on my digital assistant journey a few years back, it was with the Amazon Alexa platform. Then once Google got into the market, I moved over to […]
The post Sharing a smart home with multiple digital assistants isn’t bad appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Develop boards remotely, in real time with new hardware-as-a-service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471812</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/develop-boards-remotely-in-real-time-with-new-hardware-as-a-service/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T10:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New service from MIKROE claims to be embedded industry’s first hardware-as-a-service offer that enables remote embedded hardware design from $4 a day.
The post Develop boards remotely, in real time with new hardware-as-a-service appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 대선은 2030이 결정한다 (ft. 2030 공약 비교)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83050</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83050"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T09:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[왜 20대 대통령선거를 90여 일 앞두고 정치권은 여야 구분 없이 2030 청년 세대를 호명하는가? 지금까지 그래왔듯이 이러한 호명은 대선을 코앞에 둔 각 정당과 대선 후보자들의 표몰이에 그칠 것인가? 이용·소비·동원되는 2030, 선거 핵심 캐스팅 보터 얼마 전 이재명 더불어민주당 대선 후보는 18세 고등학생을 광주 공동선대위원장에 임명하고, 과학 분야 2030세대 전문가 4명을 선대위원으로 영입했다. 윤석열 국민의힘 대선 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Examples of 7 Handy Functions for Associative Containers in Modern C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/handy-map-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/handy-map-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’d like to show you examples of several handy “map” functions from Modern C++. Associative containers like std::map, std::set, and their “unordered” counterparts are essential for many algorithms and techniques. With this new functionality, you can save the creation of temporary objects, write smaller and, what’s more, safer code.
Background code
To illustrate all the mechanics of a map, especially in terms of what happens with our objects, I have the following helper custom class:
struct User {
    std::string name {"default"};
    
    User() {
        std::cout << "User::User() " << name << '\n';
    }

    explicit User(std::string str) : name(std::move(str)) {
        std::cout << "User::User(std::string str) " << name << '\n';
    }

    ~User() {
        std::cou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT News of the week for Dec. 10, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9456</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-dec-10-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T05:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A different perspective on the Matter standard: I don’t spend a lot of time thinking about TVs in part because I don’t spend much time watching one. This isn’t a snob thing, just a function of my family spending more time watching shows on an iPad and not spending much time with TV in general. But for […]
The post IoT News of the week for Dec. 10, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch  5.16-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878418/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878418/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T00:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc5 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


Do give it a good testing - with the holidays coming up, things are
probably going to slow down both on the development and testing front,
and as a result I expect that I will also extend the rc series by
another week not because it's necessarily needed (too early to tell,
but doesn't feel that way), but simply because nobody will want to
open the next merge window immediately in the new year.


One small change of note in this -rc is that the default limit for the
number of pages that can be locked into memory by an unprivileged process
has been raised to
8MB; see this article for a summary of the
discussions leading up to this change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I think about writing]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/writing-non-advice/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/writing-non-advice/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see a lot of essays framed as writing advice which are actually thinly veiled descriptions of how someone writes that basically say "you should write how I write", e.g., people who write short posts say that you should write short posts. As with technical topics, I think a lot of different things can work and what's really important is that you find a style that's suitable to you and the context you operate in. Copying what's worked for someone else is unlikely to work for you, making "write how I write" bad advice.
We'll start by looking at how much variety there's been in what's worked1 for people, come back to what makes it so hard to copy someone else's style, and then discuss what I try to do in my writing.
If I look at the most read programming blogs in my extended social circles2 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘아랍의 봄’ 그 자리에 남은 절망: 27살 아델 케드리가 분신한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82892</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82892"/>
        <updated>2021-12-12T23:43:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[폴 쉠은 북아프리카 특파원으로 모로코의 수도 라바트에서 근무했다. ‘아랍의 봄’(2010년 12월 튀니지 혁명로 촉발된 아랍권의 민주화 시위. 튀니지, 이집트, 예멘의 정권이 교체되었고, 2011년에 절정, 그 후 소강 상태다.)이 터지기 직전 그의 사무실 벽에는 카다피 포스터가 걸려있었고, 거리는 시위로 늘 시끄러웠다. ‘낙타’ 이야기보다 독자의 관심받지 못한 ‘아랍의 봄’  그는 매일 기사를 써서 보냈지만, 아무도 관심을 갖지 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Giving AVs a better sense of hearing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471903</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/giving-avs-a-better-sense-of-hearing/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-12T19:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If drivers can hear a siren, why can’t autonomous vehicles do the same? In emergency situations such as severe traffic accidents, every second counts, and...
The post Giving AVs a better sense of hearing appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anne-Françoise Pelé</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Log4j mess]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878390/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878390/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-12T16:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those who have not yet seen it, this
advisory from Apache describes a nasty vulnerability in the widely used
Log4j package.


	Apache Log4j2 <=2.14.1 JNDI features used in configuration, log
	messages, and parameters do not protect against attacker controlled
	LDAP and other JNDI related endpoints. An attacker who can control
	log messages or log message parameters can execute arbitrary code
	loaded from LDAP servers when message lookup substitution is
	enabled. From log4j 2.15.0, this behavior has been disabled by
	default.


Updating this package is, of course, necessary, but that will only help so
much; it is bundled into a lot of other deployed products.
For more information see
this
Ars Technica article or, for desperate cases,
the Logout4Shell
utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 유사성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222593614037</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222593614037"/>
        <updated>2021-12-12T10:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[찰스 기농(구글은 ‘기논’이라고 부르고 있다)은 <비트겐슈타인과 하이데거 이후의 철학>이라는 논문에서 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 유사성에 대해서 이야기하고 있다. 기농은 예전에 칸트 없이 철학을 할 수 없었더라면, 마찬가지로 이제 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거 없이 철학을 할 수 없을 것이라는 로티의 말을 빌려 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 중요성에 대해서 암시하고 있다. 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 차이에도 불구하고 그들은 다음과 같은 유사성을 보여준다. 첫째, 그들은 모두 실천적, 실행적 삶을 강조한다. 이것은 이성이나 세계에 대한 탈시간적 진리를 강조하는 것에 반대된다. 둘째, 그들은 세계에 대한 표상주의적 혹은 재.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>