<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2022-09-26T20:19:49.827Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Supporting CHERI capabilities in GCC and glibc]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909265/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909265/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T20:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CHERI
architecture is the product of a research program to extend common
CPU architectures 
in a way that prevents many types of memory-related bugs (and
vulnerabilities).  At the 2022 GNU Tools Cauldron,
Alex Coplan and Szabolcs Nagy described the work that has been done to
bring GCC and the GNU C Library (glibc) to this architecture.  CHERI is a fundamentally
different approach to how memory is accessed, and supporting it properly is anything
but a trivial task.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] BPF for HID drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909109/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909109/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T14:31:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Human
Interface Device (HID) standard dates back to the Windows 95 era.
It describes how devices like mice and keyboards present themselves to the
host computer, and has created a world where a single driver can handle a
wide variety of devices from multiple manufacturers.  Or it would have, if
there weren't actual device manufacturers involved.  In the real world,
devices stretch and break the standard, each in its own special way.  At
the 2022 Linux Plumbers Conference,
Benjamin Tissoires described how BPF can be used to simplify the
task of supporting HID devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909439/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909439/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (expat and poppler), Fedora (dokuwiki), Gentoo (fetchmail, grub, harfbuzz, libaacplus, logcheck, mrxvt, oracle jdk/jre, rizin, smarty, and smokeping), Mageia (tcpreplay, thunderbird, and webkit2), SUSE (dpdk, permissions, postgresql14, puppet, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (linux-gkeop and sosreport).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선운사 꽃무릇을 담아보다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587875</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587875/%ec%84%a0%ec%9a%b4%ec%82%ac-%ea%bd%83%eb%ac%b4%eb%a6%87-2"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yale’s new Assure Lock 2 is smaller and missing Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11037</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/yales-new-assure-lock-2-is-smaller-and-missing-matter/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T13:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assa Abloy, the company behind the Yale and August brands of connected locks, has released a new smart lock that’s smaller, sleeker, and waiting on the Matter smart home interoperability protocol. It’s been a while since I reviewed a connected lock. And other than an exhaustively prepared installation process, it’s clear smart locks haven’t changed […]
The post Yale’s new Assure Lock 2 is smaller and missing Matter appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: Functions and the Stack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476445</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-functions-and-the-stack/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you seen your stack lately? I mean, have you really looked at the stack memory and observed what exactly happens when a function is...
The post Programming embedded systems: Functions and the Stack appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Find errors in packages through mass builds]]></title>
        <id>0ebf20fc-5f39-4cff-bf81-9b729880a1b3</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/26/find-errors-packages-through-mass-builds"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even after thorough unit testing on both applications and their library dependencies, builds often go wrong and turn up hidden errors. This article introduces a new tool, the Mass Prebuilder (MPB), that automates builds on enormous numbers of reverse dependencies to find problems that are not caught through package testing.
Let's look at a simple example. Roughly 1,200 packages in Red Hat-based distributions depend on GNU Autoconf. Knowing all of the packages by heart is unlikely, building them manually would take ages, and judging whether a failure is due to a change in GNU Autoconf is very difficult. A job for the Mass Prebuilder!
What is the Mass Prebuilder?
The Mass Prebuilder is an open source set of tools that help developers create mass rebuilds around a limited set of packages, in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frédéric Bérat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 유아론(solipsism)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222884563200</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222884563200"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T04:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 주관적 관념론자인 버클리에 의하면, 우리가 아는 모든 것은 경험으로부터 오는 것이다. 따라서 경험으로부터 오지 않는 것은 지식이 되지 못한다. 버클리는 이 주장에 따라 직접 경험의 대상이 아닌, 추론의 대상이 되는 물리적 대상의 존재를 삭제해 버린다. 우리 마음에서 독립적으로 존재하고 있는 물리적 대상은 없다. 따라서 존재하는 모든 것은 우리 마음에 의존적이다. 공적(公的)이고 객관적이라고 상정되는 물리적 대상의 존재를 삭제하고 있지만, 그럼에도 이 물리적 대상이 담당하고 있는 공적인 객관성을 유지하기 위해 버클리는 타인의 마음과 신이 존재한다는 것을 인정하고 있다. 그러나 타인의 마음은 관찰 가능한가? 신의 존.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways to Improve or Avoid Loops in C++20...23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/improve-loops-cpp2b/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/improve-loops-cpp2b/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this short article, I’ll show you several techniques to improve raw loops. I’ll take an example of a reverse iteration over a container and then transform it to get potentially better code.
The loop expression is an essential building block of programming. When you iterate over a container in C++20, we have the following options:
Range based for loop with an initializer
Iterators
Algorithms
Ranges and views
See examples below:



     
    


Let’s start with the following code; we’d like to print a std::vector in reverse:
std::vector vec { 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 };
for (auto i = vec.size() - 1; i >= 0; --i) {
    std::cout << i << ": " << vec[i] << '\n';
}


This code is broken, as auto i will be unsigned and cannot be “less than 0”!  This is not a breakthrough, and we discussed this topic i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[꼬리풀과 나비]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587867</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587867/%ea%bc%ac%eb%a6%ac%ed%92%80%ea%b3%bc-%eb%82%98%eb%b9%84"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T23:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[150조 채권 운영하는 건들락의 전망, 채권의 시대가 온다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587863</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587863/%ea%b1%b4%eb%93%a4%eb%9d%bd%ec%9d%98-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-%ec%b1%84%ea%b6%8c%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%9c%eb%8c%80%ea%b0%80-%ec%98%a8%eb%8b%a4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T23:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공용방송이 ‘또’ 위험하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87092</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87092"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T23:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[언론의 제1기능은 사회 제반 권력의 비판·감시·견제다. 선한 권력이야 별문제 없겠지만, 권력을 부당하게 사용할 가능성이 있는 세력에게는 눈엣가시다. 그래서 부당한 권력일수록 언론 장악의 유혹에 빠지기 쉽다. 그동안 공영방송에 끊임없이 불만을 제기한 국민의힘과 윤석열 정부도 그 유혹을 극복하지는 못하는 것 같다. 곳곳에서 공영방송 장악 움직임이 가시화되고 있다. 뜻 있는 공영방송 구성원들은 당연히 권력의 침탈에 저항할 것이고, 암흑의 […]
The post 공용방송이 ‘또’ 위험하다 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.0-rc7]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909392/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909392/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T22:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.0-rc7 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.



	So I was thinking rc7 might end up larger than usual due to travel
	hitting rc6, but it doesn't really seem to have happened.

	Yeah, maybe it's marginally bigger than the historical average for
	this time of the release cycle, but it definitely isn't some
	outlier, and it looks fairly normal. Which is all good, and makes
	me think that the final release will happen right on schedule next
	weekend, unless something unexpected happens. Knock wood.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overview of broad US data on IT job hiring/firing and quitting]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7129</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/09/25/overview-of-broad-us-data-on-it-job-hiring-firing-and-quitting/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T21:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software developers are employed by organizations and people change jobs, either voluntarily or not; every year a new batch of people join the workforce, e.g., new graduates. Governments track employment activities for a variety of reasons, e.g., tax collection, and monitoring labour supply and demand (for the purposes of planning). The US Bureau of Labor […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국의 클라우드 산업: 아마존, MS, 구글이 힘 못쓰는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87077</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87077"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T18:22:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[성공적인 기업은 클라우드로 이전하는 것이 목표가 아니라 실질적인 비즈니스 가치를 제공하기 위해 클라우드를 사용하는 데 중점을 둔다. 중국의 클라우드 산업은 상대적으로 도입이 늦었던 것에 비해 전환 속도에서는 세계에서 가장 빠르게 성장하고 있으며, 규모에서는 미국에 이어 세계에서 두 번째로 큰 시장이다. 중국의 퍼블릭 클라우드 시장은 2021년 320억 달러에서 2025년 900억 달러로 향후 몇 년 동안 세 […]
The post 중국의 클라우드 산업: 아마존, MS, 구글이 힘 못쓰는 이유 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역사상 최악의 약세장에서 살아남는 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587854</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587854/%ec%95%bd%ec%84%b8%ec%9e%a5-%ec%82%b4%ec%95%84%eb%82%a8%ea%b8%b0"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T10:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논증적 분석철학과 문학적 대륙철학 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222883646168</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222883646168"/>
        <updated>2022-09-25T05:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[크립키나 분석철학이 인문학적 관심과 소양이 있는 사람들에게 멀어진 이유로 문학이나 종교와의 괴리를 들었다. 어떤 의미에서 분석철학은 하나의 방법론적 개념이기에, 문학에 대한 분석철학이나 종교에 대한 분석철학이 충분히 가능하다. 그러나 일반적으로 가령 문학에 대한 분석철학은 문학 작품에서 우리가 귀담아 새겨야 할 어떤 철학적 주제나 명제를 해명해 주는 대신에 문학 자체에 대해서 학문적 분석을 하고 있다. 따라서 분석적 문학철학은 문학의 허구성이 어떤 개념이며, 그것이 사실과 어떻게 다른 것인지, 허구에 대한 심리적 반응이나 상상력, 은유 등을 탐구하고 있다. 이것이 일반적 경향이지만, 분석철학의 철학적 분석이나.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김치힐을 운영하는데 들어가는 시간과 비용]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2354</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2022/09/24/kr-cost-and-time-to-operate-kimchihill/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=kr-cost-and-time-to-operate-kimchihill"/>
        <updated>2022-09-24T08:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주변에서 도대체 시간이 어떻게 나서 김치힐을 운영하는지 질문을 자주 받습니다. 뉴스레터 구독자 분들께서도, 웹사이트 제작, 마케팅, 콘텐츠 제작 등 정말 혼자 하는 것이 맞는지, 분명 엄청 바쁠 텐데, 어떻게 시간이 나서 김치힐을 운영하는지 궁금해 하십니다. 오늘은 제가 김치힐에 들이는 돈과 시간, 그리고 운영 방법을 숨김 없이 공유하겠습니다. 김치힐 운영을 위한 구성 요소와 총 비용 김치힐Continue reading "김치힐을 운영하는데 들어가는 시간과 비용"
김치힐을 운영하는데 들어가는 시간과 비용 appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 23, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11034</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-23-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T20:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swarm announces new asset tracker: Swarm, the IoT satellite company purchased by SpaceX, has created a satellite-connected asset tracker that costs $99 and requires a $5 a month connectivity subscription. The idea is to make a satellite-powered tracker easier to access for companies that don’t have the technical expertise to build their own. This all fits […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 23, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux drops Python 2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909226/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909226/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T15:06:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arch Linux has announced
that Python 2 is being removed from the distribution's repositories.
"If you still require the python2 package you can keep it around, but
please be aware that there will be no security updates."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] BPF as a safer kernel programming environment]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909095/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909095/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T14:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For better or worse, C is the lingua franca in the world of kernel
engineering. The core logic of the Linux kernel is written entirely in
C (with a bit of assembly), as are its drivers and modules. While C is
rightfully celebrated for
its powerful yet simple semantics, it is an older language that lacks
many of the features present in modern languages such as
Rust. The
BPF subsystem, on the other hand,
provides a programming environment that allows engineers to write
programs that can run safely in kernel space. At the 2022 Linux Plumbers 
Conference in Dublin, Ireland, Alexei Starovoitov presented an overview
of how BPF has evolved over the years to provide a new model for kernel
programming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909210/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909210/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T14:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.19.11, 5.15.70, and 5.10.145 stable kernels are now available.  As
usual, they contain important fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909208/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909208/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T13:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bind9, expat, firefox-esr, mediawiki, and unzip), Fedora (qemu and thunderbird), Oracle (webkit2gtk3), SUSE (ardana-ansible, ardana-cobbler, ardana-tempest, grafana, openstack-heat-templates, openstack-horizon-plugin-gbp-ui, openstack-neutron-gbp, openstack-nova, python-Django1, rabbitmq-server, rubygem-puma, ardana-ansible, ardana-cobbler, grafana, openstack-heat-templates, openstack-murano, python-Django, rabbitmq-server, rubygem-puma, dpdk, freetype2, rubygem-rack, and virtualbox), and Ubuntu (etcd, libjpeg-turbo, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-raspi, linux-oem-5.17, linux-raspi-5.4, python-oauthlib, and python3.5).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘서울의 문’인가 ‘차별의 문’인가: 동대문구 성소수자 단체 대관 취소 사건 (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87070</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87070"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T09:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022. 8. 19. 대법원 3부는 서울 동대문구와 동대문구시설관리공단이 성소수자 인권단체의 체육관 대관을 취소한 것이 ‘성적 지향 등을 이유로 한 차별행위’에 해당하므로 손해배상을 해야 한다는 판결을 확정했다(대법원 제3부 2022. 8. 19. 2022다241875). 이 소송은 인권단체 퀴어여성네트워크 소속 언니네트워크와 활동가 4인이 제기한 것이다. 퀴어여성네트워크는 퀴어여성 생활체육대회(2017. 10. 21.)를 열기 위해 동대문구 체육관 대관을 신청했다. 그러나 성소수자 행사라는 […]
The post ‘서울의 문’인가 ‘차별의 문’인가: 동대문구 성소수자 단체 대관 취소 사건 (2022) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만삭스 S&P 500 전망을 3600으로 16% 하향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587846</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587846/%ea%b3%a8%eb%93%9c%eb%a7%8c%ec%82%ad%ec%8a%a4-sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join the Red Hat team at NodeConf EU 2022]]></title>
        <id>af2d04c4-c425-4b66-b2db-7b7fc5ba23c0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/23/join-red-hat-team-nodeconf-eu-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's that time of the year again, and NodeConf EU is almost upon us. This annual event is one of the leading Node.js events in Europe. It brings together contributors and innovators from the Node.js community to deliver a wide range of talks and workshops.
The conference will be back in person this year after being virtual for the past two years on October 3rd–5th in Kilkenny, Ireland.
The Node.js team here at Red Hat will be talking about lesser-known Node.js Core modules as well as guiding attendees through a workshop that will get you familiar with cloud-native development with Node.js. 
Talk: Journey into mystery: Lesser-known Node Core modules and APIs
Wednesday, October 4th, 2022, 9:30 UTC
Presenter: Luke Holmquist (@sienaluke), Senior Software Engineer, Red Hat
One of the key concep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Holmquist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[27 제물론의 진리]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222881943541</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222881943541"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T23:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김형효에 의하면, 제물론의 진리는 다음과 같은 특성을 갖고 있다. 첫째, 제물론의 진리는 심재(心齋)와 좌망(坐忘)이 보여주는 것처럼 우리의 의식적 마음을 제거할 것을 요구한다. 따라서 그 진리는 의식적인 것이 아니라, 소유적인 것이 아니라, 자연적이고 물학(物學)적이며, 기학(氣學)적이다. <심재(心齋)>가 잘 보여주듯이 우리는 눈으로, 마음으로 보는 것이 아니라, 기(氣)로 보아야 한다. 기(氣)는 허공(虛空) 같아서 모든 것을 수용한다. 둘째, 제물론의 사유는 유희적이며 놀이적 사유이다. 이 놀이의 사유는 자연적 사실처럼 특정한 목적 추구 없이 상호 의존하면서 공생의 질서를 이루는데 적합하다. 이러한 사유는 자연의 이.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] NYT 칼럼니스트들의 고백 “내가 틀렸습니다”]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75315</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/22/npc_iwaswrong/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_iwaswrong"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뉴욕타임스 칼럼란에 흥미로운 인터랙티브 기획이 실렸습니다. 8인의 칼럼니스트가 과거에 기고한 글 가운데 잘못된 예측을 담았거나 사안에 대해 의견이 달라진 글을 들고나와 자신의 “과오”를 고백하는 일종의 반성문을 쓴 것입니다. 뉴욕타임스는 “당파성과 양극화가 극대화된 시대, 소셜미디어상의 반향실이 원래 의견을 고수하는 쪽에 인센티브를 주는 시대”에 자신이 틀렸다는 점을 인정하기란 쉽지 않다면서, 여전히 선의의 지적인 토론을 통해 자신의 관점을 돌아보고 필요하면 고치는 게 가능하다는 점을 보여주기 위해 이런 기획을 했다고 설명했습니다. 단연 화제가 된 글은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Safer flexible arrays for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908817/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908817/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T22:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2022 Linux
Security Summit Europe (LSS EU), Gustavo A. R. Silva reported in on
work he has been doing on "flexible" arrays in the kernel.  While these
arrays provide some ... flexibility ... they are also a source of bugs,
which 
can often result in security vulnerabilities.  He has been working on ways
to make the use of flexible arrays safer in the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to quickly evaluate data converters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476434</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-quickly-evaluate-data-converters/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T15:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how to record a macro and how to use it within Python and MATLAB environments to automate certain evaluation tasks without having...
The post How to quickly evaluate data converters appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lluis Beltran Gil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.64.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909085/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909085/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:51:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.64.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Changes include the
stabilization of the IntoFuture
trait, easier access to C-compatible types, the availability of
rust-analyzer via
rustup, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Struggles and suggestions with master/slave terminology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476417</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/struggles-and-suggestions-with-master-slave-terminology/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T14:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Removing the use of Master/Slave terminology across the industry is doable, but I suspect it will take a long time and generate a lot of...
The post Struggles and suggestions with master/slave terminology appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Related Site!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1456/a-new-related-site-mlrelated</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1456/a-new-related-site-mlrelated"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are delighted to announce the launch of the very first new Related site in 15 years!  The new site will be dedicated to the trendy and quickly growing field of Machine Learning and will be called - drum roll please - MLRelated.com.
We think MLRelated fits perfectly well within the “Related” family, with:

the fast growth of TinyML, which is a topic of great interest to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909051/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909051/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:25:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (e17, fish, mako, and tinygltf), Fedora (mingw-poppler), Mageia (firefox, google-gson, libxslt, open-vm-tools, redis, and sofia-sip), Oracle (dbus-broker, kernel, kernel-container, mysql, and nodejs and nodejs-nodemon), Slackware (bind), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi-controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi-uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, containerized-data-importer, go1.18, go1.19, kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-tools-container, virt-operator-container, libconfuse0, and oniguruma), and Ubuntu (bind9 and pcre2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: The FTC eyes Amazon’s iRobot buy]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11028</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-the-ftc-eyes-amazons-irobot-buy/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T13:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Federal Trade Commission is looking into Amazon’s decision to purchase the maker of Roomba vacuum cleaners for $1.7 billion. The agency this week asked Amazon and iRobot for more information about the deal, so Kevin and I took a moment to explain exactly what the FTC should worry about. Then we talk about Wi-Fi […]
The post Podcast: The FTC eyes Amazon’s iRobot buy appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“We are Waterfall—can we work with you?”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/waterfall-how-can-it-work/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/waterfall-how-can-it-work/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T10:58:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, a client using a Waterfall approach asks if we can work together. They usually work in a fixed-price, fixed-scope type […]
The post “We are Waterfall—can we work with you?” appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jane Orme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1세대 ‘미디어 커머스’의 한계, 앞으로는 양방향 (라이브) 소통과 브랜드가 답이다]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2328</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2022/09/22/kr-future-of-media-commerce/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=kr-future-of-media-commerce"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:27:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미디어 커머스는 미디어(Media)와 상업을 뜻하는 커머스(Commerce)의 합성어로 유튜브, 인스타그램, 틱톡 등의 SNS 채널을 통해 제품을 홍보하고 판매하는 방식의 전자 상거래 서비스를 말한다. D2C로 대변되며, 초기 상품 기획에 강점을 가지고 등장한 미디어 커머스는 점차 웹예능, 웹드라마, 숏폼 영상 등을 즐기는 소비자들의 미디어 소비 행태에 발맞추어 진화해 나갔으며, 2021년 약 106조 원의 거대 시장으로 성장했다. (소비자 통계청Continue reading "1세대 ‘미디어 커머스’의 한계, 앞으로는 양방향 (라이브) 소통과 브랜드가 답이다"
1세대 ‘미디어 커머스’의 한계, 앞으로는 양방향 (라이브) 소통과 브랜드가 답이다 appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about the new BGP capabilities in Red Hat OpenStack 17]]></title>
        <id>d3766211-f376-45f2-b86d-2b3cbe44900a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/22/learn-about-new-bgp-capabilities-red-hat-openstack-17"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Hat OpenStack Platform is an Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS) offering from Red Hat. Version 17.0 of the platform includes dynamic routing for both the control and data planes. This lets you deploy a cluster in a pure layer-3 (L3) data center, overcoming the scaling issues of traditional layer-2 (L2) infrastructures such as large failure domains, large broadcast traffic, or long convergence times in the event of failures.
This article will illustrate this new feature by outlining a simple three-rack spine and leaf topology, where the layer-2 boundaries are within each rack on the Red Hat OpenStack Platform. The control plane spans the three racks, and each rack also hosts a compute node. Figure 1 illustrates our topology.




          
The main characteristics of this deployment…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Alvarez Sanchez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반(反)시민적인 것만 남은, 대리 미디어 시대의 종말]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87052</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87052"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T04:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[민주화 이후 지난 40년은 시민을 “위한” 미디어 시대였다. 언론은 시민의 목소리를 대변하는 역할을 스스로 자임하며 여론 형성의 중추적 역할을 수행해 왔다. TV와 라디오는 이에 더하여 시민의 문화 생활을 위한 각종 방송 프로그램을 제작하고 공급해 왔다. 법과 제도 역시 시청자와 독자 및 이용자 권리 진흥을 위한 규제 정책을 만들어 왔다. 다양한 공공 조직과 기관 및 위원회도 […]
The post 반(反)시민적인 것만 남은, 대리 미디어 시대의 종말 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 22, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908080/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908080/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-22T01:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 22, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Two visions for the future of sourceware.org]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908638/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908638/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T22:41:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public hosting systems for free software have come and gone over the years
but one of them, Sourceware, has been
supporting the development of most of the GNU toolchain for nearly
25 years. 
Recently, an application was made to bring
Sourceware under the umbrella of the Software Freedom Conservancy (SFC), at least for
fundraising purposes.  It turns out that there is a separate initiative,
developed in secret until now, with a different vision for the future of
Sourceware.  The 2022 GNU
Tools Cauldron was the site of an intense discussion on how this
important community resource should be managed in the coming years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reworking C and C++ front-end — or how we deal with 16-year legacy code in PVS-Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0992/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0992/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2022, the PVS-Studio static analyzer for C and C++ turns 16 years old. If the analyzer were a human, it would have already finished high school! This project was started a long time ago, and since then its type system has not almost changed. In this article, we will look at the analyzer over time — what required improvements and how we went about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME 43 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908928/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908928/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T18:11:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 43 of the GNOME desktop environment has been released; see the release notes for details.



	This latest GNOME release comes with improvements across the board,
	ranging from a new quick settings menu, a redesigned Files app, and
	hardware security integration. GNOME 43 continues the trend of
	GNOME apps migrating from GTK 3 to GTK 4, and includes many other
	smaller enhancements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just launched: Apply for support from Google Play’s $2M Indie Games Fund in Latin America]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/apply-for-support-from-google-play-2m-indie-games-fund-in-latin-america.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/apply-for-support-from-google-play-2m-indie-games-fund-in-latin-america.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T17:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Patricia Correa, Director, Global Developer Marketing
  
As part of our commitment to helping all developers grow on our platform, at Google Play we have various programs focused on supporting small games studios. A few weeks ago we announced the winners of the Indie Games Festival in Europe, Korea and Japan, and the 2022 class of the Indie Games Accelerator.

Today, we are launching the Indie Games Fund in Latin America. We will be awarding $2 million dollars in non-dilutive cash awards, in addition to hands-on support, to selected small games studios based in LATAM, to help them build and grow their businesses on Google Play.
The program is open to indie game developers who have already launched a game - whether it’s on Google Play or another mobile platform, PC or console. Each selected recipient will get between $150,000 and $200,000 dollars to help them take their game to the next level, and build successful businesses.
Check out all eligibility criteria and apply now. Priority will be given to applications received by 12:00 p.m. BRT, 31 October, 2022. 
For more updates about all our programs, resources and tools for indie game developers, follow us on Twitter @GooglePlayBiz and Google Play business community on LinkedIn.





How useful did you find this blog post?
★ ★ ★ ★ ★]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So I made a LoRa-based prototype using a dev kit]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11005</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/so-i-made-a-lora-based-prototype-using-a-dev-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T15:32:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After talking about IoT development kits for the past several years, I figured it was time to get my hands dirty. So the folks at Blues Wireless sent me their Sparrow Development Kit for review. And I got my hands dirty! Over the past week, I’ve been using the Sparrow components to gather temperature and […]
The post So I made a LoRa-based prototype using a dev kit appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rendered linux-next documentation on kernel.org]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908911/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908911/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T14:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konstantin Ryabitsev has announced
the availability of rendered
documentation from linux-next on kernel.org.  This will be useful for
anybody wanting to see what the documentation for the next kernel release
will look like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908893/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908893/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T13:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (libconfuse, moodle, rizin, and thunderbird), Oracle (ELS kernel, gnupg2, ruby, and webkit2gtk3), Red Hat (booth, dbus-broker, gnupg2, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, mysql, nodejs, nodejs-nodemon, ruby, and webkit2gtk3), Slackware (expat and mozilla), SUSE (kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-tools-container, virt-operator-container and vsftpd), and Ubuntu (bind9, ghostscript, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-bluefield, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, lnux-hwe, inux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, and mako).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT Supply Chains, Compliance & Expert Workshops – IoTSF Conference 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21684</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/iot-supply-chains-compliance-expert-workshops-iotsf-conference-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T12:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are looking forward to welcoming you to the IoTSF Annual conference on October 5th In our last blog we highlighted the morning sessions on offer. This time we look into the afternoon tracks. After the chance to meet some friends over lunch and make contact with colleagues we sit down]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>-</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부동산 이해충돌 의혹 의원 46명에게 질문하다 (17명 ‘무응답’)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87043</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87043"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T11:35:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[작년 공직자의 직무수행 과정에서 공직을 활용하여 사익을 추구할 수 있는 이른바 이해충돌을 막기 위해 이해충돌방지법과 국회법이 제정, 개정되어 올해부터 시행 중이다. 개정된 국회법에 따르면, 국회의원은 재산, 민간활동 내역 등 사적 이해관계를 등록하여 국회 윤리심사자문위원회의 이해충돌 심사를 받도록 되어 있다. 이해충돌 심사를 거쳐 국회의장은 이해충돌 소지가 있는 국회의원을 해당 상임위에 배정하지 못하도록 하고 있다. 경실련은 하반기 […]
The post 부동산 이해충돌 의혹 의원 46명에게 질문하다 (17명 ‘무응답’) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost OpenShift Data Science with the Intel AI Analytics Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>7849f887-5a57-47f1-8494-774bce6f5161</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/21/boost-openshift-data-science-intel-ai-analytics-toolkit"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel has been partnering with Red Hat to offer a solution for Red Hat OpenShift Data Science that includes Intel AI tools. With the help of these tools, OpenShift Data Science can perform faster and more efficiently.
The partnership between Intel and Red Hat came in response to the needs of their customers for an enterprise-grade solution for data science. The need for a more efficient and faster solution stems from the rise in demand for data scientists, which is happening at an exponential rate.
The new tools include support for popular frameworks such as TensorFlow, PyTorch, and MXNet, as well as optimized workflows for deploying AI models on Kubernetes clusters. OpenShift Data Science also provides tight integration with key components of the Intel Xeon Scalable processors family, inc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Karl Eklund, Audrey Reznik</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bind services created with AWS Controllers for Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>ea05a1b5-94fc-4f41-9f45-43a331d6a4c7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/21/bind-services-created-aws-controllers-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application developers can define Amazon Web Services (AWS) resources directly from Kubernetes using AWS Controllers for Kubernetes (ACK). You can use the Service Binding Operator to easily connect applications to any AWS service provisioned through ACK.
This article explores the connection with an RDS database and demonstrates configuring ACK to create a service instance for the AWS Relational Database Service (RDS). You can also learn how to use Service Binding Operator annotations to bind a PostgreSQL service created using RDS and a REST API.
Benefits of the Service Binding Operator and AWS Controllers for Kubernetes 
One benefit of the Service Binding Operator and ACK is that they streamline the formation of a connection. The Service Binding Operator implements the Service Binding spec…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Baiju Muthukadan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assignment delay's and Verilog's wait statement]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2022/09/21/vlog-wait.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2022/09/21/vlog-wait.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve now spent more time than I want to admit to debugging simulation issues
when using Verilog’s simulation semantics.  Let me therefore share some
problems I’ve come across, together with my proposed solution for them.
The Problems
Today’s problem stems from logic like the following:
always @(trigger_condition)
begin
	if (some_other_condition_determining_relevance)
	begin
		#1;
		state_variable = complex_expression;
		// This then continues for another 50 lines or so
	end
end


In general, this comes to me in “working” simulation code that’s been handed
down to me to maintain.  The simulations that use this logic often take hours
to run, and so debugging this sort of thing can be very time consuming.
(Costly too–my hourly rate isn’t cheap.)
Let’s walk through this logic for a moment–befo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[크립키 혹은 분석철학에 대한 관심]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222880273099</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222880273099"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T01:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[신문검색을 해보니 아직 크립키의 부고(訃告)에 대한 기사가 없다. 그런데 인문학에 관심이 있는 사람들이 크립키에 대해서 관심을 갖고 있는가? 나아가 러셀이나 비트겐슈타인을 제외하고 분석철학자의 이름이나 철학에 대해서 우리 사회는 어느 정도 알고 있는 것인가? 분명한 것은 현대 유럽철학자들에 비해 그 인문학적, 철학적 관심이 현저하게 떨어진다는 것이다. 남경태의 <현대철학>(2010)에 분석철학자, 혹은 영미철학자로 비트겐슈타인과 토마스 쿤, 두 사람만 소개되고 있다. 현대 철학을 소개하고 해설해 주고 있는 몇몇 책에서도 비트겐슈타인이나 포퍼가 소개되고 있지만, 거의 현대 유럽철학자 중심이다. 이순성의 <오늘.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개발자, 어떻게 살것인가?]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=11626</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2022/09/21/how_to_live/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-21T01:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 분위기 코로나에서 촉발된 인플레이션우크라이나 전쟁으로 가속화.그로 인한 금리인상, 소비심리 위축 등 … 은, IT 투자시장을 위축시켰습니다.한동안 고용은 줄고 퇴직이 늘겠죠. 전초증상으로 한경이 이런 기사를 냈습니다. 개발자 시장도 이 분위기를 따라갑니다.연봉 높은 아저씨들은 퇴직하고,신입직원으로 빈자리를 채우죠. 제 블로그에 사회 초년생분들이 꽤 계시다보니,이런 이야기를 한 번 정리하고 싶었습니다. 파도 그동안 이런 한파를 여러번 맞았습니다.대부분 살아남긴 했지만 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debian's firmware vote]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908825/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908825/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T23:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Debian project has begun voting on
changes to its approach to firmware needed to install a working
distribution.  The original ballot options described in this article are still there, but this is
Debian so there are several others as well.  Some of the additions include
changes to the Debian Social Contract that explicitly allow the shipping of
firmware needed to use Debian on hardware requiring that firmware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 게임화(gamification)에 대처하는 법]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75299</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/20/npc_gamification/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_gamification"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T22:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[모든 생명체는 자신의 생존과 번식을 위해 주변 환경을 변화시킵니다. 여기서 말하는 환경에는 같은 종의 다른 개체가 포함되며, 특히 인간을 비롯한 사회적 동물은 사회적 상호작용, 곧 다양한 종류의 의사소통을 통해 같은 목적을 실현합니다. 게임의 요소를 이용해 사람들의 행동을 변화시키는 것을 목적으로 하는 게임화(gamification)도 그 연장선에 존재합니다. 물론 개체의 행동을 변화시키는 의사소통이 그 개체에 반드시 부정적 효과만을 가져오지 않는 것처럼 게임화 역시 부정적인 것만은 아닙니다. 그러나 “Hooked”의 저자 니르 아얄이 말하는 것처럼, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Introducing io_uring_spawn]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908268/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908268/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T21:08:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The traditional mechanism for launching a program in a new process on Unix
systems—forking and execing—has been with us for decades, but it is not
really the most efficient of operations.  Various alternatives have been
tried along the way but have not supplanted the traditional approach.  A new
mechanism created by Josh Triplett adds process creation
to the io_uring asynchronous I/O API and
shows great promise; he came to the 2022
Linux Plumbers Conference (LPC) to introduce io_uring_spawn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mapping the Privacy Landscape for Central Bank Digital Currencies]]></title>
        <id>3561796</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3561796"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T15:51:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another round of stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908780/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908780/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:26:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.19.10,
5.15.69,
5.10.144,
5.4.214,
4.19.259,
4.14.294, and
4.9.329
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908779/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908779/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (dokuwiki and rizin), SUSE (libcontainers-common, permissions, sqlite3, and wireshark), and Ubuntu (tiff, vim, and xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything I could find out about Amazon’s Sidewalk Network]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10998</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/everything-i-could-find-out-about-amazons-sidewalk-network/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T13:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was first published on Sept. 16, 2022 in my weekly newsletter.  Since Amazon announced its Sidewalk Network in 2019, I’ve been eagerly awaiting the Low-Power Wide-Area Network (LPWAN) for the internet of things. But since Amazon turned on the network in mid-2021, an influx of Sidewalk devices and widespread use hasn’t occurred. Instead Amazon is slowly […]
The post Everything I could find out about Amazon’s Sidewalk Network appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Sustainable Refillable Active Coal Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=13198</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2022/09/20/build-a-sustainable-refillable-active-coal-filter/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T12:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever used air filters to keep smells, fumes and dust at a low level in your workshop, you for sure came in contact with these expensive throwaway active coal filters. While throwing-away the used active coal seems to be unavoidable, all the thrown away plastic and packaging of the filter can easily be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[길상사 꽃무릇, 천재시인을 사랑한 여인의 사랑법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587809</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587809/%ea%b8%b8%ec%83%81%ec%82%ac-%ea%bd%83%eb%ac%b4%eb%a6%87"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T11:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년, 무주택 서민은 집을 꿈꿀 수 있는가 (ft. 분양가 상한제와 고무줄 건축비)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87032</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87032"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T09:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[분양가 상한제는 아파트 선분양제의 폐해를 막기 위하여 도입됐다. 짓지도 않은 아파트를 분양할 수 있도록 허용하자 소비자들은 집값 거품, 부실시공, 설계변경 등 건설사의 횡포에 무방비로 노출됐다. 소비자 피해를 최소화하기 위하여 분양가격만큼은 기본형 건축비를 넘지 못하도록 규제한 것이다. 분양가 상한제가 분양받은 소비자들에게 시세보다 낮게 분양을 받게 해준다는 논란이 있지만, 주택 가격에 거품이 끼지 않도록 하기 위해 소비자 […]
The post 2022년, 무주택 서민은 집을 꿈꿀 수 있는가 (ft. 분양가 상한제와 고무줄 건축비) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How hashing and cryptography made the internet possible]]></title>
        <id>60312bd5-c40d-4f54-9a4e-fbce728d8518</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/20/how-hashing-and-cryptography-made-internet-possible"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A lot of technologies, business choices, and public policies gave us the internet we have today—a tremendous boost to the spread of education, culture, and commerce, despite its well-documented flaws. But few people credit two deeply buried technologies for making the internet possible: hashing and cryptography.
If more people understood the role these technologies play, more money and expertise would go toward uncovering and repairing security flaws. For instance, we probably would have fixed the Heartbleed programming error much earlier and avoided widespread vulnerabilities in encrypted traffic.
This article briefly explains where hashing and cryptography come from, how they accomplish what they do, and their indelible effect on the modern internet.
Hashing
Hashing was invented in the 1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andy Oram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[27 계몽이란 무엇인가]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222879282248</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222879282248"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T23:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음을 요약하고 평가해 보라. <계몽이란 우리가 마땅히 스스로 책임져야 할 미성년의 상태로부터 벗어나는 것이다. 미성년의 상태란 다른 사람의 지도 없이는 자신의 지성을 사용할 수 없는 상태이다. 이 미성년 상태의 책임을 마땅히 져야 하는 것은 그 미성년의 원인이 지성의 결핍에 있는 경우가 아니다. 오히려 그것은 다른 사람의 지도 없이 지성을 사용할 수 있는 결단과 용기가 결여되어 있을 경우이다. 그러므로 “과감히 알려고 하라”(Sapere aude), “너 자신의 지성을 사용할 용기를 가져라”는 것이 계몽의 표어이다. 대부분의 사람들이 외부의 지도에서 해방된 뒤에도 일생 동안 미성년의 상태에 머물고, 다른 사람들이 손쉽.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sorting in C#: OrderBy.OrderBy or OrderBy.ThenBy? What's more effective and why?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0991/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0991/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Suppose we need to sort the collection by multiple keys. In C#, we can do this with the help of OrderBy().OrderBy() or OrderBy().ThenBy(). But what is the difference between these calls? To answer this question, we need to delve into the source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing functionally safe RTD systems: RTD design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476362</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/implementing-functionally-safe-rtd-systems-rtd-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This first article in a two-part series on implementing functionally safe RTD systems discusses resistance temperature detector (RTD) circuit design and safety certification considerations. In...
The post Implementing functionally safe RTD systems: RTD design appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary McCarthy and Wasim Shaikh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The 2022 Linux Kernel Maintainers Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908320/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908320/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T16:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a two-year hiatus, the 2022 Linux Kernel Maintainers Summit returned
to an in-person format in Dublin, Ireland on September 15.  Around 30
kernel developers discussed a number of process-related issues relating to
the kernel community.  LWN had the privilege of being there and is able,
once again, to report from the event.  This years sessions included
discussions of regression handling, the imminent merging of Rust support,
BPF, the kernel development process, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908627/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908627/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T13:43:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (connman and e17), Fedora (curl, open-vm-tools, pcs, and python-lxml), Mageia (curl, dpkg, freecad, gimp, libtar, libtiff, mediawiki, ostree, python-lxml, schroot, SDL12, sdl2, wireshark, and zlib), Oracle (kernel and php:7.4), Red Hat (php:7.4), Slackware (vim), SUSE (chromium, kernel, libarchive, libtirpc, mupdf, python-rsa, ruby2.5, and virtualbox), and Ubuntu (linux-intel-iotg).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways Matter will disappoint users at launch]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10996</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/5-ways-matter-will-disappoint-users-at-launch/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was first published on Sept. 16, 2022 in my weekly newsletter.  After participating in a panel on Matter at Silicon Labs’ Works With event on Tuesday and conversing with attendees throughout the event, I think the initial response to Matter is going to be tepid at best and downright aggravated at worst. One person […]
The post 5 ways Matter will disappoint users at launch appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Zero to One Hundred]]></title>
        <id>3561799</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3561799"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T12:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing a power-saving solenoid driver: Design concepts￼]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476302</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/designing-a-power-saving-solenoid-driver-design-concepts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most common approach to drive a solenoid is to apply the required voltage in the solenoid coil but using a current regulated driver to...
The post Designing a power-saving solenoid driver: Design concepts￼ appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maicon Bruno Hofmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[신당역 스토킹 살인사건: 클릭 저널리즘의 2차 가해, 부끄럽지 않은가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87023</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87023"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T09:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[불법 촬영으로 직위해제 된 전 서울교통공사 직원이 동료를 살해하는 사건이 벌어졌다. 2차 피해를 우려해 언론 보도를 원치 않는다는 유가족의 당부에도 불구하고 언론은 수많은 기사를 쏟아냈고, 선정적이고 부적절한 기사도 많았다. ‘클릭 수’만 노린 기사는 고인이 된 피해자와 슬픔에 잠긴 유족을 위한 배려는커녕 자극적이고 비윤리적인 내용으로 클릭질 장사에 몰두했다. 여성 피해자 강조, 선정적 제목 난무 9월 15일 […]
The post 신당역 스토킹 살인사건: 클릭 저널리즘의 2차 가해, 부끄럽지 않은가 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best ways to learn about Linux from Red Hat Developer]]></title>
        <id>02dd2697-1069-4f18-a29a-6798c4e87270</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/19/best-ways-learn-about-linux-red-hat-developer"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for tips and deep dives on Linux, including Red Hat Enterprise Linux? Red Hat Developer has a wide range of content for you. These are some of our favorite and most popular articles, cheat sheets, and lessons to help you get the most out of Linux, along with underlying tools like GCC and Linux-based platforms like Docker:
Helpful Linux commands
Don't know where to get started in RHEL? This interactive lesson schools you in a series of must-know commands.
Modular Perl in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 8 (Author: Petr Pisar)
Red Hat Enterprise Linux comes with modules, a packaging concept allowing system administrators to select the desired software from multiple packaged versions. Learn how to manage Perl as a module, as well as how to manage CPAN modules provided by Perl.
Intermediate Li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An X11 Apologist Tries Wayland (artemis.sh)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908561/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908561/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T06:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The artemis.sh blog has a
detailed review of the state of Wayland compared to X.org.


	It feels fantastic. It even made my software cursor
	not feel so softwarey, which I’ve never experienced with a software
	cursor before. I have a pretty bad GPU, but on a higher end card
	you’d get a huge benefit to this in games. If your card can render
	the game many times faster than your monitor refresh rate, you can
	unlock your FPS in the game, tune your max_render_time to the
	absolute minimum, and get EXTREMELY low latency while still having
	absolutely no screen tearing whatsoever.
	
	And like, this is the first time I’ve ever seen the vsync setting
	in a game actually sync the game up with the vblank interval in a
	way that matters. It works for games in wine. It’s amazing. I have
	never experienced gaming on Linux that looked this smooth in my
	life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.0-rc6]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908560/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908560/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T06:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.0-rc6 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	So this is an artificially small -rc release, because this past
	week we had the Maintainers' Summit in Dublin (along with OSS EU
	and LPC 2022), so we've had a lot of maintainers traveling.

	Or - putting my ridiculously optimistic hat on - maybe things are
	just so nice and stable that there just weren't all that many
	fixes?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Signed and Unsigned Mismatches with std::ssize()]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/ssize-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/ssize-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I’ll show another technique that avoids mixing signed and unsigned types.
In my article Integer Conversions and Safe Comparisons in C++20 we learned about cmp_* integer comparison functions that allow us to compare various types of integer types. The functions are safe because they help with mixing signed and unsigned types. In C++20, there’s another handy feature: the non-member std::ssize() function that returns a signed number of elements in a container.
Let’s see how to use it.



     
    


C++20 offers many ways to avoid working with raw array/container indices:
Algorithms (they can avoid raw loops),
Ranges and views (for example, views::reverse),
Iterators,
Range based for loop with an initializer (for example, to update the index count).
On the other hand, you ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 현대 전쟁의 공급망]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75290</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/18/npc_tb2warfare/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_tb2warfare"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T22:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[현대전(戰)이라고 하면 어떤 이미지가 떠오르시나요? 21세기 초 미국이 전 세계에서 벌인 ‘테러와의 전쟁’ 때만 해도 없었지만, 요즘엔 거의 빠짐없이 쓰이는 전술적인 핵심 무기가 바로 드론입니다. 지난 4월에 뉴욕타임스는 미국 공군 소속 드론 조종사들의 정신건강 문제가 얼마나 심각한지 고발했습니다. 조종사들은 라스베거스 근처의 평범한 사무실(처럼 보이지만, 실제로는 기밀 군사 시설)에 매일 출근해 지구 반대편의 드론으로 작전을 수행하는데, 예전에는 할 수 없던 명령을 수행하다가 외상 후 스트레스 장애(PTSD)를 비롯한 참전 군인들이 겪는 정신 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[귀천(歸天)  솔 크립키]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222878303750</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222878303750"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T22:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philosopher and Logician Saul Kripke’s Obituary at 81 One of the most influential analytic philosophers Saul Kripke’s obituary was revealed after his death at the age of 81 on September 15, 2022. Kripke was a Distinguished Professor of Philosophy at the Graduate Center of the City University of New York. He was also an emeritus professor at Princeton University. Saul was a central figure in a number of fields related to mathematical logic, philosophy of language, modal logic, metaphysics, epistemology, philosophy of mathematics, and recursion theory. 철학자이자 논리학자인 Saul Kripke, 81세로.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimal sizing of a product backlog]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7113</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/09/18/optimal-sizing-of-a-product-backlog/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T22:01:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers working on the implementation of a software system will have a list of work that needs to be done, a to-do list, known as the product backlog in Agile. The Agile development process differs from the Waterfall process in that the list of work items is intentionally incomplete when coding starts (discovery of new […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[하나증권] 9월 FOMC의 관전 포인트]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587807</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587807/9%ec%9b%94-fomc-%ea%b4%80%ec%a0%84-%ed%8f%ac%ec%9d%b8%ed%8a%b8"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T12:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence hails EDA 2.0 with unified data and AI driven verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476340</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/cadence-hails-eda-2-0-with-unified-data-and-ai-driven-verification/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T05:53:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New platform enables engineers to obtain ‘actionable intelligence’ from massive volumes of chip design and verification data, opening the door to a generation of AI-driven design and verification tools to improve productivity.
The post Cadence hails EDA 2.0 with unified data and AI driven verification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 맹자의 의리지변(義利之辨)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222877519724</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222877519724"/>
        <updated>2022-09-18T01:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이명휘가 주장하고 싶은 논제가 다음과 같은 것이다. (1) 서양 윤리학에서 공맹(孔孟)의 윤리학과 가장 잘 부합하는 것이 칸트의 윤리학이다. 이 두 가지 윤리학은 모두 자율 윤리학에 속한다. (2) 따라서 칸트의 윤리학을 통해 가령 유가의 <의리지변(義利之辨)>, 즉 도덕적 올바름은 이익과 구분해야 한다는 주장을 해명할 수 있다. 칸트도 유사하게 도덕과 행복을 구분하고 있다. (3) <의리지변(義利之辨)>에서 해명된 주장에 따라 <의리지변(義利之辨)>의 논의와 <공사지분(公私之分)>의 논의가 서로 다른 것이라고 주장할 수 있다. <공사지분(公私之分)>은 이익에 대한 논의이다. (4) <의리지변(義利之辨.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC's new fortification level: The gains and costs]]></title>
        <id>aa8105eb-3693-4988-8f01-b822ce7471ee</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/17/gccs-new-fortification-level"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article describes a new level of fortification supported in GCC. This new level detects more buffer overflows and bugs which mitigates security issues in applications at run time.
C programs routinely suffer from memory management problems. For several years, a _FORTIFY_SOURCE preprocessor macro inserted error detection to address these problems at compile time and run time. To add an extra level of security, _FORTIFY_SOURCE=3 has been in the GNU C Library (glibc) since version 2.34. I described its mechanisms in my previous blog post, Broadening compiler checks for buffer overflows in _FORTIFY_SOURCE. There has been compiler support for this builtin in Clang for some time. Compiler support has also been available for GCC since the release of version 12 in May 2022. The new mitigation…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddhesh Poyarekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Basic Go tooling for generics]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/basic-go-tooling-for-generics/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/basic-go-tooling-for-generics/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T14:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Continuing the recent theme of blog posts about <a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/tag/go-tooling">Go tooling</a>, this post will briefly
discuss how analysis tools interact with one of Go's newest features - generics.
As usual, this post provides a motivating example and discusses a couple of
approaches to writing a tool. The full code is <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/eliben/code-for-blog/tree/master/2022/go-tool-generic-calls">on GitHub …</a></p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding smarts to a garage door isn’t always ideal]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10961</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/adding-smarts-to-a-garage-door-isnt-always-ideal/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, we took a question from Sam on our Voicemail hotline. Sam has a Chamberlain MyQ connected garage door opener and he wants to make it easier for his children to open the garage. Currently, Sam can open the garage with his phone or with old-school Genie remotes typically […]
The post Adding smarts to a garage door isn’t always ideal appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Picoprobe: Using the Raspberry Pi Pico as Debug Probe]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=35421</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/09/17/picoprobe-using-the-raspberry-pi-pico-as-debug-probe/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T10:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Getting Started: Raspberry Pi Pico RP2040 with Eclipse and J-Link I used a SEGGER J-Link EDU for debugging: unfortunately, probably because of silicon shortage, these EDU probes are out of stock everywhere. Luckily, there is a solution: just use another … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글로벌 SaaS 만드시려면, ‘제발’ 영어 콘텐츠랑 SEO 하셔야 합니다]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2189</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2022/09/17/please-kr-do-seo-for-going-global/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=please-kr-do-seo-for-going-global"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T08:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국에도 SaaS 스타트업이 인기를 얻어 많은 SaaS 기반의 스타트업이 등장하는 것이 반갑습니다. 하지만, 아래 분석에서도 살펴볼 수 있듯, 인수합병을 생각하는 것이 아니라면, 유의미한 타깃 시장 (TAM: Total Addressable Market)이 최소 2~5조 원이 필요한 SaaS 산업에서 해외 진출은 선택이 아닌 필수입니다. 해외 진출을 바꾸어 말하면, 해외 고객의 유치, 해외 고객의 매출을 중심으로 한 성장을 말하며, 이를Continue reading "글로벌 SaaS 만드시려면, ‘제발’ 영어 콘텐츠랑 SEO 하셔야 합니다"
글로벌 SaaS 만드시려면, ‘제발’ 영어 콘텐츠랑 SEO 하셔야 합니다 appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내부의 순수성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222876905666</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222876905666"/>
        <updated>2022-09-17T02:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[그가 내부와 외부의 이분법을 공박하는 것은 어떤 의미에서 비트겐슈타인이 마음 내부와 마음 외부의 이분법을 공박하는 것과 같다. 물론 내부와 외부의 이분법을 공박한다고 해서, 내부와 외부의 이원성을 부정하는 것은 아니다. 외부와 단절된 순수한 내부성, 바로 이런 생각을 공박하는 것이다. 이럼에도 왜 내부와 외부를 공박하는 그의 주장에 선뜻 찬동하지 못했는가? <내부의 순수성은 비본질적이며 오히려 본질에 해가 되는 하나의 대리 보충(supplement)으로서, 즉 그 내부의 훼손되지 않은 완전성을 위해서는 결코 부가되지 말았어야 할 어떤 잉여로서,(그 오염의) 책임들이 외부로 돌려질 때, 오로지 그때에만 복원될 수 있다. 그.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eu Cyber Resilience Act]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21681</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/eu-cyber-resilience-act/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T19:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Initial Look A European proposal for a regulation that 'bolsters cybersecurity rules to ensure more secure hardware and software products' within European Union internal markets has been published (Sept 15th). The Eu Cyber Resilience Act (CRA) is the current culmination of a thorough process and has, according to the proposal, has had input from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My advice for updating Docker Hub's OpenJDK image]]></title>
        <id>3bcb8704-1585-4386-8123-ee3bcc089043</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/16/updating-docker-hubs-openjdk-image"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Java runtime environment in your containers could stop receiving updates in the coming months. It's time to take action. This article explains the decisions that led to this issue and proposes a solution.
OpenJDK and Java SE updates
OpenJDK is an open source implementation of the Java Platform, Standard Edition (Java SE), on which multiple companies and contributors collaborate.
A project at OpenJDK represents each new feature release of the Java SE specification. Subsequent updates to those features, including functional and security fixes, are led by maintainers working in the JDK updates project. Long-term supported releases such as Java SE 8 (since March 2014), Java SE 11 (since Sept 2018), and Java SE 17 (since Sept 2021) undergo a quarterly release update under the guidance of a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Ellison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 16, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10994</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-16-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EU is proposing some good security rules for connected hardware: On Thursday the EU proposed a Cyber Resilience Act that would mandate that connected products come with specific security rules. One of the rules is that a device come with a specified support time frame or that the device be supported for up to five years […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 16, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Discovery Ad Performance Analysis]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/introducing-discovery-ad-performance-analysis.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/introducing-discovery-ad-performance-analysis.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Manisha Arora, Nithya Mahadevan, and Aritra Biswas, gPS Data Science team
  

 
Overview of Discovery Ads and need for Ad Performance Analysis
 
Discovery ads, launched in May 2019, allow advertisers to easily extend their reach of social ads users across YouTube, Google Feed and Gmail worldwide. They provide brands a new opportunity to reach 3 billion people as they explore their interests and search for inspiration across their favorite Google feeds (YouTube, Gmail, and Discover) -- all with a single campaign. Learn more about Discovery ads here.


Due to these uniquenesses, customers need a data driven method to identify textual & imagery elements in Discovery Ad copies that drive Interaction Rate of their Discovery Ad campaigns, where interaction is defined as the main user a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 steps to designing an embedded software architecture, Step 1]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476278</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-steps-to-designing-an-embedded-software-architecture-step-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T15:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some think that a clean software architecture can just emerge from coding efforts but that’s like believing that pouring a package of spaghetti into boiling...
The post 5 steps to designing an embedded software architecture, Step 1 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 common mistakes in audio signal chain designs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476273</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-common-mistakes-in-audio-signal-chain-designs/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T14:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[These five common issues in signal chain designs in cost-sensitive audio solutions, if solved, will have everything working together as a balancing act. There’s a...
The post 5 common mistakes in audio signal chain designs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruce Ryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Arrival of Zero Trust: What Does it Mean?]]></title>
        <id>3561826</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3561826"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T12:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The road to Zettalinux]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908026/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908026/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T12:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody should need more memory than a 64-bit pointer can address — or so
developers tend to think.  The range covered by a pointer of that size
seems to be nearly infinite.  During the Kernel Summit track at the 2022 Linux Plumbers Conference, Matthew
Wilcox took the stage to make the point that 64 bits may turn out to
be too few — and sooner than we think.  It is not too early to start
planning for 128-bit Linux systems, which he termed "ZettaLinux", and we
don't want to find ourselves wishing we'd started sooner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908297/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908297/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T11:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bzip2, chromium, glib2.0, libraw, mariadb-10.3, and mod-wsgi), Fedora (kdiskmark, wordpress, and zlib), Oracle (.NET 6.0, .NET Core 3.1, mariadb:10.3, nodejs:14, nodejs:16, ruby:2.7, and ruby:3.0), Red Hat (.NET 6.0, php:7.4, and webkit2gtk3), SUSE (389-ds, flatpak, kernel, libgit2, and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (sqlite3, vim, and wayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[금융노조가 총파업에 나선 이유: 금융공공성 강화 위한 세 가지 방안]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87016</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87016"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T09:26:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[전국금융산업노조(금융노조)가 9월 16일 오늘 6년 만에 총파업에 총파업에 돌입했다. 5대 시중은행인 KB국민‧신한‧하나‧우리‧NH농협의 참여율은 0.8% 수준으로 저조했지만, 부산으로의 이전으로 노사가 대립하고 있는 산업은행의 파업 참여율은 전체 조합원의 78%인 약 1,600여 명에 이르렀다. 금감원에 의하면, 전체 파업 참여율은 9.4% 정도고, 조합원 수를 기준으로는 13.6%인 9,807명이 파업에 참여했다. 금융노조가 은행에 요구하는 건 뭘까. 금융노조가 총파업에 나선 이유를 하나씩 […]
The post 금융노조가 총파업에 나선 이유: 금융공공성 강화 위한 세 가지 방안 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Regex how-to: Quantifiers, pattern collections, and word boundaries]]></title>
        <id>2182a29a-626a-444f-a313-1e4a14d6eeb7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/16/regex-how-quantifiers-pattern-collections-and-word-boundaries"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filtering and searching text with regular expressions is an important skill for every developer. Regular expressions can be tricky to master. To work with them effectively, you need a detailed understanding of their symbols and syntax.
Fortunately, learning to work with regular expressions can be incremental. You don't need to learn everything all at once to do useful work. Rather, you can start with the basics and then move into more complex topics while developing your understanding and using what you know as you go along.
This article is the second in a series. The first article introduced some basic elements of regular expressions: The basic metacharacters (.*^$\s\d) as well as the escape metacharacter \.
This article introduces some more advanced syntax: quantifiers, pattern collectio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Reselman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See My New Book: C++ Initialization Story]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/cpp-init-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/cpp-init-book/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to announce that my new book on C++ Initialization is published!
Have a look at the background story and how to get it.
Note: Initially, the book was called “Data Member Initialization in Modern C++”, but in September 2022, I updated it heavily and changed the title.



     
    


As for my other books, I used the Leanpub platform for the PDF/Epub generation. Here’s the book’s website:

C++ Initialization Story @Leanpub 


And also have a look at Goodreads: C++ Initialization Story by Bartłomiej Filipek and leave youre review.



     
    


Initialization in C++ is a hot topic. With each C++ Standard, we’ll get some updates to the syntax, rules, and new capabilities. With this book, I wanted to clarify the confusion and make it simpler to reason about Modern C++ code.
Have I …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 질병을 앓는 이에게 공감하는 법에 관하여]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75276</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/15/npc_cancerempathy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_cancerempathy"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T22:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[큰 병을 앓게 된 사람들이 병으로 인한 육체적인 괴로움 외에 공통적으로 꼽는 어려움이 있습니다. 정신적인 고통과 더불어, 좋지 않은 소식을 접한 주변 사람들과의 관계인데요, 가족과 친구의 존재는 어려운 상황에서 심리적 지지대 역할을 하기도 하지만, (때로는 나쁜 의도가 없는) 배려 없는 말과 행동이 환자들에게 큰 상처를 주기도 합니다. 지난달 초, 워싱턴포스트는 암 환자와 대화할 때 지켜야 할 에티켓에 관한 칼럼을 실었습니다. 암 생존자인 필자는 칼럼 서두에 각종 “나쁜 예”를 소개합니다. 처음 만난 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come to the Tag1 & Google Performance Workshop at DrupalCon Europe 2022, Prague]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/come-to-tag1-google-performance-workshop-at-drupalcon-europe-2022-prague.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/come-to-tag1-google-performance-workshop-at-drupalcon-europe-2022-prague.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Andrey Lipattsev, EMEA CMS Partnerships Lead 
    

  
TL;DR: If you’re attending @DrupalConEur submit your URL @ https://bit.ly/CWV-DrupalCon-22 to get your UX & performance right on #Drupal at the Tag1 & Google interactive workshop.


Getting your User Experience right, which includes performance, is critical for success. It’s a key driver of many success metrics (https://web.dev/tags/web-vitals) and a factor taken into account by platforms, including search engines, that surface links to your site (https://developers.google.com/search/docs/advanced/experience/page-experience).
Quantifying User Experience is not always easy, so one way to measure, track and improve it is by using Core Web Vitals (CWV, https://web.dev/vitals/). Building a site with great CWV on Drupal is easier than on many platforms on average (https://bit.ly/CWV-tech-report) and yet there are certain tips and pitfalls you should be aware of.  
In this workshop the team from Tag1 and Google (Michael Meyers, Andrey Lipattsev and others) will use real life examples of Drupal-based websites to illustrate some common pain points and the corresponding solutions. If you would like us to take a look at your website and provide actionable advice, please submit the URL via this link (https://bit.ly/CWV-DrupalCon-22). The Workshop is interactive, so bring your laptop - we'll get you up and running and teach you hands-on how to code for the relevant improvements.
We cannot guarantee that all the submissions will be analysed as this depends on the number of submissions and the time that we have. However, we will make sure that all the major themes cutting across the submitted sites will be covered with relevant solutions.
See you in Prague! 
  
Date & Time: Wednesday 21.09.2022, 16:15-18:00]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Tactics to Unit Test RTOS Tasks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14341</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/4-tactics-to-unit-test-rtos-tasks/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T15:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 50% of all embedded software projects use Real-time Operating Systems (RTOS). Unfortunately, using an RTOS can pose several problems to developers looking to use modern development techniques such as Test-Driven Development (TDD), DevOps, or automated test harnesses. For example, the first problem developers encounter when they try to write tests for their tasks … Continue reading 4 Tactics to Unit Test RTOS Tasks
4 Tactics to Unit Test RTOS Tasks first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crash Consistency]]></title>
        <id>3561654</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3561654"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T14:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The perils of pinning]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907876/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907876/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:42:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Parts of the Rust language may look familiar to C programmers, but the two
languages differ in fundamental ways.  One difference that turns out to be
problematic for kernel programming is the stability of data in memory — or
the lack thereof.  A challenging session at the 2022 Kangrejos conference wrestled with
ways to deal with objects that should not be moved behind the programmer's
back.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Is Matter ready for its close up?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10987</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-is-matter-ready-for-its-close-up/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m in Austin this week, for Silicon Labs’ Works With event, and while there I hosted a panel that provided a good sense of what is going to happen with the Matter smart home interoperability protocol. I think Kevin is a bit more optimistic than I am. We also got some small updates on Amazon’s […]
The post Podcast: Is Matter ready for its close up? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908138/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908138/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T12:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 5.19.9, 5.15.68, 5.10.143, 5.4.213, 4.19.258, 4.14.293, and 4.9.328 stable kernels.  As usual, they
contain important fixes throughout the kernel tree; users of those series
should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908137/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908137/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T12:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (nova, pcs, and rails), Fedora (firejail, moby-engine, and pspp), Oracle (.NET 6.0, gnupg2, kernel, python3, and rsyslog rsyslog7), Red Hat (.NET 6.0 and .NET Core 3.1), SUSE (kernel), and Ubuntu (intel-microcode, poppler, and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[검찰개혁 역주행 방지법이 필요하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87007</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87007"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T08:48:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 정부의 검찰개혁 역행을 막을 제대로된 수사-기소 분리 법안 통과를 위해 형사사법개혁특별위원회(이하 ‘사개특위’) 논의를 촉구해주세요. 캠페인에 참여하시면 논의 촉구 내용이 담긴 메시지가 사개특위 소속 의원들에게 직.접. 발송됩니다 검찰 직접수사 왜 더 확대되었죠? 2020년 수사권조정이 되었습니다: 수사권과 기소권 모두 무제한 행사하며 무소불위 권력을 누렸던 검찰 권한을 분산해야 한다는 요구가 조금은 해소되었습니다. 검경 간 수사권이 조정되어 검찰은 […]
The post 검찰개혁 역주행 방지법이 필요하다 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Silicon macOS에서 iOS 바이너리 구동]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13088407</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13088407"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T02:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[애플 실리콘(Apple Silicon)이 탑재된 macOS 환경은 사실상 iOS와 동일한 arm64 ISA(instruction set architecture)를 갖는다. 그렇기 때문에 iOS용으로 빌드된 바이너리를 macOS에서 native speed로 구동할 수 있을 것이라는 관측이 있었고, 실제로 Google Project Zero의 Samuel Groß 이 이를 분석한 글을 게시했다. 
https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2021/05/fuzzing-ios-code-on-macos-at-native.html
본 포스팅에서는 해당 글에 대한 약간의 번역 + 내 나름대로의 분석 + 실험을 해보려고 한다.
우선 Samuel에 따르면 macOS에 존재하지 않는 iOS 관련 런타임 라이브러리와 프레임웍들이 /System/iOSSupport 형태로 제공되기 때문에 대부분 호환이 가능할 것으로 전망했다. 
그렇다면 이를 이용하면 단순히 애플리케이션 형태 뿐만 아니라, iOS용 바이너리와 라이브러리 파일들도 macOS에서 구동할 수 있을 것이다. 이렇게 된다면 iOS용으로 컴파일된 상용 프로그램을 퍼징할 때 보다 성능이 좋은 macOS 컴퓨터에서 수행할 수 있다는 장점이 있다. 그리고 iOS 코드를 동적으로 분석하는 경우에도 보다 용이한 환경이 제공된다.
우리의 목표는 임의의 iOS용 바이너리와 라이브러리들을 iOS와 동일한 수준으로 macOS환경에서 직접 구동할 것이다. 이를 실험하기 위해 몇가지 코드를 테스트할 것이다. 기본적으로 실험에 사용된 환경은 SIP(System Inte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이샤야 벌린의 소극적 자유]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222875109883</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222875109883"/>
        <updated>2022-09-15T01:08:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아주 중요한, 서로 구분되어야 하는 두 가지 의미의 자유 개념이 있다. <첫 번째의 의미를 나는 “소극적(negative)” 의미라고 한다. 이것은 다음과 같은 질문에 대한 답변에 함유되는 종류의 것이다. “인민, 한 사람 또는 일군의 사람이 다른 사람의 간섭 없이 스스로 할 수 있는 일을 할 수 있도록, 또는 스스로 될 수 있는 존재가 될 수 있도록 방임되어야 할 영역은 무엇인가?” 두 번째 의미를 나는 적극적(positive） 의미라 지칭한다. 이것은 다음과 같은 질문에 대한 답변에 함축되는 종류이다. “한 사람으로 하여금 이것 말고 저것을 하게끔, 이런 사람 말고 저런 사람이 되게끔 결정할 수 있는 통제 및 간섭의 근원이 누구 또는.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 15, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907454/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907454/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T23:12:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 15, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The check of the Rhino JavaScript engine or how the unicorn met the rhino]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/0990/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/0990/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the wide variety of programming languages, what our users want the most is that the PVS-Studio analyzer to start supporting JavaScript. The Rhino engine is a project that our team can use to create a PVS-Studio analyzer for JavaScript. In this article, we will use the PVS-Studio analyzer to check the source code of Rhino.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Git’s garbage collection (GitHub blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908035/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908035/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T17:51:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub blog has a
detailed look at garbage collection in Git and the work that has been
done to make it faster.


	To solve this problem, we turned to a long-discussed idea on the
	Git mailing list: cruft packs. The idea is simple: store an
	auxiliary list of mtime data alongside a pack containing
	just unreachable objects. To garbage collect a repository, Git
	places the unreachable objects in a pack. That pack is designated
	as a “cruft pack” because Git also writes the mtime data
	corresponding to each object in a separate file alongside that
	pack. This makes it possible to update the mtime of a
	single unreachable object without changing the mtimes of
	any other unreachable object.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unicode 15 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/908032/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/908032/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T17:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
15 of the Unicode standard has been released.


	This version adds 4,489 characters, bringing the total to 149,186
	characters. These additions include two new scripts, for a total of
	161 scripts, along with 20 new emoji characters, and 4,193 CJK
	(Chinese, Japanese, and Korean) ideographs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A level set on Matter and its future]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10971</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/a-level-set-on-matter-and-its-future/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T17:24:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we near the availability of Matter devices, this is the perfect time to understand exactly what to expect once we have those devices in our home. That’s the main takeaway I got from virtually attending a Silicon Labs Works With session on Tuesday. Panelists included representatives from Arm, The Connectivity Standards Alliance, Comcast, Google, […]
The post A level set on Matter and its future appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Helping Developers Build with Google, Matters]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/helping-developers-build-with-google-matters.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/helping-developers-build-with-google-matters.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeannie Zhang and Kevin Po; Product Managers, Nest
 

As the smart home industry prepares for a major shift in usability and interoperability with Matter launching later this year, we are working to help you build more devices and connections with Google products and beyond. 
At Google I/O this year, we shared updates on how Google is continuing to support smart home developers, including the launch of our new and improved Google Home Developer Center. Today, we are excited to share that the Google Home Developer Console is now in Developer Preview at console.home.google.com.

What is the Google Home Developer Console?

The Google Home Developer Console is a guided flow for developers looking to integrate with Google. It provides everything needed to build intelligent and innovat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[신구대식물원 꽃무릇을 담아보다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587780</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587780/%ec%8b%a0%ea%b5%ac%eb%8c%80%ec%8b%9d%eb%ac%bc%ec%9b%90-%ea%bd%83%eb%ac%b4%eb%a6%87"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[분당 중앙공원 꽃무릇을  담아보다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587764</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587764/%eb%b6%84%eb%8b%b9-%ec%a4%91%ec%95%99%ea%b3%b5%ec%9b%90-%ea%bd%83%eb%ac%b4%eb%a6%87"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T13:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8월 CPI을 보는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587758</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587758/8%ec%9b%94-cpi-%ed%95%b4%ec%84%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T12:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Four Horsemen of an Ailing Software Project]]></title>
        <id>3561798</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3561798"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T12:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A Python security fix breaks (some) bignums]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907572/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907572/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:38:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Typically, an urgent security release of a project is not for a
two-year-old CVE, but such is the case for a recent
Python release of four versions of the language.  The bug is a
denial of service (DoS) that can be caused by converting enormous numbers to
strings—or vice versa—but it was not deemed serious enough to fix
when it 
was first 
reported.  Evidently more recent reports, including a remote exploit of the
bug, have raised its importance—causing a rushed-out fix.  But the
fix breaks some existing Python code, and the process of handling the
incident has left something to be desired, leading the project to look at
ways to improve its processes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907983/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907983/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T11:31:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (open-vm-tools), Debian (freecad and sqlite3), Fedora (qt5-qtwebengine and vim), SUSE (firefox, kernel, libzapojit, perl, postgresql14, and samba), and Ubuntu (dotnet6, dpdk, gdk-pixbuf, rust-regex, and systemd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내부자거래 사전공시제도, 환영하지만 더 확대 적용해야]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86997</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86997"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T07:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어제(9월 13일) 금융위원회(이하 ‘금융위’)는 “상장회사 내부자(임원 및 지분율 10%이상 경영대주주)가 발행주식 수의 1%이상 또는 거래대금 50억원 이상 매매 시에는 30일 전에 사전공시 의무를 부과하겠다.”고 발표했다 지난해(2021년) 12월 10일 카카오페이 류영준 대표이사 등 경영진 8명이 코스피200 지수편입 당일 상장 때(11월 3일) 행사했던 스톡옵션(주식매수선택권) 주식 총 440,933주, 시가 899억원 상당을 매도하여 상장 대비 약 92억원(옵션 대비 약 […]
The post 내부자거래 사전공시제도, 환영하지만 더 확대 적용해야 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A beginner’s guide to regular expressions with grep]]></title>
        <id>d2745cb9-0e7f-4c18-88b2-a5ce98fb99ac</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/14/beginners-guide-regular-expressions-grep"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A regular expression (also called a regex or regexp) is a rule that a computer can use to match characters or groups of characters within a larger body of text. For instance, using regular expressions, you could find all the instances of the word cat in a document, or all instances of a word that begins with c and ends with t.
Use of regular expressions in the real world can get much more complex—and powerful—than that. For example, imagine you need to write code verifying that all content in the body of an HTTP POST request is free of script injection attacks. Malicious code can appear in any number of ways, but you know that injected script code will always appear between  HTML tags. You can apply the regular expression .*, which matches any block of code text bracketed by  tags, to the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Reselman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[윤리와 사상] 자유주의와 공화주의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222874178709</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222874178709"/>
        <updated>2022-09-14T00:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 현대 사회사상가 갑, 을의 입장으로 적절한 것만을 〈보기〉에서 고른 것은? 갑: 지배 없는 상태로서의 자유와 간섭 없는 상태로서의 자유가 충돌할 때, 전자를 후자보다 우선해야 한다. 그것이 공화국의 핵심이다. 공화국의 공공선은 지배 없는 상태로서의 자유를 추구하는 시민들에게 좋은 것을 의미한다. 을: 자유라는 것은 한 사람 또는 일군의 사람이 다른 사람의 간섭 없이 스스로 할 수 있는 일을 할 수 있도록 방임되어야 할 영역은 무엇인가에 관한 물음과 관련된다. 이것은 통제나 간섭의 근원을 묻는 적극적 의미의 자유와 구분된다. 갑과 을이 누군지 알 수 있는가? 대충 을이 누구지 짐작할 수 있었지만, 그 짐작이 맞는지 자신이.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updates to Emoji: New Characters, New Animation, New Color Customization, and More!]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/updates-to-emoji-new-characters-animation-colors-and-more.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/updates-to-emoji-new-characters-animation-colors-and-more.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T19:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jennifer Daniel, Emoji and Expression Creative Director
     @import url('https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Noto+Emoji&display=swap'); @import url('https://fonts.googleapis.com/css2?family=Noto+Color+Emoji&display=swap');   }         
It’s official: new emoji are here, there, and everywhere.
But what exactly is “new” and where is “here”? Great question. 
Emoji have long eclipsed their humble beginnings in sms text messages in the 1990’s. Today, they appear in places you'd never expect like self-checkout kiosks, television screens and yes, even refrigerators 😂. As emoji increase in popularity and advance in how they are used, the Noto Emoji project has stepped up our emoji game to help everyone get “🫠” without having to buy a new device (or a new refrigerator). 
Over the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 ways to make the most of remote working]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476458</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/7-ways-to-make-the-most-of-remote-working/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T17:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pearls and pitfalls of working from home as an engineer. One of the many side products of the COVID-19 pandemic has been the emergence...
The post 7 ways to make the most of remote working appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Pitchford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LXC and LXD: a different container story]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907613/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907613/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T17:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OCI containers are the most popular type
of Linux container, but they are not the only type, nor were they the
first.  LXC (short for "LinuX
Containers")  predates Docker by several years, though it was also not the
first.  LXC dates back to its first release in 2008; the earliest version of
Docker, which was tagged in 2013, was actually a wrapper around LXC.
The LXC project is still going strong and shows no signs of winding
down; LXC 5.0 was released in July and comes with a promise of support until
2027.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Features Available in the Google Identity Services (GIS) Library]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/new-features-available-in-google-identity-services-library.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/new-features-available-in-google-identity-services-library.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gina Biernacki, Product Manager
  

 At Google, we're committed to making authentication safer and easier for our developers, so users can easily access the apps and websites they love. Google Identity Services (GIS) continues to advance and further develop our authentication solutions that offer immense value to our partner ecosystem, including highly requested features including a new verified phone number directly embedded in our authentication flows. 
For developers, our focus has always been to offer a frictionless experience that makes it easier for users to onboard and return to partner platforms, while also helping developers create a trusted relationship with their users.

What’s New
Today we are announcing a few new features that are now available across our libraries: …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: Arrays and pointer arithmetic]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476224</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/learn-how-to-program-embedded-systems-arrays-and-pointer-arithmetic/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T16:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This second installment of the “Programming embedded systems” series covers arrays and pointer arithmetic, but obviously, with an embedded twist. Welcome to the second installment...
The post Programming embedded systems: Arrays and pointer arithmetic appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our Cities Have an API Problem. Startups Can Fix It.]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7073</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/cities-broken-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Cities are technological artifacts,” Kevin Kelly once wrote, “the largest technology we make.” What if we looked at America’s cities not metaphorically as tech, but literally as a technological system? Rather than fighting about politics, we’d ask our cities the mundane questions that engineers and entrepreneurs ask about any other technology: “Is it expensive to... Read More
The post Our Cities Have an API Problem. Startups Can Fix It. appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zach Caceres</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907869/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907869/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T14:23:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (connman and python-oslo.utils), Fedora (libapreq2), Red Hat (booth, gnupg2, kernel, kernel-rt, mariadb:10.3, nodejs:14, nodejs:16, python3, ruby:2.7, and ruby:3.0), SUSE (chromium, opera, python2-numpy, and rubygem-kramdown), and Ubuntu (poppler).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Luos adds plug and play microservices to ESP32 MCU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476220</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/luos-adds-plug-and-play-microservices-to-esp32-mcu/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T14:08:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for ESP32 MCUs means developer community add plug and play functionality and bring microservices approach to IoT products.
The post Luos adds plug and play microservices to ESP32 MCU appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSRB's Opus One]]></title>
        <id>3561797</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3561797"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T13:17:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why smart glasses are on the cusp of being a gamechanger]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10931</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-smart-glasses-are-on-the-cusp-of-being-a-gamechanger/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to believe that Google Glass debuted nearly a decade ago. I was one of the early “Glass Explorers,” which is a far kinder name than the other ones that were used to describe people like me at the time. Google Glass both ushered in the smart glasses movement and quickly died off as a consumer […]
The post Why smart glasses are on the cusp of being a gamechanger appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renesas delivers RISC-V based motor control ASSP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476215</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/renesas-delivers-risc-v-based-motor-control-assp/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T11:48:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pre-programmed motor control ASSP eliminates RISC-V related tools and software investment, making it easier to target applications such as home and building automation, healthcare devices, and drones.
The post Renesas delivers RISC-V based motor control ASSP appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agenda Deep Dive – IoT Security Foundation Conference 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21674</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/agenda-deep-dive-iot-security-foundation-conference-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T09:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are looking forward to welcoming you to the IoTSF Annual Conference on October 5th But what can you expect? On offer this year are leading speakers from across the IoT Security field and great opportunities to meet people from across the sector during the day, at the drinks reception and the networking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>-</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트위터에서 생긴 일: 케이크 디아망의 기적 (ft. 사자솜)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86982</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86982"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T09:16:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘케이크 디아망’은 경기도 용인시 서천동에 위치한 제과점으로 빵과 케이크와 커피 음료를 파는 소담스러운 가게다. 2020년 여름께 문을 연것으로 보이는 이 가게는 흔히 다른 베이커리나 카페들이 그렇듯 인스타그램에 계정을 만들었고, 다시 1년이 지나서는 트위터에도 가게를 알리기 위한 계정을 개설했다. 케이크 디아망의 작은 기적 (ft. 사자솜)  그리고 코로나가 모두를 덮치는 나날 사이 가끔씩 타임라인에 먹음직스런 빵 사진과 […]
The post 트위터에서 생긴 일: 케이크 디아망의 기적 (ft. 사자솜) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nomodem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kafka Monthly Digest: August 2022]]></title>
        <id>195c9344-8250-48a9-9554-85515b7d00a9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/13/kafka-monthly-digest-august-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This 55th edition of the Kafka Monthly Digest covers what happened in the Apache Kafka community in August 2022.
For last month’s digest, see Kafka Monthly Digest: July 2022.
Releases
There is currently one release in progress, 3.3.0.
3.3.0
The release process for 3.3.0 continued. José Armando García Sancio published the first release candidate on August 29. A few issues, including KAFKA-14187 and KAFKA-14156, were found during testing, so José built RC1 on September 1. The vote is currently ongoing. You can find the release plan in the wiki.
Kafka Improvement Proposals
Last month, the community submitted three Kafka Improvement Proposals (KIPs) (KIP-863 to KIP-865). I'll highlight a couple of them:
KIP-864: Add End-To-End Latency Metrics to Connectors. This KIP proposes adding a few new m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mickael Maison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Derivative of the Exponential Function]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/derivative-of-the-exponential-function/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/derivative-of-the-exponential-function/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-13T03:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It's a known piece of math folklore that <em>e</em> was &quot;discovered&quot; by Jacob Bernoulli
in the 17th century, when he was <a class="reference external" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/E_(mathematical_constant)#Compound_interest">pondering compound interest</a>,
and defined thus <a class="footnote-reference" href="#id3" id="id1">[1]</a>:</p>
<object class="align-center" data="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/images/math/b38717ee73c9714fb983060c8880bbcddbd7ece8.svg" style="height: 43px;" type="image/svg+xml">
\[e=\displaystyle \lim_{n \to \infty}\left ( 1+\frac{1}{n}\right )^n\]</object>
<p><em>e</em> is extremely important in mathematics for several reasons …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모리스 엥겔의 <비트겐슈타인과 칸트> 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222873193286</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222873193286"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T23:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인과 칸트에 대한 모리스 엥겔(Morris Engel)의 논문은 1970년에 나왔다. 오래 되었지만, 칸트와 비트겐슈타인에 대해서 고찰하고 있는 초창기에 몇 안 되는 논문이다. 흥미롭게 엥겔은 그 당시까지 나왔던 비트겐슈타인에 관한 저술들에서 칸트에 대한 고찰이 얼마나 희미했는지를 보여주고 있다. 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 관계는 비트겐슈타인 학자들에 의해 거의 무시되었지만, 그럼에도 막스 블랙, 스테니우스, 알렉산더 매슬로, 카벨 등이 비트겐슈타인과 칸트의 유사성에 대해서 지적하고 있다. 막스 블랙은 <Companion to Wittgenstein's Tractatus>(1964)에서 비트겐슈타인이 “어떻게 순수 수학이 가능한가?”라는 칸.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 상처만 남긴 보리스 존슨 총리의 3년]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75258</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/12/npc_ukjohnsonexit/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_ukjohnsonexit"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T22:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[보리스 존슨 총리가 총리 자리에서 물러나겠다고 밝힌 뒤 7월 13일에 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 쓴 글입니다.   2016년 6월 영국 국민은 국민투표를 통해 유럽연합을 탈퇴하겠다고 선언합니다. 유럽연합의 일원으로 계속 남아있어야 한다는 의견보다 52%:48%로 근소하게 앞선 표 차였지만, 어쨌든 국민투표 결과는 결과였습니다. 집권 보수당은 국민투표 결과에 자신의 직을 걸었던 데이비드 캐머런 총리의 후임으로 테리사 메이 총리를 구원투수로 투입합니다. 유럽연합에서 탈퇴하기로 했어도 아예 모든 관계를 끊고 남으로 지내는 건 아니니 유럽의 일원이 아닌 영국과 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-standard containers in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0989/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0989/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Container is an object which stores a collection of related objects (or elements). The container manages the storage space that is allocated for its elements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud & Kotlin GDE Kevin Davin helps others learn in the face of challenges]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-cloud-kotlin-gde-kevin-davin-helps-others-learn-in-the-face-of-challenges.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-cloud-kotlin-gde-kevin-davin-helps-others-learn-in-the-face-of-challenges.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kevin Hernandez, , Developer Relations Community Manager
 

 


Kevin Davin speaking at the SnowCamp Conference in 2019


Kevin Davin has always had a passion for learning and helping others learn, no matter their background or unique challenges they may face. He explains, “I want to learn something new every day, I want to help others learn, and I’m addicted to learning.” This mantra is evident in everything he does from giving talks at numerous conferences to helping people from underrepresented groups overcome imposter syndrome and even helping them become GDEs. In addition to learning, Kevin is also passionate about diversity and inclusion efforts, partly inspired by navigating the world with partial blindness.


Kevin has been a professional programmer for 10 years now and h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we can learn about buttons from the Hue Tap Dial switch]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10955</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/what-we-can-learn-about-buttons-from-the-hue-tap-dial-switch/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T13:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[First up, I love buttons. While voice is convenient and routines and other automations are the best way to keep a smart home running smoothly most of the time, buttons are the tool I reach for when life gets weird. Maybe you’re sleeping poorly and want to get up in the middle of the night to […]
The post What we can learn about buttons from the Hue Tap Dial switch appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A pair of Rust kernel modules]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907685/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907685/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T11:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The idea of being able to write kernel code in the Rust language has a
certain appeal, but it is hard to judge how well that would actually work
in the absence of examples to look at.  Those examples, especially for
modules beyond the "hello world" level of complexity, have been somewhat
scarce, but that is beginning to change.  At the 2022 Kangrejos gathering
in Oviedo, Spain, two developers presented the modules they have developed
and some lessons that have been learned from this exercise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11.0rc2 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/09/python-3110rc2-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/09/python-3110rc2-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T11:26:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second release candidate of Python 3.11
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3110rc2/
This release, 3.11.0rc2, is the last preview before the final release of Python 3.11.0 on 2022-10-24.
Entering the release candidate phase, only reviewed code changes which are clear bug fixes are allowed between this release candidate and the final release. The second candidate and the last planned release preview is currently planned for Monday, 2022-09-05 while the official release is planned for Monday, 2022-10-24.
There will be no ABI changes from this point forward in the 3.11 series and the goal is that there will be as few code changes as possible.
Modification of the final release
Due to the fact that we needed to delay the last release candidate by a week and because of pe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907770/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907770/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T10:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (gdk-pixbuf, libxslt, linux-5.10, paramiko, and zlib), Fedora (webkit2gtk3), Mageia (gstreamer1.0-plugins-good, jupyter-notebook, kernel, and rpm), Slackware (vim), SUSE (bluez, clamav, freetype2, frr, gdk-pixbuf, keepalived, libyang, nodejs16, python-PyYAML, qpdf, samba, and vim), and Ubuntu (linux-azure-fde and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making the Fancy User Interface on ESP Has Never Been Easier!]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/e44e79c0ae3</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/making-the-fancy-user-interface-on-esp-has-never-been-easier-e44e79c0ae3?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T08:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you tried to make some fancy UI without any graphic library, you know, how hard it is. Fortunately, there are lot of graphical libraries…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vilem Zavodny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.0-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907729/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907729/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T06:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.0-rc5 for testing.
"Nothing looks particularly scary, so jump right in".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integer Conversions and Safe Comparisons in C++20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/safe-int-cmp-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/safe-int-cmp-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, If you mix different integer types in an expression, you might end up with tricky cases. For example, comparing long with size_t might give different results than long with unsigned short. C++20 brings some help, and there’s no need to learn all the complex rules :)



     
    


Let’s have a look at two comparisons:
#include <iostream>

int main() {
    long a = -100;
    unsigned short b = 100;
    std::cout << (a < b);   // 1
    size_t c = 100;
    std::cout << (a < c);   // 2
}   


If you run the code @Compiler Explorer (GCC 12, x86-64, default flags) you’ll see:
10


Why? Why not 11?
(By the way, I asked that question on Twitter, see https://twitter.com/fenbf/status/1568566458333990914 - thank you for all the answers and hints)
If we run C++Insights, we’ll see the follo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Futurist prediction methods and accuracy]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/futurist-predictions/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/futurist-predictions/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been reading a lot of predictions from people who are looking to understand what problems humanity will face 10-50 years out (and sometimes longer) in order to work in areas that will be instrumental for the future and wondering how accurate these predictions of the future are. The timeframe of predictions that are so far out means that only a tiny fraction of people making those kinds of predictions today have a track record so, if we want to evaluate which predictions are plausible, we need to look at something other than track record.
The idea behind the approach of this post was to look at predictions from an independently chosen set of predictors (Wikipedia's list of well-known futurists1) whose predictions are old enough to evaluate in order to understand which prediction techni…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[vim netrw로 탐색하기 메모]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/vim-netrw-for-quick-nav/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/vim-netrw-for-quick-nav/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T22:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[단축키/명령 탐색하기:  또는 명령행 도구에서  등 사용 새 윈도우에서 파일 열기:  또는  사용 미리보기: 탐색에서 파일 위로 커서 이동 후  미리보기 창 닫기:  설정 미리보기 우측에 표시:  미리보기 표시 크기:  탐색기 상단 표시 숨기기:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Career progression: an invisible issue in software development]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7103</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/09/11/career-progression-an-invisible-issue-in-software-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T22:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Career progression is an important issue in the development of some software systems, but its impact is rarely discussed, let along researched. A common consequence of career progression is that a project looses a member of staff, e.g., they move to work on a different project, or leave the company. Hiring staff and promoting staff […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[안양예술공원, 안양 전망대(Anyang Peak)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587743</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587743/%ec%95%88%ec%96%91%ec%98%88%ec%88%a0%ea%b3%b5%ec%9b%90-%ec%95%88%ec%96%91-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d%eb%8c%80"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T12:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aug 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/df38986c985d</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/aug-2022-df38986c985d?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-11T07:46:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 9, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10953</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-9-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T18:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trifecta of IoT fundings worth a mention: We covered these in the podcast this week, but I’m trying to be a bit more thorough with the weekly news roundups. So if you’re tracking this sort of thing, know that satellite IoT company OQ received $12.9 million in funding, Wi-Fi HaLow chip maker Morse Micro received $140 […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 9, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AutoSens, Vision 22, next gen hearables, AIaaS and more embedded]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476196</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/autosens-vision-22-next-gen-hearables-aiaas-and-more-embedded/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T16:56:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s embedded news features in-cabin monitoring at AutoSens Brussels, smart embedded vision at Vision 22, a next generation hearable design, plus the offer of AI as a service, and more.
The post AutoSens, Vision 22, next gen hearables, AIaaS and more embedded appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Request Waiting List]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/request-waiting-list.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/request-waiting-list.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T16:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nodes often have to contact several other nodes to form a quorum to
      handle a client request. Unmesh Joshi how 
      a waiting list keeps track of the outstanding requests and sorting out
      what to do when it receives enough responses.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Compiling Rust with GCC: an update]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907405/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907405/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T13:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the Rust language has appeal for kernel development, many developers are
concerned by the fact that there is only one compiler available; there are
many reasons why a second implementation would be desirable.  At the 2022
Kangrejos gathering, three developers
described projects to build Rust 
programs with GCC in two different ways.  A fully featured, GCC-based Rust
implementation is still going to take some time, but rapid progress is
being made.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907573/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907573/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T12:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (mediawiki), SUSE (libEMF, libnl-1_1, libnl3, mariadb, nodejs16, php8-pear, postgresql12, and rubygem-rake), and Ubuntu (linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Edge, zonal or central: getting the balance right for ADAS architectures]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476188</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/edge-zonal-or-central-getting-the-balance-right-for-adas-architectures/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T12:09:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three different classes of ADAS system processing are needed – edge, zonal and central – with three different profiles. Edge AI must be fast and low cost, zonal processors consolidate input from multiple edge devices, and the central driving policy engine will very likely be a high premium multi-chiplet device.
The post Edge, zonal or central: getting the balance right for ADAS architectures appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gil Abraham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A guide to the initiatives driving IoT standardization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476182</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/a-guide-to-the-initiatives-driving-iot-standardization/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T11:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the fragmentation challenges and some of the initiatives helping drive IoT standardization. Standardization helps breed creativity, innovation, and differentiation, enabling developers to leverage existing software and not need to worry about compatibility issues.
The post A guide to the initiatives driving IoT standardization appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohamed Awad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Radar detection software improves accuracy using less compute power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476175</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/radar-detection-software-improves-accuracy-using-less-compute-power/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T10:08:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Teraki’s ML-detection software on Infineon Technologies’ microcontrollers delivers more points per object, leading to less false positives and increased safety compared to other radar processing techniques, such as CFAR.
The post Radar detection software improves accuracy using less compute power appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[안양예술공원, 나무 위의 선으로 된 집(Linear Building Up in the Trees)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587730</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587730/%ec%95%88%ec%96%91%ec%98%88%ec%88%a0%ea%b3%b5%ec%9b%90-%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4-%ec%9c%84%ec%9d%98-%ec%84%a0%ec%9c%bc%eb%a1%9c-%eb%90%9c-%ec%a7%91"/>
        <updated>2022-09-09T05:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 사우디아라비아 방문 앞둔 바이든, 현실과 이상의 괴리]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75244</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/08/npc_saudiarabia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_saudiarabia"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T22:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 7월 바이든 미국 대통령이 사우디아라비아를 방문해 무함마드 빈 살만 알사우드(MBS) 사우디 왕세자를 만나고 돌아오기 전에 올라온 기사와 칼럼들을 모아 정리한 글입니다.   모든 국가가 외교 무대에서 국익을 증진하기 위해 노력하지만, 국제 관계는 현실주의와 이상주의, 명분과 실리 사이의 줄타기이기도 합니다. 미국은 압도적인 국력으로 국제 질서를 주도해온 동시에 국제무대에서 민주주의와 인권이라는 가치를 지속적으로 내세워 온 국가입니다. 말과 행동 사이의 괴리가 도마 위에 오르는 것은 피할 수 없는 운명일 것입니다. 이달 중순으로 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Simple Script to Automate C Module Creation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14315</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/a-simple-script-to-automate-c-module-creation/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T20:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During development, a very common activity is to create new C modules. Creating a new C module often comes with a bunch of repetitive work. For example, if you are creating a Gpio module, you likely have header and source comment text to copy and paste into the new files to look consistent. Undoubtedly, you … Continue reading A Simple Script to Automate C Module Creation
A Simple Script to Automate C Module Creation first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907522/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907522/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T19:52:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 5.19.8, 5.15.66, and 5.10.142. As usual, those contain important
fixes throughout the kernel tree. Immediately thereafter, he released
5.15.67 to fix a permissions problem on a
kernel build script.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The transparent huge page shrinker]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906511/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906511/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T18:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Huge pages are a mechanism implemented by the CPU that allows the management
of memory in larger chunks.  Use of huge pages can increase performance
significantly, which is why the kernel has a "transparent huge page"
mechanism to try to create them when possible.  But a huge page will only
be helpful if most of the memory contained within it is actually in use;
otherwise it is just an expensive waste of memory.  This patch
set from Alexander Zhu implements a mechanism to detect underutilized
huge pages and recover that wasted memory for other uses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907508/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907508/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libgoogle-gson-java), Fedora (autotrace, insight, and open-vm-tools), Oracle (open-vm-tools), Red Hat (open-vm-tools, openvswitch2.13, openvswitch2.15, openvswitch2.16, openvswitch2.17, ovirt-host, and rh-nodejs14-nodejs and rh-nodejs14-nodejs-nodemon), Scientific Linux (open-vm-tools), Slackware (python3), SUSE (clamav, gdk-pixbuf, gpg2, icu, ImageMagick, java-1_8_0-ibm, libyajl, mariadb, udisks2, webkit2gtk3, and yast2-samba-provision), and Ubuntu (dnsmasq).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Insurers come for the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10949</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-insurers-come-for-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week launched with a bang for those interested in the role insurers might play in the smart home as State Farm agreed to make a 1.2 billion equity investment in security firm ADT. This follows on the heels of Google’s equity investment in ADT in 2020 and signals a shift in the way insurance companies […]
The post Podcast: Insurers come for the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESP Insights: Playing with Device Tags]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/ece2c3691712</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/esp-insights-playing-with-device-tags-ece2c3691712?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T12:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s world which is completely engulfed in social media, the notion of tags is not new. Most of the media publicly shared on the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adwait Patankar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[금융사기에 악용? 돈 벌면 장땡! (ft. 금결원과 은행의 무책임 앙상블)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86970</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86970"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T09:33:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[9월 4일 자 경향신문은 금융·공동인증서비스를 제공하는 한국금융결제원(이하 ‘금결원’)이 운영하는 오픈뱅킹이 전기통신금융사기의 창구로 악용되고 있음에도  시중은행들과 본인확인조치 책임을 서로 떠밀고 거짓말만 하고 있어서 피해 배상이 이루어지지 않고 있다고 지적했다. 경실련 역시 최근 피해자 고발대회를 열고 금융사들의 엉터리 핀테크 비대면 신분증 사본인증 금융사고를 문제제기 했다. 오픈뱅킹: 금융결제원에 참가한 기관(시중은행 및 일부 카드사, 카카오뱅크, 토스 등 )이 상호간 […]
The post 금융사기에 악용? 돈 벌면 장땡! (ft. 금결원과 은행의 무책임 앙상블) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[frida-ios-dump 를 이용한 애플리케이션 IPA 파일 추출]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13054011</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13054011"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T05:52:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기본적으로 Apple iOS앱들은 암호화(Encrypted) 되어 있을 수 있다. 하지만 아무리 보안을 위해 암호화를 했다하더라도, 실행을 하기 위해서는 반드시 암호화를 해제한 상태로 구동을 하게 된다. 이 시점에 복호화된 애플리케이션을 덤프해서 원본 IPA를 획득할 수 있을 것이다.
이런 경우에 사용되는 도구가 frida-ios-dump이다.
https://github.com/AloneMonkey/frida-ios-dump

사전 준비 
이 글에서는 사전준비가 미리 되어있다고 가정하겠다. 필요한 부분은 이전 블로그 게시글을 확인하면 좋다.
- 탈옥한 iphone : https://cpuu.postype.com/post/10436260
- frida 도구 설치 방법 : https://cpuu.postype.com/post/10415747


Frida-ios-dump 설치
% git clone https://github.com/AloneMonkey/frida-ios-dump.git
% cd frida-ios-dump/
% pip3 install -r requirements.txt --upgrade
설치가 완료되면 dump.py 파일이 존재하는데, 여기에서 아래의 정보를 알맞게 입력해야 한다.
User = 'root'
Password = 'alpine'
Host = 'IP주소'
Port = 22
탈옥된 아이폰이 root 계정 비밀번호가 alpine 이라고 할 때, 동일한 네트워크라면 192 또는 172로 시작하는 주소를 찾아서 입력하면 되고, ssh port 도 기본은 22 이지만 필요한 경우 알맞게 변경하면 된다.


애플리케이션 추출
dump 파이썬 스크립트에서 -l 옵션을 이용한다.
또는 frida-ps 를 사용해도 같다.


이렇게 확인된 Identifier 값을 입력하면 된다. 참고로 덤프를 할 때 해당 디바이스는 화면 잠금이 해제된 상태여야만 작업이 진행된다.


추출된 IPA 파일은 사실상 압축된 형태의 내용으로, unzip 명령어를 사용하면 해제가 가능하다.
% unzip unc0ver.ipa
디렉토리 내부에 보면 arm64 형식의 Mach-O 바이너리 파일을 획득할 수 있다.
% file unc0ver
unc0ver: Mach-O 64-bit executable arm64
리버스 엔지니어링을 하면 된다.
참고 : 
https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11085234]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solar’s role in EV charging]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476283</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/solars-role-in-ev-charging/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T03:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solar power may provide the means to offload stress from existing power grid infrastructure as EV adoption steadily grows. The world is experiencing an enormous...
The post Solar’s role in EV charging appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 8, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906796/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906796/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-08T00:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 8, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“법복과 털외투는 악행을 감춰주지”]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=83336</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/83336/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T23:17:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Edwin Austin Abbey – Metropolitan Museum of Art, online database: entry 10049, Public Domain, Link 넝마 옷 사이로 보이는 악행은 크게 보이는 법이지만, 법복과 털외투는 그 모든 걸 감춰주지. 죄에 황금 칠을 하면 강력한 정의의 창이라도 상처 하나 못 입히고 부러지는 거다. 누더기로 무장하면, 난쟁이의 지푸라기라도 뚫을 수 있다.[리어 왕, 윌리엄 셰익스피어, 김태원 옮김, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ML.NET: can Microsoft's machine learning be trusted?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0988/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0988/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2018, Microsoft created ML.NET, a machine learning framework for .NET developers. Since then, the machine learning library has undergone significant changes and acquired new features to identify patterns within data. Let's see how these changes have affected the quality of ML.NET source code. And explore the errors, of course!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay | Meet Sam from Chicago. More stories from Peru, Croatia and Estonia.]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/weareplay-meet-sam-from-chicago-and-more-stories.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/weareplay-meet-sam-from-chicago-and-more-stories.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Leticia Lago, Developer Marketing
 

 A medical game for doctors, a language game for kids, a scary game for horror lovers and an escape room game for thrill seekers! In this latest batch of #WeArePlay stories, we’re celebrating the founders behind a wonderful variety of games from all over the world. Have a read and get gaming! 

To start, let’s meet Sam from Chicago. Coming from a family of doctors, his Dad challenged him to make a game to help those in the medical field. Sam agreed, made a game and months later discovered over 100,000 doctors were able to practice medical procedures. This early success inspired him to found Level Ex - a company of 135, making world-class medical games for doctors across the globe. Despite his achievements, his Dad still hopes Sam may one day get into medicine himself and clinch a Nobel prize.   




Next, a few more stories from around the world:

Aldo and Sandro from Peru - founders of Dark Dome. They combine storytelling and art to make thrilling and chilling games, filled with plot twists and jump scares.






Vladimir, Tomislav and Boris from Croatia - founders of Pine Studio. They won the Indie Games Festival 2021 with their game Cats In Time. 





Kelly, Mikk, Reimo and Madde from Estonia - founders of ALPA kids. Their language games for children have a huge impact on early education and language preservation.





Check out all the stories now at g.co/play/weareplay and stay tuned for even more coming soon.




How useful did you find this blog post?
★ ★ ★ ★ ★]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Lazy imports for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907226/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907226/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T16:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Starting a Python application typically results in a flurry of imports as
modules from various locations (and the modules they import) get added
into the application process.  All of that occurs before the application
even gets started doing whatever it is the user actually launched it for;
that delay can be significant—and annoying.  Beyond that, many of those
imports may not be necessary at all for the code path being followed, so
eagerly doing the import is purely wasted time.  A proposal back in May
would add a way for applications to choose lazy imports, where the import
is deferred until the module is actually used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만 삭스, 이익 증가와 IRA법안 수혜로 테슬라 주식 매수를 강력 추천]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587718</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587718/%ea%b3%a8%eb%93%9c%eb%a7%8c%ec%82%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%eb%a7%a4%ec%88%98-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T14:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 하반기 테슬라 이익 전망 – 테슬라 영업이익률 40% 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587710</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587710/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T13:39:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python releases 3.10.7, 3.9.14, 3.8.14, and 3.7.14 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/09/python-releases-3107-3914-3814-and-3714.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/09/python-releases-3107-3914-3814-and-3714.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T13:03:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have some security content, and plenty of regular bug fixes for 3.10. Let’s dive right in.


CVE-2020-10735
Converting between int and str in bases other than 2 (binary), 4, 8 (octal), 16 (hexadecimal), or 32 such as base 10 (decimal) now raises a ValueError if the number of digits in string form is above a limit to avoid potential denial of service attacks due to the algorithmic complexity.
Security releases for 3.9.14, 3.8.14, and 3.7.14 are made available simultaneously to address this issue, along with some less urgent security content.
Upgrading your installations is highly recommended.
Python 3.10.7
Get it here:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3107/
This bugfix version of Python was released out-of-schedule to address the CVE, and as such contains a smaller number …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10년 다닌 회사를 떠나며 – 어느 퇴사 후배의 당부]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587706</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587706/%ed%87%b4%ec%82%ac-%ed%9b%84%eb%b0%b0%ec%9d%98-%eb%8b%b9%eb%b6%80"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T12:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[기록용]원달러 환율이 1400원을 위협하던날]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587703</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587703/%ec%9b%90%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac-%ed%99%98%ec%9c%a8-1400%ec%9b%90"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T12:13:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘내 마음 속’ 반민주, 비민주와의 싸움: 민주화 시즌 3]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86966</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86966"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T09:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[상당히 많이 헷갈리기도 한다. 여 대 야의 구도가 개입하는 바람에 지금 대한민국을 이끌어 가고 있는 큰바람이 어디로 불고 있는지를 정확히 파악하지 못하고 있다. 내로남불형 진영논리에 갇혀서 민주주의를 향한 새로운 기운을 발견하지 못하고 있다. 대한민국의 민주주의를 다시 한 번 더 도약시킬 도도한 물결이 흘러가고 있음에도 관심을 쏟지 못하고 있다. 직업정치 분야에서 도드라지고 있지만, 사실은 대한민국 다양한 […]
The post ‘내 마음 속’ 반민주, 비민주와의 싸움: 민주화 시즌 3 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907382/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907382/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T09:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (curl, protobuf-c, and vim) and SUSE (gimp, java-1_8_0-openj9, libostree, openvswitch, python-bottle, python-Flask-Security-Too, and zabbix).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to set up your GitOps directory structure]]></title>
        <id>7d5b3487-1afe-4a54-8f34-fa45098dd950</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/07/how-set-your-gitops-directory-structure"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: The following is an excerpt from our The Path to GitOps e-book, which outlines Git best practices for GitOps deployment.
When adopting GitOps, organizations must plan carefully to divide tasks and configuration files appropriately between repositories and directories in each repository. Standard practices have long existed for using Git-based workflows for infrastructure and software delivery. But with the dawn of cloud-native architectures and Kubernetes, you can now automate a wide range of deployments based on declarations stored in a Git repository.
The question of best practices comes up a lot when creating repositories for GitOps. There is no magic bullet, but several common patterns exist to match the various ways the organization interacts internally.
Conway's Law and GitOps
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Hernandez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 examples of security automation with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>c5e44d48-3733-4add-8dfc-4e49bc4ad593</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/07/5-examples-security-automation-ansible"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security automation encompasses a wide variety of products and services designed to prevent loss or damage to data, applications, IT systems, and networks and to protect devices from malicious or unintended activities. Developers can use the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform to pull together different security vendors and processes to speed up deployment and reduce errors from performing repetitive manual tasks.
This article explores five common security use cases that Ansible can automate:
Enterprise firewalls
Intrusion Detection and Prevention Systems, IDPS
Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) systems
Privileged Access Management (PAM) tools
Endpoint Protection Platform (EPP)
Enterprise firewalls
Firewalls control the traffic allowed to traverse networks, protecting line-of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jamie Beck, Himanshu Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Connectors: Configuring change data capture]]></title>
        <id>41f98b40-5aa6-451e-9c6d-2655264e4f6a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/07/configuring-change-data-capture"/>
        <updated>2022-09-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Connectors is a new cloud service offering from Red Hat. The service provides prebuilt connectors to enable quick and reliable connectivity across data, services, and systems. Each connector is a fully managed service, tightly integrated with Red Hat OpenShift Streams for Apache Kafka, Red Hat's managed cloud service for Apache Kafka.
Change data capture (CDC) is a software process that detects changes (inserts, updates, deletes) to data in a database and transforms these changes into event streams that can be consumed by other systems or applications to react to these changes.
Typical use cases for change data capture include: 
Data replication
Streaming analytics
Event-driven distributed applications
Red Hat OpenShift Connectors offers several source connectors for chan…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernard Tison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power supply design for primary cell powered patient monitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476147</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/power-supply-design-for-primary-cell-powered-patient-monitors/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T19:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remote patient monitoring patches help doctors provide better care, but they pose challenges for power supply designers who must balance system performance and battery life...
The post Power supply design for primary cell powered patient monitors appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fahad Masood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not yet fall, but Matter is already here]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10928</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/its-not-yet-fall-but-matter-is-already-here/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:30:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you know where to look, the Matter smart home protocol is already here. At the IFA show in Berlin which took place this week, Eve Systems is showing off its sensors interoperating with other Matter-compatible devices, while Google has a sign-up sheet for people to access Matter as part of a private developer preview program. If […]
The post It’s not yet fall, but Matter is already here appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Dev Library Letters : 13th Issue]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-dev-library-letters-13th-issue.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/09/google-dev-library-letters-13th-issue.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Garima Mehra, Program Manager


 


 
 
    
                    
                                    
Welcome to the 13th Issue: ‘Google Dev Library letters’ is a technology newsletter curated to bring you some of the best projects developed with Google tech and submitted to the Google Dev Library platform. We are back with another boost of inspiration for your next project!
                            
            


Hero Content of the month
Check out shortlisted content from the Google technologies of your choice.
Android




Contact Store API by Alex Styl
Contact Store is a modern API that makes access to contacts on Android devices simple to use. It solves for the most frequent use cases and makes developing enjoyable.





Custom Progress Indicator by Samson Achiaga
Custom…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can TinyML really provide on-device learning?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10924</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/can-tinyml-really-provide-on-device-learning/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine if your smart speaker could be trained to recognize your accent, or if a pair of running shoes could alert you in real time if your gait changed, indicating fatigue. Or if, in the industrial world, sensors could parse vibration information from a machine that changed location and function often in real time, halting […]
The post Can TinyML really provide on-device learning? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A look at Linux Mint 21]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906859/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906859/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T16:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint 21 "Vanessa" was released
on July 31.  There are no real headline-grabbing features that come
with the new release, as the project generally seeks to make incremental
changes, rather than larger, potentially disruptive ones.
Changes in this release include a new Bluetooth manager that brings several
improvements,  driverless printing and scanning
by default, a process monitor to inform the user
about resource-intensive background tasks, new functionality for the
Timeshift system backup tool, and several major under-the-hood improvements
to the Cinnamon 
desktop environment.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Request Batch]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/request-batch.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/request-batch.html"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When distributing data leads to lots of small messages around a cluster
      then network latency and the request processing time (including
      serialization, deserialization of the request on the server side) can add
      significant overhead. Unmesh Joshi shows how requests can
      be combined into a Request Batch to improve throughput.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 elements of an effective smart manufacturing platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476142</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/4-elements-of-an-effective-smart-manufacturing-platform/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T14:14:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The manufacturing industry, in particular, sees cloud computing as an opportunity to implement revolutionary solutions that usher in the rise of the smart factory. Source:...
The post 4 elements of an effective smart manufacturing platform appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Whitley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE): A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://novelbits.io/?p=22402</id>
        <link href="https://novelbits.io/bluetooth-low-energy-ble-complete-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T11:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet of Things (IoT) has been a buzzword for decades, but today this market is far from theoretical. There are over 10 billion active IoT devices globally, and one of the key technologies enabling this market growth is Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE).  Introduced in 2012, this flexible protocol provides wireless connection for many of […]
The post Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE): A Complete Guide appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammad Afaneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A brief history of embedded operating systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/?p=12296</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/training/a-brief-history-of-embedded-operating-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T10:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are often surrounded by embedded operating systems every day without realising it. That can be through the embedded systems in […]
The post A brief history of embedded operating systems appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>bluefruit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘가처분’ 주호영의 가짜뉴스 확성기로 전락한 언론 (ft. 따옴표 저널리즘)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86958</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86958"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T09:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[국민의힘 비상대책위원회 효력 정지 가처분 결정 직후 주호영 비대위원장을 비롯해 국민의힘 인사 일부는 판사가 법원 내 특정 연구모임 소속이라며 “정당 자치를 훼손한 정치적 결정”이라고 주장했습니다. 주호영 비대위원장은 “재판장이 특정 연구모임 출신으로 편향성이 있고 이상한 결과가 있을 거라는 우려가 있었는데 그 우려가 현실화된 것 같다”고 말했는데요. 언론은 주 비대위원장 발언을 검증 없이 받아쓰기했고, 비슷한 보도는 우후죽순 […]
The post ‘가처분’ 주호영의 가짜뉴스 확성기로 전락한 언론 (ft. 따옴표 저널리즘) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gawk 5.2.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907278/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907278/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T08:51:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 5.2.0 of the GNU Awk implementation is out.  The biggest change,
perhaps, is the addition of "persistent memory" support that allows gawk to
keep values around between runs.  Old-timers will be disappointed by
the removal of VAX/VMS support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907275/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907275/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T08:46:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Red Hat (pcs), SUSE (389-ds and firefox), and Ubuntu (linux-hwe-5.4 and linux-oracle).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개발자는 꼭 성장해야 하는가?]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=11579</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2022/09/06/developers_growth/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T08:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[01.학교? 학교 식으로 생각하면 이렇다. 주어진 기준환경이 있고, 주어진 커리큘럼이 있고,거기에서 1등을 하는 거다. 그러면 어떤 보상이 따라온다.많은 학생들이 “성장”이라는 단어를 그렇게 받아들인다. 하지만, 아니다.세상은 무규칙 경기장이다.1등 한다고 보장해주는 것도 없고 상을 주는 사람도 없다.아니, 상 자체가 아무런 의미가 없다. 내가 잘하는 걸 상사에게 알려서 좀 더 높은 연봉을 제시받거나,다른 회사의 CEO가 알게 해서, 이직을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenWrt 22.03.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907238/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907238/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T07:10:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
22.03.0 of the OpenWrt distribution for routers (and beyond) has been
released.  "It incorporates over 3800 commits since branching the
previous OpenWrt 21.02 release and has been under development for about one
year".  Changes include a new firewall implementation using nftables,
year-2038 readiness, dark mode in the LuCI web-based administration tool,
and support for many more devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Developer roundup: Best of August 2022]]></title>
        <id>8ed9f141-704e-4dfc-945c-32531df66593</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/06/red-hat-developer-roundup-best-august-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's officially September, and we're back with our monthly roundup to catch you up on the latest top articles and community resources featured on Red Hat Developer. In August, we published tutorials to help you improve the observability of your microservices, build security into your Node.js development process, easily containerize .NET applications, and more. Let's dive into the August highlights.
Containerize .NET applications automatically
To run a .NET application in a container, you need a Dockerfile—but writing and managing Dockerfiles can be tedious. Enter the dotnet build-image tool, which enables you to create a container image from a .NET application without writing a Dockerfile.
In one of our most popular articles from the past month, Tom Deseyn shows you how to use build-image …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build trust in continuous integration for your Rust library]]></title>
        <id>af4e4d46-5834-4409-9225-eb8bfeaf27b1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/06/build-trust-continuous-integration-your-rust-library"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article concludes the 4-part series about how to take advantage of the recent Rust support added to Linux. I hope you have read the previous articles in the series:
Part 1: 3 essentials for writing a Linux system library in Rust


Part 2: How to create C binding for a Rust library


Part 3: How to create Python binding for a Rust library



This article will demonstrate how to build trust in a Continuous Integration (CI) system for your Rust library.
You can download the demo code from its GitHub repository.
The package contains:
An echo server listening on the Unix socket /tmp/librabc
A Rust crate that connects to the socket and sends a ping packet every 2
seconds
A C/Python binding
A command-line interface (CLI) for the client
The CI system of this GitHub repository is built on Gith…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gris Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Silicon macOS에서 ARM64 assembly programming]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13004865</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13004865"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T05:59:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[누가 macOS에서 어셈블리 프로그래밍을 할까? 하겠냐만.. 그냥 심심해서 "이게 되네?"를 해보고자 테스트.
% sw_vers
ProductName:    macOS 
ProductVersion: 12.5.1
BuildVersion:   21G83
우선 실험환경은 Apple Silicon 버전의 일명 M1 macmini 이고 macOS Monterey(12.5) 운영체제 환경이다.


개발 환경 구축
기본적으로 컴파일 및 여러가지 진행을 위해 터미널에서 아래의 명령어로 관련 도구를 설치한다.
% xcode-select --install
명령어를 입력하면 화면에 위와 같은 메시지가 뜨고, 설치를 눌러 진행한다.


설치 완료후 아래와 같이 현재 도구 버전을 확인해볼 수 있다.
% xcode-select --version
xcode-select version 2395. 
% gcc --version          
Apple clang version 13.1.6 (clang-1316.0.21.2.5)     
Target: arm64-apple-darwin21.6.0   
Thread model: posix    
InstalledDir:/Applications/Xcode.app/Contents/Developer/Toolchains/XcodeDefault.xctoolchain/usr/bin       
참고로 일반적인 리눅스와 다르게 애플은 clang 컴파일러를 사용한다. gcc를 이용했을 때 자동으로 clang 으로 연결된다.


어셈블리 프로그래밍
그렇다면 어셈블리 언어로 "Hello World!" 문자열…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“치명적인 실수”를 수습해야할 한국 정부]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=83306</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/83306/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T04:13:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“우리는 한국의 우려를 진지하게 받아들이고 진지한 논의를 할 자세가 되어있다.” (美국무부 산하의) 경제성장, 에너지, 환경 차관 호세 W. 페르난데즈는 한 논평에서 이렇게 말했다. “우리는 다음 달에 국내 규칙제정 과정을 시작함에 따라 더 자세한 사항을 알 수 있을 것이다.” 윤은 언급한 문제에 익숙한 두 번째 인물이라 할 수 있는 美하원의장 낸시 팰로시가 지난달 남한을 방문했을 때에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in August]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/august-2022-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/august-2022-roundup"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
August
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 틱톡과 알고리듬]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75239</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/05/npc_tiktok/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_tiktok"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T22:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2020년 여름, 미국 트럼프 대통령은 틱톡에 대해 얼핏 무리해 보이는 공격을 시작했습니다. 중국의 IT 기업이지만 엄연히 사기업인 바이트댄스에 틱톡의 지분을 미국 회사에 매각하라고 명령했고, 이를 따르지 않으면 미국에서 틱톡의 사용을 금지하겠다고도 말했습니다. 어떤 이들은 이를 트럼프가 대선 승리를 위해 중국을 공격하는 것이라 이야기하기도 했습니다. 트럼프는 재선에 실패했고, 법원 역시 트럼프의 행정명령에 제동을 걸었습니다. 바이든은 트럼프의 행정명령을 폐기했습니다. 지난 5월, 뉴욕타임스의 칼럼니스트이자 복스(Vox)의 창업자인 에즈라 클라인은 틱톡이 가진 위험성을 다시 경고하는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The risks of using vulnerable dependencies in your project, and how SCA helps manage them]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0987/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0987/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most applications today use third-party libraries. If such a library contains a vulnerability, an app that uses this library may also be vulnerable. But how can you identify such problematic dependencies?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Concurrent page-fault handling with per-VMA locks]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906852/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906852/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T15:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel is, in many ways, a marvel of scalability, but there is a
longstanding pain point in the memory-management subsystem that has
resisted all attempts at elimination: the mmap_lock.  This lock
was inevitably a topic at the 2022 Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit (LSFMM), where the idea of
using per-VMA locks was raised.  Suren Baghdasaryan has posted
an implementation of that idea — but with an interesting twist on how
those locks are implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907202/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907202/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T14:52:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monday's crop of stable kernels consists of 5.19.7, 5.15.65, 5.10.141, 5.4.212, 4.19.257, 4.14.292, and 4.9.327.  They are relatively small updates,
but still contain important fixes in various parts of the kernel tree;
users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three-layer stacking shrinks global shutter image sensor for eye tracking]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476125</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/three-layer-stacking-shrinks-global-shutter-image-sensor-for-eye-tracking/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T14:28:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Omnivision has launched a BSI global shutter (GS) image sensor, the OG0TB, which it said is the world’s smallest image sensor for eye and face tracking in AR/VR/MR and metaverse consumer devices.
The post Three-layer stacking shrinks global shutter image sensor for eye tracking appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907201/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907201/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T14:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (flac, ghostscript, libmodbus, qemu, rails, ruby-rack, and thunderbird), Fedora (kernel, kernel-headers, kernel-tools, libtar, qt5-qtwebengine, subscription-manager-cockpit, tcpreplay, and vim), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, webkit2, and ytnef), SUSE (curl, firefox, freerdp, gdk-pixbuf, ImageMagick, json-c, libgda, php-composer2, and python-pyxdg), and Ubuntu (libzstd, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure-5.4, and linux-oem-5.17).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sudoku, Go and WebAssembly]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/sudoku-go-and-webassembly/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/sudoku-go-and-webassembly/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Over the summer my family has experienced a brief renaissance of interest in
Sudoku, particularly as I've tried to get my kids to practice solving some
non-trivial puzzles (pro tip: YouTube videos help).</p>
<object class="align-center" data="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/images/2022/sudoku-puzzle.svg" type="image/svg+xml">
Sudoku puzzle sample</object>
<p>Naturally, whenever a programmer encounters Sudoku it's hard to avoid thinking
about automated solvers …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인텍플러스 리스크 분석을 통한 인텍플러스 주가 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587701</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587701/%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%8d%ed%94%8c%eb%9f%ac%ec%8a%a4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T11:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are you trying to hire the first VP of Sales in your SaaS startup? You have to read this]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2172</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2022/09/05/are-you-trying-to-hire-the-first-vp-of-sales-in-your-saas-startup-you-have-to-read-this/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=are-you-trying-to-hire-the-first-vp-of-sales-in-your-saas-startup-you-have-to-read-this"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T09:25:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are the founder of a B2B SaaS startup and have finally reached the stage of hiring your VP of Sales, we hope this helps you. The reason why we phrased the title so strongly is that the VP of Sales position is almost the first external executive hire at a B2B SaaS startupContinue reading "Are you trying to hire the first VP of Sales in your SaaS startup? You have to read this"
Are you trying to hire the first VP of Sales in your SaaS startup? You have to read this appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[통보 없는 통신자료 수집 ‘헌법불합치’ 판결이 놓친 것]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86947</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86947"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T07:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[헌법재판소는 2022년 7월 21일 수사기관이 법원의 허가없이 통신사업자에 이용자의 인적사항(이용자 성명, 주민등록번호, 주소, 가입 및 해지일자, 전화번호, ID 등 가입자 정보)을 직접 요청하여 제공받을 수 있도록 한 ‘통신자료제공’ 제도(전기통신사업법 제83조 제3항)에 대해 헌법불합치 결정을 선고했다(헌법재판소 2022. 7. 21. 선고 2016헌마388 등 결정). 헌법재판소는 본 결정에서, 당사자의 기본권 제한 사실에 관한 통지는 당사자가 기본권 제한 사실을 […]
The post 통보 없는 통신자료 수집 ‘헌법불합치’ 판결이 놓친 것 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create Python binding for a Rust library]]></title>
        <id>b3d1c182-4a4d-4c01-9cd0-42f9d9f0063a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/05/how-create-python-binding-rust-library"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article continues a series about how to take advantage of the recent Rust support added to Linux. The previous articles in the series are:
3 essentials for writing a Linux system library in Rust (part 1)
How to create C binding for a Rust library (part 2)
Build trust in continuous integration for your Rust library (part 4)
This third installment demonstrates how to create Python bindings so that Python projects can use your Rust library.
You can download the demo code from its GitHub repository. The package contains:
An echo server listening on the Unix socket /tmp/librabc
A Rust crate that connects to the socket and sends a ping packet every 2 seconds
A C/Python binding
A command-line interface (CLI) for the client
Elements of a Python binding
The PyO3 project can generate a Python-c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gris Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create C binding for a Rust library]]></title>
        <id>e48f9d2b-2a03-42cf-b213-c51d8d6649bc</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/05/how-create-c-binding-rust-library"/>
        <updated>2022-09-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the second installment of a series about how to take advantage of the recent Rust support added to Linux. The first article in the series, 3 essentials for writing a Linux system library in Rust, describes special considerations that system libraries require when you are writing in Rust. This article demonstrates how to create a C binding so that programmers in C or C++ can call your Rust library. Rust has not conquered the Linux world yet, so our system library needs to provide bindings to other languages.
Check out the other three articles in this series:
Part 1: 3 essentials for writing a Linux system library in Rust


Part 3: How to create Python binding for a Rust library


Part 4: Build trust in continuous integration for your Rust library



The Rust team has created…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gris Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[루나 디스플레이 mac-to-mac 모드 짧은 사용기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/mac-to-mac-mode-on-luna-display/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/mac-to-mac-mode-on-luna-display/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T23:13:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[그동안 아이맥 정말 잘 사용했지만 아쉽게도 타겟 디스플레이 모드가 지원되지 않는 2014년 레티나 5K 모델이다. 게다가 더 이상 macOS 업데이트도 해당이 없어서 최근 macOS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 기후변화를 향한 미국 대법원의 ‘눈 가리고 아웅’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75230</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/04/npc_scotusepa/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_scotusepa"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[팟캐스트 아메리카노 이번 시즌에서 두 번째로 읽은 책이 기후변화 소송을 다룬 “지구를 살린 위대한 판결”이었던 만큼 올해 대법원 판결 가운데 기후변화와 관련된 판결 이야기도 여러 차례 소개했습니다. 오늘은 그 가운데 지난 7월 6일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 소개한 글을 올립니다.   6:3의 압도적인 보수 우위의 미국 대법원이 7월 휴지기를 앞두고 기존 판례와 상당히 동떨어진 판결을 잇달아 내렸습니다. 수정헌법 2조를 맹신하는 대법관들은 공공의 안전을 위해 개인의 총기 소지를 제한하고 규제하던 법률을 위헌으로 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.0-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906672/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906672/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T21:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.0-rc4 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "We're up to rc4, and things mostly still look fairly
normal".

Beyond the usual fixes, 6.0-rc4 includes one feature change: a hook to allow
security modules to control access to the io_uring command pass-through
mechanism.  See this article for the
background behind this late-arriving change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Languages: History and Fundamentals]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7089</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/09/04/programming-languages-history-and-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T20:55:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Languages: History and Fundamentals by Jean E. Sammet is often cited in discussions of language history, but very rarely read (I appreciate that many oft cited books have not been read by those citing them, but age further reduces the likelihood that anybody has read this book; it was published in 1969). I read […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tutorial: Creating Bare-bare Embedded Projects with CMake, with Eclipse included]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=35353</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/09/04/tutorial-creating-bare-bare-embedded-projects-with-cmake-with-eclipse-included/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T16:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MCU vendors offer SDKs and configuration tools: that’s a good thing, because that way I can get started quickly and get something up and running ideally in a few minutes. But this gets you into a dependency on tools, SDK … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Eckersley RIP]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907114/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907114/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Eckersley, one of the original founders of the Let's Encrypt non-profit TLS certificate authority, has died suddenly, as reported by Seth Schoen:

Peter was the leader of EFF's contributions to Let's Encrypt and ACME over the course of several years during which these technologies turned from a wild idea into an important part of Internet infrastructure. He also took a lot of initiative in coalescing the EFF, Mozilla, and University of Michigan teams into a single team and a single project. He later served on the initial board of directors of the Internet Security Research Group.
[...]
Toward the end of his life, Peter focused his career on ethics and safety of artificial intelligence, and he founded the AI Objectives Institute to examine the concrete parallels he saw between surprising and undesirable outcomes that can emerge within economies and those that can emerge in machine learning systems.


More about Eckersley can be found at his web site, on his Wikipedia page, and in a Hacker News discussion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extreme Integers – Doom from Below]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=13025</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2022/09/04/extreme-integers-doom-from-below/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T09:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a beginner or immediate C++ programmer, you heard never mixing unsigned and signed integer types or avoiding unsigned integers at all. There was also this talk about undefined behaviour. Yet, in embedded software development, there is no way around unsigned integers – so what is behind all these warnings? Wonderful that you strive to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[<노자가 옳았다>]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222866276393</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222866276393"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T03:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<노자는 고조선의 사상가이다. 나는 그렇게 생각한다. 아니, 그렇게 느낀다.> 이 구절을 보았을 때, 매우 황당하고, 그가 과장하고 있다고 생각했다. 그럼에도 불구하고 그는 <노자>를 우리 과거 사상가들의 관점에서 이해하고자 시도하고 있다. 그래서 초원 이충익의 노자에 대한 서적인 <담노(談老)>, 최수운의 <불연기연(不然其然)>, <대승기신론>과 원효의 논평, 최치원의 <풍류도> 등을 예로 들어 혹은 논거로 하여 노자의 <도덕경>을 풀어내고 있다. 그 결과, 그는 흥분하여 다음처럼 말한다. <이 노자는 정말 우리 조선인의 가슴과 조선인의 삶과 조선의 우주에 편재해 있는 것이다.> 그.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parent links in Go ASTs]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/parent-links-in-go-asts/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/parent-links-in-go-asts/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T12:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A common question that comes up when writing AST-based tooling in Go is &quot;how do
I find a node's parent?&quot;, or more generally, &quot;what are all the ancestors of
a given node?&quot;</p>
<p>Go's <a class="reference external" href="https://pkg.go.dev/go/ast">AST package</a> does not come with parent links
out of the box; this is a common choice …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[필즈상 수상 허준이교수가 서울대 졸업생에게 당부한 것, 서로에게, 그리고 자신에게 친절하시길..]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587691</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587691/%ed%97%88%ec%a4%80%ec%9d%b4%ea%b5%90%ec%88%98-%ec%84%9c%ec%9a%b8%eb%8c%80-%ec%a1%b8%ec%97%85-%ec%b6%95%ec%82%ac"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T11:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 주관적 관념론]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222865515516</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222865515516"/>
        <updated>2022-09-03T00:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 우리가 경험하는 것, 따라서 우리가 알 수 있는 것은 정신적 표상물, 감각 인상, 감각 소여, 관념이다. 반면에 실재 세계, 물리적 대상이 직접 경험할 수 없는 것이기 때문에, 이것과 정신적 표상물이 <유사>한지 우리는 알 수 없다. 나아가 이러한 실재 세계, 물리적 세계가 존재하는지 알 수 없다. 이것이 로크의 표상적 실재론을 비판하는 버클리의 주장이다. * 우리의 모든 지식은 경험으로부터 온다. 이것이 경험론의 근본적 논제이다. 로크를 비판하는데 버클리는 이 주장을 사용하고 있다. 경험으로부터 오지 않는 것, 즉 경험할 수 없는 것에 대해서 우리는 그것을 알 수 없다. 따라서 직접 경험의 대상이 아니라, 간접적 추론의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arti 1.0.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/907023/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/907023/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T23:23:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arti is a reimplementation of the Tor server in Rust; version 1.0.0 has
just been released and proclaimed ready for production use.


	When we defined our set of milestones, we defined Arti 1.0.0 as
	"ready for production use": You should be able to use it in the
	real world, to get a similar degree of privacy, usability, and
	stability to what you would with a C client Tor. The APIs should be
	(more or less) stable for embedders.

	We believe we have achieved this. You can now use arti
	proxy to 
	connect to the Tor network to anonymize your network connections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Sept. 2, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10910</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-sept-2-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T20:15:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Kitty, meet Raspberry Pi: There’s yet another use for the inexpensive Raspberry Pi compute board. And you’re not likely to guess it, so I’ll just tell you: Someone made a cat doorbell using a Pi. No, the cat doesn’t press a button or show up on video. Instead, the Raspberry Pi listens at the […]
The post IoT news of the week for Sept. 2, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What's in a (type) name?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906496/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906496/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T14:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's manual
pages are in a bit of an interesting position.  They 
are managed as a separate project, distinct from the kernel's
documentation, and have the task of documenting both the kernel's
system-call interface and the wrappers for that interface provided by the C
library.  Sometimes the two objectives come into conflict, as can be seen
in a discussion that has been playing out over the course of the last year
on whether to use C standard type names to describe kernel-defined
structures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siemens at Nissan, MEMS mic, CXL memory, and more embedded]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476116</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/siemens-at-nissan-mems-mic-cxl-memory-and-more-embedded/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T13:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s embedded news features Siemens at Nissan EV plant, Arm suing Qualcomm, a first bio-inspired directional MEMS microphone, memory connectivity platform for CXL, and more.
The post Siemens at Nissan, MEMS mic, CXL memory, and more embedded appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906973/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906973/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T12:32:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (firefox, rsync, systemd, and thunderbird), Debian (chromium, dpdk, and sofia-sip), Fedora (kernel, thunderbird, and zlib), Red Hat (pcs and rh-mariadb103-galera and rh-mariadb103-mariadb), Slackware (poppler), SUSE (cifs-utils, curl, dwarves and elfutils, firefox, flatpak, gnutls, gpg2, harfbuzz, ignition, kernel, ldb, samba, libslirp, libsolv, libzypp, zypper, libtirpc, logrotate, mozilla-nss, ncurses, open-vm-tools, openssl-1_1, p11-kit, pcre, pcre2, podman, postgresql12, postgresql13, postgresql14, python-M2Crypto, python3, rsync, salt, spice, systemd-presets-common-SUSE, tiff, ucode-intel, xen, and zlib), and Ubuntu (curl, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.15, linux-gkeop, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-kvm,
 linux-snapdragon, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4,
 linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle,
 linux-oracle-5.4, and linux-aws-hwe).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[론스타와 모피아 그리고 ISDS 폐기해야 하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86940</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86940"/>
        <updated>2022-09-02T10:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 8월 31일 론스타와 한국정부 간 투자자-국가분쟁(Investor-State Dispute, ISD)사건의 중재판정 결과가 발표되었습니다. 중재판정부는 금융 쟁점에 대한 론스타 측 주장을 일부 받아들여, 우리 정부 측에 한화 약 2,800억원에 상당하는 금액 및 2011. 12. 3.부터 완제일까지 한 달 만기 미국 국채 수익률에 따른 이자를 배상할 것을 명하였습니다. 산업자본인 론스타는 대주주 적격성을 충족하지 못해 처음부터 외환은행을 인수할 자격이 […]
The post 론스타와 모피아 그리고 ISDS 폐기해야 하는 이유 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 박탈된 여성의 임신중단권과 디지털 사생활 보호]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75216</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/09/01/npc_newerawithdobbs/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_newerawithdobbs"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 5월 초 유출된 문서의 내용대로 미국 대법원이 여성의 임신중단권을 헌법상의 권리로 본 “로 대 웨이드 판결(Roe v. Wade, 1973)”을 뒤집는 결정을 내렸습니다. 이에 따라 임신중단 불법화 조치가 주 단위에서 본격적으로 진행되면, 여성들은 인생을 계획하고 안전한 의료 혜택을 누리는 문제에 있어 1973년 전과 비슷한 어려움을 마주하게 될 것입니다. 시대의 변화와 기술의 발전으로 인해 새로 추가되는 문제도 있습니다. 바로 디지털 사생활 보호의 문제입니다. 판결이 알려진 직후, 미국에서는 검찰이 인터넷에 올린 정보나 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A framework for code tagging]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906660/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906660/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T14:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel code can, at times, be quite inward looking; it often refers to
itself.  To enable this introspection, the kernel has evolved several
mechanisms for identifying specific locations in the code and carrying out
actions related to those locations.  The code-tagging
framework patch set, posted by Suren Baghdasaryan and Kent Overstreet,
is an attempt to replace various ad hoc implementations with a
single framework, and to add some new applications as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research Twice, Build Once: How to Know Your Users as You Grow]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7011</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/user-research-as-you-grow/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T14:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Far too many products still fail because there’s simply no demand for them. How does that happen? Or, how do so many startups launch entire businesses without realizing users didn’t need their products?  By overlooking user research.  Every tech company has to build and ship new products to continue growing. And, whether there are 10... Read More
The post Research Twice, Build Once: How to Know Your Users as You Grow appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Glasgow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906778/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906778/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T13:49:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (pdns-recursor, thunderbird, and vim), Gentoo (firefox, thunderbird-bin, virtualbox, and webkit-gtk), Red Hat (convert2rhel), SUSE (gstreamer-plugins-good, open-vm-tools, postgresql12, rsync, and ucode-intel), and Ubuntu (linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-hwe).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Is Kickstarter still relevant for smart devices?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10906</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-is-kickstarter-still-relevant-for-smart-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we start off talking about the Federal Trade Commission suing a data broker for sharing sensitive location data. It’s a topic we’re following closely, in part because location information can’t be anonymized even when companies promise that it strips identifying information from it. With that in mind, Fight for the Future, a nonprofit […]
The post Podcast: Is Kickstarter still relevant for smart devices? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My advice on why you should build containers on your PC]]></title>
        <id>8055d5b0-1333-4669-9324-58cf32128e69</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/01/my-advice-why-you-should-build-containers-your-pc"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will present options for building containers that will run in Kubernetes and Red Hat OpenShift. There are many reasons against development in the environment that will ultimately run the container, such as cost, speed, tooling, and so on. Creating a container that works on your PC requires a local development environment that gives you the complete experience of coding, building, debugging, and running—and then pushes all pieces of the container to a host or cloud service. The best way to describe this process is tantamount to encapsulating your entire software building experience into one file and then sending it off to a server.
Container development offers a new way of thinking about software development. It is an application development model in which you decide whic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Schenck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 essentials for writing a Linux system library in Rust]]></title>
        <id>692bc784-5a5d-453e-9b61-ed3ba64a597a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/09/01/3-essentials-writing-linux-system-library-rust"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust is a good choice for writing a Linux
system library due to guarantees on memory and thread safety, a revolutionary approach to memory ownership, and a polished Foreign Function Interface. In spite of a slightly steep learning curve, you will come to love Rust and especially its compiler.
This article is the first in a series focusing on Rust for Linux. Check out the other three articles:
Part 2: How to create C binding for a Rust library


Part 3: How to create Python binding for a Rust library


Part 4: Build trust in continuous integration for your Rust library



I have created a demo Git repository with simple code to help explain the points in this article. The repository contains:
An echo server listening on the Unix socket /tmp/librabc
A Rust crate that connects to the socket a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gris Ge</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 1, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906067/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906067/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T02:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for September 1, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크로서비스의 여섯 가지 베스트 프랙티스]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86923</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86923"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T01:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[프랙티스(practice)는 정보·통신 분야에서 작업 산출물이나 프로세스 능력을 개선하는 소프트웨어 공학 활동이나 관리 활동을 의미한다. 왜 마이크로서비스인가? 오늘날의 비즈니스 환경은 전무후무하게 경쟁적이다. 기업의 규모나 업종에 상관없이 디지털 전환의 시대에는 제품이나 서비스의 스피드, 품질, 판매 후 유지 보수 등 모든 면에서 우위를 유지하기 쉽지 않다. 신규 진입자가 시장에 진입하는 것이 그 어느 때보다 쉬워지고, 예전 버전에서 생성된 […]
The post 마이크로서비스의 여섯 가지 베스트 프랙티스 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반존재론(反存在論)과 차이의 대긍정]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222863777061</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222863777061"/>
        <updated>2022-09-01T01:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(가) 곤(鯤)이 북녘 바다에 있다가 붕(鵬)이 되어 ‘天池’라 불리워지는 남녘 바다에로 날아간다는 것이다. 또 이와 유사한 우화가 外編 <秋水>장에도 나온다. 혜시가 양나라 재상시절에 자기의 자리를 노리는 것이 아닌가 두려워하고 있었는데, 장자가 혜시의 마음을 읽고 다음과 같이 말한다. 남쪽 바다에 원추라는 새가 있는데 북해로 날아가는데 오동나무가 아니면 머무르지 않고 대나무 열매가 아니면 먹지 않고 체천(體泉)이 아니면 마시지를 않으니 자네 혜시는 나 장자가 자네의 자리를 뺏을까 하고 전전긍긍하지 말라는 식으로 장자가 말하였다. (나) 곤(鯤)은 붕(鵬)이 되어 북에서 남으로 날아가고, 또 원추라는 새는 남쪽에서.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python multi-level break and continue]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906512/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906512/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fairly lengthy discussion of whether there should be a way to
break out of (or 
continue) more than one level of nested loops in Python recently
took place in the Ideas
category of the language's discussion forum.  The idea is
attractive, at least in an abstract sense—some other languages support
jumping out of 
multiple loops at once—but it seems unlikely to go anywhere for Python.
The barrier to new features is fairly high, for sure, but there is also a
need for proponents to provide real-world examples that demonstrate their
advantages.  That, too, is a difficult bar to clear, as was seen in the
discussion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build to order? Checking MSBuild for the second time]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0986/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0986/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MSBuild is a popular open-source build platform created by Microsoft. Developers all over the world use MSBuild. In 2016, we checked it for the first time and found several suspicious places. Can we find anything this time? Let's see!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel puts more weight behind RISC-V with Pathfinder platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476097</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/intel-puts-more-weight-behind-risc-v-with-pathfinder-platform-and-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T19:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Intel Pathfinder for RISC-V platform enables developers to create their own products using RISC-V cores and IP from the partner ecosystem, instantiate on FPGA and simulator platforms, and run operating systems and tool chains within a unified IDE. 
The post Intel puts more weight behind RISC-V with Pathfinder platform appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grow or Die: A Framework for Turning Your Company Around Fast]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7009</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/grow-or-die-supergoals/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T18:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post originally ran here. Most great teams would agree, there’s nothing more powerful for executing on big ambitions than a clearly defined and well-communicated goal. But sometimes the stakes are much higher than usual. In these instances, a goal requires even more focus, execution, and clarity. All of these can be achieved through a... Read More
The post Grow or Die: A Framework for Turning Your Company Around Fast appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Mignano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 embedded software architecture pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476093</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-embedded-software-architecture-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T16:53:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software architecture is a critical design element that guides developers in building an embedded application successfully. Here are five pitfalls that can get in the...
The post 5 embedded software architecture pitfalls appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few more stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906628/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906628/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T16:34:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.19.6,
5.15.64, and
5.10.140
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes, as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git’s Database Internals III: File History Queries (GitHub blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906604/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906604/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T14:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub blog series on how the Git database works continues with this
look at file-history queries.


	If these history modes usually have the same output, then why
	wouldn’t we always use --full-history
	--simplify-merges? The reason is performance. Not only
	does simplified history speed up the query by skipping a large
	portion of commits, it also allows iterative output. The simplified
	history can output portions of the history without walking the
	entire history. By contrast, the --simplify-merges algorithm is
	defined recursively starting at commits with no parents. Git cannot
	output a single result until walking all reachable commits and
	computing their diffs on the input path. This can be extremely slow
	for large repositories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906579/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906579/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T13:31:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (dpdk, net-snmp, php-horde-mime-viewer, php-horde-turba, and webkit2gtk), Fedora (rsync), Oracle (openssl and systemd), Red Hat (booth, kernel, kernel-rt, and openssl), Slackware (vim), SUSE (bluez, java-1_8_0-ibm, postgresql10, and zlib), and Ubuntu (kernel, linux, linux-raspi, linux-aws, and linux-oem-5.14).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the heck is this Helium 5G network?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10889</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/what-the-heck-is-this-helium-5g-network/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T13:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, we took a question from John on our Voicemail hotline. John heard the recent news that Helium has added 5G hotspots alongside its existing LoRa hotspots. This is the result of Nova Labs, the company behind Helium, acquiring FreedomFi. He wants to understand what these new hotspots do […]
The post What the heck is this Helium 5G network? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[당원 총투표, 정의당의 유치 찬란한 자해극]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86914</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86914"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T10:39:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정의당이 듣도 보도 못한 걸 시작했다. 31일부터 닷새 동안 정의당 소속 비례대표 5명에게 총사퇴 권고 여부를 묻는 당원 총투표를 한다고 한다. 물론 가결이 된다고 5명이 자동으로 의원직을 잃거나 하는 건 아니다. 그런 건 전혀 없다. 다만 총사퇴를 ‘권고’하는 것일 뿐. 이런 황당한 소동은 어떻게 시작된 것일까. 정의당 전 수석대변인 정호진이 7월 5일 비례대표 총사퇴를 요구하는 […]
The post 당원 총투표, 정의당의 유치 찬란한 자해극 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>자작나무</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역시 생성모델 (Generative AI)이 미래다]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2138</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2022/08/31/kr-generative-ai-is-the-future/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=kr-generative-ai-is-the-future"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T08:30:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[가트너가 ‘2022년 이머징 테크놀로지 하이프 사이클 (Hype Cycle for Emerging Technologies, 2022)’보고서를 발표하며, AI 자동화 및 가속화가 중요한 화두이며, 이를 위해 주목해야 할 기술로 제너레이티브 AI (Generative AI, 생성형 AI모델)를 선정했습니다 제너레이티브 AI란?  제너레이티브 AI는 이용자가 AI에게 어떤 것을 만들어 달라고 요구하면, 그 요구에 맞춰서 결과를 만들어내는 인공지능을 말합니다. AI에게 특정 개념을 학습 시키는 것이Continue reading "역시 생성모델 (Generative AI)이 미래다"
역시 생성모델 (Generative AI)이 미래다 appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Summit: Connect 2022 in Brooklyn: Learn about RHEL, cloud, and more]]></title>
        <id>a298d43f-64d8-4efb-bc3e-f9911f17f297</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/08/31/red-hat-summit-connect-2022-brooklyn"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us at Red Hat's annual Summit: Connect on September 15, 2022. The event is free and open to the public, and will be held at the New York Marriott at the Brooklyn Bridge and hosted by Red Hat employees and leaders. This year, we're offering several sessions, including Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9 discussions. Learn how to create your apps the cloud-native way with Red Hat OpenShift developer tools, and how to use Red Hat's cloud services to rapidly deliver cloud-native applications—all for free!
The conference is for those who are interested in open source technologies, as well as people interested in learning more about what Red Hat does every day. You can attend the speaking sessions and see demos of some of Red Hat's latest tools and technologies.
From the morning through the evening,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[26 대당 관계과 직접 추리]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222862761022</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222862761022"/>
        <updated>2022-08-31T00:16:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 논증들의 타당성과 부당성을 판별하라. (1) 모든 인간은 죽는다. 따라서 약간의 인간은 죽는다. (2) 모든 인간은 죽지 않는다. 따라서 약간의 인간은 죽지 않는다. (3) 약간의 인간은 죽지 않는다. 따라서 모든 인간은 죽지 않는다. (4) 약간의 인간이 죽는다는 것은 거짓이다. 따라서 모든 인간은 죽는다는 것도 거짓이다. ** 전통 논리학에 의하면, 문장, 진술, 명제는 질과 양을 갖고 있다. 질은 긍정과 부정이며, 양은 전칭양과 특칭양, 즉 ‘모든’과 ‘약간’이다. 질과 양을 조합하면 네 가지 표준적 정언명제가 도출된다. 즉 전칭 긍정명제, 전칭 부정명제, 특칭 긍정명제, 특칭 부정명제가 그것들이다. 이 표준적인 네 가지 명제.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 생선과 비타민]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75212</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/08/30/npc_poissonvitamin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_poissonvitamin"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T22:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘날, 건강과 장수는 인류의 가장 큰 관심사라 말할 수 있을 겁니다. 그래서 이 코너에서도 건강에 관한 소식을 가장 많이 다루게 됩니다. 바로 지난주에도 ‘영생’이라는 충분히 비현실적인 소재를 다뤘죠. 이번 주에는 최근 발표된 훨씬 더 현실적인 건강에 관한 뉴스 두 가지를 소개합니다. 물론 현실적이라고 해서 여러분께 명확한 지시사항을 말씀드리지는 못합니다. 오히려 그 반대에 가깝습니다. 현실이란 원래 그런 것이니까요. 첫 번째 소식은 6월 초 소개된 연구로, 바로 생선의 섭취에 관한 것입니다. 생선이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Debian to vote on its firmware path]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906380/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906380/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T21:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dealing with the non-free firmware that is increasingly needed to install
Debian has been a hot topic for the
distribution over the past few months.  The problem goes back further 
still, of course, but Steve McIntyre re-raised the 
issue in April, which resulted in a predictable lengthy discussion
thread on the debian-devel mailing list.  Now McIntyre has proposed a
general resolution (GR) with the intent of resolving how to give users a way to
install the distribution on their hardware while trying to avoid trampling
on the 
"100% free" guarantee in the Debian Social
Contract.  Finding the right balance is going to be tricky as is shown
by the multiple GR 
options that have been proposed in the discussion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The feedback for our C++ quiz and why it matters]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0985/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0985/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier we wrote about our quiz for C++ developers. Since the quiz launch, we have been carefully collecting your feedback. Some of the comments were related to the quiz errors, that we obviously sought to fix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sourceware seeking support from the Software Freedom Conservancy]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906502/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906502/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T20:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sourceware.org has long hosted the
repositories for many important free-software projects, including much of
the GNU toolchain.  Frank Ch. Eigler has posted
about some changes coming to Sourceware:


	Red Hat has been and continues to be a generous sponsor of the
	hardware, connectivity, and the very modest employee time it
	requires.  We are glad to report there are zero indications of any
	change to this commitment.  Things are stable, new services are
	coming online, and users seem to be happy.  However, it is always
	good to think about any future needs.

	To protect confidence in the long term future of this hosting
	service, we have reached out to the Software Freedom Conservancy
	(SFC) to function as a "fiscal sponsor".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git’s database internals II: commit history queries (GitHub blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906501/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906501/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T20:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub blog has posted a
detailed look at how Git stores the commit history to be able to
quickly answer queries.


	The commit-graph file provides a location for adding new
	information to our commits that do not exist in the commit object
	format by default. The new information that we store is called a
	generation number. There are multiple ways to compute a
	generation number, but the most important property we need to
	guarantee is the following:

	If the generation number of a commit A is less than the generation
	number of a commit B, then A cannot reach B.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for a lot of talk about digital twins]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10900</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/get-ready-for-a-lot-of-talk-about-digital-twins/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T14:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to industrial IoT, it’s pretty clear that sustainability use cases are driving more investments, although a new report from Microsoft shows how ROI is still a bigger use case in industrial automation. The report, which was released earlier this month, also shows how far companies have come in adopting smart manufacturing, and anticipates that the […]
The post Get ready for a lot of talk about digital twins appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Synthetic Embryos Can and Can’t Do, Now and in the Future]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6979</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/what-synthetic-embryos-can-do/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T14:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Magdalena Zernicka-Goetz is the Bren Professor of Biology and Biological Engineering at the California Institute of Technology and a Professor of Stem Cell Biology and Development at the University of Cambridge. In this interview, we discuss recent advances in technologies that allow us to use stem cells to create embryo-like structures with a brain and... Read More
The post What Synthetic Embryos Can and Can’t Do, Now and in the Future appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Magda Zernicka-Goetz and Nicole Neuman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906461/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906461/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (thunderbird), Fedora (ctk, dcmtk, OpenImageIO, and varnish-modules), Red Hat (systemd), SUSE (libslirp, open-vm-tools, and opera), and Ubuntu (jupyter-notebook, libsdl1.2, and systemd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Google for Startups Accelerator: Black Founders Class of 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/08/black-founders-class-of-2022.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/08/black-founders-class-of-2022.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Matt Ridenour, Head of Startup Developer Ecosystem - USA
    


Today only 1% of venture capital goes to Black founders in the US, with Black women founders receiving even less. At Google, we are committed to building racial equity in the North American startup ecosystem. In May, we announced an open call for applications for our third class of Google for Startups Accelerator: Black Founders, bringing the best of Google's programs, products, people and technology to Black founders across North America. From hundreds of applicants, we're proud to announce the 12 exceptional startups selected to join the accelerator:


Beam.city DNA (Toronto, Ontario): A growth coordination AI Platform helping businesses maximize growth using ads, email and social.

EdLight (Melrose, Massachusetts)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개인적인 주식 투자 일지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587679</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587679/%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%ec%9d%bc%ec%a7%80"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T11:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선거자유화 운동의 중대한 전환점: 공선법 위헌 등 판결비평]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86905</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86905"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T08:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국형 민주공화제의 성취는 자타가 공인하고 있다. 분단, 동족상잔, 냉전의 파고를 넘어 산업화와 민주화를 병행하여 성취하여 인권 존중과 민주적 정치질서가 높은 수준의 민주공화제를 구축하였다. 국가후견주의의 그늘  그러나 아직도 한국형 민주공화제에 남겨진 과제가 적지는 않음은 새삼 강조할 필요조차 없다. 민주화 이후에도 주권자 국민을 무시하는 권력의 오남용이 근절되지 않고 있기 때문이다. 이와 같은 민주주의의 지체가 지속되는 근본 원인은 […]
The post 선거자유화 운동의 중대한 전환점: 공선법 위헌 등 판결비평 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[틱톡을 활용한 Z세대 접근 전략]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587677</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587677/%ed%8b%b1%ed%86%a1-%ed%95%a0%ec%9a%a9-z%ec%84%b8%eb%8c%80-%ec%a0%91%ea%b7%bc-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T08:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes 101 for developers: Names, ports, YAML files, and more]]></title>
        <id>26eb2c94-6713-408a-8cf8-1846479a9d30</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/08/30/kubernetes-101-developers-names-ports-yaml-files-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once you've written your first container-based application and have it running in Docker or Podman, you're ready to move to the next level. That means multiple applications—microservices—running within a managed environment. Kubernetes, an open source container orchestration platform, is just such an environment, and by far the most popular one at that. Let's consider it from a developer's perspective.
Run multiple containers on Kubernetes
Running a container with Docker or Podman is great, but it's only a start. To implement an entire system, you need several services (or microservices, if you will). Kubernetes can orchestrate the entire system in a namespace, giving you both isolation from other namespaces and a shared environment within a namespace. You can just plop your applications i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Schenck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's not my fault!  Your code is broken.]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/zipcpu/2022/08/30/not-my-fault.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/zipcpu/2022/08/30/not-my-fault.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-30T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve  always commented that the way to get an interface working is to lock
the engineers responsible for each side of the interface together in a room
until it works.  I like to say it in jest, but in many ways there’s a lot of
truth to it.
One of the challenges of working with Open Source anything really is debugging.
To be successful, an open source engineer needs to commit their time to
supporting their design–no matter how it is used.  As an illustration, what
happens when one engineer uses an open source design, uses it inappropriately,
and then declares that it doesn’t work?  It can reflect poorly on the quality
of the design–even if the design was and remains fully functional.
As an example, someone recently attempted to use my digital
PLL.  They commented
that the PLL
worked great,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating peripheral monitoring in wearables with DMA]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476068</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/accelerating-peripheral-monitoring-in-wearables-with-dma/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T23:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses use of direct memory access (DMA) in embedded systems programming and how DMA interacts with peripheral and memory modules for more efficient...
The post Accelerating peripheral monitoring in wearables with DMA appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brandon Hurst</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of smart pointer static_ptr&lt;T&gt; in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0983/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0983/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have several smart pointers in C++ – 'std::unique_ptr', 'std::shared_ptr', 'std::weak_ptr'.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unicorns of PVS-Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0984/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0984/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let us guess: you're reading this article right now because you saw our unicorn illustrations and liked it. Anyway, we are pleased to see you here. In this article, we're going to tell you why we draw these unicorns, what they mean and what we do in general.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is TinyML too much?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=10885</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/when-is-tinyml-too-much/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T16:15:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to machine learning (ML), sometimes every problem looks like it needs a neural net, when in fact it just needs some statistics. This is especially true when it comes to running algorithms on microcontrollers and for industrial use cases such as predictive maintenance, according to Bernard Burg, director of AI and data […]
The post When is TinyML too much? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Crash recovery for user-space block drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906097/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906097/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T15:10:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new user-space block driver mechanism
entered the kernel during the 6.0 merge window.  This subsystem, called
"ublk", uses io_uring to communicate with
user-space drivers, resulting in some impressive performance numbers.  Ublk
has a lot of interesting potential, but the current use cases for it are
not entirely clear.  The recently posted crash-recovery
mechanism for ublk makes it clear, though, that those use cases do
exist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Fried on Why He Doesn’t Do Planning or Politics at Work]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=6947</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/jason-fried-basecamp-hey-interview/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T15:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compared with many startups, 37signals cofounder Jason Fried’s views around workplace culture, structure, and strategy could be considered subversive. He’d call them “honest,” a word he uses often when describing his leadership style. The outspoken maker of Basecamp and HEY has cultivated a reputation as a tech industry contrarian over the past two decades with... Read More
The post Jason Fried on Why He Doesn’t Do Planning or Politics at Work appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Fried and Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Earth Engine GDE Liza Goldberg uses tech to fight climate change]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/08/google-earth-engine-gde-liza-goldberg-uses-tech-to-fight-climate-change.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/08/google-earth-engine-gde-liza-goldberg-uses-tech-to-fight-climate-change.html"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:45:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Janelle Kuhlman, Developer Relations Program Manager 
 

   


Liza Goldberg, Google Earth GDE

Google Earth Engine GDE Liza Goldberg uses tech to fight climate change
Liza Goldberg learned to code through Google Earth Engine at age fourteen, when her mentors at NASA, where she was an intern, introduced the tool as a way to model global trends in environmental change. Liza, who had arrived at NASA with no coding or remote sensing experience, gradually gained expertise in the platform, thanks to strong mentorship, Google training, and guidance from the Google Earth Engine developer community. The fact that Google Earth Engine is built for scientists and has a clear world impact aligned with Liza’s commitment to using technology to combat climate change.  “Earth Engine enabled me t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906356/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906356/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released the 5.19.5
and 5.10.139 stable kernels to fix a problem
stemming 
from an incorrect merge of a patch
to the dummy-tools used for building kernels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906355/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906355/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T14:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (curl, exim4, maven-shared-utils, ndpi, puma, webkit2gtk, and wpewebkit), Fedora (dotnet3.1, firefox, and webkit2gtk3), Mageia (clamav, mariadb, net-snmp, postgresql, python-ldap, and thunderbird), SUSE (freeciv, gnutls, keepalived, libyang, nim, python-Django, and varnish), and Ubuntu (schroot).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476058</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-introduction/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T13:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is no shortage of books, articles, and courses, but to truly understand a concept, I always found it necessary to see how it worked...
The post Programming embedded systems: Introduction appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["대통령 님 파이팅"과 이해충돌 방지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=86894</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/86894"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T11:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 공직 사회는 새로운 법 하나를 공부하느라 이곳저곳에서 연일 교육과 특강이 열리고 있다고 합니다. 바로 지난 5월 16일부터 시행에 들어간 ‘이해충돌방지법’에 어떻게 대처해야 하는지를 알려주는 속성과외가 한창인 모양입니다. 200만 공직자가 적용 대상인데, 입법 과정에서 이른바 김영란법(부정청탁금지법)처럼 언론인도 포함시켜야 한다는 주장이 있었지만, ‘다행히’ 그냥 넘어갔습니다. 법안이 아니라더라도 이해충돌(conflict of interests)이란  용어는 요즘 뉴스에서 매우 흔하게 접하게 […]
The post "대통령 님 파이팅"과 이해충돌 방지 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTV 광고 시장에서 격돌하는 유튜브와 틱톡 경쟁 상황]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587653</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587653/ctv-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5%ec%9d%98-%ec%9c%a0%ed%8a%9c%eb%b8%8c%ec%99%80-%ed%8b%b1%ed%86%a1-%ea%b2%bd%ec%9f%81"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T10:30:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Containers and container images 101 for developers]]></title>
        <id>eaeb35d4-6a27-4010-9260-ae0102993164</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/08/29/containers-and-container-images-101-developers"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers, Kubernetes, and microservices have been a hot topic for the past few years, yet many developers may still be wondering how they all work. To take a somewhat different angle on the subject, this article will describe how a container image is constructed and executed using a non-traditional, conversational approach.
First, let's take a quick look at the layers of a container image and how they relate to one another.
What is a container image?
Briefly, an image is an operating system that runs libraries and runtimes and an application, all enclosed in an Open Container Initiative (OCI) compliant file.
Figure 1 illustrates an example: a Node.js application that uses the Express library, running on the Red Hat Universal Base Image (UBI) operating system. If you're not familiar with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Schenck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHPStan으로 PHP 제네릭 활용하기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/php-generics-with-phpstan/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/php-generics-with-phpstan/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T02:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여러 동적 타입 언어가 각자의 방식대로 강타입을 지원해가는 과정은 정말 흥미롭습니다. php에서도 타입에 대한 더욱 다양한 지원을 추가하려는 노력이 계속되고 있는 데다 PHPStan, Psalm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSJ, 미국 경제는 침체가 아닌 정체일 수 있습니다. 미국 경제에 대한 새로운 해석]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587646</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587646/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ea%b2%bd%ec%a0%9c-%ed%95%b4%ec%84%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T02:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[돈의 심리학에서 배우는 10가지 교훈]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587644</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587644/%eb%8f%88%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%ac%eb%a6%ac%ed%95%99"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T01:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사중명(謝仲明)의 <유학과 현대 세계>]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222860888811</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222860888811"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:11:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[맹자-왕양명과 주희를 대조시키는 이명휘의 글을 보다가 사중명의 <유학과 현대 세계>(1998)가 생각났다. 영미철학과 스트로슨을 전공한 사중명의 책도 이명휘와 유사하게 모종삼의 철학적 주장을 옹호하고 있다. (그러나 옹호의 논증을 제시하기 보다는 모종삼의 주장은 자세하게 풀어주고 있을 뿐이다.) 그가 다음처럼 말한다. <유학은 그 본질 면에서 말한다면, 그것은 심성(心性)의 학이요, 다른 말로 하면 내성(內省)의 학이다. 만약 그것이 학문의 일종이라면, 그것은 특별한 의미를 가지는 학문으로 일반적으로 일컬어지는 학문(knowledge, science)과 다르다. 그것은 개체에서 우주에 이르기까지의 도덕적 완성을 관계하는 생명.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[20+ Ways to Init a String, Looking for Sanity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/init-string-options/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/init-string-options/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++ is famous… or infamous for its complex initialization syntax. In this article, I’ll show you around 20 ways to initialize simple std::string variables. Can we somehow make it easier to understand?



     
    


Have a look:
void foo() {
    std::string str0;
    std::string str1 {};
}


We have two local variables (with automatic storage duration), str0 is default initialized, while str1 is value initialized.
While default initialization is unsafe for integers or other built-in types, it’s relatively fine (but less readable) for class types with a default constructor. In that case, a default constructor will be called, and the string object will get an empty value. The same constructor is invoked for value initialization.
Nevertheless, it’s best to set a value:
void foo() {
    int x…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 수정헌법 2조와 클래런스 토머스 대법관의 비뚤어진 원전주의]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75199</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/08/28/npc_scotusgunoriginalism/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_scotusgunoriginalism"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T22:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국 대법원과 관련 있는 사람들이 절대로 휴가를 쓸 수 없는 달이 있다면 6월입니다. 법으로 정해진 미국 대법원의 한 해는 10월 첫 번째 월요일에 시작해서 이듬해 10월 첫 번째 월요일 전날인 일요일에 끝납니다. 보통 대법관들은 6월 말 또는 7월 초부터 여름휴가 및 휴지기를 갖고, 한 해 동안 고민하고 논의한 사건들에 관해 내린 결정을 휴지기 직전인 6월에 잇달아 발표합니다. 대법관은 물론 대법관의 심복인 로클럭들, 재판에 참여한 변호사, 로펌, 담당 기자들에게도 6월은 가장 바쁜 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.0-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/906315/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/906315/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T22:40:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.0-rc3 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	So as some people already noticed, last week was an anniversary
	week - 31 years since the original Linux development
	announcement. How time flies.

	But this is not that kind of historic email - it's just the regular
	weekly RC release announcement, and things look pretty normal.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Task backlog waiting times are power laws]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7073</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/08/28/task-backlog-waiting-times-are-power-laws/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T22:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once it has been agreed to implement new functionality, how long do the associated tasks have to wait in the to-do queue? An analysis of the SiP task data finds that waiting time has a power law distribution, i.e., , where is the number of tasks waiting a given amount of time; the LSST:DM Sprint/Story-point/Story […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 파월 의장 잭슨홀 연설에 녹아있는 폴 보커  정신]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587637</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587637/%ed%8c%8c%ec%9b%94-%ec%9d%98%ec%9e%a5-%ec%9e%ad%ec%8a%a8%ed%99%80-%ec%97%b0%ec%84%a4%ea%b3%bc-%ed%8f%b4-%eb%b3%b4%ec%bb%a4-%ec%a0%95%ec%8b%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-08-28T12:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a BLE Module for Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://novelbits.io/?p=22320</id>
        <link href="https://novelbits.io/how-to-choose-ble-module-for-your-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T14:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a way to add BLE connectivity to your project, you have many options. So how do you know which module is right for you? We’ll help you understand the options available and make the best decision for your needs. How to select a BLE module There are a few key considerations […]
The post How to Choose a BLE Module for Your Project appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nthatisi Hlapisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>