<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-05-27T20:13:24.987Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/27, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594796</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594796/5-27-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T17:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LLVM improvements for BPF verification]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974945/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974945/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T17:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Jowett gave a remote presentation at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit about what features could be
added to LLVM to make writing BPF programs easier. While there is nothing specific
to LLVM about BPF code (and the next session in the track was led by GCC
developer José Marchesi about better support for that compiler), LLVM is currently the most
common way to turn C code into BPF bytecode. That translation, however, runs
into problems when the BPF verifier cannot understand the code LLVM's
optimizations produce.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fleshing out memory descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974937/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974937/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the long-term goals of the folio conversion in the kernel's
memory-management subsystem is the replacement of the page
structure, which describes a page of physical memory, with an eight-byte
"memory descriptor".  This change would reduce the overhead of tracking
physical memory, increase type safety, and make memory management more
flexible.  Thus far, though, details on what the memory-descriptor future
will look like have been relatively scarce.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Matthew Wilcox led a
discussion to try to fill in the picture somewhat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975399/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975399/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache2, bluez, chromium, fossil, libreoffice, python-pymysql, redmine, and ruby-rack), Fedora (buildah, crosswords, dotnet7.0, glycin-loaders, gnome-tour, helix, helvum, libipuz, loupe, maturin, mingw-libxml2, ntpd-rs, perl-Email-MIME, and a huge list of Rust-based packages due to a "mini-mass-rebuild" that updated the toolchain to Rust 1.78 and picked up fixes for various pieces), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, mariadb, and roundcubemail), Oracle (kernel, libreoffice, nodejs, and tomcat), and SUSE (cJSON, libfastjson, opera, postgresql15, python3, and qt6-networkauth).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.10 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974869/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974869/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T13:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released 6.10-rc1 and closed
the 6.10 merge window on May 26.  By that time, 11,534 non-merge
changesets had been pulled into the mainline for the next release; nearly
5,000 of those came in after "The first half of
the 6.10 merge window" was written.  While the latter half of the merge
window tends to focus more on fixes, there was also a lot of new
functionality that landed during this time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The next steps for the maple tree]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974860/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974860/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T12:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maple tree data structure was added
during the 6.1 development cycle; since then, it has taken its
place at the core of the kernel's memory-management subsystem.
Unsurprisingly, work on maple trees is not yet done.  Maple-tree maintainer
Liam Howlett ran a session in the memory-management track of the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit to discuss the current
state of the maple tree and which features can be expected next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Core competencies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1666.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1666.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T07:35:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a good, albeit rather general, rule that applies to the management of a successful business: focus on what you do well, then do it better than everyone else. There are numerous examples of how companies have been very successful by following this approach.
But the world of embedded software is commonly an exception …
To start with, I can cite some examples of good practice:
Have...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공익소송의 가치, 돈으로 막아서도 괜찮은가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109234</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109234"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T04:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[호주제 폐지, 낙태죄 헌법소원 등 ‘공익소송’은 우리 사회에 전향적인 변화를 일으켜 왔습니다. 소송에서의 승패를 넘어서서, 국가기관이나 대기업 등을 향한 소송 제기 자체가 사회의 변화를 촉구하는 공익적 목적을 가지는데요. 하지만 패소한다면 막대한 소송비용을 오롯이 떠맡아야 합니다. 현행 민사소송법이 예외 없이 소송비용은 무조건 패소한 측이 부담한다고 규정하고 있기 때문입니다(패소자부담주의). 이에 공익소송 당사자들이 헌법소원을 제기했지만, 헌법재판소는 해당 법조항이...
The post 공익소송의 가치, 돈으로 막아서도 괜찮은가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Function Composition and the Pipe Operator in C++23 – With std::expected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/pipe-operator/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/pipe-operator/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll show how to implement a custom pipe operator and apply it to a data processing example. Thanks to C++23 and std::expectedwe can write a rather efficient framework that easily handles unexpected outcomes.
This is a collaborative guest post by prof. Bogusław Cyganek:
        
        

        
Prof. Cyganek is a researcher and lecturer at the Department of Electronics, AGH University of Science and Technology in Cracow, Poland. He has worked as a software engineer for a number of companies such as Nisus Writer USA, Compression Techniques USA, Manta Corp. USA, Visual Atoms UK, Wroclaw University in Poland, and Diagnostyka Inc. Poland. His research interests include computer vision and pattern recognition, as well as the development of embedded systems. See his recent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975145/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975145/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T22:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released
6.10-rc1 and closed the merge window for this release.  For reasons
that have not been spelled out, the codename for the release has been
changed to "Baby Opossum Posse".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“정의 구현” 대 “마녀사냥”, 프레임 전쟁의 승자와 패자는]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79414</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/26/npsp_trumptrialelection/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_trumptrialelection"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T22:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이달 초 뉴욕타임스가 공개한 대선 여론조사 결과를 보면, 바이든 대통령이 트럼프 전 대통령에게 계속 뒤처지는 거로 나왔습니다. 여러 가지 원인이 지목되는 가운데, 지난달 맨해튼 법정에서 시작된 트럼프 전 대통령의 소위 “입막음용 뒷돈” 재판은 트럼프에게 오히려 득이 되고 있다는 주장이 설득력을 얻고 있습니다. 로스 더우댓이 그런 주장을 담은 칼럼을 썼습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 여론조사 결과를 해설로 덧붙였습니다. 전문 번역: 야당 대통령 후보 향한 이런 식의 법정 공세, 정치 과잉의 부조리 아닌가: 이것은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열의 계란말이 파티, 기자들은 아무것도 묻지 않았다: 슬로우레터 5월27일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109185</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109185"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T22:04:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[술은 없었지만 화기애애했다. “국민 분노 비웃나.” 쟁점과 현안. 윤석열 지지율은 여전히 24%. 특검법 이탈표 4명으로 늘었다. “라인 사태 외교 사안 아니다.” 더 깊게 읽기. “44% 받겠다” 이재명 제안에 국민의힘 ‘움찔’. “연금 개혁은 코끼리 옮기기 같은 것.” 모수 개혁과 구조 개혁. 다르게 읽기. 대북 송금 사건? 쌍방울 주가조작 사건이다. 엥겔 지수의 함정. 시진핑은 왜 안 왔을까....
The post 윤석열의 계란말이 파티, 기자들은 아무것도 묻지 않았다: 슬로우레터 5월27일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sampling error in software engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8811</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/05/26/sampling-error-in-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T21:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the physical sciences, measurement error occurs because of accuracy limits on the device used to make the measurement and the interpretation of the data by the person doing the measurement. In software engineering, some measurements appear to be error free. For instance, lines of code is a discrete value that is easily counted. While […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한미반도체 HBM 기술 관련 삼성전자 기술탈취 소송을 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594788</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594788/%ec%83%81%ec%a0%84%ec%a0%84%ec%9e%90-%ea%b8%b0%ec%88%a0%ed%83%88%ec%b7%a8"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T13:03:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모처럼 조선일보가 이재명을 칭찬하는 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109158</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109158"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T07:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 국민연금 막판 협상, 누가 거짓말을 하나: 더 내고 더 받는 개혁, 이것이 최선일까. 이재명(민주당 대표)이 승부수를 던졌다. 국회에서 기자간담회를 열고 “여당이 제시한 소득대체율 44%를 전적으로 수용하겠다”고 말했다. “꼭 해야 할 일인데 시간은 없으니 불가피하게 민주당이 다 양보하겠다”면서 “1%포인트 차이 때문에 연금 개혁안을 무산시킬 수는 없다”고 강조했다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 핵심 쟁점. 충돌하는 지점. 말이...
The post 모처럼 조선일보가 이재명을 칭찬하는 이유. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight weekend stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975072/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975072/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-26T00:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9.2, 6.8.11, 6.6.32, 6.1.92, 5.15.160, 5.10.218, 5.4.277, and 4.19.315
stable kernel updates have all been released. Each contains an
important set of fixes. Users of those kernels should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Two talks on multi-size transparent huge page performance]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974826/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974826/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T16:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using huge pages has been known for years to improve the performance of
many workloads.  But traditional huge pages, often sized by the CPU at 2MB,
can be difficult to allocate and can waste memory due to internal
fragmentation.  Driven by both the folio transition and hardware
improvements, attention to smaller, multi-size transparent huge pages
(mTHPs) has been on the rise.  In two memory-management-track sessions at
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, developers discussed the
kernel's ability to reliably allocate mTHPs and the performance gains that
result.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arenas and the almighty concatenation operator]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/25/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/25/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I continue to streamline an arena-based paradigm, and stumbled
upon a concise technique for dynamic growth — an efficient, generic
“concatenate anything to anything” within an arena built atop a core of
9-ish lines of code. The key insight originated from a reader suggestion
about dynamic arrays. The subject of concatenation can be a string,
dynamic array, or even something else. The “system” is extensible, and
especially useful for path handling.
Continuing from last time, the examples are in light, C-style C++.
I chose it because templates and function overloading express the concepts
succinctly. It uses no standard library functionality, so converting to C,
or similar, should be straightforward. The core concatenation “operator”:

template<typename T>
T concat(arena *a, T head, T tail)
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guidelines for computing sizes and subscripts]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/24/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/05/24/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T22:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Occasionally we need to compute the size of an object that does not yet
exist, or a subscript that may fall out of bounds. It’s easy to miss
the edge cases where results overflow, creating a nasty, subtle bug, even
in the presence of type safety. Ideally such computations happen in
specialized code, such as inside an allocator (calloc, reallocarray)
and not outside by the allocatee (i.e. malloc). Mitigations exist with
different trade-offs: arbitrary precision, or using a wider fixed integer
— i.e. 128-bit integers on 64-bit hosts. In the typical case, working only
with fixed size-type integers, I’ve come up with a set of guidelines to
avoid overflows in the edge cases.
Range check before computing a result. No exceptions.
Do not cast unless you know a priori the operand is in range.
Never…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Atomic writes without tears]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974578/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974578/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T21:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Garry and Ted Ts'o led a discussion about supporting atomic writes for buffered
I/O, without any torn (or partial) writes to the device, at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  It is something of a
continuation of a discussion at last year's
summit. The goal is to help PostgreSQL, which writes its data using
16KB buffered I/O; it currently has to do a lot of extra work to ensure
that its data is safe on disk.  A promise of non-torn, 16KB buffered writes
would allow the database 
to avoid doing double writes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Allocator optimizations for transparent huge pages]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974636/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974636/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T20:42:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The original Linux kernel, posted in 1991, ran on a system with a 4KB page
size.  Over 30 years later, most of us are still running on systems
with 4KB pages, even though the amount of installed memory has grown by a
few orders of magnitude.  It is generally accepted that using large page
sizes results in better performance for most applications, but allocating
larger pages is often difficult.  During a memory-management session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Yu Zhao presented his
ideas on improving the allocation of huge pages in the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google @ KotlinConf 2024: A Look Inside Multiplatform Development with KMP and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T20:13:52.290Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following our recent Google I/O announcement recommending Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) for sharing business logic across mobile, web, server, and desktop platforms, and our move to use KMP in Google Workspace, KotlinConf 2024 was the next moment to share the highlights and connect with the Kotlin community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Recent improvements to BPF's struct_ops mechanism]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974848/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974848/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T19:37:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kui-Feng Lee spoke early in the BPF track at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit about some of the
recent improvements to BPF. These changes were largely driven by the
sched_ext work that David Vernet had covered in
the previous talk. Lee focused on changes relevant to struct_ops
programs, but several of those changes apply to all BPF programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Readying DNF5 for Fedora 41]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/969640/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/969640/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the release of Fedora 40 it's time to
start looking ahead to what Fedora 41 has in store. One of the largest
changes planned for the next release is a switch to
DNF5, a C++ rewrite of the DNF
package manager. A previous attempt to make the switch, during the Fedora 39 cycle, was called off, and
deferred to Fedora 41. The developers have had nearly a year to address
compatibility problems and bring DNF5 to a state suitable to replace DNF4. Signs point to a successful switch in
the upcoming release, though there may be a few surprises lurking for Fedora users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: a look at the implications of the Cyber Resilience Act (CRA)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482387</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/podcast-a-look-at-the-implications-of-the-cyber-resilience-act-cra/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The European Parliament approved the CRA in March 2024, which means companies will now need to step up their preparations or be prepared to pay fines for non-compliance.
The post Podcast: a look at the implications of the Cyber Resilience Act (CRA) appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFC I2C bridge tag enables secure contactless IoT device authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482382</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nfc-i2c-bridge-tag-enables-secure-contactless-iot-device-authentication/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T15:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Infineon Technologies has launched a high-performance NFC I2C bridge tag for single-tap authentication and secured configuration of IoT devices. 
The post NFC I2C bridge tag enables secure contactless IoT device authentication appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated parking replaces ultrasonic with vision cameras]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482377</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/automated-parking-replaces-ultrasonic-with-vision-cameras/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nodar said its solution is able to combine different independently mounted stereo pairs of cameras around the vehicle to generate high-resolution 3D point clouds.
The post Automated parking replaces ultrasonic with vision cameras appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Large-folio support for shmem and tmpfs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974630/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974630/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T14:02:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel contains a pair of related filesystems that, among other things,
can be used for shared-memory applications; shmem is an internal mechanism
used within the kernel, while the tmpfs filesystem is mounted and
accessible from user space.  As is the case elsewhere in the kernel, these
subsystems would benefit from the addition of large-folio support.  During
a joint storage, filesystem, and memory-management session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Daniel Gomez talked about
the work he is doing to add that support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BitKeeper, Linux, and licensing disputes: How Linus wrote Git in 14 days 
(Graphite blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974914/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974914/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
Graphite blog post retells the history of the BitKeeper fiasco and the
dawn of the Git era.


	When we think of history, we often romanticize it as being born of
	a sudden stroke of inspiration. But the creation of git shows the
	far harsher reality of invention: a slowly escalating disagreement
	over a license; the need for a scrappy backup solution to unblock
	work; and then continued polishing and iteration through years and
	years, led not by the inventor, but rather a community.


For those who weren't around in those days, a perusal of the LWN coverage
from the time might be of interest too, including:


 Our first mention of BitKeeper
     in October 1998
 Not quite open source,
     1999
 Linus tries out BitKeeper, 2002
 The free software community and proprietary
     packages, 2002
 The kernel and BitKeeper part ways,
     2005
 How Tridge reverse engineered
     BitKeeper, 2005
 The guts of Git, 2005


...and a lot more for those who care to search for it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974913/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974913/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T13:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium, libreoffice, and thunderbird), Red Hat (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, gdk-pixbuf2, git-lfs, glibc, python3, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), SUSE (firefox, opensc, and ucode-intel), and Ubuntu (cjson and gnome-remote-desktop).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trustworthy AI using Confidential Federated Learning]]></title>
        <id>3665220</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3665220"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T12:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[스노우플레이크 실적을 읽는월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594786</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594786/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%8a%a4%eb%85%b8%ec%9a%b0%ed%94%8c%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:22:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/24, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594784</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594784/5-24-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T08:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement AI-driven edge to core data pipelines]]></title>
        <id>0e750f45-625d-460e-8591-9f922c1b562e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/24/implement-ai-driven-edge-core-data-pipelines"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The interaction of AI/ML and edge computing occurs in a variety of businesses. For example, in the retail industry, customer behavior and patterns can be used to determine promotions. In a manufacturing facility, likewise, data inference can help improve processes where machines are failing, products are not up to standard, and so on. The basic premise is that you might collect data and then infer from it in order to make decisions based on it.
In the context of this retail use case example, a superstore company has branches spread across the country. Each branch decides the products it wants to sell and can customize an AI/ML intelligent app for customers to use.
This article presents a video demonstration illustrating an opinionated solution capable of automating a continuous cycle for r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno Meseguer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Run OpenShift sandboxed containers with hosted control planes]]></title>
        <id>d8d96b3f-e3b0-47e1-977f-c50b0810079b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/24/run-openshift-sandboxed-containers-hosted-control-planes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hosted control planes, available via the multi-cluster engine, has been generally available since Red Hat OpenShift 4.14. Hosted control planes reduce costs and improve productivity for organizations adopting a multi-cluster approach.
OpenShift sandboxed containers, based on Kata Containers, and generally available since OpenShift 4.8, is a native Kubernetes CRI runtime that provides an additional layer of isolation for workloads through hardware virtualization.
When used together, hosted control planes and OpenShift sandboxed containers offer several benefits, such as speed, separation of concerns, and the necessary hardening to run multi-tenant workloads with stringent security constraints. 
This article provides a detailed guide on how to configure and run sandboxed workloads for OpenSh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Camilla Conte, Adel Zaalouk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MBTI? 30점짜리 심리테스트, 100점짜리 예능 소품]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108188</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108188"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T06:47:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 분석합니다. 이번 케이스는 MBTI(두둥!). “MBTI의 핵심은 내 성격을 내가 안다는 게 아니에요. 내가 세상 모든 사람을 MBTI 하나로 다 알 수 있다고 생각(착각)하는 거죠.” (캡콜드) MBTI, 더 말이 필요한가. 그 열풍에 관해 캡콜드(김낙호 펜실베이니아주립대학교 커뮤니케이션학과 교수)에게 물었다. MBTI 개요 MBTI 누가 만들었나. MBTI는 ‘마이어스-브리그스 유형 지표'(Myers-Briggs...
The post MBTI? 30점짜리 심리테스트, 100점짜리 예능 소품 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 이보다 더 좋을 순 없다, 목표주가 1400$까지 상향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594776</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594776/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T00:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 환율도 제각각, 음식값도 매일 달라지는 ‘메시의 나라’, “다시 위대”해질 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79059</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/23/npsp_javiermilei/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_javiermilei"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T22:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 3일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난 3월 초, 엿새간 아르헨티나에 다녀왔습니다. 다소 촉박하게 일정이 잡혀서 처음 가보는 나라, 지역임에도 미리 충분히 공부하고 준비하지 못한 채 비행기에 몸을 실었습니다. 사실 열정적인 축구팬인 저는 “현재 월드컵 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 ‘격노’ 담긴 녹음 파일, ‘스모킹 건’이 될까: 슬로우레터 5월24일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109076</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109076"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T22:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김계환 녹취 파일, ‘스모킹 건’이 될까. ‘격노’ 이후 모든 게 달라졌다. 김계환의 양심선언이 필요할 때다. 쟁점과 현안. 연금 개혁은 다음 국회로. 반도체 산업에 26조 원 투입. 물가 때문에… 기준 금리 동결. 가계 실질 소득, 7년 만에 최대폭 감소. 더 깊게 읽기. 4년 중임제 개헌, 해볼 만하다. “외롭습니다.” 다르게 읽기. 이종섭 출국 금지는 공수처 작품이었다. ‘버닝썬’이...
The post 윤석열 ‘격노’ 담긴 녹음 파일, ‘스모킹 건’이 될까: 슬로우레터 5월24일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A new swap abstraction layer for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974587/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974587/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T19:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Swapping may be a memory-management technique at its core, but its
implementation also involves the kernel's filesystem and storage layers.
So it is not surprising that a session on the kernel's swap abstraction
layer, led by Chris Li at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, was held jointly by all
three of those tracks.  Li has some ambitious ideas for an improved
subsystem, but getting to a workable implementation may not be easy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What's scheduled for sched_ext]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974387/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974387/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T17:34:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Vernet's second talk at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit was a summary of the state of
sched_ext, the extensible BPF scheduler that LWN
covered a in early May. In short, sched_ext is intended as a platform for
rapid experimentation with schedulers, and a tool to let performance-minded
administrators customize the scheduler to their workload. The patch set has seen
several revisions, becoming more generic and powerful over time.
Vernet spoke about what has been done in the past year,
and what is still missing before sched_ext can be considered pretty much
complete.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Splitting in Single-Page Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#IntroducingUserdetailcardComponent</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#IntroducingUserdetailcardComponent"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Single-Page Applications often require a lot of code to be downloaded
       to the browser, which can delay a page's initial
       appearance. Juntao Qiu's next pattern, Code Splitting,
       describes how this code can be divided up, so that modules are only
       loaded if they are going to be needed, and the dangers of doing so.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE Gear 24.05.0]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974708/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974708/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:16:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The KDE Project has announced the
release of KDE Gear 24.05.0, with new features and updates for the
more than 200 applications that
are part of the project. In addition to new versions of the Dolphin
file manager, Kdenlive video
editor, and Elisa music player, this
release includes five applications new to KDE Gear: the Audex CD-ripper application,
an application Accessibility
Inspector, the Francis
Pomodoro timer, Kalm to teach breathing techniques, and a Sokoban-like game
called Skladnik. See the
full
changelog for a complete list of changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The twilight of the version-1 memory controller]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974575/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974575/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T14:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Almost immediately after the merging of control
groups, kernel developers set their sights on reimplementing them
properly.  The second version of the control-group API started trickling
into the kernel around the 3.16 release in 2014 and users have long since
been encouraged to migrate, but support for (and users of) the initial API
remain.  At the 2024
Linux Storage, Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit,
memory-management developers discussed whether (and when) it might be
possible to remove the version-1 memory controller.  The session was led by
Shakeel Butt and (participating remotely) Roman Gushchin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974824/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974824/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T13:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (chromium, libxml2, pgadmin4, and python-libgravatar), Mageia (ghostscript), Red Hat (389-ds:1.4, ansible-core, bind and dhcp, container-tools:rhel8, edk2, exempi, fence-agents, freeglut, frr, ghostscript, glibc, gmp, go-toolset:rhel8, grafana, grub2, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, gstreamer1-plugins-base, gstreamer1-plugins-good, harfbuzz, httpd:2.4, idm:DL1, idm:DL1 and idm:client modules, kernel, kernel-rt, krb5, LibRaw, libreoffice, libsndfile, libssh, libtiff, libX11, libxml2, libXpm, linux-firmware, motif, mutt, openssh, osbuild and osbuild-composer, pam, pcp, pcs, perl-Convert-ASN1, perl-CPAN, perl:5.32, pki-core:10.6 and pki-deps:10.6 modules, pmix, poppler, postgresql-jdbc, python-dns, python-jinja2, python-pillow, python27:2.7, python3.11, python3.11-cryptography, python3.11-urllib3, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9 modules, qt5-qtbase, resource-agents, squashfs-tools, sssd, systemd, tigervnc, tomcat, traceroute, varnish:6, virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel modules, vorbis-tools, webkit2gtk3, xorg-x11-server, xorg-x11-server-Xwayland, and zziplib), SUSE (chromium, perl, postgresql14, and python-sqlparse), and Ubuntu (klibc, linux-aws-hwe, openssl, and vlc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidential Computing or Cryptographic Computing?]]></title>
        <id>3664295</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664295"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T12:27:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[네이버의 진짜 위기는 라인이 아니다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109022</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109022"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:32:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 최대 실적 내고도 주가가 안 오르는 이유: 검색 광고 시장 위축에 한 발 늦은 AI 전략, 새로운 성장 엔진이 필요한 시점. 누구나 잘 아는 것 같지만 의외로 잘 모르는 기업. 오늘 슬로우리포트에서는 네이버의 위기를 살펴봅니다. 국민주 네이버는 왜 사상 최대의 실적을 기록하고도 주가가 지지부진할까요? 라인야후 사태도 심각하지만 근본적으로 전망이 안 보인다는 관측이 많습니다. 한동안...
The post 네이버의 진짜 위기는 라인이 아니다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 1: Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) Introduction]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:65dfa3dd-b3dd-42ee-930d-1301a6ee028b</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/arm-scalable-matrix-extension-introduction"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog series provides an introduction to the Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) including SVE and SVE2.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zenon Xiu (修志龙）</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift Virtualization for VMware vSphere admins: Disaster and site recovery]]></title>
        <id>c724ccd6-3b6b-4679-8c6a-3541dd2bf6e7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/24/virtualization-vsphere-disaster-recovery"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nobody likes to think about disasters. Surely that won’t happen to you. Often the mantra is to hope for the best and plan for the worst. In today’s IT world, downtime, no matter how small, can have a disastrous effect on a business’ ability to compete in the marketplace. 
What is disaster recovery?
There are many options to consider when it comes to the concepts of business continuity and disaster recovery. Primarily we find ourselves concerned with two major metrics: the recovery point objective (RPO) and the recovery time objective (RTO). 
The RPO is what amount of data is considered an acceptable loss in the event of a disaster. If you lose data due to an unforeseen event, and your last successful backup and restore point is three days old, is that an acceptable loss of data? 
The RTO i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Cowles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing frameworks for images built via Insights image builder]]></title>
        <id>55dd06bd-950c-41d2-888a-fef10af36296</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/23/testing-frameworks-images-built-insights-image-builder"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building images for cloud deployments or on-premises servers provides a number of challenges. These include reducing the attack surface, ensuring the images are hardened, and monitoring their compliance on an ongoing basis. We will explore how Red Hat Insights can achieve what no other service can by leveraging Red Hat’s open hybrid cloud strategy. You can use Red Hat Insights image builder to deploy pre-hardened images then monitor the systems with our compliance tool, compared to using custom-built testing frameworks leveraging tools such as AWS Security Hub.
Building images
Insights image builder makes the process of hardening images much simpler because it leverages OpenSCAP remediations at build time before the image has even been launched. This is desirable since some options, such a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gianluca Zuccarelli, Obinna Ezeakachi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install and migrate to Red Hat build of Keycloak]]></title>
        <id>e8fa57ec-4e86-49e9-b732-e8ac2fd534f5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/23/migrate-sso-red-hat-build-keycloak"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat's single sign-on tool has long been a trusted solution for securing web applications and providing centralized identity management. However, with the introduction of the Red Hat build of Keycloak, a next-generation option has emerged. This article will guide you through how to migrate from Red Hat's single sign-on to Red Hat build of Keycloak, highlighting the benefits and considerations involved in this strategic move.
We'll delve into the key advantages of Red Hat build of Keycloak, such as its cloud-native architecture, enhanced performance, and streamlined configuration. Additionally, we'll provide a step-by-step approach to the migration process, ensuring a smooth transition with minimal disruption to your existing infrastructure. Whether you're seeking improved scalability, c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Pablo Castelo, Ignacio Lago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘희생양 이론’으로 보는 학생인권조례 폐지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109000</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109000"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T06:21:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[심리학 및 사회학 연구에 뿌리를 둔 ‘희생양 이론’은 개인이나 집단이 자신의 문제나 실패에 관해 부당하게 다른 사람이나 집단을 비난하는 현상을 말한다. 희생양 메커니즘의 본질은 한 개인이나 단체·사회가 서로의 이해관계가 충돌했을 때 또는 그저 그들의 욕망이 충돌해서 문제가 드러날 때 힘없는 또는 상대적으로 미약한 희생양에게 책임을 전가함으로써 진짜 문제의 원인인 가해자가 자신의 죄책감, 좌절감 또는 무능함을...
The post ‘희생양 이론’으로 보는 학생인권조례 폐지 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤지명</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 실적 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594774</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594774/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-2"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T03:33:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 23, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973888/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973888/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T01:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 23, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“검사 위에 여사, 이게 나라냐”, 동아일보 김순덕의 분노: 슬로우레터 5월23일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108962</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108962"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T22:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘VIP 격노’ 들은 사람이 또 있다. “이탈 표 10명은 나올 것.” “박정훈 기소 취소하자” 보고서 뭉갰다. 쟁점과 현안. “공매도 재개는 이복현 개인 의견.” 카드 연체율 9년 만에 최고. “전통과 권위의 정론지, 조선일보.” 더 깊게 읽기. 정권 말 복지부동이 벌써 시작됐다. 윤석열에게는 ‘레드팀’이 필요하다. 다르게 읽기. 나이 들면 운전 제한? 하루 만에 말 바꾼 이유. 안보동맹이...
The post “검사 위에 여사, 이게 나라냐”, 동아일보 김순덕의 분노: 슬로우레터 5월23일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++: freeing resources in destructors using helper functions]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1125/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1125/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll look at how to correctly destroy objects in the OOP-based C++ program without redundant operations. This is the final article in the series about the bugs in qdEngine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Supporting larger block sizes in filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974219/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974219/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T20:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a 
combined storage and filesystem session at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Luis Chamberlain led a
discussion on filesystem support for block sizes larger than the usual 4KB
page size, 
which followed up on  discussion from last year.  While the
session was meant to look at the intersection of larger block sizes
with atomic block writes  that avoid torn
(partial) writes (which was also discussed last year), it mostly focused on the
filesystem side.  Over time, the
block sizes offered by storage devices have risen from the original
512 bytes; Chamberlain
wanted to discuss filesystem support for block sizes larger than 4KB.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The path to deprecating SPARSEMEM]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974517/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974517/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T18:58:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term "memory model" is used in a couple of ways within the kernel.
Perhaps the more obscure meaning is the memory-management subsystem's view
of how physical memory is organized on a given system.  A proper
representation of physical memory will be more efficient in terms of memory
and CPU use.  Since hardware comes in numerous variations, the kernel
supports a number of memory models to match; see this article for details.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Oscar Salvador,
presenting remotely, made the case for removing one of those models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Two sessions on CXL memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974518/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974518/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T18:56:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compute
Express Link (CXL) is a data-center-oriented memory solution that,
according to some in the industry, will yield large cost savings and
performance improvements.  Others are more skeptical.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, two sessions covered CXL
and how it will be supported in future kernels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A short note on how I use and render footnotes]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-footnote-rendering.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-footnote-rendering.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T18:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week I added a small feature to this website, changing the way it
       renders footnotes. That prompted me to write this quick note about how I
       use footnotes, and how that influences the best way to render them.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Documenting page flags by committee]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974515/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974515/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T17:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For every page of memory in the system, the kernel maintains a set of page
flags describing how the page is used and various aspects of its current
state.  Space for page flags has been in chronic short supply, leading to a desire to
eliminate or consolidate them whenever possible.  That objective, though,
is hampered by the fact that the purpose of many page flags is not well
understood.  In a memory-management-track session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Matthew Wilcox set out to
cooperatively update the page-flag documentation to improve that situation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Merging msharefs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974512/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974512/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T17:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The problem of sharing page tables across processes has been discussed
numerous times over the years, Khaled Aziz said at the beginning of his 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit session on the topic.  He
was there to, once again, talk about the proposed mshare() system call (which, in its
current form, is no longer actually a system call but the feature still
goes by that name) and to see what can be done to finally get it into the
mainline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 실적에서 살펴볼 5가지 요소]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594772</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594772/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Toward the unification of hugetlbfs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974491/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974491/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's hugetlbfs
subsystem was the first mechanism by which the kernel made huge pages
available to user space; it was added to the 2.5.46 development kernel in
2002.  While hugetlbfs remains useful, it is also viewed as a sort of
second memory-management subsystem that would be best unified with the rest
of the kernel.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Peter Xu raised the
question of what that unification would involve and what the first steps
might be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The KeePassXC kerfuffle]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973782/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973782/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T16:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KeePassXC is an open-source (GPLv3),
cross-platform password manager with local-only data storage. The
project comes with a number of build
options that can be used to toggle optional features, such as browser
integration and password
database sharing. However, controversy ensued when Debian Developer Julian Klode decided to
make use of these compile flags to disable these features to improve security in the
keepassxc package uploaded to Debian unstable for the
upcoming Debian 13 ("Trixie") release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidential Container Groups]]></title>
        <id>3664293</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664293"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The interaction between memory reclaim and RCU]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974487/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974487/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit was a development
conference, where discussion was prioritized and presentations with a lot
of slides were discouraged.  Paul McKenney seemingly flouted this
convention in a joint session of the storage, filesystem, and
memory-management tracks where he presented about 50 slides — in five
minutes, twice.  The subject was the use of the read-copy-update (RCU)
mechanism in the memory-reclaim process, and whether changes to RCU would
be needed for that purpose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alpine Linux 3.20.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974576/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974576/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T15:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
3.20.0 of the Alpine Linux
distribution has been released with initial support for 64-bit
RISC-V. Other important changes include updates to GNOME 46, 
KDE Plasma 6, and replacing Redis with Valkey due to Redis's
adoption of a non-free
license model. See the release
notes for more on this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing the contents of generated HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Level2TestingHtmlStructure</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Level2TestingHtmlStructure"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Vaccari continues his testing of
       template-generated HTML by describing tests for the contents of that
       HTML. He shows how to gradually build up the template, using Test-Driven
       Development in Go and Java. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Faster page faults with RCU-protected VMA walks]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974392/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974392/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking up a virtual memory area (VMA) in a process's address space, for
the handling of page faults or any of a number of other tasks, in
multi-threaded processes has long been bedeviled by lock contention in the
kernel.  As a result, developer gatherings have been subjected to many
sessions on how to improve the situation.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit, developers in the
memory-management track met, in a session led by Liam Howlett, to talk
about a situation that has improved considerably in recent times, but which
still offers opportunities for optimization.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974572/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974572/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (webkit2gtk), Fedora (kernel), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, djvulibre, gdk-pixbuf2.0, nss & firefox, postgresql15 & postgresql13, python-pymongo, python-sqlparse, stb, thunderbird, and vim), Red Hat (go-toolset:rhel8, nodejs, and varnish:6), SUSE (gitui, glibc, and kernel), and Ubuntu (libspreadsheet-parseexcel-perl, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gcp, python-idna, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Virtual machine scheduling with BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974363/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974363/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vineeth Pillai gave a remote talk at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit explaining how BPF could be
used to improve the performance of virtual machines (VMs). Pillai has

a patch
set designed to let guest and host machines share scheduling information in
order to eliminate some of the overhead of running in a VM. The assembled
developers had several comments on the design, but seemed overall to approve of
the prospect.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced container management at the edge for Node.js apps]]></title>
        <id>5ddfc0f2-1d39-4049-975f-c17b04bdd828</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/22/advanced-container-management-edge-nodejs-apps"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is part three in our series on running Node.js applications on the edge with Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL)/Fedora, which includes: 

Running Node.js applications on the edge with RHEL/Fedora
Containerizing your Node.js applications at the edge on RHEL/Fedora
Advanced container management at the edge for Node.js applications (this post)  

In the first part, we introduced you to the hardware and software for our Node.js-based edge example as well as some of the details on laying the foundation for deploying the application by building and installing the operating system using Fedora IoT.
In the second part we dug a bit deeper into the application itself, and how to build, bundle, deploy, and update the Node.js application using Podman and containers.
In this third and final part, we'…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Configure SOAP web services with Apache Camel on Quarkus]]></title>
        <id>57067f3e-06d2-47e8-ad3f-71028d587598</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/22/configure-soap-web-services-apache-camel-quarkus"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores how to integrate SOAP and REST services using Quarkus and Apache Camel. Through practical examples, we will learn how to create a Quarkus project, configure and consume SOAP services, and expose RESTful endpoints. Additionally, we will see how to manage JSON data serialization and deserialization using Camel Quarkus.
Quarkus project creation
For project configuration, it is required to create the application named code-with-quarkus-camel-soap, which will be using Quarkus 3.2 with Apache Camel version 4.0.


Review the compatibility matrix.
There are two options to carry out this configuration, detailed below.


Creation through the web interface
Access the link https://code.quarkus.redhat.com and fill in the required information as shown in Figure 1. Then, click the G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Falero Otiniano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The road toward AI: Fundamentals]]></title>
        <id>df098c45-b3b3-4179-9e8a-3392e93fb731</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/22/ai-fundamentals"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's no question that artificial intelligence (AI) is the talk of the town these days, overshadowing almost everything else in the world of technology. In this series of articles, we'll explore the road toward AI (Figure 1 ) and how your organization can smoothly transition toward incorporating AI into its platforms and applications. 
Clean architecture isn't the only topic I cover, you know! So, welcome aboard as we steer our focus toward artificial intelligence and machine learning (for now, at least, as these principles will map on the domain of AI/ML as well). 


  
      
        
  


  

Figure 1: A visualization of a technical road / learning path toward AI. Created by Maarten Vandeperre. License under Apache 2.0.

Don't worry if AI is still a bit of a mystery to you—we'll start…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Vandeperre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[둘이 같은 목소리 낼 때도 있네? ‘두 번째 차이나 쇼크’ 어떻게 될까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79391</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/21/npsp_chinashock/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_chinashock"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T02:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오는 11월 미국 대선에서 맞붙을 바이든과 트럼프가 의외로 같은 목소리를 내는 분야가 몇 가지 있는데, 그중 하나가 대중국 무역정책입니다. 물론 세부적인 방침은 다를 수 있지만, 기본적으로 중국이 미국을 상대로 불공정 무역을 하고 있으므로, 이를 바로잡겠다는 의지는 같으며, 이를 숨기지 않고 오히려 적극적으로 드러낸다는 점도 비슷합니다. 다만 트럼프가 직접적으로 관세를 매기고, 중국과 전면적인 관세 전쟁을 매겼다면, 바이든의 정책은 미국이 전략적으로 중국에 뒤처져선 안 되는 분야를 정해놓고 미국의 동맹국을 동원해 중국을 압박하는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low-Power Optimization Techniques for ARM Cortex-M Microcontrollers]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40522</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/05/22/low-power-optimization-techniques-for-arm-cortex-m0-microcontrollers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T00:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Europe, companies are focusing on sustainability due to the ongoing energy crisis. Embedded engineers are taking action to minimize energy consumption from electronic devices. This article demonstrates the possibility of reducing energy consumption by factor 100 or more and provides insights on low power optimizations using the ARM Cortex microcontroller. It uses tools such as NXP MCUXpresso IDE and MCU-Link Pro for measurements and demonstrations. The article explores low power optimization steps such as reducing voltage, frequency, and using low power modes, achieving significant energy savings. It provides a comprehensive overview of the concepts and practical techniques for reducing energy consumption. The project is shared on GitHub for reference. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Another try for address-space isolation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974390/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974390/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T22:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brendan Jackman started his memory-management-track session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory-Management and BPF Summit by saying that, for some
years now, the kernel community has been stuck in a reactive posture with
regard to hardware vulnerabilities.  Each problem shows up with its own
scary name, and kernel developers find a way to mitigate it, usually losing
performance in the process.  Jackman said that it is time to take back the
initiative against these vulnerabilities by reconsidering the more
general use of address-space isolation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/22, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594751</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594751/5-22-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T22:22:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[책은 버리고 디올 백은 남겼다? 김건희의 결정적 실수: 슬로우레터 5월22일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108917</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108917"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T22:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[결국 채 상병 특검법에 거부권 행사. 조선일보도 ‘쉴드’가 안 된다. “국민에게도 불행한 일.” 핵심은 윤석열의 ‘격노’. 벌써 3명 이탈. 국회 입법조사처가 못을 박았다. 쟁점과 현안. 책을 함부로 버리면 벌어지는 일. 책은 버리고 디올 백만 보관했다고? 김건희는 오랜만에 단독 행보. 윤석열 탈당설을 흘리는 이유. 다르게 읽기. 이명박은 어떻게 지지율을 끌어올렸을까. 더 깊게 읽기. “굳이 읽을 필요...
The post 책은 버리고 디올 백은 남겼다? 김건희의 결정적 실수: 슬로우레터 5월22일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Garnet. Does Microsoft's cache -store also store bugs?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1124/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1124/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has introduced Garnet, an open-source, cross-platform, fast cache-store project written in C#. Let's equip ourselves with a static analyzer to see what bugs and oddities hide in the project...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Memory-allocation profiling for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974380/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974380/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:34:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing the kernel's memory use is made much easier if developers have
an accurate idea of how memory is being used, but the kernel's
instrumentation is not as good as it could be.  When Suren Baghdasaryan and
Kent Overstreet presented their
memory-allocation profiling work, which is meant to address this
shortcoming, at the 2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem, Memory Management, and
BPF Summit, their objective was uncontroversial but the proposed solution
ran into opposition that played out at length on the mailing lists (example)
over the last year.  So it may be a bit surprising that, when the two
returned to the memory-management track in the 2024 gathering, the
controversy was gone and the discussion focused on improving details of the
implementation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2024: What’s new in Android Development Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-android-development-tools-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-android-development-tools-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T20:14:29.963Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android Studio Koala feature drop (2024.1.2) is now available in the Android Studio canary channel, with productivity enhancements, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux forms engineering steering committee]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974488/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974488/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AlmaLinux project has announced
the formation of the AlmaLinux Engineering
Steering Committee (ALESCo):
The initial members of ALESCo appointed by the AlmaLinux OS
Foundation board are Andrew Lukoshko, Ben Thomas, Cody Robertson,
Elkhan Mammadli, Jonathan Wright, and Neal Gompa. The AlmaLinux Wiki has
more information on the committee's activities and how to get involved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Dynamically sizing the kernel stack]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974367/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974367/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:37:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel stack is a scarce and tightly constrained resource; kernel
developers often have to go far out of their way to avoid using too much
stack space.  The size of the stack is also fixed, leading to situations
where it is too small for some code paths, while wastefully large for
others.  At the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Pasha Tatashin proposed
making the kernel stack size dynamic, making more space available when
needed while saving memory overall.  This change is not as easy to
implement as it might seem, though.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using markup for fallbacks when fetching data]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#fallback-markup</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#fallback-markup"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juntao Qiu's next data fetching pattern looks at how to specify
       fallback behavior using markup. This allows developers to
       pull such declarations out of the JavaScript components and into the
       markup they use while laying out the rest of the page. Juntao's React
       example shows how this works with the Suspense element, with a similar
       approach in vue.js.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test-Driving HTML Templates]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When building a server-side rendered web application, it's valuable
       to test the HTML that's generated through templates. While these can be
       tested through end-to-end tests running in the browser, such tests are
       slow and more work to maintain than unit tests. My colleague
       Matteo Vaccari has written an article on how to use TDD
       to test drive these templates using xunit-style tools which can be run
       easily from the command line or as part of build scripts.
In this first installment Matteo describes how such tests can check the
       generated HTML for validity, with examples in Java and Go.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Where should you put the { ?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482371</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/where-should-you-put-the/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few topics other than politics and religion that can get an engineering team fired up than trying to decide where to put the...
The post Where should you put the { ? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Facing down mapcount madness]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974223/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974223/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The page
structure is a complicated beast, but some parts of it are more
intimidating than others.  The mapcount field is one of the
scarier parts.  It allegedly records the number of references to the page
in page tables, but, as David Hildenbrand described during the
memory-management track at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, things are more
complicated than that.  Few people truly understand the semantics of this
field, but the situation will hopefully get better over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974450/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974450/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (firefox, nodejs, and thunderbird), Fedora (uriparser), Oracle (firefox and thunderbird), Slackware (mariadb), SUSE (cairo, gdk-pixbuf, krb5, libosinfo, postgresql14, and python310), and Ubuntu (firefox, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, and linux-azure).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IoT serves public safety and security services]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482367</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-iot-serves-public-safety-and-security-services/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T12:23:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement agencies are increasingly turning to cutting-edge connectivity and IoT solutions to improve operational efficiencies, increase transparency and safety, and enhance collaboration. Under mounting...
The post How IoT serves public safety and security services appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dennis Kelly</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[베런스]점점 다가오는 금리인하. 금리인하 수혜자는 누구일까]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594737</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594737/%ea%b8%88%eb%a6%ac%ec%9d%b8%ed%95%98-%ec%88%98%ed%98%9c%ec%9e%90"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Eclipse Projects with custom external Shell Scripts]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40588</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/05/21/building-eclipse-projects-with-custom-external-shell-scripts/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eclipse offers various ways to build projects, including a built-in builder, external tools like make or cmake, and custom scripts for advanced needs. By setting the C/C++ Build settings to 'External Builder,' a script can be used in place of the compiler for custom steps. However, portability issues may arise between different host machines. Nonetheless, using custom scripts allows for flexibility in the build process. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Native memory tracking in GraalVM Native Image]]></title>
        <id>ed9656d0-43bb-416f-b522-3f0b1e344f38</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/21/native-memory-tracking-graalvm-native-image"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Initial support for native memory tracking (NMT) has recently been added as a feature to GraalVM Native Image. It is currently available in early access builds and will be available in the future GraalVM for JDK 23 release. The addition of NMT will allow users of Native Image to better understand how their applications are using off-heap memory. 
Background
The terminology “native memory” is sometimes used interchangeably with “off-heap memory” or “unmanaged memory.” When a Java application is run on the JVM, "native memory" refers to any memory not allocated on the Java heap. Since the the JVM is implemented in C++, this includes the memory that the JVM uses under the hood for its internal operations as well as memory requested with Unsafe#allocateMemory(long), or from external libraries.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Toyonaga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve basic programming safety with Rust lang]]></title>
        <id>4922761c-f16d-4c24-b321-34af7cda0a73</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/21/improve-basic-programming-safety-rust-lang"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As software becomes increasingly integrated into our daily lives, the importance of secure coding and programming safety cannot be overstated. From online banking to healthcare records, sensitive information is being transmitted and stored in software systems, making them prime targets for cyber attacks. As a result, it's crucial for developers to understand and implement best practices for secure coding to ensure the safety and privacy of user data. In this article, we explore the various techniques and strategies that can be used to make software more secure and resilient to attacks.
Programming safety
Programming safety is multidimensional and subjective. We consider four types of programming safety: memory safety, null safety, type safety, and thread safety.
Memory safety
A service pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandipan Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/21, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594726</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594726/5-21-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T02:34:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Not Just Do Simple C++ RAII in C?]]></title>
        <id>https://thephd.dev/just-put-raii-in-c-bro-please-bro-just-one-more-destructor-bro-cmon-im-good-for-it</id>
        <link href="https://thephd.dev/just-put-raii-in-c-bro-please-bro-just-one-more-destructor-bro-cmon-im-good-for-it"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever since I finished publishing the “defer” paper and successfully defended it on its first go-around (it now has tentative approval to go to a Technical Specification, I just need to obtain the necessary written boilerplate to do so), an old criticism]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Pasture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 자본주의가 가장 마지막에 줄여야 하는 비용은 이것]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79039</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/20/npsp_techlayoffs/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_techlayoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 1일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 경영대학원 회계 수업에서 교수님은 늘 같은 질문으로 수업을 시작했습니다. 이건 학생의 의견을 묻거나 토론을 위한 발제를 기대하고 하는 질문이 아니었습니다. 오히려 그 반대였습니다. 답이 정해져 있는, 전형적인 ‘답정너’ 문항이었죠. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[차갑게 식은 조중동, 이제는 아무도 신경쓰지 않는 윤석열의 격노: 슬로우레터 5월21일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108886</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108886"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T22:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[탄핵 마일리지가 쌓이고 있다. 거부권 행사? 28일 재표결 들어간다. 가족 방탄에 이은 셀프 면죄부. 더 깊게 읽기. 잘못 건드렸다. ‘안방 호랑이’의 참사. 또 격노했나. 고질병처럼 반복되는 당정 소통 부재. 잠룡 경쟁이 시작됐다. 민심이 부르면 출마한다. 쟁점과 현안. 이란 대통령 사망. 국민의힘 총선 백서, 왜 시끄러울까. ‘개딸’의 분노? 1만 명 탈당 러시. 다르게 읽기. 카카오 지분...
The post 차갑게 식은 조중동, 이제는 아무도 신경쓰지 않는 윤석열의 격노: 슬로우레터 5월21일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design of a OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482361</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/design-of-a-ocp-orv3-smart-battery-backup-unit/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article outlines the system requirements for the Open Compute Project (OCP) Open Rack V3 (ORV3) battery backup unit. This article outlines the system requirements...
The post Design of a OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Cruz, Gary Sapia, and Marvin Neil Cabueñas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[만악의 근원은 그놈이었네… “이미 늦었다”면 뭘 할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79376</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/20/npsp_pollenallergy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_pollenallergy"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T19:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[봄철의 불청객 꽃가루 알레르기는 정말 “안 겪어본 사람은 모르는” 일입니다. 올봄 몇 년 만에 극심한 꽃가루 알레르기가 도져서 고생했는데, 뉴욕타임스에 꽃가루 알레르기와 기후변화의 상관관계를 짚어본 칼럼이 실렸습니다. 칼럼을 쓴 마가렛 렝클이 겪은 고초에 공감하면서 글을 번역하고 나서 우리도 모르는 사이에 이미 너무 많이 진척된 기후변화 문제를 살펴봤습니다. 최근에 대서양의 거대한 해류의 속도가 느려지고 있다는 충격적인 사실을 알게 됐는데, 그 이야기를 해설로 담았습니다. 전문 번역: ‘느낌적 느낌’ 아니다, 봄이 최악의 계절인 사람들에겐 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What's next for the SLUB allocator]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974138/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974138/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T18:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two fundamental levels of memory allocator in the Linux kernel:
the page allocator, which allocates memory in units of pages, and the slab
allocator, which allocates arbitrarily-sized chunks that are usually (but
not necessarily) smaller than a page.  The slab allocator is the one that
stands behind commonly used kernel functions like kmalloc().  At
the 2024 Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, slab maintainer
Vlastimil Babka provided an update on recent changes at the slab level and
discussed the changes that are yet to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A plan to make BPF kfuncs polymorphic]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974102/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974102/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T15:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Vernet kicked off the BPF track at 2024's BPF track at the
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit
with a
talk about polymorphic kfuncs — or, with less jargon, kernel functions that can
be called from BPF which use different implementations depending on context.
He explained how this would be useful to
the sched_ext BPF scheduling framework,
but expected it to be helpful in
other areas as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Better support for locally-attached-memory tiering]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974126/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974126/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T14:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The term "memory tiering" refers to the management of memory placement on
systems with multiple types of memory, each of which has its own
performance characteristics.  On such systems, poor placement can lead to
significantly worse performance.  A memory-management-track discussion at
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit took yet another look at
tiering challenges with a focus on upcoming technologies that may simplify
(or complicate) the picture.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Trinity keeps KDE 3 on life support]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973130/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973130/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T14:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the shiny new KDE Plasma 6 desktop makes its way into distribution
releases, a small group of developers is still trying to preserve the
KDE experience circa 2008. The Trinity Desktop Environment
(TDE), is a continuation of KDE 3 that has maintained the
old-school desktop with semi-regular releases since 2010. The most
recent release, R14.1.2,
was announced
on April 28. TDE does deliver a usable retro desktop, but with
some limitations that hamper its usability on modern systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Two Trips]]></title>
        <id>3664275</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664275"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T14:01:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axboe: What's new with io_uring in 6.10]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974341/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974341/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T13:09:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jens Axboe describes
the new io_uring features that will be a part of the 6.10 kernel
release.


	Bundles are multiple buffers used in a single operation. On the
	receive side, this means a single receive may utilize multiple
	buffers, reducing the roundtrip through the networking stack from N
	per N buffers to just a single one. On the send side, this also
	enables better handling of how an application deals with sends from
	a socket, eliminating the need to serialize sends on a single
	socket. Bundles work with provided buffers, hence this feature also
	adds support for provided buffers for send operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974339/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974339/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T12:54:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bind9, chromium, and thunderbird), Fedora (buildah, chromium, firefox, mingw-python-werkzeug, and suricata), Mageia (golang), Oracle (firefox and nodejs:20), Red Hat (firefox, httpd:2.4, nodejs, and thunderbird), and SUSE (firefox, git-cliff, and ucode-intel).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[개인투자일지] 엔비디아 실적을 기다리며]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594713</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594713/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:01:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Application binary interface compatibility testing with libabigail]]></title>
        <id>11adf510-3ef9-4090-9b93-5e930f22613e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/20/application-binary-interface-compatibility-testing-libabigail"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores how you can leverage application binary interface (ABI) compatibility testing with libabigail to determine the functionality of binaries running on older distributions or versions.
Software evolution and compatibility
Linux distributions are a living thing. During their lifetime, they are born at release, receive updates, and eventually "die" when support ends. They spawn descendant distributions. They sometimes even fight! The whole point of the distribution is to make an interdependent, cohesive whole, so there are many shared components. When those shared components are changed within a distribution, the question of compatibility is imminent.
Application binary interface (ABI) compatibility is a specific type of dependency: between separately compiled binaries and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Frank Eigler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend Red Hat Insights client to execute custom automation]]></title>
        <id>1d5f945e-262d-44f1-b8da-7c6d91e561ce</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/20/extend-red-hat-insights-client-execute-custom-automation"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Insights is a Software-as-a-Service offering that enables users to obtain actionable intelligence regarding their Red Hat Enterprise Linux environments, helping to identify and address operational and vulnerability risks before an issue occurs. Red Hat Insights requires a client tool to run on the system to collect data and perform necessary analytics to proactively detect misconfiguration and alert system administrators. This article explores how one can leverage the client’s existing functionality to run its own automation using a simple shell script.
In its default configuration, Insights client runs daily on each registered Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) system. For RHEL 7.5 and above, the execution is triggered by a scheduled systemd daemon. The insights-client configuration …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerome Marc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift Virtualization for vSphere admins: A change in the traditional storage paradigm]]></title>
        <id>f3f4031d-3e05-42c1-b6ad-49b83fee322f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/20/openshift-virtualization-vsphere-admins-change-traditional-storage-paradigm"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the second entry in our series introducing Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization to VMware vSphere administrators, we are going to discuss storage. In our previous article, we compared OpenShift Virtualization network configurations to how networks are often laid out in most general deployments of VMware vSphere. With this article, we will focus on how a containerized virtualization solution presents an entirely new storage paradigm when compared to what traditional virtualization administrators are used to. 
The traditional view of hypervisor storage
In traditional hypervisor storage paradigms, the anchorpoint is the shared datastore. A datastore is a single large volume presented to our hypervisor as either a block storage device (LUN) through a SAN protocol (iSCSI, FCP, FC-NVMe), or a re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Cowles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘빼박’ 탄핵 사유, 윤석열이 모를 리 없다: 슬로우레터 5월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108860</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108860"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T22:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[직구 금지, 사흘 만에 없던 일로. 6조8000억 원. 할 말은 한다. 쟁점과 현안. R&D 예타 폐지? 민주당은 반대. 국민이 실험 대상인가. 다르게 읽기. “‘빼박’ 탄핵 사유다.” “임계점을 넘는 순간이 온다.” 채 상병 특검법, 내일 거부권 쓴다. 더 깊게 읽기. “김 여사 공이 컸다.” 전공의 복귀 시한 한 달 늦추나. 전직 검사 전성시대. 늙어가는 한국, 정부...
The post ‘빼박’ 탄핵 사유, 윤석열이 모를 리 없다: 슬로우레터 5월20일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A surprising retrospective task estimation dataset]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8779</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/05/19/a-surprising-retrospective-task-estimation-dataset/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T21:22:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When estimating the time needed to implement a task, the time previously needed to implement similar tasks provides useful guidance. The implementation time for these previous tasks may itself be estimated, because the actual time was not measured or this information is currently unavailable. How accurate are developer time estimates of previously completed tasks? I […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCU-Link-MR v0.2 Drone and Robot Debug Probe with UART-2-USB Bridge]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40503</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/05/19/mcu-link-mr-v0-2-drone-and-robot-debug-probe-with-uart-2-usb-bridge/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new PCBs for the MCU-Link MR for drones and robots have arrived. With the parts populated, it serves as a UART bridge and debug probe for the PixHawk. The main improvement was fixing the UART connection, and changes include a new PCB color and a push button replacing the ISP firmware update jumper. Files and BOM on GitHub have been updated.  Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 행동하지 않나, 뉴욕타임스가 맞닥뜨린 복잡한 질문.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108807</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108807"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T06:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 언론의 객관성을 둘러싼 오래된 고민: 바이든이 뉴욕타임스와 인터뷰하지 않는 이유. 진실과 정의 가운데 무엇을 선택할 것인가. 누군가는 정의가 곧 진실이라고 말할 것이다. 애초에 정의가 아닌 진실에 관심이 없는 사람들도 있고 진실 역시 상대적인 개념 아니냐고 말하는 사람들도 있다. 세마포(Semafor)의 벤 스미스(Ben Smith)가 뉴욕타임스 편집국장 조셉 칸(Joseph Kahn)을 인터뷰했다. 벤 스미스의 질문은 “왜 뉴욕타임스는 조...
The post 왜 행동하지 않나, 뉴욕타임스가 맞닥뜨린 복잡한 질문. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Extending the mempolicy interface for heterogeneous systems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973964/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973964/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-18T14:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Non-uniform memory access (NUMA) systems are organized with their CPUs
grouped into nodes, each of which has memory attached to it.  All memory in
the system is accessible from all CPUs, but memory attached to the local
node is faster.  The kernel's memory-policy
("mempolicy") interface allows threads to inform the kernel about how
they would like their memory placed to get the best performance.  In recent
years, the NUMA concept has been extended to support the management of
different types of memory in a system, pushing the limits of the mempolicy
subsystem.  In a remotely presented session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Gregory Price discussed
the ways in which the kernel's memory-policy support should evolve to
handle today's more-complex systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 중국이 ‘서구의 대안’? 아니라는 게 확실해지고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79011</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/17/npsp_chinaandthewest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_chinaandthewest"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T22:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 싱가포르 난양공대의 이종혁 교수가 3월 27일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 엠마누엘 토드의 책 “제국의 몰락(Après L’empire)”은 2002년 출간될 당시에 많은 주목을 받았습니다. (직역하면 “제국, 그 이후”에 가깝지만, “제국의 몰락”이란 제목으로 번역됐습니다.) 당시 미국은 9.11 테러 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in the Red Hat build of Quarkus 3.8]]></title>
        <id>7622980d-b48e-4b2f-a84b-1cc7c946794c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/17/whats-new-red-hat-build-quarkus-38"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T20:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuing the mission of supporting enterprise developers to build cloud-native and Kubernetes-native Java applications, Red Hat has released version 3.8 of the Red Hat build of Quarkus. The latest release has some great features and performance improvements including tools to improve developer productivity.
Let’s take a look at some highlights of this release. For a complete list of new features, check out the official Red Hat build of Quarkus 3.8 release notes.
Improved developer productivity
One of the founding principles of Quarkus is to provide joy to Java developers by creating a frictionless experience with a combination of tools, libraries, extensions, and more. In this release, developers can access local development and testing services easily using new tools and services, such …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeff Beck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] GitLab CI for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972713/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972713/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T20:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working on the Linux kernel has always been unlike working on
many other software projects.
One particularly noticeable difference is the decentralized nature of the
kernel's testing infrastructure. Projects such as

syzkaller, KernelCI,
or the kernel self tests
test the kernel in different ways. On February 28, Helen
Koike

posted a patch set that would add continuous integration (CI) scripts for
the whole kernel. The response was generally positive, but several people
suggested changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974064/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974064/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T14:36:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.9.1,
6.8.10,
6.6.31,
6.1.91,
5.15.159,
5.10.217,
5.4.276, and
4.19.314 stable kernels have been released.
These versions include several important fixes; as usual, Greg Kroah-Hartman advises
users to update right away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] An update and future plans for DAMON]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973702/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973702/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T14:05:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The DAMON
subsystem was the subject of the first session in the memory-management
track at the Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  DAMON
maintainer SeongJae Park introduced the data-access monitoring
framework, which can generate snapshots of how memory is accessed, enabling
the detection of hot and cold regions of memory in both the virtual and
physical address spaces.  The session covered recent changes and future
plans for this tool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/974055/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/974055/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T13:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium, firefox, and podman), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, ghostscript, and java-1.8.0, java-11, java-17, java-latest), Red Hat (bind, Firefox, firefox, gnutls, httpd:2.4, and thunderbird), SUSE (glibc, opera, and python-Pillow), and Ubuntu (dotnet7, dotnet8, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4,
 linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4,
 linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-oracle,
 linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-6.5, linux-azure, linux-azure-6.5, linux-gcp,
 linux-gcp-6.5, linux-hwe-6.5, linux-laptop, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-nvidia-6.5, linux-oem-6.5, linux-oracle,
 linux-oracle-6.5, linux-raspi, linux-signed, linux-signed-aws,
 linux-signed-aws-6.5, linux-starfive, linux-starfive-6.5, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure-4.15, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm,
 linux-oracle, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, and linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde,
 linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gkeop,
 linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15,
 linux-intel-iotg, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15,
 linux-nvidia, linux-oracle, linux-raspi).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[White paper: Vendor Kernels, Bugs and Stability]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973996/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973996/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T13:24:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ronnie Sahlberg, Jonathan Maple, and Jeremy Allison of CiQ have published
a white
paper looking at the security-relevant bug fixes applied (or not
applied) to the RHEL 8.x kernel over time.


	This means that over time, the security of the RHEL kernels get
	worse and worse as more issues are discovered in the upstream code
	and are potentially exploitable but fewer and fewer of the fixes
	for these known bugs are back-ported into RHEL kernels.

	After reaching RHEL 8.7, the theory is that the kernel has been
	stabilized, with a corresponding improvement in security. However
	we still have an influx of newly discovered bugs in the upstream
	kernel affecting RHEL 8.7 that are not addressed. Each minor
	version of upstream is released on an approximately quarterly basis
	and we can see that the influx of new bugs that are unaddressed in
	RHEL is growing. The number of known issues in these kernels
	increases by approximately 250 new bugs per quarter or more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Elevating Security with Arm CCA]]></title>
        <id>3664291</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3664291"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T13:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Device Authority: 10 key principles to ensure connected car security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482337</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/device-authority-10-key-principles-to-ensure-connected-car-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:46:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“The integration of AI with IoT is reshaping the automotive world, but it demands the most effective security possible, enabling performance without compromising on protection and compliance.”
The post Device Authority: 10 key principles to ensure connected car security appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아, NV1의 실패로 시작하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108679</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108679"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T10:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 미국 주식시장에서 상장 주식 시가 총액 2조 달러를 넘어섰던 엔비디아. 반도체 기업으로 AI 붐의 대표 수혜 기업이다. 그래픽카드 제조 시장 진입에서 AI 연산 장치 제조의 선두가 되기까지 놀라운 성장을 거듭해 온 엔비디아는 이제 기업 가치상으로는 애플과 마이크로소프트를 넘보는 거대 기술기업으로 각인되고 있는 오늘이다. 엔비디아는 어떻게 이런 성공을 거둘 수 있었을까? 성공의 화려한 조명 뒤에는...
The post 엔비디아, NV1의 실패로 시작하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nomodem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we used Java Flight Recorder to resolve authentication issues]]></title>
        <id>eb85c8e1-8ec7-4295-b52e-0540a373140d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/17/how-we-used-java-flight-recorder-resolve-authentication-issues"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine one of the following scenarios: 

Your kids are going on vacation with their grandparents; you want to increase their cell phone plan with more bandwidth and gigabytes so you can see them enjoy the beach through a video call with your parents.
You’re on a business trip and you're relying on your company’s telco provider for roaming.

But you can’t do either of those things, because there’s an issue with the mobile application provider. Enter Red Hat Technical Account Management to assist in this situation. 
Diagnosing the problem
Let’s add a little more context. A telecommunications service provider (telco) provides a mobile application whose front end targets Red Hat's single-sign on (SSO) tool to authenticate and authorize users to either pay plans or enlarge plans. 
The issue oc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerczey Godoy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서초동 검사들이 “석열이형 생각을 이해하기 어렵다”고 말하는 이유: 슬로우레터 5월17일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108750</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108750"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T22:04:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희가 나타났다. 쟁점과 현안. ‘명심’ 업고 뛴 추미애의 탈락. 89:80. 국회의장의 파워. 의대 증원, 법원이 정부 손을 들어줬다. “25만 원 준다고 가계 펴지지 않는다.” “소주만 한 병 딱 있으면”, YTN 돌발영상이 사라졌다. 더 깊게 읽기. “석열이형 생각을 이해하기 어렵다.” “이원석 자리지킬 이유 없다.” 일본 정부는 왜 거짓말을 할까. 다르게 읽기. 최저임금 못 받는 노동자 534만...
The post 서초동 검사들이 “석열이형 생각을 이해하기 어렵다”고 말하는 이유: 슬로우레터 5월17일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about Google Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T20:13:04.997Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the new features and enhancements Google Wallet announced at I/O this year, focused on security, wearables, push notifications, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome India to the Google Wallet API]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T20:13:04.997Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To all developers in India: Welcome to the Google Wallet API! Now you can create digital assets like boarding passes, event tickets, gift cards, loyalty cards, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The first half of the 6.10 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973687/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973687/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T17:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The merge window for the 6.10 kernel release opened on May 12; between
then and the time of this writing, 6,819 non-merge commits were pulled into
the mainline kernel for that release.  Your editor has taken some time out
from LSFMM+BPF in an attempt to keep
up with the commit flood.  Read on for an overview of the most significant
changes that were pulled in the early part of the 6.10 merge window.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neovim 0.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973917/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973917/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T16:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
0.10 of the Vim-based text editor Neovim is now available. This release
includes a new default color scheme, enhanced support for rendering
multibyte characters, support for hyperlinks, system clipboard
synchronization, and more. Many features have been deprecated
in 0.10 and will be removed in future release. Neovim core contributor
Gregory Anders has written a summary
of some of the highlights and thoughts on upcoming releases:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973908/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973908/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:17:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, and nodejs:20), Debian (chromium, firefox-esr, ghostscript, and libreoffice), Fedora (djvulibre, mingw-glib2, mingw-python-jinja2, and mingw-python-werkzeug), Oracle (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, kernel, and nodejs:18), Red Hat (nodejs:20), Slackware (gdk and git), SUSE (python), and Ubuntu (linux-hwe-5.15, linux-raspi).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[챗GPT 탑재 아이폰?! 세상에 쉬운 게임은 없다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108709</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108709"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:58:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최우선, GPU가 기본이다 다들 엔비디아 GPU를 너무 쉽게 생각하는 것 같다. 구글이 모든 것을 가지고 있는데도 왜 허덕대는지 의아해한다. 구글은 가장 강력한 슈퍼컴퓨팅 인프라를 보유했다. 하지만 자사 AI 서비스를 위한 인프라와 고객 대상으로 그런 인프라를 빌려주고 관리하도록 하는 클라우드는 전혀 다른 영역이다. 생성형 AI 인프라 투자에는 시간이 걸린다. 자체 칩을 만들었다고 해도 엔비디아의 최신형 칩에...
The post 챗GPT 탑재 아이폰?! 세상에 쉬운 게임은 없다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>도안구</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift Virtualization for vSphere admins: Introduction to network configurations]]></title>
        <id>4924d39a-ff9c-406b-966c-7de5ad3e96b3</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/16/openshift-virtualization-vsphere-admins-introduction-network-configurations"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This post was originally published on the Red Hat Blog.
Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization is Red Hat's solution for companies trending toward modernization by adopting a containerized architecture for their applications, but find virtualization remains a necessary part of their data center deployment strategy.
Frankly, some applications are still simply unable to be containerized, and that's okay. OpenShift Virtualization addresses this by providing a more modern paradigm that cohesively manages the need for containers and virtual machines in a unified platform.
One concern we at Red Hat must address is this: in addition to providing feature parity, how do we maintain a customer experience that is similar to that of the products and configurations that the customer is used to so that …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Cowles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve user experience in the Butane command-line utility]]></title>
        <id>03824dcd-9247-4a8f-b22e-f3ad2b48dc93</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/16/improve-user-experience-butane-command-line-utility"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Butane (formerly the Fedora CoreOS Config Transpiler, or FCCT) is a command-line utility that is used to generate human readable configuration into Ignition configuration files. Butane is an open source repo maintained by CoreOS, and contributed to and enhanced by many. If you take a look at the Butane repo and look in the Config folder, you can almost see some of the stakeholders. These are configurations which are used to target different platforms (i.e., FCOS, Flatcar Container Linux, Red Hat OpenShift, etc.) Each of these configurations will have a stable and experimental phase that also targets stable and experimental specs of Ignition. I would describe these as levers that a contributor can exercise to impact the functionality they want to expose to the end users of these target plat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Presti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using OpenShift 4's inspect for middleware troubleshooting]]></title>
        <id>58486283-3376-4c2e-a2bd-f400e5f1c1c8</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/16/using-openshift-4s-inspect-middleware-troubleshooting"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given a problem with an application in Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform (RHOCP 4) upon opening a case with the support team, our support team might ask for a namespace’s inspect file. The inspect file is a very useful tool for troubleshooting applications and systems deployed in RHOCP 4 and can be extremely useful in a series of situations.
It also avoids the unnecessarily separated collection of data (Pod Logs, route YAML, BuildConfig YAMLs) given it brings everything that is namespace bounded—except custom resources—directly to one goal. 
This article covers what the inspect file is, how to collect it, how to use it for troubleshooting, and how it compares to the must-gather file (spoiler: it is not the same thing). This will help clarify why we usually ask for this file during the t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior, Alexander Barbosa Ayala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 16, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973073/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973073/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T03:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 16, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Foundation Welcomes Nabiha Syed as Executive Director]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973820/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973820/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T02:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Mozilla Foundation has announced
that its new executive director will be Nabiha Syed.


	Syed is known for her mission-driven leadership, focused on
	increasing transparency into the most powerful institutions in
	society. She comes to Mozilla after leading The Markup, an
	award-winning publication that challenges technology to serve the
	public good, from its launch through its successful acquisition in
	2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Zephyr - West workspaces (Part 6)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/practical_zephyr_west</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/practical_zephyr_west"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous articles, we used freestanding applications and relied on a global Zephyr installation. In this article, we’ll see how we can use West to resolve global dependencies by using workspace applications. We first explore West without even including Zephyr and then recreate the modified Blinky application from the previous article in a West workspace.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“촛불이 어른거린다”, 김건희를 버리라는 조선일보의 조언: 슬로우레터 5월16일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108689</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108689"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T22:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[중앙지검은 마비 상태. “촛불이 눈에 어른거린다.” ‘상남자’가 칭찬으로 들리나. 쟁점과 현안. 5년 만에 만난 윤석열과 조국. 한동훈이 국민의힘 대표가 되려면. 이준석의 5·18 참배. 다르게 읽기. 25만 원 민생 지원금, 위헌일까 아닐까. 모든 국민? 선별 지원? 의대 증원 법원 결정 나온다. 더 깊게 읽기. 한국의 국익과 네이버의 이익. 김범석은 왜 쿠팡의 총수가 아닌가. “루시아가 언제 수영을...
The post “촛불이 어른거린다”, 김건희를 버리라는 조선일보의 조언: 슬로우레터 5월16일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's check the qdEngine game engine, part three: 10 more bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1123/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1123/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first article about qdEngine, we've discussed 10 errors selected by the PVS-Studio plugin. However, we have 10 more bugs that are worth mentioning. As they say, it's better to learn from other...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch: High Performance Inference of Pytorch Models on Mobile Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-high-performance-inference-of-pytorch-models-on-mobile-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-high-performance-inference-of-pytorch-models-on-mobile-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.401Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Released today, AI Edge Torch enables support for PyTorch, JAX, Keras, and Tensorflow with TFLite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build for Tomorrow in the Gemini API Developer Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-for-tomorrow-in-the-gemini-api-developer-competition/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-for-tomorrow-in-the-gemini-api-developer-competition/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.401Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build a new app with the Gemini API or integrate our Gemini API into an existing application for a chance to win some really cool prizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of Checks is now available to all Android and iOS Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/checks-now-available-to-all-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/checks-now-available-to-all-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.401Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checks identifies potential privacy issues, provides recommendations, monitors app compliance, and provides results in an intuitive dashboard or directly in your CI/CD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google AR at I/O 2024: New Geospatial AR features and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-ar-at-io-2024-new-geospatial-ar-features-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-ar-at-io-2024-new-geospatial-ar-features-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.400Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've been exploring new ways to create engaging, easy to use, and shareable experiences and connect your Geospatial AR creations with more users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home APIs: Enabling all developers to build for the home]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/home-apis-enabling-all-developers-to-build-for-the-home/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/home-apis-enabling-all-developers-to-build-for-the-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.400Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've re-envisioned Google Home as a platform for all developers – not just those that build smart home devices – to create innovative experiences for the home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Building with Project IDX Today]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-project-idx-today/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-project-idx-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.400Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve removed the waitlist for Project IDX. Now, anyone can sign up to start building with AI-assistance, collaboration capabilities, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2024 recap: Making AI accessible and helpful for every developer]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-io-2024-recap-making-ai-accessible-and-helpful-for-every-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-io-2024-recap-making-ai-accessible-and-helpful-for-every-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.400Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for joining us at this year's Google I/O. Check out all of the Google I/O announcements and updates with 150+ sessions and learning content available on demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Firebase at  I/O '24]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-firebase-io-24/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-firebase-io-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.400Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase, is evolving to enable you to rapidly build and run AI-powered experiences in your apps across platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Firebase Genkit helped add AI to our Compass app]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T20:14:35.399Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We used Firebase Genkit – Firebase’s open source framework for building powerful AI features into your apps with familiar patterns and paradigms – to add AI to an existing application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux maintainers were infected for 2 years by SSH-dwelling backdoor
(ars technica)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973783/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973783/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T18:15:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ars technica looks
at a a
recent report on the Ebury root kit, with a focus on the 2011 compromise of kernel.org, which may have
been more extensive than believed at the time.


	In 2014, ESET researchers said the 2011 attack likely infected
	kernel.org servers with a second piece of malware they called
	Ebury. The malware, the firm said, came in the form of a malicious
	code library that, when installed, created a backdoor in OpenSSH
	that provided the attackers with a remote root shell on infected
	hosts with no valid password required. In a little less than 22
	months, starting in August 2011, Ebury spread to 25,000
	servers. Besides the four belonging to the Linux Kernel
	Organization, the infection also touched one or more servers inside
	hosting facilities and an unnamed domain registrar and web hosting
	provider.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parallel Data Fetching]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#ImplementTheFriendsList</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html#ImplementTheFriendsList"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second pattern in Juntao Qiu's series on data
       fetching is on how to avoid the dreaded Request Waterfall. Parallel Data
       Fetching queries multiple sources in parallel, so that the latency of the
       overall fetch is largest of the queries rather than the sum of them.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 126.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973763/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973763/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T14:03:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
126.0 of the Firefox browser is out.  Changes include improvements to
the "copy link without site tracking" feature, support for zstd
compression, and a new tracking "feature": "Telemetry was added to create
an aggregate count of searches by category to broadly inform search feature
development."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The state of the page in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973565/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973565/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of the folio structure to
describe groups of pages has been one of the most fundamental
transformations within the kernel in recent years.  Since the folio
transition affects many subsystems, it is fitting that the subject was
covered at the beginning of the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit in a joint session of the
storage, filesystem, and memory-management tracks.  Matthew Wilcox used the
session to review the work that has been done in this area and to discuss
what comes next.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973746/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973746/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T13:13:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (sssd and tcpdump), Red Hat (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, expat, kernel, and kernel-rt), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (kernel, postgresql15, postgresql16, python-arcomplete, python-Fabric, python-PyGithub, python- antlr4-python3-runtime, python-avro, python-chardet, python-distro, python- docker, python-fakeredis, python-fixedint, pyth, and python3), and Ubuntu (linux-bluefield).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering motor control: implementation in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482293</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mastering-motor-control-implementation-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I present a test-driven development approach for a motor controller application using a user-friendly development environment on a Windows PC with Microsoft Visual Studio and...
The post Mastering motor control: implementation in C++ appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Radonic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New C++ features in GCC 14]]></title>
        <id>b83bdd36-4014-4ad3-8314-c421c30c75f0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/15/new-c-features-gcc-14"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next major version of the GNU Compiler Collection (GCC), 14.1, was released on May 7 2024. Like every major GCC release, this version brings many additions, improvements, bug fixes, and new features. GCC 14 is already the system compiler in Fedora 40. Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) users will get GCC 14 in the Red Hat GCC Toolset (RHEL 8 and RHEL 9), and as the system compiler in RHEL 10. It's also possible to try GCC 14 on Compiler Explorer and similar pages.
Like the article I wrote about GCC 13, this article describes only new features implemented in the C++ front end; it does not discuss developments in the C++ language itself which will have a separate blog post. Interesting changes in the standard C++ library that comes with GCC 14 will be described in a separate blog post as we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marek Polacek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 잠시 찾아왔다가 금방 사라진 ‘복지국가’ 미국, 그리고 지금은?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78996</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/14/npsp_ussocialsafety/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_ussocialsafety"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 3월 25일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 경제 지표만 보면 미국 경제는 분명 호황인데, 미국 사람들이 느끼는 체감 경기는 왜 이렇게 나쁜 걸까? 지난해 말부터 이 질문에 대한 직·간접적인 답을 찾는 칼럼과 해설만 벌써 여러 번 소개해 드렸습니다. 모든 사회, 경제 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Touch OLED displays will redefine automotive user interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482286</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/touch-oled-displays-will-redefine-automotive-user-interfaces/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like the consumer industry, the automotive industry is adopting OLED technology for its high-quality visuals and thin form factor but also for other automotive-specific reasons....
The post Touch OLED displays will redefine automotive user interfaces appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Thomas Souche</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“대통령 교체, 못할 선택도 아니다”, 동아일보 논설위원 주장의 의미는?: 슬로우레터 5월15일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108635</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108635"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T22:10:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“인사는 인사, 수사는 수사.” “용산 뜻대로 안 될 수도.” 이창수가 이원석을 패싱할까. 윤석열의 폭주, 조선일보도 돌아섰다. 쟁점과 현안. 오늘도 윤석열은. 낙천‧낙선자들이 키를 쥐고 있다. 억대 연봉 기관장 빈자리 90개. 라인야후 지분 매각 안 한다? 다르게 읽기. 미국 슈퍼 관세, 중국 전기차 100%로. 트럼프 당선 가능성 높아졌다. 더 깊게 읽기. GPT-4o의 충격. 오늘의 TMI. 네이버보다 인스타그램...
The post “대통령 교체, 못할 선택도 아니다”, 동아일보 논설위원 주장의 의미는?: 슬로우레터 5월15일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making development across platforms easier for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/making-development-across-platforms-easier-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/making-development-across-platforms-easier-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:14:35.440Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do what works best for your business; whether you’re sharing both UI and business logic across multiple platforms with Flutter or development with Kotlin Multiplatform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing PaliGemma, Gemma 2, and an Upgraded Responsible AI Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-and-toolkit-expansion-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-and-toolkit-expansion-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:14:35.440Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gemma family expands further with the introduction of PaliGemma, and a sneak peek into the near future with the announcement of Gemma 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Gameface launches on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/project-gameface-launches-on-android/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/project-gameface-launches-on-android/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T20:14:35.440Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re open sourcing the code for Project Gameface to help developers build an application on Android to make every Android device more accessible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manjaro 24.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973686/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973686/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T17:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 24.0
of the Arch-based Manjaro distribution is now available with
the 6.9 kernel, GNOME 46, Xfce 4.18, and an update to the
Pamac package
installer. This is also the project's first release with KDE Plasma 6:
The Plasma edition comes with the latest Plasma 6.0 series and KDE
Gear 24.02. It brings exciting new improvements to your desktop.
With Plasma 6, KDE's technology stack has undergone major upgrades:
a transition to the latest version of application framework, Qt, and
an improved graphics platform when Wayland is used. These changes are
as smooth and unnoticeable to the users as possible. You will see the
same familiar desktop environment that you know and love. But these
under-the-hood upgrades benefit Plasma's security, efficiency, and
performance, and improve support for modern hardware. Thus Plasma
delivers an overall more reliable user experience, while paving the
way for many more improvements in the future.
The project also offers minimal install images with the 6.6 LTS
and 6.1 LTS kernels to support older hardware.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Portable LLMs with llamafile]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971195/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971195/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) have been the subject of much discussion and
scrutiny recently. Of particular interest to open-source enthusiasts are the
problems with running LLMs on one's own hardware — especially when doing so
requires NVIDIA's proprietary CUDA toolkit, which remains unavailable in many
environments.
Mozilla has developed
llamafile as a
potential solution to these problems. Llamafile can compile LLM weights
into portable, native executables for easy integration, archival, or
distribution. These executables can take advantage of supported GPUs when
present, but do not require them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Fetching Patterns in Single-Page Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/data-fetch-spa.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juntao Qiu is a thoughtful front-end
       developer experienced with the React programming environment. He's
       contributed a couple of useful articles to this site, describing helpful
       patterns for front-end programming. In this article he describes patterns
       for how single-page applications fetch data. This first installment
       describes how asynchronous queries can be wrapped in a handler to provide
       information about the state of the query.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973667/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973667/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:06:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (glib2.0 and shim), Fedora (glib2, gnome-shell, tcpdump, tpm2-tools, tpm2-tss, and uriparser), Mageia (mutt), Oracle (git-lfs, glibc, kernel, kernel-container, nodejs:18, nodejs:20, and pcp), SUSE (apache2, opensc, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, perl, python-Pillow, python-pyOpenSSL, python-Werkzeug, SUSE Manager Client Tools Beta, tpm2-0-tss, and tpm2.0-tools), and Ubuntu (sqlparse and strongswan).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use OperatorPolicy to manage Kubernetes-native applications]]></title>
        <id>d75884c5-59f1-4ef4-ba18-cea735c9f6ba</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/14/use-operatorpolicy-manage-kubernetes-native-applications"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can use the policy framework in Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes (RHACM) to define and manage configurations of resources across a fleet of clusters. When packaged with the Operator Lifecycle Manager (OLM), Kubernetes-native applications become resources that you can manage, similar to the built-in resource types on a cluster. In the 2.10 release of RHACM, we are introducing a new kind of policy template, OperatorPolicy, as a tech preview feature which helps manage these specific types more completely and more easily.
In this article, you’ll learn the basics of the OperatorPolicy, and you’ll see a demo about how to use it. Because this is a tech preview feature, we are looking forward to hearing your feedback about how we can improve these features for you.
OperatorPo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Berger, Justin Kulikauskas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[드래곤볼의 ‘원기옥’처럼? 억만장자에게 세금을 걷자는 “증세 동맹” 가능할까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79339</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/13/npsp_taxbillionaires/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_taxbillionaires"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T01:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[불평등이 우리 시대의 화두가 된 지도 꽤 오랜 시간이 흘렀습니다. 지난해에는 40세 이하 경제학자 가운데 앞으로의 연구 성과가 기대되는 학자에게 수여하는 존 베이츠 클라크 메달을 받은 UC 버클리의 가브리엘 쥐크망 교수가 뉴욕타임스에 칼럼을 썼습니다. 더 늦기 전에 전 세계가 부자 증세에 나서야 한다는 주장으로, 점점 더 시대의 사명이 돼 가고 있는 불평등을 줄이는 문제에 관해 우리 사회는 어디쯤 와 있는지 돌아보게 해주는 글입니다. 전문 번역: 억만장자들이 최소한의 소득세도 내지 않는 이유, 세금을 걷는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 수사 검사들의 ‘좌천성 승진’, 조선일보도 “꼭 지금 했어야 했나”: 슬로우레터 5월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108575</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108575"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T22:12:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 수사 중단? 검찰을 갈아엎었다. ‘좌천성 승진’, 너무나도 노골적인 방탄 인사. 조선일보도 “꼭 지금 했어야 했나.” 쟁점과 현안. “본질은 대통령 권한 사유화다.” 탄핵 연대로 뭉친다. 더 깊게 읽기. 한우 943만 원어치, 위반 사항 없었다고? ‘갑진국치’ 논란에 네이버는 ‘난감’. 일본이 버튼 눌린 이유. 네이버 구하기 세 가지 다른 관점. 다르게 읽기. 여성가족부 대신 저출생부? 보도 공정성?...
The post 김건희 수사 검사들의 ‘좌천성 승진’, 조선일보도 “꼭 지금 했어야 했나”: 슬로우레터 5월14일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eleven moments of ReactOS: user mode gets better?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1122/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1122/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ReactOS is a project where the victory over regression and the delivery of a new feature (or its working prototype) are loudly celebrated. Even the FOSS community has to take a break from rewriting...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some 6.9 development statistics]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972605/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972605/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T17:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9 kernel was released
on May 12 after a typical nine-week development cycle.  Once again,
this is a major release containing a lot of changes and new features.  Our
merge-window summaries (part 1, part 2) covered those changes; now that
the development cycle is complete, the time has come to look at where all
that work came from — and to introduce a new and experimental LWN feature
for readers interested in this kind of information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Managing expectations with a contributions and credit policy]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971817/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971817/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T15:35:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintainers of open-source projects sometimes have disagreements with
contributors over how contributions are reviewed, modified, merged, and
credited. A written policy describing how contributions are handled can
help maintainers set reasonable expectations for potential contributors.
In turn, that can make the maintainer's job easier because it can help
reduce a source of friction in the project.  A guide to help create this
kind of policy for a project has recently been developed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aetina launches its latest AI platforms for edge computer vision]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482278</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/aetina-launches-its-latest-ai-platforms-for-edge-computer-vision/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T15:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AIP-KQ67 enables edge AI computing and inference based on Intel's 12th/13th generation Core processors and Nvidia’s A2 Tensor core GPU.
The post Aetina launches its latest AI platforms for edge computer vision appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prophesee has event-based machine vision dev kit for AMD Kria]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482274</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/prophesee-has-event-based-machine-vision-dev-kit-for-amd-kria/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T14:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Company claims industry’s first event-based vision development kit compatible with an AMD platform.
The post Prophesee has event-based machine vision dev kit for AMD Kria appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SiPearl unveils features of Rhea1 HPC / AI inference processor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482267</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/sipearl-unveils-features-of-rhea1-hpc-ai-inference-processor/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T14:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rhea1 will integrate 80 Arm Neoverse V1 cores, built in high-bandwidth memory with four HBM stacks, and four DDR5 interfaces.
The post SiPearl unveils features of Rhea1 HPC / AI inference processor appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973496/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973496/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T13:07:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (nodejs:18 and shim), Debian (atril and chromium), Fedora (chromium, glib2, gnome-shell, mediawiki, php-wikimedia-cdb, php-wikimedia-utfnormal, stb, and tcpdump), Gentoo (Kubelet, PoDoFo, Rebar3, and thunderbird), Mageia (glibc and libnbd), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (bind and dhcp and varnish), and SUSE (chromium, cpio, freerdp, giflib, gnutls, opera, python-Pillow, python-Werkzeug, tinyproxy, and tpm2-0-tss).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[안에서 본 선거 심의: 세 갈래로 ‘찢어진’ 선거 심의]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108454</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108454"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T08:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[5개월 단기 비정규직 아르바이트(?)를 마쳤다. 이번 22대 총선기간 신문 잡지 등 정기간행물과 뉴스통신사의 선거기사를 심의하는 언론중재위원회 산하 선거기사 심의위원회의 더불어민주당 추천 위원으로 일했다. 어제(10일) 위원회 활동이 끝났다. 선거는 끝났지만, 선거가 남긴 숙제와 후유증은 여전히 진행형이다. 보도 공정성? 심의 공정성이 먼저다 선거 보도 심의를 둘러싼 논란은 넘어갈 수 없는 후유증 중 하나다. 그 중심에 선방심의위가 있었다....
The post 안에서 본 선거 심의: 세 갈래로 ‘찢어진’ 선거 심의 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김준형</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/13, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594702</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594702/5-13-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T06:48:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지지율 24%, 윤석열에게 최악의 순간은 아직 오지 않았다: 슬로우레터 5월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108517</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108517"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T22:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[취임 2주년 기준 역대 최저 수준 지지율. 쟁점과 현안. 김건희 소환 조사한다. 디올 백 건넨 목사 소환 조사. 채 상병 사건 대통령실이 챙겼다. 국회의장은 추미애? 1주택자 종부세 폐지, 이재명의 대선 전략일까. 2000명 근거 입증, 누가 후달리나. 숨기는 게 아니라 없어서 못 내놓는 것. 다르게 읽기. 내각제라는 카드. 라인야후 사태, 윤석열이 침묵하는 이유. “반일 감정과 엮는...
The post 지지율 24%, 윤석열에게 최악의 순간은 아직 오지 않았다: 슬로우레터 5월13일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9 kernel is out]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972886/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972886/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T22:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released the 6.9 kernel. 
"So 6.9 is now out, and last week has looked quite stable (and the
whole release has felt pretty normal)."
Significant changes in this release include
the ability to create pidfds for individual
threads,
the BPF arena subsystem,
the BPF token security mechanism,
truncate() support in io_uring,
support for the Rust language on 64-bit Arm systems,
weighted interleaving in the
memory-management subsystem,
the device-mapper
virtual data optimizer target,
initial FUSE passthrough support,
and more.

See the LWN merge-window summaries
(part 1, part 2) for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Workshop on data analysis for software developers]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8772</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/05/12/workshop-on-data-analysis-for-software-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T21:59:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m teaching a workshop on data analysis for software engineers on 22 June. The workshop is organized by the British Computer Society’s SPA specialist group, and can be attended remotely. Why is there a small registration charge (between £2 and £15)? Typically, 30% to 50% of those registered for a free event actually turn up. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[photostream 131]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/photos/131.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/photos/131.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민희진이 말한 ‘꼼수’가 바로 이것이었다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108460</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108460"/>
        <updated>2024-05-12T09:45:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] ‘앨범깡’과 ‘팬사컷’, ‘K-팝 쓰레기’ 만드는 음반 밀어내기… 성장 동력이었지만 근본적인 한계. 민희진과 방시혁의 어도어 경영권 분쟁에서 빠뜨리지 말아야 할 것이 있다. 단순히 한 엔터테인먼트 기업의 내부 갈등을 넘어 K-컬처 산업의 향방을 결정할 중요한 사건이다. 민희진 사건은 워낙 정보의 비대칭이 심하다. 아는 사람은 잘 알고 모르는 사람은 전혀 모른다. 그래서 이 글은 역순으로 작성했다. 중요한...
The post 민희진이 말한 ‘꼼수’가 바로 이것이었다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating MCU-Link CMSIS-DAP Debug Probe Firmware, Jumper-less]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40447</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/05/11/updating-mcu-link-cmsis-dap-debug-probe-firmware-jumper-less/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T17:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explains how to update the firmware on NXP's versatile MCU-Link and MCU-Link Pro debug probes. It covers the traditional method using an ISP jumper and the new method using a command line script, eliminating the need for a jumper. The new method simplifies the process and is beneficial for automation and test labs. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With CUDA C on an Nvidia Jetson: A Meaningful Algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1664.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1664.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T15:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous blog post, Getting Started With CUDA C on an Nvidia Jetson: GPU Architecture, I described how the underlying architecture of a GPU makes it ideal for graphics image processing. In the prior blog post, Getting Started With CUDA C on an Nvidia Jetson: Hello CUDA World!, we implemented a simple array addition algorithm using a GPU and a CPU. Unfortunately, we observed no...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논문 – 부동과 이동의 연결공간으로서 주차장 (〈문화역사지리〉 36(1))]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3823</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2024/parking-space-as-the-connecting-space/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T05:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이 글은 주차장을 사례로, 이동성 편향을 뛰어넘어 부동성의 관점으로의 확장을 강조하고, 부동성을 인간의 행위에 맞춰 설명해온 방식에서 벗어나 부동성이 실현된 공간과 그 공간을 규정하는 제도와 역사적 측면을 다룹니다. 이로써 부동성의 공간적 속성이 이동성의 개념만큼 상대적이며 능동적인 특징을 갖는다는 점을 규명합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 영어 아닌 외국어 사용이 문제라고? ‘효율적 소통’ 이면에도 문제가 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78954</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/10/npsp_englishofficial/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_englishofficial"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 3월 20일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 대한민국의 공용어는 무엇일까요? 2005년 제정된 국어기본법은 제3조 1항에서 “‘국어’란 대한민국의 공용어로서 한국어를 말한다”고 명시하고 있습니다. 여기에 2016년 8월 한국수화언어법 시행과 함께 한국수화어가 공용어로 지정되면서, 현재 우리나라의 공용어는 총 2개입니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mediatek new flagship Dimensity 9300+ targets on-device LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482263</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mediatek-new-flagship-dimensity-9300-targets-on-device-llms/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T17:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New SoC features 10% performance boost for AI processing over previous generation as a result of MediaTek’s new NeuroPilot speculative decode acceleration technology in latest generative AI engine.
The post Mediatek new flagship Dimensity 9300+ targets on-device LLMs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Debian dismisses AI-contributions policy]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972331/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972331/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T16:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In April, the Gentoo Linux project banned the use of
generative AI/ML tools due to copyright, ethical, and quality
concerns. This means contributors cannot use tools like ChatGPT or GitHub Copilot to
create content for the distribution such as code, documentation,
bug reports, forum posts. A proposal for Debian to adopt a similar
policy revealed a distinct lack of love for those kinds of tools,
though it would also seem few contributors support
banning them outright.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux backdoor threat is a wake-up call for IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482256</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/linux-backdoor-threat-is-a-wake-up-call-for-iot/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T15:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux is often the default choice for many IoT devices, but with recent backdoor threat we look at why an RTOS can better deliver security and minimalism.
The post Linux backdoor threat is a wake-up call for IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Carsten Rhod Gregersen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973206/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973206/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T13:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (container-tools:4.0, container-tools:rhel8, git-lfs, glibc, libxml2, nodejs:18, and nodejs:20), Debian (dav1d and libpgjava), Fedora (kernel and pypy), Red Hat (glibc and nodejs:16), SUSE (ffmpeg, ffmpeg-4, ghostscript, go1.21, go1.22, less, python-python-jose, python-Werkzeug, and sssd), and Ubuntu (fossil, glib2.0, and libspreadsheet-parsexlsx-perl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A step-by-step guide to determining battery life in LPWAN devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482246</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/a-step-by-step-guide-to-determining-battery-life-in-lpwan-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T11:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Battery life estimation is a key part of developing an efficient and effective wireless IoT edge device. A structured approach using readily available hardware and software tools is the only way to gain confidence in your final estimates.
The post A step-by-step guide to determining battery life in LPWAN devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Björn Rosqvist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비현실성 리뷰 2 : 갈라 포라스-김]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3782</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2024/unrealistic-2-galaporraskim/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-10T08:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[포라스-김은 자신의 회화 작업을 가리켜 ‘페인팅’이라 하지 않고 ‘드로잉’임을 강조한다. 사회과학자의 드로잉에 장르적으로 더 가깝기 때문이다. 그래서 사물의 표면에는 음영을 넣을 수 있어도, 사물이 놓여져 있는 공간에는 그림자가 없다. 사물과 공간의 관계를 표현하는 것이 중요하지 않기 때문이다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[어제 기자회견 한 줄 요약, 윤석열의 ‘침대 축구’가 시작됐다: 슬로우레터 5월10일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108407</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108407"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T22:12:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“대통령이 사과했다”, 감격한 조선일보. 기자회견 핵심 키워드는 ‘특검 거부’. “피가 거꾸로 솟는다.” 윤석열의 침대 축구. 윤석열은 그저 섭섭할 뿐이다. 쟁점과 현안. 문제는 디올 백이 아니다. 금투세 도입하면 증시 자금 이탈? 사실 아니다. 어제 기자회견 핵심 요약. 다르게 읽기. 기자들이 하지 않은 질문. 끊이지 않는 비선 논란. 더 깊게 읽기. 네이버의 고민. “정부가 관여할 수 없다.”...
The post 어제 기자회견 한 줄 요약, 윤석열의 ‘침대 축구’가 시작됐다: 슬로우레터 5월10일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Embedded Linux Topics for Newbies !]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1663.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1663.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T20:39:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Five Embedded Linux topics for newbies !DELL-E 2 generated
Have you been working with regular Embedded system and want to expand your skills by leaning Embedded Linux ? If you feel lost and overwhelmed this article is for you!

This article aims to provide you with essential keywords for each topic, allowing you to explore and learn independently at your own pace

Like Father,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Another push for sched_ext]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972710/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972710/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T14:17:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The extensible scheduler class (or "sched_ext") is a comprehensive
framework that enables the implementation of CPU schedulers as a set of BPF
programs that can be loaded at run time.  Despite having attracted a fair
amount of interest from the development community, sched_ext has run into
considerable opposition and seems far from acceptance into the mainline.
The posting by Tejun Heo of a new
version of the sched_ext series at the beginning of May has restarted
this long-running discussion, but it is not clear what the end result will
be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/973071/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/973071/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T13:31:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (ansible-core, avahi, bind, buildah, containernetworking-plugins, edk2, fence-agents, file, freeglut, freerdp, frr, git-lfs, gnutls, golang, grafana, grafana-pcp, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, gstreamer1-plugins-base, gstreamer1-plugins-good, harfbuzz, httpd, ipa, libjpeg-turbo, libnbd, LibRaw, libreswan, libsndfile, libssh, libtiff, libvirt, libX11, libXpm, mingw components, mingw-glib2, mingw-pixman, mod_http2, mod_jk and mod_proxy_cluster, motif, mutt, openssl and openssl-fips-provider, osbuild-composer, pam, pcp, perl, pmix, podman, python-jinja2, python-jwcrypto, python3.11, python3.11-cryptography, python3.11-urllib3, qemu-kvm, qt5-qtbase, runc, skopeo, sssd, systemd, tcpdump, tigervnc, toolbox, webkit2gtk3, xorg-x11-server, xorg-x11-server-Xwayland, and zziplib), CentOS (firefox, grub2, kernel, squid, thunderbird, tigervnc, and xorg-x11-server), Debian (chromium, glib2.0, python-idna, webkit2gtk, and wordpress), Fedora (freerdp, freerdp2, and pypy), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, exfatprogs, freeglut, libtiff, libvirt, libxml2, openpmix, php-tcpdf, ruby, tpm2-tools, tpm2-tss, traceroute, and zziplib), Oracle (bind, buildah, git-lfs, gnutls, golang, grafana, grafana-pcp, libreswan, libvirt, libxml2, mod_http2, podman, python-jwcrypto, skopeo, sssd, and tigervnc), Red Hat (nodejs:18, nodejs:20, and squid:4), and SUSE (avahi, ghostscript, go1.21, go1.22, python-pymongo, python-Werkzeug, and sssd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[작업 기억과 휴대폰 그리고 23분]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108391</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108391"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T11:24:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[작업 기억이라는 게 있다. 작업 기억 모든 학습에는 작업 기억(Working Memory)이 필요하다. 기억한 것을 조작하는 일은 매순간 일어난다. 정보가 지식이 되려면 기억해야 하고 기존에 아는 정보와 연결해야 한다. 맥락을 잃는 순간 정보는 지식으로서 가치를 잃는다. 수업과 생활지도의 모든 순간이 학습과 연결되고 성장의 밑거름이 되는 이유다. 인지심리학의 연구에 따르면 눈앞에 휴대폰을 두고 대화하는 것만으로 작업 기억에...
The post 작업 기억과 휴대폰 그리고 23분 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>천경호</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역대급 기자회견, 20가지 질문과 답변. (2024년 5월9일)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108381</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108381"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T09:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우 스크립트] 631일만에 열린 윤석열의 두 번째 기자회견 핵심 내용. 미루고 미뤘던 윤석열(대통령)의 기자회견이 5월9일 오전에 열렸다. 주요 질문과 답변을 정리해 본다. 지루했던 모두 발언. 형식의 문제. 총선 패배의 원인. 국정 기조 전환. 김건희 특검법. 채 상병 특검법. ‘런종섭’ 사태. 협치는 어떻게 할 건가. 한동훈과의 갈등. 개각은 어떻게. 주한 미군 방위비 협상. 우크라이나 전쟁. 강제...
The post 역대급 기자회견, 20가지 질문과 답변. (2024년 5월9일) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부서진 사람들의 말을 꿰매며 & 인권에서 동물권으로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108354</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108354"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T08:29:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, ‘정부가 없다’ 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기. “나는 인권이 짓밟힌 사람들의 이야기를 기록한다. 장애인이나 부랑인 수용소의 생존자 같은 이들을 만나 ‘말로는 설명할 수 없다’는 것을 기어이 말하게 하고 그것을 글로 바꾸는 일이다. 삶이 부서진 사람들의 말은 갈가리 찢기고 조각나 있기 일쑤였다. 장애 때문이기도 하고 낮은...
The post 부서진 사람들의 말을 꿰매며 & 인권에서 동물권으로 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[그래서 디올 백은 지금 어디 있느냐고 아무도 묻지 않았다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108362</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108362"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T08:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 윤석열의 두 번째 기자회견, 기대도 없었지만 실망은 더 컸다. 윤석열(대통령) 취임 이후 두 번째 기자회견이다. 631일만에 어렵게 열린 기자회견, 주요 쟁점과 의미, 전망 등을 살펴보자. 어떻게 봤나. 끝까지 피하려던 기자회견을 한 이유는 뭘까. 지루했던 모두 발언. 20가지 질문. 빠뜨린 질문이 어떤 것들이 있을까. 한국 기자는 왜 대통령에게 질문할 때 이렇게 소극적일까. 출입처 시스템이 공손한...
The post 그래서 디올 백은 지금 어디 있느냐고 아무도 묻지 않았다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대통령 장모 최은순 가석방은 당연한 일이다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108301</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108301"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T04:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[나는 윤석열 대통령을 지지하지 않지만, 그의 장모 최은순 씨가 가석방 대상이 된 건 당연한 일이라고 생각한다. 최은순 씨와 같은 고령의 여성 수형자는 교도소에서 난동을 부려 징벌방에 가지 않는 한 가석방되지 않을 길이 없다. 그러나 오늘(5.8) 법무부 결정에 대해 민주당(황정아 민주당 대변인)은 “법무부가 대통령 장모에게 ‘따뜻한 어버이날 선물’을 보냈습니다”라는 제호로 서면 브리핑을 냈고, 조국혁신당(김보협 대변인)도 “어버이날...
The post 대통령 장모 최은순 가석방은 당연한 일이다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김동규</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/9, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594699</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594699/5-9-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T03:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 9, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972160/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972160/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-09T00:03:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 9, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[장모 가석방 다음날, 윤석열 기자회견에서 나올 불편한 질문들: 슬로우레터 5월9일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108312</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108312"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T22:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 장모 가석방, “어버이날 선물인가.” 김건희에게 디올 백 건넨 목사, 피의자 신분으로 조사. 한동훈 딸 스펙 논란 보도한 기자들 명예훼손 혐의로 수사. 8월로 미뤄진 국민의힘 전당대회, 다시 한동훈 등판론. 쟁점과 현안. 2년째 국회 탓, 오늘 기자회견에 남은 3년이 달렸다. 오늘 기자회견은 다를까. 채 상병 사건 ‘스모킹 건’ 나왔나. 전공의 빈 자리, 외국 의사로 채운다. 더...
The post 장모 가석방 다음날, 윤석열 기자회견에서 나올 불편한 질문들: 슬로우레터 5월9일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 beta 1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/05/python-3130-beta-1-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/05/python-3130-beta-1-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.13 beta 1 (and feature freeze for Python 3.13).
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130b1/
 
This is a beta preview of Python 3.13
Python 3.13 is still in development. This release, 3.13.0b1, is the first of four beta release previews of 3.13.
Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the 
opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their 
projects to support the new feature release.
We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects to test with 3.13 during the beta phase and report issues found to the Python bug tracker
 as soon as possible. While the release is planned to be feature 
complete entering the beta phase, it is possible that features may be 
modified or, in rare …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마트가서 우유 하나 사고 아보카도 있으면 6개 사와]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/milk-and-avocado/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/milk-and-avocado/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T17:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["마트가서 우유 하나 사고 아보카도 있으면 6개 사와" 요즘 숏폼으로도 많이
돌아다니길래 재미삼아서. 가장 먼저 코드를 작성하기 전에 요구...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드: undefined</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Securing Git repositories with gittuf]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972467/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972467/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T16:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The so-called software supply chain starts with source code. But most security measures and tooling
don't kick in until source is turned into an artifact—a source
tarball, binary build, container image, or other method of delivering a
release to users. The gittuf project
is an attempt to provide a security layer for Git that can handle key management,
enforce security policies for repositories, and guard against attacks
at the version-control layer. At Open Source Summit North America (OSSNA), Aditya Sirish A
Yelgundhalli and Billy Lynch presented
an introduction to gittuf with an overview of its goals and
status.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Asahi Remix 40 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972874/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972874/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T15:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Magazine reports
that the Fedora Asahi
Remix for Apple Arm hardware, based on Fedora
40, is now available:
KDE Plasma 6 as our flagship desktop
experience. It also features a custom Calamares-based initial setup
wizard. A GNOME variant is also available, featuring GNOME 46, with
both desktop variants matching what Fedora Linux offers. Fedora Asahi
Remix also provides a Fedora Server variant for server workloads and
other types of headless deployments. Finally, we offer a Minimal image
for users that wish to build their own experience from the ground up.


See the installation
guide to get started with the Asahi Remix.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to PIC Timers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1654.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1654.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:49:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuing getting started with PIC 8-bit development,
this fourth in a series of five articles looks at configuring and using
timers on the PIC 8-bit platform.  
Topics discussed include:


	
PIC Timers

	
Timer0 Module
	

	
Timer Application


The completed code for this post can be downloaded from GitHub.

PIC®, MPLAB® X, PICkit™ 4 On-Board, and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972861/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972861/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (glib2.0 and php7.3), Gentoo (Commons-BeanUtils, Epiphany, glibc, MariaDB, Node.js, NVIDIA Drivers, qtsvg, rsync, U-Boot tools, and ytnef), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (git-lfs and kernel), SUSE (flatpak, less, python311, rpm, and sssd), and Ubuntu (libde265, libvirt, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp,
 linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4,
 linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi,
 linux-raspi-5.4, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde,
 linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gkeop,
 linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15, linux-oem-6.5, and nghttp2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will Zephyr become the dominant RTOS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482221</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/will-zephyr-become-the-dominant-rtos/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zephyr adoption and development have been snowballing recently, which might make you wonder if Zephyr will become the dominant RTOS. Real-time operating systems (RTOS) are...
The post Will Zephyr become the dominant RTOS? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: to block or not to block, that is the question!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482218</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-to-block-or-not-to-block-that-is-the-question/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T13:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This final installment in the series aims to help you realize that applying or avoiding blocking is the most consequential decision for your embedded software’s...
The post Programming embedded systems: to block or not to block, that is the question! appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The challenges of migrating operating systems for medical devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482214</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-challenges-of-migrating-operating-systems-for-medical-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T12:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating to a newer OS is necessary but comes with major challenges around legacy hardware compatibility, recertification, updated security standards, and performance requirements. Many medical...
The post The challenges of migrating operating systems for medical devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Graeme Wintle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“스마트폰이 정신건강에 문제야”…그렇긴 한데 다른 이유가 더 있다면?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79313</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/08/npsp_mentalhealthsmartphone/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_mentalhealthsmartphone"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T07:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[청소년 정신건강과 스마트폰, 소셜미디어의 관계는 최근 들어 자주 논의되는 주제입니다. 청소년기가 스마트폰과 소셜미디어를 빼놓고 얘기할 수 없는 세상이 된 뒤로 청소년들의 정신건강이 ‘위기’라고 불러야 할 만큼 나빠졌다는 주장을 해온 대표적인 학자가 조너선 하이트입니다. 반대로 정신건강이 어느 정도 나빠졌을 수 있지만, 이를 위기라고 단정 짓기엔 아직 일러 보이며, 그 원인이 스마트폰과 소셜미디어에만 있는지도 신중하게 살펴야 한다고 주장하는 학자들도 있습니다. 뉴욕타임스 데이비드 월러스웰스가 양측의 의견을 두루 살핀 칼럼을 번역하고 해설을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift 101 for OpenStack admins: Data plane deployment]]></title>
        <id>412fb258-691e-42bc-bade-a3e4f97bf082</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/08/red-hat-openshift-101-openstack-admins-data-plane-deployment"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So far in this series, we oversaw the required Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform operators, their roles, and the format used to create the Red Hat OpenStack Services on OpenShift (RHOSO) control plane. Then, we walked through control plane deployment and data plane configuration. 
We’re now ready to add OpenStack compute nodes to the control plane to run virtual machines. The deployment, unsurprisingly, relies on another YAML file. 
When released, you can either join an already deployed Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 9.4 node or pilot bare metal deployment from scratch. For the scope of this article, we are going with the first option. The RHEL compute server has two network cards (eth0 and eth1). Details about the exact process can be found here; we will focus on the YAML files used t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JP Jung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift 101 for OpenStack admins: Configuration]]></title>
        <id>d0cc3216-c93b-486e-be44-1676b31c2701</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/08/red-hat-openshift-101-openstack-admins-configuration"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous post, we oversaw the required Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform operators, their roles, and the format used to create the Red Hat OpenStack Services on OpenShift (RHOSO) control plane. In this article, let’s review the deployment process.
We’ll base our observations on the Development Preview 3 code from https://github.com/rh-osp-demo/dp-demo/.
Let’s begin with the OpenStack Operator.
The OpenStack Operator
The OpenStack Operator consists of three parts (a CatalogSource, an OperatorGroup, and a Subscription), each defining a different resource for managing Operators within an OpenShift/Kubernetes cluster using the Operator Lifecycle Manager (OLM). The resources aim to set up an Operator for OpenStack, likely for managing OpenStack services within the cluster, are as foll…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JP Jung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don't Need an RTOS (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1652.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1652.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least, probably not as often as you think you do. Using a preemptive RTOS can help make a system schedulable (i.e. help all of its tasks meet their deadlines) but it comes at a cost: "concurrently" running tasks can interact in unforeseen ways that cause system failures, that dreaded class of errors known as "race conditions". In part, this is because humans have difficulty thinking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Open Source Summit 2024 Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/eoss-recap</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/eoss-recap"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We cover the talks I was able to see in person, as well as some talks seen by
my colleagues since they were posted. Obviously this is just our little biased
selection, we have not been able to see everything, let us know in the comments
what we missed!
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지지율 바닥 윤석열의 ‘캐비닛 정치’가 시작됐다: 슬로우레터 5월8일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108264</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108264"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T22:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대선 공약 깨고 민정수석을 내세웠다. 캐비닛 정치가 시작된다. 채 상병 사건 생존 병사들의 편지. 쟁점과 현안. 연금 특위 이대로 끝내나. 25만 원 지원금, 민주당 1호 법안으로 간다. 윤석열 장모 풀려나나. 2000명 근거, 제출 안 하는 게 아니라 없는 거 아닐까. 다르게 읽기. 멀티플렉스가 아니라 모노플렉스. 예쁜 쓰레기 만드는 일회용 매장. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘30년 차르’...
The post 지지율 바닥 윤석열의 ‘캐비닛 정치’가 시작됐다: 슬로우레터 5월8일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A proposal to switch Fedora Workstation's desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/970929/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/970929/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T21:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A proposal to switch the default desktop for Fedora Workstation from GNOME
to KDE Plasma largely went over like the proverbial lead balloon—unsurprisingly.
But the 
conversation about the proposal did surface some areas where the
distribution could 
perhaps be more inclusive with regard to the other desktop choices
available.  The project believes that it
benefits from being opinionated and not requiring users to make
multiple decisions before they can even install the distribution, but there
is a balance 
to be found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Publish your Keras models on Kaggle and Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/publish-your-keras-models-on-kaggle-and-hugging-face/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/publish-your-keras-models-on-kaggle-and-hugging-face/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T20:11:19.896Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now you can publish your fine-tuned models directly from the Keras API to either Kaggle or Hugging Face]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unuglify C++ FSM with DSL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1645.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1645.php"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T19:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the third installment of my finite state machine in C++ series. In the first post, I introduced the subject of a state machine and how to go from a trivial but poor implementation to a more robust and better scalable one.

In the second article, I showed how to decouple the implementation of the state machine engine (for reuse) and the specific part (that can't be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Systemd heads for a big round-number release]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971866/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971866/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T15:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The

systemd project is preparing for a new release.

Version 256-rc1 was released
on April 25 with a large number of changes and new features. Most of the
changes relate to security, easier configuration, unprivileged access to system
resources, or all three of these. Users of systemd will find setting up
containers — even without root access — much simpler and more secure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[InstructLab: Advancing generative AI through open source]]></title>
        <id>56ff36af-898c-42cf-ac51-7c94e65c50e8</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/instructlab-open-source-generative-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While large language models (LLMs) offer incredible potential, they also come with their share of challenges. Working with LLMs demands high-quality training data, specialized skills and knowledge, and extensive computing resources. The process of forking and retraining a model is also time consuming and expensive.
The InstructLab project offers an open source approach to generative AI, sourcing community contributions to support regular builds of an enhanced version of an LLM. This approach is designed to lower costs, remove barriers to testing and experimentation, and improve alignment—that is, ensuring the model's answers are accurate, unbiased, and consistent with the values and goals of its users and creators. 
What is InstructLab?
Initiated by IBM and Red Hat, the InstructLab project…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alina Ryan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apply generative AI to app modernization with Konveyor AI]]></title>
        <id>4d2c2efd-c82c-47f7-b58d-858c7e654153</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/modernize-apps-konveyor-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Konveyor community has developed Konveyor AI (Kai), a tool that uses generative AI to accelerate application modernization. Kai integrates large language models (LLMs) with static code analysis to facilitate code modifications within a developer's IDE, helping transition to other modern programming languages and frameworks efficiently. 
Using a retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) approach, Kai enhances LLM outputs with historical code changes and analysis data, ensuring context-specific guidance. This method is model agnostic and does not require model fine-tuning, making Kai a versatile tool for large-scale modernization projects, demonstrated by updating a Java EE application to Quarkus using a Visual Studio Code (VS Code) plug-in. This unique approach will enable organizations to s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Syed M Shaaf, John Matthews</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Lab Recipes]]></title>
        <id>2050f7db-7445-468e-a70d-578c6ab393c4</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/podman-ai-lab-recipes"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if we told you there's a GitHub repository that makes building, running, and developing AI-powered applications from your laptop as easy as making toast? No cloud-based AI platform required, no specialized hardware accelerators needed, and with the most up-to-date open source models? If you like what’s cooking, dig in to explore AI Lab Recipes. 
What is AI Lab Recipes?
The ai-lab-recipes repository is a collaboration of data scientists and application developers that brings together best practices from both worlds. The result is a set of containerized AI-powered applications and tools that are fun to build, easy to run, and convenient to fork and make your own.
AI Lab recipes started as the home for the Podman Desktop AI Lab extension’s sample applications, or recipes. There’s an exce…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally O'Malley, Michael Clifford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing image mode for Red Hat Enterprise Linux]]></title>
        <id>df0bb59e-3a11-47ac-8d05-6a97bf98b99a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/announcing-image-mode-red-hat-enterprise-linux"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Red Hat, we work on a wide range of technologies and sit at the crossroads of our communities, customers, and partners. We believe our best work is done when we work together to find new solutions. So we asked, what if an operating system could be updated via image-based transactions, and what if those images could be built and shipped like a container? What if we could use the same tools, skills, and patterns as today’s containerized applications, closing the gaps between pipeline and production? The result is a way to think differently about how to build, deploy, and manage Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL).
Introducing image mode for Red Hat Enterprise Linux
Image mode for Red Hat Enterprise Linux is a new deployment method that takes a container-native approach to deliver the OS as a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Micene</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing image mode for RHEL and bootable containers in Podman Desktop]]></title>
        <id>03c90bf3-7769-470e-8a6a-f8f37ad2dfb5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/image-mode-rhel-bootable-containers"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers have used Linux since the start. But there have always been two different types of Linux: the host operating system, and the one inside each container. Each one operates independently and requires a completely different set of tools for building, managing, and configuring.
But no more! Image mode for Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) allows you to build and manage a full operating system just like a container image.
What are bootable containers?
Application container base images are Open Container Initiative (OCI) container images that are usually trimmed down as far as possible, to exclude the OS kernel, hardware support, and anything else that application containers do not need when running inside of a host OS.
Bootable containers use this same OCI image format, but contain the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim deBoer, Charlie Drage</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Podman Desktop for containers and Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>f77dd167-f7f8-482b-bc02-c5cb2326789f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/manage-containers-podman-desktop"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Podman Desktop is the central place to work with containers as a developer. Podman Desktop uses the Docker, Podman, and Kubernetes APIs to communicate with container engines and Kubernetes clusters to provide users with a unified graphical interface across all these resources. It also provides extensions to help you manage these resources: install the Podman engine and Kubernetes clusters locally, configure access to remote Kubernetes clusters, configure access to images registries, install various commnd-line interfaces (CLIs), and more.
Architecture
The containers technology is a Linux kernel technology. On a Linux system, you can run Docker and/or Podman directly. On other systems like Windows and macOS, you will need to run a Linux instance inside a virtual machine and run Docker or Po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philippe Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Podman AI Lab: Developer tooling for working with LLMs]]></title>
        <id>2d88ce7a-84ae-428a-8915-a7a29d519ddf</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/introducing-podman-ai-lab"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rapid proliferation of generative AI (gen AI) and open source large language models (LLMs) is revolutionizing computing, and AI-enabled applications are now becoming the norm. As a result, application developers now have to learn best practices and how to build applications taking advantage of AI in their solutions. Hence, the need for tools and technologies that make AI more accessible and approachable, enabling developers to tap into its vast potential. 
However, this shift also underscores the importance of ensuring data privacy and security, as sensitive information is being processed and stored in these new AI-powered systems. To address this growing demand, it is essential to develop and deploy solutions that not only simplify AI development, but also safeguard user data, fosteri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stevan Le Meur, Jeff Maury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podman Desktop brings the Red Hat Developer Subscription to your fingertips]]></title>
        <id>a27d0a2f-06c6-42b7-83b8-8f1ca7c79921</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/07/podman-desktop-red-hat-developer-subscription"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Hat Developer Subscription for Individuals is a no-cost benefit of the Red Hat Developer program that includes access to Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) and other Red Hat products for development use. It is an offering designed for individual developers. You can no-cost subscription by joining the Red Hat Developer program.
As announced at Red Hat Summit 2024, you can now easily consume the Red Hat Developer Subscription for Individuals on your desktop. Whether you are using macOS, Windows, or Linux, the Podman Desktop Red Hat Account Extension puts the Developer Subscription and the Red Hat ecosystem right at your fingertips. In just a few clicks, you can sign into your Red Hat account or create a new one with a custom email address or social login via your Google, Microsoft, or G…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentin Rothberg, Stevan Le Meur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC 14.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972683/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972683/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T12:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
14.1 of the GCC compiler suite has been released.  The list of changes
is long; it includes support for more C++26 features, preparation for
Fortran 2023 support, a new -fhardened flag to enable
security-hardening features, vectorizer improvements, and a number of static-analyzer improvements.  See the release notes for
details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure Randomness in Go 1.22 (Go Blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972680/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972680/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T12:46:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go Blog has a detailed
article on the new, more secure random-number generator implemented for
the 1.22 release.


	For example, when Go 1.20 deprecated math/rand's Read, we heard
	from developers who discovered (thanks to tooling pointing out use
	of deprecated functionality) they had been using it in places where
	crypto/rand's Read was definitely needed, like generating key
	material. Using Go 1.20, that mistake is a serious security problem
	that merits a detailed investigation to understand the
	damage. Where were the keys used? How were the keys exposed? Were
	other random outputs exposed that might allow an attacker to derive
	the keys? And so on. Using Go 1.22, that mistake is just a mistake.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972679/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972679/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T12:29:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel), Gentoo (libjpeg-turbo, xar, and Xpdf), Red Hat (bind, dhcp and glibc), and SUSE (bouncycastle, curl, flatpak, less, and xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[샤오미 미밴드 8 구입기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/xiaomi-mi-band-8/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/xiaomi-mi-band-8/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T11:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[애플워치를 한동안 사용했지만 도무지 매일 충전하는 일이 익숙해지지 않았다. 온갖
알림 덕분에 모든 것을 놓치지 않고 살게 하지만 눈 앞에...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드: undefined</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5/7, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594690</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594690/5-7-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T04:08:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AMD 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, AMD 비전은 변하지않았다. 하락 시 매수 기회]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594686</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594686/24%eb%85%84-1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-amd-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T00:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Showcasing Innovation: eInfochips Product Demos at Embedded World 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482208</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/showcasing-innovation-einfochips-product-demos-at-embedded-world-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eInfochips participated in the Embedded World Exhibition & Conference 2024, a global platform for the entire embedded community. They showcased their next-gen DC Fast Charger...
The post Showcasing Innovation: eInfochips Product Demos at Embedded World 2024 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EInfochips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eInfochips’ Connected and Future-Ready DC Fast Charger Reference Design at Embedded World 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482204</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/einfochips-connected-and-future-ready-dc-fast-charger-reference-design-at-embedded-world-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T23:07:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eInfochips participated in Embedded World 2024 and showcased their intelligent, connected and future-ready DC Fast Charger (DCFC) Reference design. Embedded World brings together suppliers, academia,...
The post eInfochips’ Connected and Future-Ready DC Fast Charger Reference Design at Embedded World 2024 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EInfochips</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 여긴 굶주리고 저긴 식량 남고…이 또한 ‘정치의 실패’다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78909</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/06/npsp_famine/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_famine"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 3월 18일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 20세기 정치, 외교, 그리고 대중문화 역사에 큰 족적을 남긴 1985년 라이브 에이드(Live Aid) 공연을 기억하실 겁니다. 당대의 내로라하는 가수들을 한자리에 모은 건 에티오피아를 비롯한 아프리카 대륙 곳곳에서 기승을 부리던 기근이었습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[631일만의 기자회견, 곳곳이 폭탄인데 수습이 될까: 슬로우레터 5월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108224</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108224"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T22:07:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열의 총리 추천 제안, 이재명이 거절했다. 윤석열 기자회견, 9일 오전 10시. 쟁점과 현안. 김건희 뇌물죄 성립 쉽지 않다. 국민의힘에서도 “채 상병 특검법 거부권 안 된다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 윤석열의 예상 답변과 모범 답안. 윤석열의 생각이 바뀐 이유. 다르게 읽기. “공부하면 부끄러울 것이다.” “당론 입법 반대 안 된다”, 이재명 발언 논란. “나는 중산층”이란 사람들, 다 같지...
The post 631일만의 기자회견, 곳곳이 폭탄인데 수습이 될까: 슬로우레터 5월7일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 PSF annual impact report]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972596/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972596/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:21:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Software
Foundation (PSF) has announced
its annual
impact report for 2023. The report includes updates from PSF staff
as well as summaries of the foundation's activities, financials, and
infrastructure. The PSF celebrated the
20th anniversary of PyCon US, distributed more than $370,000 in grants, and
enjoyed impressive traffic on PyPI:
See the full report for a breakdown of grant disbursements and
trends, PSF expenses, and high-level plans for the rest of 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's check the qdEngine game engine, part two: simplifying C++ code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1121/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1121/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll discuss how the PVS-Studio static analyzer encourages developers to refactor their code. After all, the shorter, simpler, and clearer the code is, the fewer errors it contains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Silicon Labs SiWx917 Ultra-low Power Wi-Fi 6 SoC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482201</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/introducing-silicon-labs-siwx917-ultra-low-power-wi-fi-6-soc/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:45:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Benford, Principal Field Applications Engineer discusses the features and benefits of Silicon Labs’ SiWx917 ultra-low power Wi-Fi 6 SoC https://www.silabs.com/wireless/wi-fi/siwx917-wireless-socs https://www.silabs.com/whitepapers/harnessing-the-power-of-wi-fi-6-in-the-new-age-of-iot
The post Introducing Silicon Labs SiWx917 Ultra-low Power Wi-Fi 6 SoC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silicon Labs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Altera CRO Ben Lee Introduces Agilex 5 and the Latest Altera Innovations]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482198</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/altera-cro-ben-lee-introduces-agilex-5-and-the-latest-altera-innovations/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:36:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Embedded World this year, Ben Lee (Altera CRO) introduces the Agilex 5 FPGA, which is the world’s first FPGA infused with AI and the...
The post Altera CRO Ben Lee Introduces Agilex 5 and the Latest Altera Innovations appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Altera</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stenberg: I survived curl up 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972603/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972603/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T20:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Stenberg has

posted a report about the recent curl up conference about 
curl development. It was held over two days in
Stockholm. The report has short summaries of the talks with links to the
recordings.



curl up is never a big meeting/conference but we have in the past
sometimes been around twenty-five attendees. This year's amount of
fifteen was the smallest so far, but in this small set of people we
have a set of long-term well-known curl contributors. It is not a
big list of attendees that creates a good curl up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Modernizing accessibility for desktop Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971541/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971541/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T17:08:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In some aspects, such as in gaming, the Linux desktop has made
enormous strides in the past few years. In others, such as
accessibility, things have stagnated. At Open Source Summit North America (OSSNA), Matt Campbell spoke
about the need for, and an approach to, modernizing accessibility for
desktop Linux. This included a discussion of Newton, a fledgling
project that may greatly improve accessibility on the Linux desktop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 FSF Free Software Awards]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972572/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972572/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T14:55:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Free Software Foundation has announced
the recipients of its 2023 Free Software Awards: Bruno Haible for work on
gnulib, Nick Logozzo as
the "outstanding new free software contributior", and code.gouv.fr for projects of social
benefit.


	When presenting the award to Haible, FSF executive director Zoë
	Kooyman commented on the significance of Haible's work, saying that
	Haible's work enabled free software programmers around the world to
	focus on the main, innovative portions of their program, thus
	facilitating the development of more and more free software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972571/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972571/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T14:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (glibc, intel-microcode, less, libkf5ksieve, and ruby3.1), Fedora (chromium, gdcm, httpd, and stalld), Gentoo (Apache Commons BCEL, borgmatic, Dalli, firefox, HTMLDOC, ImageMagick, MediaInfo, MediaInfoLib, MIT krb5, MPlayer, mujs, Pillow, Python, PyPy3, QtWebEngine, Setuptools, strongSwan, and systemd), Oracle (grub2 and shim), Red Hat (git-lfs, kpatch-patch, unbound, and varnish), and SUSE (avahi, grafana and mybatis, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, skopeo, SUSE Manager Client Tools, SUSE Manager Salt Bundle, and SUSE Manager Server 4.3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is platform engineering and why do we need it?]]></title>
        <id>e46fd9bc-e608-4529-b1db-3df51a03144b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/06/what-platform-engineering-and-why-do-we-need-it"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps transformed software development. By bringing development and operations teams together, companies achieved a dramatic boost in both speed (agility) and efficiency. But DevOps is just the first chapter. The future of software development lies in platforms. These platforms are like building blocks–scalable and reusable, enabling companies to develop and deliver software even faster and more efficiently than ever before. The best way to achieve this is by making developers happy and more productive.
Why we need platform engineering
Development and Ops teams are navigating a lot of obstacles these days. Not only are tools, frameworks, languages, data storage, and messaging systems becoming increasingly complex, but the shift to cloud environments and closer Dev/Ops integration adds ano…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Eisele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift 101 for OpenStack admins: Operators and prerequisites]]></title>
        <id>1f9f1654-3d65-4b10-9578-8151604dd715</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/06/red-hat-openshift-101-openstack-admins-operators-and-prerequisites"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T06:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenStack Services on OpenShift (RHOSO) service providers can scale faster and maximize their resources. By integrating Kubernetes with OpenStack, organizations see improved resource management and scalability, greater flexibility across the hybrid cloud, simplified development and DevOps practices, and more. 
In this article, we’ll cover some of the finer points of OpenShift for OpenStack admins, including the three Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform operators that are prerequisites: cert-manager, MetalLB, and NMstate.



  
        



  

Figure 1: A high-level view of a simple RHOSO deployment.

What is an Operator?
An Operator is a method of packaging, deploying, and managing a Kubernetes/OpenShift application. An OpenShift/Kubernetes application is both deployed on OpenShif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JP Jung</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[퀄컴 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, AI덕분 프리미엄 스마트폰 수요 증가로 퀄컴 주가도 긍정]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594682</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594682/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%80%84%ec%bb%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T05:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[std::expected - Monadic Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/expected-cpp23-monadic/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/expected-cpp23-monadic/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[std::expected from C++23 not only serves as an error-handling mechanism but also introduces functional programming paradigms into the language. In this blog post, we’ll have a look at functional/monadic extensions of std::expected, which allow us to chain operations elegantly, handling errors at the same time. The techniques are very similar to std::optional extensions - see How to Use Monadic Operations for `std::optional` in C++23 - C++ Stories.
Here’s a brief overview of these functional capabilities:
Update: Thanks to prof. Boguslaw Cyganek for finding some errors in my initial text!
and_then() 
  




     
    


The and_then member function enables chaining operations that might produce a std::expected object. It’s invoked when the std::expected object holds a value and allows for s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.9-rc7]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972473/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972473/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T23:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9-rc7 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "The stats for 6.9 continue to look very normal, and nothing
looks particularly alarming."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 대학 캠퍼스 시위를 외면할 수 없는 ‘바이든의 딜레마’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79291</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/05/npsp_campusprotestbiden/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_campusprotestbiden"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T22:35:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뉴욕에 있는 컬럼비아대학교에서 시작된 반전 시위가 2주를 넘어 계속되고 있습니다. 대학 측이 시위에 참여한 학생들에게 정학 등 징계를 내리고, 여기에 반발한 학생들이 학교 건물을 점거하면서 거세게 항의하는 등 상황은 악화일로입니다. 팔레스타인 가자지구에 있는 무고한 민간인들의 희생이 무엇보다 우려되는 상황에서 휴전이나 평화를 위한 협상도 지지부진합니다. 바이든 대통령으로선 특히 지금 상황이 더욱 난처한 이유가 따로 있습니다. 젊은 세대, 특히 대학생들 사이에서는 이스라엘의 전쟁 범죄를 규탄하는 시각이 압도적으로 우세하기 때문에 이스라엘을 지금보다 더 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주가조작 아니고 디올 백으로? 김건희 검찰 포토라인에 설까: 슬로우레터 5월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108201</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108201"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T22:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 디올 백 사건, 전담 수사팀 만든다. 주가조작 사건은 언제 하나. 쟁점과 현안. 10번째 거부권? 이번에는 다르다. 채 상병 특검의 세 가지 쟁점. 안철수도 “재투표하면 찬성표 던지겠다.” 친윤의 퇴장? 윤석열 기자회견, 드디어 열리나. 이화영 검찰 술판도 특검으로 간다. 더 깊게 읽기. “모든 전제가 다 바뀌었다.” 가정 밖 청소년 최소 30만 명. ‘미공포’와 K팝 쓰레기. 다르게...
The post 주가조작 아니고 디올 백으로? 김건희 검찰 포토라인에 설까: 슬로우레터 5월6일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Survey papers: LLMs will restore some level of usefulness]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8756</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/05/05/survey-papers-llms-will-restore-some-level-of-usefulness/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T22:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scientific papers are like soap operas, in that understanding them requires readers to have some degree of familiarity with the ongoing plot. How can people new to an opera quickly get up to speed with the ongoing story lines, without reading hundreds of papers? The survey paper is intended to be the answer to this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pay - Enabling liability shift for eligible Visa device token transactions globally]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-pay-enabling-liability-shift-for-eligible-visa-device-token-transactions-globally/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-pay-enabling-liability-shift-for-eligible-visa-device-token-transactions-globally/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.024Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to announce the general availability [1] of liability shift for Visa device tokens fo...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models On-Device with MediaPipe and TensorFlow Lite]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/large-language-models-on-device-with-mediapipe-and-tensorflow-lite/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/large-language-models-on-device-with-mediapipe-and-tensorflow-lite/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.023Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Test out the MediaPipe LLM Inference API via our web demo. The Web SDK will be released in the next few weeks with the iOS SDK coming soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Next '24 session library is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-cloud-next-24-session-library-is-now-available/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-cloud-next-24-session-library-is-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.023Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Next 2024 is coming soon, and our session library is live!Next ‘24 covers a ton of grou...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Gemma models in Keras]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-models-in-keras/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-gemma-models-in-keras/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.023Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Keras team is happy to announce that Gemma, a family of lightweight, state-of-the art open model...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build with Gemini models in Project IDX]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-with-gemini-models-in-project-idx/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-with-gemini-models-in-project-idx/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.023Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, we announced a series of product updates to Project IDX to help streamline and simp...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5: Our next-generation model, now available for Private Preview in Google AI Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-our-next-generation-model-now-available-for-private-preview-in-google-ai-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-our-next-generation-model-now-available-for-private-preview-in-google-ai-studio/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.023Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, we released Gemini 1.0 Ultra in Gemini Advanced. You can try it out now by signing up for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay | How two sea turtle enthusiasts are revolutionizing marine conservation]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/weareplay-how-two-sea-turtle-enthusiasts-are-revolutionizing-marine-conservation/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/weareplay-how-two-sea-turtle-enthusiasts-are-revolutionizing-marine-conservation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.023Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When environmental science student Caitlin returned home from a trip monitoring sea turtles in Weste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay | Meet the founders changing women's lives: Women’s History Month Stories]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/weareplay-meet-the-founders-changing-womens-lives-womens-history-month-stories/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/weareplay-meet-the-founders-changing-womens-lives-womens-history-month-stories/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.022Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To celebrate Women’s History Month, meet the founders behind groundbreaking apps and games made by women or for women.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build with Google AI video series, Season 2: more AI patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-with-google-ai-video-series-season-2-more-ai-patterns/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-with-google-ai-video-series-season-2-more-ai-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.022Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are excited to bring you the second season of Build with Google AI. Check out Season 2 right now, and stay tuned for future episodes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune Gemini Pro in Google AI Studio or with the Gemini API]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/tune-gemini-pro-in-google-ai-studio-or-with-the-gemini-api/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/tune-gemini-pro-in-google-ai-studio-or-with-the-gemini-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.022Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tune Gemini 1.0 Pro in Google AI Studio and with the Gemini API. Customize the model with your data for higher quality outputs, tune in minutes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune in for Google I/O on May 14]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/tune-in-for-google-io-on-may-14/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/tune-in-for-google-io-on-may-14/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.022Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Register to stay informed about I/O and other related events coming soon. The live-streamed keynotes start May 14 at 10am. Mark your calendar.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDE Women’s History Month Feature: Gema Parreño Piqueras, AI/ML GDE]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gde-womens-history-month-feature-gema-parreno-piqueras-aiml-gde/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gde-womens-history-month-feature-gema-parreno-piqueras-aiml-gde/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.022Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For Women's History Month, we're shining a spotlight on Gema Parreño Piqueras, an AI/ML Google Developer Expert (GDE) from Madrid, Spain.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google for Games is coming to GDC 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-for-games-is-coming-to-gdc-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-for-games-is-coming-to-gdc-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.022Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Join us on March 19 for the Game Developers Conference (GDC) where game developers will gather to learn, network, problem-solve, and shape the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get ready for Google I/O: Program lineup revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/get-ready-for-google-io-program-lineup-revealed/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/get-ready-for-google-io-program-lineup-revealed/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O kicks off on May 14, 2024 with the Google Keynote at 10am PT followed by the Developer keynote at 1:30pm PT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing new AI tools on Google for Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-new-ai-tools-on-google-for-developers-documentation/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-new-ai-tools-on-google-for-developers-documentation/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google for Developers just got smarter. Our new AI chat helps you find answers, understand code, and more. Explore AI tools right in the documentation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving privacy compliance with your CI/CD: A guide for compliance teams]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/achieving-privacy-compliance-with-your-cicd-a-guide-for-compliance-teams/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/achieving-privacy-compliance-with-your-cicd-a-guide-for-compliance-teams/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now, you can extend your CI/CD systems to catch privacy and security issuing using Checks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the inaugural cohort of our Google for Startups Accelerator: AI First North America]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/meet-the-inaugural-cohort-of-our-google-for-startups-accelerator-ai-first-north-america/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/meet-the-inaugural-cohort-of-our-google-for-startups-accelerator-ai-first-north-america/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This equity-free program provides 10 weeks of hands-on mentorship and technical project support to startups using AI in their core service or product.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro Now Available in 180+ Countries; with Native Audio Understanding, System Instructions, JSON Mode and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-now-available-in-180-countries-with-native-audio-understanding-system-instructions-json-mode-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-now-available-in-180-countries-with-native-audio-understanding-system-instructions-json-mode-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are continuing to work on making Google AI Studio and the Gemini API the easiest way to build with the latest Gemini model.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemma Family Expands with Models Tailored for Developers and Researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-expands-with-models-tailored-for-developers-and-researchers/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-expands-with-models-tailored-for-developers-and-researchers/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the new members of the Gemma family of open models, tailored to devs and researchers, offering new and innovative options.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ML Olympiad 2024: Globally Distributed ML Competitions by Google ML Community]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ml-olympiad-2024-globally-distributed-ml-competitions-by-google-ml-community/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ml-olympiad-2024-globally-distributed-ml-competitions-by-google-ml-community/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T20:12:28.021Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The third round of ML Olympiad offers developers hands-on machine learning through Kaggle competitions organized by Google ML communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1분기 애플 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 최악은  지나고 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594672</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594672/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T14:31:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[24년 1분기 아마존 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 이제 본격 성장 스토리가 시작된다..]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594664</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594664/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T12:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMSIS-DAP Debug Probe for Robots and Pixhawk with KiCAD]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40376</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/05/05/cmsis-dap-debug-probe-for-robots-and-pixhawk-with-kicad/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-05T09:03:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article describes the MCU-Link-MR debug probe. It is open source hardware based on the NXP MCU-Link debug probe. The hardware, built with KiCAD, offers different UART and debug headers suitable for various robot platforms, including Pixhawk 'full' and Pixhawk 'mini' ports. The v0.1 hardware has been assembled and tested successfully, simplifying debugging of drone platform and hardware. A v0.2 version with fixes is underway. Find it on GitHub. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국과 미국이 기술 협력한다? 이게 쉽지 않은 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79285</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/04/npsp_chinagreenpolicy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_chinagreenpolicy"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T13:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[중국은 최근 환경 기술 분야에서 눈부신 진전을 이루며 글로벌 무대에서 크게 주목받고 있습니다. 특히 시진핑의 중국은 기후변화에 적극적으로 대응하는 모습을 보이며, 국제사회에서의 리더십 공백을 메우려는 듯한 인상을 주고 있습니다. 그러나 중국이 기술 발전을 통해 환경 문제를 해결하는 것 자체보다 기술 발전을 통해 중국의 위상을 높이거나 다른 나라에 종속되지 않는 정치적 목적을 우선시하는 점은 기술 협력의 걸림돌로 보입니다. 미국과 중국이 환경 분야에서 기술 협력에 나서면 인류가 당면한 문제를 해결할 수 있다고 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[애플 주가가 상승 이유, 자사주 매입과 ROE 확대]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594660</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594660/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80%ec%99%80-%ec%9e%90%ec%82%ac%ec%a3%bc-%eb%a7%a4%ec%9e%85"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T07:44:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The file_operations structure gets smaller]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972081/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972081/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T15:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel developers are encouraged to send their changes in small batches as
a way of making life easier for reviewers.  So when a longtime developer
and maintainer hits the list with a 437-patch series touching 859 files,
eyebrows are certain to head skyward.  Specifically, this series
from Jens Axboe is cleaning up one of the core abstractions that has
been part of the Linux kernel almost since the beginning; authors of device
drivers (among others) will have to take note.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972351/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972351/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T15:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium, grub2, httpd, kernel, libcoap, matrix-synapse, python-pip, and rust-pythonize), Red Hat (kernel and libxml2), SUSE (kernel), and Ubuntu (eglibc, glibc and php7.4, php8.1, php8.2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploy computer vision applications at the edge with MicroShift]]></title>
        <id>9d369482-a758-426c-a3e0-92116c0169fb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/03/deploy-computer-vision-applications-edge-microshift"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the final instalment of this series on computer vision at the edge. We have covered all the steps needed to be ready to deploy our model at the edge, from installing a single node OpenShift to use Red Hat OpenShift AI to training our own computer vision model. If you missed any of the previous articles in this series, you can catch up here:

How to install single node OpenShift on AWS
How to install single node OpenShift on bare metal
Red Hat OpenShift AI installation and setup
Model training in Red Hat OpenShift AI
Prepare and label custom datasets with Label Studio
Deploy computer vision applications at the edge with MicroShift 

Deploying our application with MicroShift
As we embark on the final instalment of our series, we delve into the installation of MicroShift and the de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Alvarez Ponce, Kaitlyn Abdo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify Gatekeeper installation and constraint management]]></title>
        <id>20210f96-6b90-4279-8277-083a45a113f4</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/03/simplify-gatekeeper-installation-and-constraint-management"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes governance provides an extensible framework for enterprises to introduce their own security and configuration policies that can be applied to managed Red Hat OpenShift or Kubernetes clusters. For more information on Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management policies, I recommend that you read the Comply to standards using policy based governance and Implement Policy-based Governance Using Configuration Management blogs.
As part of the Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management and Red Hat OpenShift Platform Plus subscriptions, there is a supported Gatekeeper Operator that was recently updated to Gatekeeper 3.11.1. In this article, let's explore the Gatekeeper Operator and its integration with Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management, which helps you achieve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matt Prahl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한국 언론자유 지수 62위로 추락, 이명박근혜 시절로 회귀.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108162</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108162"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T03:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘국경 없는 기자회’, “정치적 양극화와 언론인에 대한 혐오 확산 심각… 광고주의 압박 등 감시자로서 역할 수행 못 해.” ‘국경 없는 기자회(Reporters Without Borders)’가 해마다 집계하는 언론자유지수에서 한국이 62위로 추락했다. 지난해는 47위였다. ‘국경 없는 기자회’는 “한국은 언론의 자유와 다원주의를 존중하는 자유민주주의 국가지만 언론이 감시자로서 해야 할 역할을 제대로 수행하지 못하는 경우가 많다”면서 “포퓰리즘적 정치 성향은 언론인에...
The post 한국 언론자유 지수 62위로 추락, 이명박근혜 시절로 회귀. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Triggering DMA from timers (or GPIO) on the SAM E70]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-05-03:/sam-e70-timers-dma.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/sam-e70-timers-dma.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SAM E70 is still a powerful MCU despite being released around 2015. It has a 300 MHz Cortex-M7, 150 MHz bus system and high-speed USB. High-speed USB (not the same thing as USB 2.0) is pretty rare in Cortex-M devices. It is usually the domain of much more powerful Cortex-A chips. When developing a data acquisition system on the SAM E70 I was surprised that there is no obvious
way to trigger a DMA transfer from a timer!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 곧 닥칠 ‘고령 사회’, 우리가 던져야 할 질문은 따로 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78864</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/02/npsp_agingsociety/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_agingsociety"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T22:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 3월 13일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 2024년 2월 우리나라 출생아 수와 합계출산율이 또다시 사상 최저를 기록했다는 소식을 여러 언론이 대서특필했습니다. 0.72명에 그친 합계출산율은 전 세계적으로 비교 대상이 없는 최저치인 데다가, 선진국 모임으로 여겨지는 OECD 평균과 비교해도 절반에 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조선일보 너마저, “국민들 의구심 커진다” 거부권에 반대: 슬로우레터 5월3일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108130</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108130"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T22:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[채 상병 특검법 통과. 또 거부권? 조선일보도 반대. 윤석열도 수사 대상이다. 쟁점과 현안. 이태원 특별법도 통과. 2000명의 근거가 뭔가. 더 깊게 읽기. 쪼그라든 여의도연구원. 5‧18 성폭행 피해자들, 44년 만에 만났다. 오늘의 TMI. AI 훈련용 데이터 절반이 뉴스. 남자 중학생 키 10년 전보다 7.4cm 커졌다. 스타벅스 아메리카노 11잔 중 1잔은 디카페인. 해법과 대안. 민원인과 통화 모두...
The post 조선일보 너마저, “국민들 의구심 커진다” 거부권에 반대: 슬로우레터 5월3일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernizing Pedal: Breaking down a Javå monolith into Quarkus microservices]]></title>
        <id>e8f3b7bf-cc7f-4d11-9ccb-79d2724b6655</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/02/modernizing-pedal-breaking-down-java-monolith-quarkus-microservices"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the mid-2010s, Netflix and Google detailed how they saved costs while scaling their software infrastructure’s components to meet rising demands. Since then, most engineers have embraced this microservices architecture. Microservices help divide a single monolithic application into small units, each acting as a service to deliver specific functions.
For companies transitioning from on-premise software to a hybrid cloud infrastructure, refactoring the application from a monolith into microservices offers several advantages. The microservice architecture isolates services, allowing companies to loosely coupled software components. This flexibility enables deploying and running specific services on premise or in the cloud as part of a hybrid setup. Consequently, companies can keep personal …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram, Ian Lawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new set of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972209/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972209/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.8.9, 6.6.30,
6.1.90, 5.15.158, 5.10.216, 5.4.275, and 4.19.313 stable kernels.  As is the norm, they
contain lots of important fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Inheritable credentials for directory file descriptors]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971825/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971825/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:10:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Unix-like systems, an open file descriptor carries the right to access
the opened object in specific ways.  As a general rule, that file
descriptor does not enable access to any other objects.  The
recently merged BPF token feature runs
counter to this practice by creating file descriptors that carry specific
BPF-related access rights.  A similar but different approach to
capability-carrying file descriptors, in the form of directory file
descriptors that include their own credentials, is currently under
consideration in the kernel community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernizing Pedal: API management for modern system design and administration]]></title>
        <id>920e94fd-e3da-4ffd-b9f0-4e23bf66675c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/02/modernizing-pedal-api-management-modern-system-design-and-administration"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T15:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early days of software, developers built applications by grouping all components into one self-contained code base for easy management — the monolithic approach. Then, the technology evolved from large codebases to smaller microservices, distinct components that collaborate like a specialized team.
Pedal, an app to buy bikes, embodies this transition. It’s evolving from a monolith to a network of independent microservices. However, it’s challenging to manage, monitor, and coordinate all these microservices efficiently.
Application programming interface (API) management tools help monitor and control multiple microservices from a central location while enhancing security. Like team captains, these tools help microservices collaborate while retaining their individual capabilities.
Our…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram, Ian Lawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.78.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972191/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972191/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T14:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.78.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Changes include a new
mechanism for diagnostic attributes, changes to how assertions around
unsafe blocks are handled, and more.


	Rust now supports a #[diagnostic] attribute namespace to
	influence compiler error messages. These are treated as hints which
	the compiler is not required to use, and it is also not an error to
	provide a diagnostic that the compiler doesn't recognize. This
	flexibility allows source code to provide diagnostics even when
	they're not supported by all compilers, whether those are different
	versions or entirely different implementations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972186/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972186/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T14:22:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and distro-info-data), Fedora (et, php-tcpdf, python-aiohttp, python-openapi-core, thunderbird, tpm2-tools, and tpm2-tss), Red Hat (nodejs:16 and podman), and Ubuntu (firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prepare and label custom datasets with Label Studio]]></title>
        <id>211b46b0-1367-455c-8842-74b41ef77d16</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/02/prepare-and-label-custom-datasets-label-studio"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the fifth chapter in our “computer vision at the edge” series, in which we will dive into the preparation of a custom dataset. Below you can see all the different episodes in this series:

How to install single node OpenShift on AWS
How to install single node OpenShift on bare metal
Red Hat OpenShift AI installation and set up
Model training in Red Hat OpenShift AI
Prepare and label custom datasets with Label Studio
Safari application deployment on MicroShift  

Data labeling with Label Studio
Data labeling is the practice of accurately labeling data for the purpose of correct identification by training models, algorithms, etc. It is crucial for training models because it provides the necessary annotations and context for algorithms to learn effectively. Machine learning models und…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Alvarez Ponce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model training in Red Hat OpenShift AI]]></title>
        <id>629e04a1-0abc-431f-95e1-eea557232858</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/02/model-training-red-hat-openshift-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the fourth episode of our series that dives into training and deploying computer vision models at the edge. And I have some good news: we're already past the halfway point. Have a look at the series outline and the remainder of the fascicles:

How to install single node OpenShift on AWS
How to install single node OpenShift on bare metal
Red Hat OpenShift AI installation and set up
Model training in Red Hat OpenShift AI
Prepare and label custom datasets with Label Studio
Deploy computer vision applications at the edge with MicroShift 

Introduction
Training artificial intelligence (AI) models is a pivotal process in the development of AI systems, demanding significant time and resources. The importance of this training phase cannot be overstated, as it is during this stage that the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Alvarez Ponce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 2, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971093/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971093/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T01:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for May 2, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“보따리 내주고 뺨 맞나”, 일본의 네이버 퇴출에 윤석열이 침묵하는 이유는?: 슬로우레터 5월2일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108080</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108080"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T22:08:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[일본의 네이버 퇴출, “적대국에나 할 법한 일”. 쟁점과 현안. 이태원 특별법 오늘 합의 처리한다. 평화누리특별자치도? “한국은 잘 사는 나라, 왜 돈을 안 내나.” 전쟁 반대 집회 컬럼비아대 학생 282명 체포. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명 싫어서 국민의힘 찍는다는 가설. 자산 상위는 국민의힘 지지율이 63%. 다르게 읽기. 기계가 심판을 보니 판이 달라졌다. ‘기후 유권자’들은 어디로 갔나. 해법과...
The post “보따리 내주고 뺨 맞나”, 일본의 네이버 퇴출에 윤석열이 침묵하는 이유는?: 슬로우레터 5월2일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compilation of gripping C++ conference talks from 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1120/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1120/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new conference season is on its way, so we'd like to invite you to read some of the best C++ talks from the last season. You can learn more about C++ and get inspired in this compilation of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU nano 8.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971980/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971980/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T17:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.0 of the terminal text editor GNU nano has been
released. This update includes several changes to keybindings to be
more newcomer-friendly, such as remapping Ctrl-F to forward-search and
adding an option for modern bindings:
The release also provides access to 14 levels of gray scale in xterm (up
from four), as well as many bug fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A look at Ubuntu Desktop LTS 24.04]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971143/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971143/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T17:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 24.04 LTS, code-named "Noble Numbat", was released on April 25. This release includes GNOME 46, installer updates,
security enhancements, a lot of updated packages, and a new App Center
that puts a heavy emphasis on using Snaps to install software. It is not an ambitious release, but it brings enough to the table that it's a worthwhile update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“숨 쉬는 건 범죄가 아니다”…노숙도 마찬가지? 간단치 않은 사정들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79247</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/05/01/npsbs_scotushomeless/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsbs_scotushomeless"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T15:30:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국 연방대법원이 노숙을 불법으로 규정하고 노숙자를 처벌한 지방 정부(시 정부)의 행동이 위헌이라는 사건에 관해 이번 회기 판결을 앞두고 구두 변론을 진행했습니다. 이에 관해 UC 버클리 로스쿨의 로라 라일리 임상 디렉터가 노숙자의 인권을 옹호하는 칼럼을 썼습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 해설에서 시 정부들은 왜 노숙자를 처벌하는 게 과도하다고 본 항소법원(고등법원)의 판결에 반발했는지 짚어봤습니다. 전문 번역: “길에서 자면 불법”…그들을 더는 벼랑 끝으로 내몰지 말라 해설: “숨 쉬는 건 범죄가 아니다”…노숙도 마찬가지? 간단치 않은 사정들]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eelco Dolstra steps down from NixOS Foundation board]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971973/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971973/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T14:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NixOS Foundation board

announced on April 30 that Eelco Dolstra is stepping down from the board
following the recent calls for his resignation.



Eelco is the principal author of Nix and undoubtedly a central figure in the
ecosystem that grew around it. We confirm that Eelco showed no intention to be
perceived as or act like the BDFL [Benevolent Dictator for Life]
of the Nix ecosystem, or the Nix code base. To
commit to that in a timely manner, he has decided to formally step down from the
board.



The board also announced its intent to set up new, explicit governance for the
project, answerable to the community:



We will appoint a constitutional assembly within the next 14 days.
Its task will be to set up a new governance structure, run by the
community, that is capable of serving the community's needs. Once
established, we will delegate our power to institutions within that
new structure. This entire process will take place in a public space,
such that it's traceable for anyone concerned. We are committed to
listening to everyone who may help with solving the problems the
community is facing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.4?]]></title>
        <id>02fe2c2a-c77c-4765-bbab-1482c2b7b62f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/01/whats-new-red-hat-enterprise-linux-94"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 9.4 is now generally available (GA). This release provides a flexible, reliable, secure, and stable foundation for innovative applications. It also provides a platform for faster and more efficient development of critical workloads with a consistent experience across physical, virtual, private, public cloud, and edge deployments.
 You can download RHEL 9.4 at no cost as part of the Red Hat Developer program subscription. 
In this article, you'll learn about enhancements in RHEL 9.4 that improve the developer experience.
Latest language runtimes, databases, and tools
Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.4 has been updated with many developers' favorite programming languages. Notable changes include: 

Python 3.12 is the latest version of Python programming language inc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Mungale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972029/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972029/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T13:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (nghttp2 and qtbase-opensource-src), Mageia (cjson, freerdp, guava, krb5, libarchive, and mediawiki), Oracle (container-tools:4.0 and container-tools:ol8), Red Hat (bind, buildah, container-tools:3.0, container-tools:rhel8, expat, gnutls, golang, grafana, kernel, kernel-rt, libreswan, libvirt, linux-firmware, mod_http2, pcp, pcs, podman, python-jwcrypto, rhc-worker-script, shadow-utils, skopeo, sssd, tigervnc, unbound, and yajl), SUSE (kernel and python311), and Ubuntu (gerbv and node-json5).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Static Analysis Ranked Defect List]]></title>
        <id>http://betterembsw.blogspot.com/2024/05/static-analysis-ranked-defect-list.html</id>
        <link href="http://betterembsw.blogspot.com/2024/05/static-analysis-ranked-defect-list.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T13:04:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crazy idea of the day: Static Analysis Ranked Defect List.



Here is a software analysis tool feature request/product idea: So many times we see the problem that a static analysis tool or other way of automatically finding bugs inundates developers with so many possible bugs they turn it off in frustration. Or maybe they have a requirement to ship only "clean" code so they don't run the tool because then there is nothing to clean up.  Put your favorite head-in-the-sand organizational dysfunction here.


I'd love to be able to recommend a static analysis or other tool that has a feature that reports that top 10 defects currently in the code base, ranked by likely risk. Go ahead and use machine learning for the ranking; fine with me. Regardless of methodology, fixing only some is a guess after all.


Ultimately, all the static analysis warnings should be cleaned up. Having a "top K warnings" feature would allow a team to make progress over time instead of simply sweeping the entire mess under the carpet and ignoring what is often very valuable information that predicts defect escapes to deployment.


For tools with many warnings an approximation can be to gradually turn on a series of warning flags over time and/or just run the warnings on a subset of modules. But a global "these are the 10 scariest warnings" would be a nice feature.


Thoughts?  Does some tool already do this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Better Embedded System SW</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift AI installation and setup]]></title>
        <id>67c07bd1-0951-430c-8220-1f8ab10475bb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/01/red-hat-openshift-ai-installation-and-setup"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the third article in this series, which covers the process to prepare and run computer vision models at the edge. The complete list of articles that compose the series are listed below:

How to install single node OpenShift on AWS
How to install single node OpenShift on bare metal
Red Hat OpenShift AI installation and setup
Model training in Red Hat OpenShift AI
Prepare and label custom datasets with Label Studio
Safari application deployment on MicroShift  

Introduction
Red Hat OpenShift AI is a comprehensive platform designed to streamline the development, deployment, and management of data science and machine learning applications in hybrid and multi-cloud environments. Leveraging the Red Hat OpenShift app dev platform, OpenShift AI empowers data science teams to exploit con…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Alvarez Ponce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary deployment strategy with Argo Rollouts]]></title>
        <id>6b8fcbab-d096-406f-971e-e17dc9570560</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/05/01/canary-deployment-strategy-argo-rollouts"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, I explained how to implement a canary deployment strategy with OpenShift Service Mesh. In this article we will go through the same example—this time using Argo Rollouts.
Argo Rollouts is a Kubernetes controller and set of CRDs that provide advanced deployment capabilities such as blue-green, canary, canary analysis, experimentation, and progressive delivery features to Kubernetes. In this demo, we are going to use canary capabilities. 
You can also check this other article for a blue/green deployment strategy with Argo Rollouts.
In the next steps, we will see a real example of how to install, deploy, and manage the life cycle of cloud native applications doing canary deployment using Argo Rollouts.
Let's start with some theory. After that, we will have a hands-on ex…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Severiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in April (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/april-2024-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/april-2024-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
April.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엉터리 주택 통계, 반 년 동안 몰랐는데 “운이 좋았다”고?: 슬로우레터 5월1일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108036</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108036"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T22:05:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[노동절에 4명 중 1명 출근한다. 반년 동안 몰랐다. 국세 수입 2조2000억 원 덜 걷혔다. 쟁점과 현안. 시작도 못 한 대통령의 정치. “정치를 안 한 게 아니다.” 채 상병 특검법과 이태원 특별법 간다. 국민연금 개혁은 다음 국회로? “한다고 봐도 될 것.” 더 깊게 읽기. 노동절 화두는 5인 미만 사업장. 외국인 없이 배 못 만든다. 중대재해법 효과,...
The post 엉터리 주택 통계, 반 년 동안 몰랐는데 “운이 좋았다”고?: 슬로우레터 5월1일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernization - Rehost to OpenShift using ArgoCD - Pedal based guide]]></title>
        <id>6ea16f17-34d2-4c93-9540-f41051c28a88</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/30/modernization-rehost-openshift-using-argocd-pedal-based-guide"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T16:27:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rehosting, a cornerstone in the evolution of software development and deployment, has traditionally enabled the concurrent operation of multiple operating systems and applications on the same physical hardware. This approach, often employed through virtual machines (VMs), enhances efficiency, scalability, and resource utilization. 
However, in contemporary software development, the focus is shifting towards containerization, as exemplified by orchestration platforms like Kubernetes. While Kubernetes excels in abstracting the deployment environment from the host system, offering superior flexibility and resource management, it’s noteworthy that not many Kubernetes platforms currently support running VMs directly on Kubernetes. 
This limitation is particularly relevant for traditional applic…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram, Ian Lawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you know what your default ISRs are doing?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482191</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/do-you-know-what-your-default-isrs-are-doing/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T16:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s very common for developers to pay attention to the interrupts they are using. However, what about those interrupts that your toolchain automatically populates for...
The post Do you know what your default ISRs are doing? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to simplify design of isolated software configurable I/O channels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482185</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-simplify-design-of-isolated-software-configurable-i-o-channels/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:42:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article presents a software configurable input/output (I/O) device and its dedicated isolated power and data solution that helps solve the design challenges in system-level...
The post How to simplify design of isolated software configurable I/O channels appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valerie Hamilton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Security patterns and anti-patterns in embedded development]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/970818/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/970818/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T15:11:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to security, telling developers to do (or not do)
something can be ineffective. Helping them understand the why behind
instructions, by illustrating good and bad practices using stories, can be
much more effective. With several such stories Marta
Rybczyńska fashioned an interesting talk
about patterns and anti-patterns in embedded Linux security at the
Embedded
Open Source Summit (EOSS), co-located with Open
Source Summit North America (OSSNA), on April 16 in Seattle, Washington.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yocto Project 5.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971785/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971785/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T14:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
5.0 of the Yocto Project
distribution builder has been released.  The list of new features is long;
see the
release notes for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["run0" as a sudo replacement]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971745/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971745/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T14:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
Mastodon stream from Lennart Poettering describes a sudo
replacement — called run0 — that will be part of the upcoming
systemd 256 release.  It takes a rather different approach to the execution
of privileged commands, avoiding the use of setuid (which he calls "SUID")
permissions entirely.


	So, in my ideal world, we'd have an OS entirely without SUID. Let's
	throw out the concept of SUID on the dump of UNIX' bad ideas. An
	execution context for privileged code that is half under the
	control of unprivileged code and that needs careful manual clean-up
	is just not how security engineering should be done in 2024
	anymore.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.45.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971742/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971742/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T13:41:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.45.0 of the Git
source-code management system has been released.  Changes include a new
list command for git reflog, a couple of new
configuration variables for git diff, the ability to drop
redundant commits while cherry-picking, a number of performance
improvements, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971740/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971740/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T13:35:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (org-mode), Oracle (shim and tigervnc), Red Hat (ansible-core, avahi, buildah, container-tools:4.0, containernetworking-plugins, edk2, exfatprogs, fence-agents, file, freeglut, freerdp, frr, grub2, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, gstreamer1-plugins-base, gstreamer1-plugins-good, harfbuzz, httpd, ipa, kernel, libjpeg-turbo, libnbd, LibRaw, libsndfile, libssh, libtiff, libvirt, libX11, libXpm, mingw components, mingw-glib2, mingw-pixman, mod_http2, mod_jk and mod_proxy_cluster, motif, mutt, openssl and openssl-fips-provider, osbuild and osbuild-composer, pam, pcp, pcs, perl, pmix, podman, python-jinja2, python3.11, python3.11-cryptography, python3.11-urllib3, qemu-kvm, qt5-qtbase, runc, skopeo, squashfs-tools, systemd, tcpdump, tigervnc, toolbox, traceroute, webkit2gtk3, wpa_supplicant, xorg-x11-server, xorg-x11-server-Xwayland, and zziplib), SUSE (docker, ffmpeg, ffmpeg-4, frr, and kernel), and Ubuntu (anope, freerdp3, and php7.0, php7.2, php7.4, php8.1).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[저널리즘 관점에서 조수진 오보 톺아보기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108020</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108020"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T09:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[조선일보와 한겨레, KBS가 쟁점 선도… 부실 검증이 초래한 대형 언론 참사 2024년 22대 국회의원 선거(총선)에서 ‘조수진 오보’ 사태가 발생했다. 지난 4월 초부터 조수진 변호사 관련 정정보도문이 몇몇 신문과 통신사에서 나오고 있다. 이와 대조적으로, 조수진 논란 쟁점을 이끌었던 언론사들은 정정보도문을 내지 않고 있다. 만약 ‘조수진 오보’의 정정보도 내용이 진실이라면, 이번 총선에서 서울 강북을 유권자들과 후보직을 사퇴한...
The post 저널리즘 관점에서 조수진 오보 톺아보기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>노동인권저널리즘센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some more C# 12]]></title>
        <id>618e4cde-f678-4c57-b88d-66f650de3eb5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/30/some-more-c-12"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous article on C# 12, you learned about collection expressions and primary constructors. In this article, we’ll take a look at some advanced features that part of the latest C# version: inline arrays, optional params and params in lambda expressions, ref readonly parameters, aliasing any type, and the UnsafeAccessorAttribute.
Inline arrays
A regular C# array is a reference type that lives on the heap. Like other reference types, the garbage collector (GC) keeps track whether the array is still referenced, and it frees up memory when the array is no longer in use.
To avoid the GC overhead in performance sensitive code, when a small array is needed that is local to a function, it can be allocated on the stack using stackalloc. Thanks to the Span<T> type introduced in .NET Core 2.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Deseyn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient image builds with FUSE in Red Hat OpenShift Dev Spaces]]></title>
        <id>663be67c-4825-4c93-9895-4acee6e5d197</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/30/efficient-image-builds-fuse-red-hat-openshift-dev-spaces"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the fuse-overlayfs storage driver, you can enable faster builds and more optimized storage usage for podman build and buildah within your Red Hat OpenShift Dev Spaces cloud development environment (CDE). Before diving into its advantages, let’s first discuss some prerequisite details about container image layers and storage drivers.
Container images consist of layers which are stored and used for building and running containers. A huge benefit of this layer structure is that, assuming that each image layer stores only the differences compared to the previous layer (i.e., the delta), each layer is small which generally allows time and space savings when building and running containers. This is because small layers promotes re-usability allowing layer sharing between images and containe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Kwon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세계화의 열매, 대도시 엘리트]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=107406</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/107406"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T03:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 위 목차 링크를 누르면 해당 항목으로 이동합니다. 오른쪽 아래 화살표(↑)를 누르면 다시 최상단으로 올라옵니다. 홍세화를 추모하며 “홍세화 선생님은 ‘똘레랑스'(tolérence: 나와는 다른 타자의 ‘다름과 차이’를 관용)로 유명해지긴 했지만, 홍세화 선생을 가장 잘 표현하는 게 똘레랑스일까 싶어요. 생각과 말과 행동을 일치시키려고 노력한 삶의 태도가 존경받아야 하지 않나 싶어요. 제가 주목한 건 그런 삶의 태도예요. 홍세화 선생님의...
The post 세계화의 열매, 대도시 엘리트 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PolarFire® devices at EW24: Accessible and Affordable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482173</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/polarfire-devices-at-ew24-accessible-and-affordable/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:05:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessible and affordable performance/Watt on FPGA. Saving you pain of having to design in heatsinks avoiding you cost. PolarFire® FPGA and SoC in action at...
The post PolarFire® devices at EW24: Accessible and Affordable appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Microchip</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understand internals of std::expected]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/expected-cpp23-internals/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/expected-cpp23-internals/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the article about std::expected, I introduced the type and showed some basic examples, and in this text, you’ll learn how it is implemented.
struct 
  




     
    


In short, std::expected should contain two data members: the actual expected value and the unexpected error object. So, in theory, we could use a simple structure:
template <class _Ty, class _Err>
struct expected {
    /*... lots of code ... */
    _Ty _Value;
    _Err _Unexpected;
};


However, there are better solutions than this. Here are some obvious issues for our “struct” approach.
The size of the object is the sum of the Value type and the Error type (plus padding if needed).
Two data members are “active” and initialized, which might not be possible - for example, what if the Value type has no default constructor?…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] Z세대 가치관에 문제 있다? 그런데 부모인 X세대가 더 문제다?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78860</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/04/29/npsp_gendergapgeneration/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_gendergapgeneration"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:59:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 3월 11일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 정치적인 성향은 어떻게 형성될까요? 정치적인 성향이 세부적인 변수라서 다소 좁은 의미로 정의하게 돼 문제라면, 좀 더 넓은 의미에서 한 사람의 가치관은 어떻게 형성되는지를 생각해 볼 수 있을 겁니다. 삶을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“가정 주부에 웬 뇌물 따지나”, 선거방송심의위가 MBC에 중징계 때린 이유: 슬로우레터 4월30일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=107961</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/107961"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T22:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열-이재명 발언 시간은 85:15. 하고 싶은 말만 했다. 허심탄회한 대화? 하나도 안 맞았다. 쟁점과 현안. 황우여로 혁신 가능한가. “가정주부에 웬 뇌물 따지냐.” 다르게 읽기. 성장률 서프라이즈의 그림자. 한국 GDP, 멕시코에 추월당했다. 윤희숙이 말하는 보수의 참패 요인. 국민의힘이 갇힌 동굴의 우상. 더 깊게 읽기. 산재 가장 많은 기업은 배달의민족. 원전 지원금 3.5조원, 쌈짓돈처럼 쓰고 쇠고랑. 엔달러...
The post “가정 주부에 웬 뇌물 따지나”, 선거방송심의위가 MBC에 중징계 때린 이유: 슬로우레터 4월30일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amarok 3.0 "Castaway" released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971568/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971568/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T20:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Amarok music player project
has announced
the release of version 3.0, which is codenamed "Castaway".  It is the first
stable version using Qt 5 and KDE Frameworks 5, and the first stable
release since the final Qt-4-based 2.9.0 in 2018.

The road to 3.0 has not been a short one. Much of the Qt5/KF5 porting was done in 2015 already, but finishing and polishing everything up has been a slow, sometimes ongoing and sometimes stalled process ever since. 3.0 Alpha was released in February 2021 and has been since used by many people, as have been nightly builds of git master available for various distributions. Now in the past few months, an effort was made to get everything ready for a proper 3.0 release.

Common usecases should work quite well, and in addition to fixing KF5 port
related regressions reported in pre-releases, 3.0 features many bugfixes
and implemented features for longstanding issues, the oldest such
documented being from 2009. However, with more than 20 years of development
history, it is likely that not every feature Amarok has been tested
thoroughly in the new release, and specifically some Internet services that
have changed their API in recent years are not available, at least for
now. It might well be that getting them in better state wouldn't require
huge effort, however, so if you know your way with Qt and KDE Frameworks
and your favourite Internet music service does not work with Amarok 3.0,
you are extremely welcome to join in and help!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A leadership crisis in the Nix community]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/970824/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/970824/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T14:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On April 21, a group of anonymous authors and non-anonymous signatories published
a lengthy open letter to the

Nix community
and Nix founder Eelco Dolstra calling for his resignation from the project. They
claimed ongoing problems with the project's leadership, primarily focusing on the
way his actions have allegedly
undermined people nominally empowered to perform various
moderation and governance tasks. Since its release, the letter has gained
more than 100 signatures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971487/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971487/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (buildah, go-toolset:rhel8, golang, java-11-openjdk, java-21-openjdk, libreswan, thunderbird, and tigervnc), Debian (chromium, emacs, frr, mediawiki, ruby-rack, trafficserver, and zabbix), Fedora (chromium, grub2, python-idna, and python-reportlab), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, firefox, opencryptoki, and thunderbird), Red Hat (container-tools:4.0, container-tools:rhel8, git-lfs, and shim), SUSE (frr, java-11-openjdk, java-1_8_0-openjdk, kernel, pdns-recursor, and shim), and Ubuntu (apache2, cpio, curl, glibc, gnutls28, less, libvirt, and pillow).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McQueen: Update from the GNOME board]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971436/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971436/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:17:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robert McQueen has posted a message
from the GNOME Foundation board describing the current financial
situation, plans to improve it, and an increase in the size of the board.


	The Foundation has a reserves policy which specifies a minimum
	amount of money we have to keep in our accounts. This is so that if
	there is a significant interruption to our usual income, we can
	preserve our core operations while we work on new funding
	sources. We've now "hit the buffers" of this reserves policy,
	meaning the Board can't approve any more deficit budgets – to keep
	spending at the same level we must increase our income.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turn It On Again: Modeling Power MOSFET Turn-On Dependence on Source Inductance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1661.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1661.php"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T10:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a short article explaining how to analyze part of the behavior of a power MOSFET during turn-on, and how it is influenced by the parasitic inductance at the source terminal. Parasitic inductance is not a good thing — the word parasite in biology refers to an external thing that feeds off a host organism; while <a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New with ESP ZeroCode]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1199e0c577fc</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/whats-new-with-esp-zerocode-1199e0c577fc?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T09:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Sovani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install single node OpenShift on bare metal]]></title>
        <id>be6d693a-0df4-4f38-b54c-2defb39e727d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/29/how-install-single-node-openshift-bare-metal"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the second installment of this series where we delve into the world of computer vision at the edge. Throughout this and the following episodes, we will explore the process of setting up all the infrastructure to develop and train AI/ML models and deploy them at the edge to perform real-time inference. This series will cover the following topics:

How to install single node OpenShift on AWS
How to install single node OpenShift on bare metal
Red Hat OpenShift AI set up
Model training in Red Hat OpenShift AI
Custom dataset preparation with Label Studio
Safari application deployment on MicroShift  

The goal of this series is to make use of the power and versatility of Red Hat OpenShift for the preparation and deployment of computer vision applications on the edge. In environments w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Alvarez Ponce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install single node OpenShift on AWS]]></title>
        <id>0f274513-5cd2-45b1-ad0f-9e6b7de4fcee</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/29/how-install-single-node-openshift-aws"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first chapter of this blog series where we delve into the world of computer vision at the edge. Throughout this and the following installments, we will explore the process of setting up all the infrastructure to develop and train AI/ML models and deploy them at the edge to perform real-time inference. This series will cover the following topics:

How to install single node OpenShift on AWS
How to install single node OpenShift on bare metal
Red Hat OpenShift AI set up
Model training in Red Hat OpenShift AI
Custom dataset preparation with Label Studio
Safari application deployment on MicroShift

The goal of this series is to make use of the power and versatility of Red Hat OpenShift for the preparation and deployment of computer vision applications at the edge. In environments…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Alvarez Ponce</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nuvoton adds MPUs for industrial edge and entry-level MCUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482159</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nuvoton-adds-mpus-for-industrial-edge-and-entry-level-mcus/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T02:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NuMicro MA35D0 series MPU targets smart infrastructure and manufacturing automation, while the M433 CAN/USB FS series MCUs are optimized specifically for industrial control and battery management systems.
The post Nuvoton adds MPUs for industrial edge and entry-level MCUs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기후변화로 인한 ‘변화’가 이 정도였어? 뜻밖의 결과들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79227</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/04/28/npsp_climatechangeimpact/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_climatechangeimpact"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T01:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기후변화로 인한 이상 기후, 자연 재해는 우리에게 더는 낯선 일이 아닙니다. 아예 “기후 재해”라는 말이 있을 정도죠. 그런데 맹렬한 기세로 타는 산불, 잦아진 태풍이나 폭우, 해수면 상승으로 인한 물난리, 혹은 폭염이나 혹한처럼 당장의 피해가 눈에 잘 띄는 문제들이 우리의 관심을 끄는 사이 눈에 잘 띄지는 않지만, 장기적으로, 점진적으로는 어쩌면 더 큰 문제를 일으키는 변화들이 있습니다. 심지어 한둘이 아니라 수많은 분야에서 그러한 이른바 “비재난적 피해”를 찾을 수 있습니다. 환경 및 노동경제학을 연구하는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.9-rc6]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/971414/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/971414/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T22:17:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9-rc6 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	Things continue to look pretty normal, and nothing here really
	stands out. The biggest single change that stands out in the
	diffstat is literally a documentation update, everything else looks
	pretty small and spread out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동아일보 김순덕이 “대통령이 ‘김치찌개’ 소리 할 때마다 슬프다”고 한 이유: 슬로우레터 4월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=107928</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/107928"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T22:03:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 만남에 남은 3년이 걸렸다. 윤석열에게는 내놓을 카드가 없다. 이재명의 25만 원 프로젝트 통할까. 쟁점과 현안. 성장률 급등? 한은도 깜짝 놀랐다. 연체율 급증, 글로벌 금융위기 수준. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘파괴왕 윤석열’의 파괴 목록, 11번째는? 옥수수 대신 반도체를 심자. 다르게 읽기. 시민 대표단에게 잘못된 자료가 전달됐다. 민희진 기자회견이 폭로하는 언론의 파산. 오늘의 TMI. 비급여 진료비 32조...
The post 동아일보 김순덕이 “대통령이 ‘김치찌개’ 소리 할 때마다 슬프다”고 한 이유: 슬로우레터 4월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinchilla Scaling: A replication using the pdf]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8729</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/04/28/chinchilla-scaling-a-replication-using-the-pdf/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T21:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paper Chinchilla Scaling: A replication attempt by Besiroglu, Erdil, Barnett, and You caught my attention. Not only a replication, but on the first page there is the enticing heading of section 2, “Extracting data from Hoffmann et al.’s Figure 4”. Long time readers will know of my interest in extracting data from pdfs and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linear Feedback Shift Registers for the Uninitiated]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1309.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1309.php"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T13:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2017 and 2018 I wrote an eighteen-part series of articles about linear feedback shift registers, or LFSRs:


    div.jms-article-content ol > li {
        list-style-type: upper-roman
    }



Ex-Pralite Monks and Finite Fields, in which we describe what an LFSR is as a digital circuit; its cyclic behavior over time; the definition of groups, rings, and fields; the isomorphism...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synopsys collaborates with TSMC on 2nm IP portfolio and photonics ICs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482152</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/synopsys-collaborates-with-tsmc-on-2nm-ip-portfolio-and-photonics-ics/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T13:34:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synopsys announces collaboration with TSMC on AI-driven design flows, silicon photonics IC integration, and IP portfolio for TSMC 2nm technology.
The post Synopsys collaborates with TSMC on 2nm IP portfolio and photonics ICs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>