<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-01T20:20:13.461Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a heavy user of Twitter over the last decade, and while
      Musk's purchase of Twitter hasn't got me running for the exit, it has
      prompted me to take a look at possible alternatives should Twitter change
      into something no longer worthwhile for me. The obvious alternative is for
      me to explore the fediverse with a Mastodon account. As I explore using
      Mastodon, I'll make some notes here so that others can learn from my
      explorations.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSL 3.0.7 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913370/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913370/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T16:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated OpenSSL 3.0.7 release, which fixes some high-risk
security problems, is available.  The release
notes list two vulnerabilities (CVE-2022-3786 and CVE-2022-3602) that
have not yet been documented on the OpenSSL
vulnerabilities page.  LWN commenter mat2 has provided the relevant information, though.  It
is worth updating quickly, but many sites do not appear to be at immediate
risk.

Update: the associated security
advisory is now available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913352/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913352/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T14:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (python3.7), Gentoo (android-tools, expat, firefox, libjxl, libxml2, pjproject, sqlite, thunderbird, and zlib), Oracle (compat-expat1), Slackware (php8 and vim), SUSE (kernel, libtasn1, podman, and pyenv), and Ubuntu (libtasn1-6).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perygee is bringing no-code ease to OT cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11263</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/perygee-is-bringing-no-code-ease-to-ot-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published on Friday Oct. 28, 2022 in my weekly IoT newsletter.  This week, a three-year-old security startup called Perygee raised $4.75 million from investors that include some significant names in cybersecurity. The company says it has created a no-code cybersecurity platform that brings in data from devices on a network and marries that […]
The post Perygee is bringing no-code ease to OT cybersecurity appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loading Multiple (Binary) Files with GDB]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=35641</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/11/01/loading-multiple-binary-files-with-gdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T11:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A typical debugging session involves just one ELF/Dwarf binary or executable. But what if I need to program multiple binary files with gdb? Things like loading both the bootloader and the application binary? Or I have a an on-chip file … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[망사용료 주장의 9가지 약점 (ft. 영국 오프콤 보고서)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87399</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87399"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T10:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[망사용료법(전기통신사업법 개정안)은 합리적인 정책인가. 망사용료법은 일반 이용자를 위한 법안인가 아니면 망사업자를 위한 법안인가. 정치권에서 추진 중인 망사용료법에 관한 판단에 참고가 될 영국 오프콤 보고서가 지난 10월 24일 발표됐다. 오프콤 보고서의 내용을 확인하기 전에 우선 몇 가지 용어와 개념을 짚고 넘어가자. 1. 오프콤 » 방송통신위원회 오프콤(Ofcom)은 영국의 방송통신규제기구다. 정식 명칭은 커뮤니케이션청(Office of Communications)이다. 영국의 방송, […]
The post 망사용료 주장의 9가지 약점 (ft. 영국 오프콤 보고서) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트위터 인수는 일론 머스크와 트위터 모두에게 하방 위험이다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588198</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588198/%ed%8a%b8%ec%9c%84%ed%84%b0-%ec%9d%b8%ec%88%98-%ec%9c%84%ed%97%98"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T07:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Kamelets simplify Camel integrations on Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>21c2c77b-e4dc-4e1e-a818-58d4aee3d5bf</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/01/how-kamelets-simplify-camel-integrations-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern applications, rarely coded from scratch, are formed by combining software components (known as subsystems) into a single system. This process is called integration. Typical subsystems include databases and web services. This article explains how Apache Camel and Kubernetes support easy integration of such services through Kamelets.
How Kamelets make Camel integration easy
Apache Camel is a popular open source integration framework based on known Enterprise Integration Patterns (EIPs). Camel is a complete, production-ready framework with a built-in set of patterns you can use in your integration flows. These patterns are based on design patterns and help connect different systems.
Developers build many frameworks on Apache Camel. This article focuses on Camel K, but several other fra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammadi Iram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring the Steps to Design Checkoff]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/formal/2022/11/01/design-checkoff.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/formal/2022/11/01/design-checkoff.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve recently had the opportunity to rebuild a NAND flash
controller for Arasan Chip
Systems, Inc.
The purpose of this redesign was to upgrade an existing flash controller
so that it can process flash requests and commands at even faster speeds than
ever before.  Indeed, this new controller is designed to handle flash chips
that operate at speeds of up to 1.6GB/s while being backwards compatible with
all previous speeds.  Those who know my typical design goals will already
know my personal goals for this design: throughput, throughput, throughput!
What I wanted to discuss today, however, was a basic management problem I
came across while working on this project.  At one time, during development,
I was asked by Arasan’s management team where I
was at in the project, and how much longer the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 252 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913287/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913287/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T22:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd version 252 has been released.  As usual, the list of changes is
long.  It includes a new systemd-measure tool for the calculation of PCR
values and a bunch of infrastructure to use the result for disk encryption:


	Net effect: if you boot a properly prepared kernel, TPM-bound disk
        encryption now defaults to be locked to kernels which carry PCR
          signatures from the same key pair. Example: if a hypothetical distro
          FooOS prepares its UKIs like this, TPM-based disk encryption is now –
          by default – bound to only FooOS kernels, and encrypted volumes bound
          to the TPM cannot be unlocked on kernels from other sources.


There's a lot more; see the announcement for all of the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lifetime extension of temporary objects in C++: common recommendations and pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1006/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1006/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After reading this article, you will learn the following: ways to extend the lifetime of a temporary object in C++, various tips and tricks; pitfalls of the lifetime extension that a C++ programmer may face, and that I have already faced myself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Still waiting for stackable security modules]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912775/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912775/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T18:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux security module (LSM) mechanism was created as a result of the first Kernel Summit in 2001; it was
designed to allow the development of multiple approaches to Linux security.
That goal has been met; there are several security modules available with
current kernels.  The LSM subsystem was not designed, though, to allow
multiple security modules to work together on the same system.  Developers
have been working to rectify that problem almost since the LSM subsystem
was merged, but with limited success; some small security modules can be
stacked on top of the "major" ones, but arbitrary stacking is not possible.
Now, a full 20 years after
security-module support went into the 2.5 development kernel series, it
looks like a solution to the stacking problem may finally be getting
closer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Matter handle IoT device security?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11252</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-does-matter-handle-iot-device-security/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T18:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a question from our Voicemail hotline from Greg. He’s asking how Matter handles IoT device security, which is a great question. It’s also a timely one as we expect to see Matter-certified device availability soon. And thankfully, the Matter specification does provide universal, robust security […]
The post How does Matter handle IoT device security? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913261/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913261/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T17:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (batik, chromium, expat, libxml2, ncurses, openvswitch, pysha3, python-django, thunderbird, and tomcat9), Fedora (cacti, cacti-spine, curl, mbedtls, mingw-expat, and xen), Gentoo (apptainer, bind, chromium, exif, freerdp, gdal, gitea, hiredis, jackson-databind, jhead, libgcrypt, libksba, libtirpc, lighttpd, net-snmp, nicotine+, open-vm-tools, openexr, rpm, schroot, shadow, sofia-sip, tiff, and xorg-server), Mageia (libreoffice), Oracle (expat), Red Hat (device-mapper-multipath), and SUSE (cacti, cacti-spine, chromium, exim, jhead, kernel, libmad, opera, and pdns-recursor).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart cities should focus on sustainability not safety]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11260</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/smart-cities-should-focus-on-sustainability-not-safety/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T15:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published on Friday Oct. 28, 2022 in my weekly IoT newsletter.  Cities adopt technology for two primary reasons: safety and cost savings. Both of these are driven by a need to please constituents who want lower taxes and the perception of safer streets. Thus, we’ve seen cities adopt LED lighting to […]
The post Smart cities should focus on sustainability not safety appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU Make 4.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913253/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913253/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T15:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.4 of the GNU make utility is out.  There is a long list of
changes and a fair number of potential compatibility issues; see the
announcement text for all the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top smart home trends plus: is Matter the key to interoperability?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477042</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/top-smart-home-trends-plus-is-matter-the-key-to-interoperability/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T14:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinciding with the launch of Matter and World Smart Home Day 2022, engineers from ByteSnap Design highlight trends to watch in smart homes, including the rise of Matter, homes powering the move to off-grid, and consumption dictated by energy suppliers.
The post Top smart home trends plus: is Matter the key to interoperability? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partnership looks at embedding quantum computing in classical]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477037</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/partnership-looks-at-embedding-quantum-computing-in-classical/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T14:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of German Aerospace Center’s quantum computing initiative, partnering companies will pool expertise from across industry to enable rapid advances in quantum computing and help roll out scalable and marketable solutions.
The post Partnership looks at embedding quantum computing in classical appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C to C++: 3 Reasons to Migrate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1478.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1478.php"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T13:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve recently written several blogs that have set the stage with a simple premise: The C programming language no longer provides embedded software developers the tools they need to develop embedded software throughout the full software stack. Now, don’t get me wrong, C is a powerhouse, with over 80% of developers still using it; however, as embedded systems have reached unprecedented...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you need living documentation for software projects (and how to do it)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/why-need-living-documentationsoftware-projects-how-to-do-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/why-need-living-documentationsoftware-projects-how-to-do-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T11:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation is often the most neglected area of software projects. It can be time-consuming and sometimes tedious, and keeping on top […]
The post Why you need living documentation for software projects (and how to do it) appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jane Orme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[48. X-윈도우와 Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://joone.net/?p=4342</id>
        <link href="https://joone.net/2022/10/31/48-x-%ec%9c%88%eb%8f%84%ec%9a%b0%ec%99%80-wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T08:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[실리콘 그래픽스 GLX와 OpenGL 개발 실리콘 그래픽스는 3D 그래픽에 특화된 워크스테이션 제조사로서 1980년대 부터 2000년대 초반까지 쥬라기 공원, 터미네이터2와 같은 영화 제작, 캐드 등 전문 분야에서 많이 사용되었다. 실리콘 그래픽스는 당시 IRIX라는 유닉스 계열 운영체제를 갖고 있었는데, Unix System V에 BSD 확장을 기반으로 개발되었다. 1991년 IRIX4.0을 발표하면서 X 윈도우를 도입했고, 3D 그래픽스가 가능하도록 GLX라는 X […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>joone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 플렉세라 보고서: 클라우드 동향과 시사점]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87378</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87378"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:37:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[플렉세라(Flexera)는 주로 IT 운영과 관련된 기업 맞춤형 컨설팅 및 서비스를 제공하는 회사로, 매년 클라우드 동향 조사 보고서를 발간하고 있다. 보고서 개요  2022년에도 총 753명의 기술 및 사업을 담당하는 전문가를 통해 클라우드 활용 현황과 향후 전략에 대한 조사를 벌였다. 조사 대상 기업의 규모도 1만 명 이상 직원을 둔 대기업부터 100명 이하의 소기업까지 다양하며, […]
The post 2022 플렉세라 보고서: 클라우드 동향과 시사점 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices for application shutdown with OpenSSL]]></title>
        <id>043f762e-53b8-4d20-b470-c1a30f2f3b5a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/31/best-practices-application-shutdown-openssl"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSL is an essential library for securing web traffic. This article offers simple procedures for initializing and terminating applications using OpenSSL. Modern applications that are more complex than "Hello, world!" usually require several external libraries like OpenSSL, which in turn often need to be properly initialized on startup and deinitialized on shutdown.
OpenSSL libraries are set up internally during program initialization. At this time, they load the configuration file, allocate resources, and handle FIPS mode, among many other tasks.
The OpenSSL API function for initialization is OPENSSL_init_crypto. This function accepts a variety of options with reasonable defaults. Initialization should be performed before any other OpenSSL function is used, though some OpenSSL functions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Belyavskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[크레딕트 스위스 2022년 글로벌 자산 보고서에서 읽는 투자 전략]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588192</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588192/2022%eb%85%84-%ea%b8%80%eb%a1%9c%eb%b2%8c-%ec%9e%90%ec%82%b0-%eb%b3%b4%ea%b3%a0%ec%84%9c-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%8b%9c%ec%82%ac%ec%a0%90"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T04:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[상관주의 혹은 초월론(transcendentalism)의 모순]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222915587684</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222915587684"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T03:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[메이야수에 의하면, 선조적 진술의 실재적 의미가 궁극적 의미이다. 그런데 상관주의는 이 주장을 받아들일 수 없다. 그것은 상관주의가 <소여에 선행하는 존재의 소여>를 인정하지 않기 때문이다. 메이야수는 <소여, 혹은 현시(manifestation)에 선행하는 존재의 소여>라는 표현을 사용하고 있는데, 나는 이런 수사적 표현이 진짜 싫다. 존재 혹은 실재가 소여되었다. 이때 소여된 것은 존재적 의미 혹은 메이야수의 주장처럼 선조적 의미에서 소여이다. 반면에 상관주의가 주장하는 소여는 인식적 소여이다. 우리 마음이나 사유가 존재하지 않는다면, 인식적 소여는 주어지지 않는다. 그의 지적처럼 <시간 자체는 인간과 세계의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 인텔 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 두려워했던 것보다 낫다, 장기적으로 파운드리 경쟁력을 갖출 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588183</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588183/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%94-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T00:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.1-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913122/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913122/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T00:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.1-rc3 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	So while rc2 was just _way_ bigger than usual, rc3 is only a bit
	larger than an average rc3 release is. But it's still on the
	largish side. I hope that things start calming down, and we'll
	start seeing the size of these rc's shrink. Please?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A study of deceit when reporting information in a known context]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7194</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/10/30/a-study-of-deceit-when-reporting-information-in-a-known-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T23:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A variety of conflicting factors intrude when attempting to form an impartial estimate of the resources needed to perform a task. The customer/manager, asking for the estimate wants to hear a low value, creating business/social pressure to underestimate; overestimating increases the likelihood of completing the task within budget. A study by Oey, Schachner and Vul […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 비행 에티켓 (2022년 판)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75514</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/30/npc_flyingetiquette/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_flyingetiquette"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T22:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난주 여름 일정을 마치고 런던에서 뉴욕으로 돌아오는 비행기 안에서 일어난 일입니다. 제 뒷자리에 앉은 승객이 비행 내내 제 의자를 발로 툭툭 차고, 의자 너머로 다리를 뻗으려다 제 팔을 자꾸 쳤습니다. 녹음해둔 팟캐스트 편집하려고 소음 차단 헤드폰을 꼈는데도 희미하게 떠드는 소리가 들릴 만큼 옆 사람과 나누는 대화의 데시벨도 컸습니다. 참다못해 잔뜩 찌푸린 표정으로 뒤돌아서 조용히 하고 발도 그만 차 달라고 말했습니다. 마뜩잖은 표정으로 알았다고 답했지만, 10분쯤 지났을까요? 발차기와 시끄러운 대화는 다시 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 애플 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588181</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588181/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T11:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[브라이도티의 반휴머니즘]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222914622845</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222914622845"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T03:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 나는 휴머니즘이나 그것이 암암리에 옹호하는 인간/휴먼 개념을 그다지 좋아하지 않는다. 반휴머니즘은 내 가족의 배경과 나의 지적, 개인적 계보의 많은 부분을 차지하고 있다. 그래서 나에게 휴머니즘의 위기는 진부하기까지 한 이야기다. ... 내가 유럽중심적이고 제국주의적인 경향을 지닌 휴머니즘의 역사적 쇠락이라는 개념을 반기는 이유는 주로 정치적이고 철학적인 이유에 근거한다. 물론, 역사적 맥락도 관련이 많다. 나는 제2차 세계대전 이후 격랑기에 지적으로 정치적으로 성인이 되었고, 이때는 휴머니즘적 이상이 근본에서부터 문제가 된 시기다. 1960년대와 1970년대 내내 페미니즘, 탈식민주의와 반인종주의, 반핵운동과 평.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912992/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912992/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.10.151 kernel was released on
October 28 with a small fix to the PAHOLE_FLAGS in the kernel
build.  October 29 saw the release of the 6.0.6, 5.15.76, and 
5.4.221 stable kernels, each with the usual
collection of important fixes throughout the tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 아마존 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 23년 본 궤도를 회복할 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588170</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588170/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T10:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알도 레오폴드의 <모래 군의 열두 달> 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222913853680</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222913853680"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T02:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 군청 장부에는 이 방목지가 당신 것으로 적혀 있는지 모르겠지만, 긴꼬리물떼새 녀석은 그런 사소한 법적 사항 따위는 가볍게 웃어넘긴다. 녀석은 인디언 시대부터 소유해온 자신의 권리를 거듭 주장하기 위해 아르헨티나에서부터 4천 마일을 날아 이제 막 돌아왔다. 그리고 새끼들이 날 수 있을 때까지 이 방목지는 녀석의 것이며, 어느 누구도 녀석의 저항 없이 이 곳을 통과할 수는 없다. (2) 선선한 팔월 밤, 다시 한 번 미주 대륙이 예로부터 하나였음을 증명하기 위해 긴꼬리물떼새가, 남미 팜파 초원을 향해 날개를 펼 때, 우리는 놈들의 휘파람 신호소리를 들을 수 있다. 남과 북의 연대가 정치인들에게는 새롭겠지만, 이 날개 달린.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477025</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-steps-to-designing-an-embedded-software-architecture-step-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T22:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores the fourth step to designing an embedded software architecture: defining task components and their interfaces. The last three articles have explored the...
The post 5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 4 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic associated types in Rust 1.65]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912932/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912932/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T20:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust Types Team announces
that the long-awaited generic associated types feature will be stable in Rust 1.65.


	At its core, generic associated types allow you to have generics
	(type, lifetime, or const) on associated types. Note that this is
	really just rounding out the places where you can put generics: for
	example, you can already have generics on freestanding type aliases
	and on functions in traits. Now you can just have generics on type
	aliases in traits (which we just call associated types).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Oct. 28, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11268</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-oct-28-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T15:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LoRa networks for private messages? Although this article doesn’t get into actual implementation, I’m surfacing it because I think the idea is spot-on. In fact, when Amazon’s Sidewalk network was introduced in 2019, I suggested the use of LoRa networks for a private messaging service. By using LoRa instead of cellular or Wi-Fi, you’d have end-to-end […]
The post IoT news of the week for Oct. 28, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Packaging Rust for Fedora]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912202/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912202/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T15:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux distributions were, as a general rule, designed during an era when
most software of interest was written in C; as a result, distributions
are naturally able to efficiently package C applications and the libraries
they depend on.  Modern languages, though, tend to be built around their
own package-management systems that are designed with different goals in
mind.  The result is that, for years, distributors have struggled to find
the best ways to package and ship applications written in those languages.
A recent discussion in the Fedora community on the packaging of Rust
applications shows that the problems have not yet all been solved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: Synaptics buys Emza, 6G RIS trials, plus more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477028</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-synaptics-buys-emza-6g-ris-trials-plus-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s embedded news features various announcements including Synaptics’ acquisition of Emza Visual Sense, various announcements from Cadence, Siemens, and Synopsys, plus Rohde & Schwarz’s evaluation and trial of RIS for 6G, and more.
The post embedded news: Synaptics buys Emza, 6G RIS trials, plus more appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912873/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912873/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T13:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (expat, ruby-sinatra, and thunderbird), Fedora (glances), Mageia (cups, firefox, git, heimdal, http-parser, krb5-appl, minidlna, nginx, and thunderbird), Oracle (389-ds:1.4, device-mapper-multipath, firefox, mysql:8.0, postgresql:12, and thunderbird), SUSE (dbus-1, libconfuse0, libtasn1, openjpeg2, qemu, and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (dbus, linux-azure-fde, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MS의 B2B 전략 ‘초자동화 통한 생산성의 극대화’ (이그나이트 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87361</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87361"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T09:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마이크로소프트는 매년 세 가지의 가장 크고도 중요 이벤트를 개최한다. 채널 파트너들을 위한 인스파이어(Inspire)와 개발자를 위한 빌드(Build)와 함께 이 모두를 포함하는 최종 사용자를 위한 이그나이트(Ignite)와 함께 매년 개최한다. 그 이유로 이그나이트는 마이크로소프트의 제품 전략과 로드맵을 볼 수 있기에 특히 기업에서 차기 비즈니스 전략을 준비하는 중요 정보로 사용할 수 있다. 올해는 10월 12일에서 14일까지 사흘간 진행되었으며, 100개가 […]
The post MS의 B2B 전략 ‘초자동화 통한 생산성의 극대화’ (이그나이트 2022) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반도체 장비주 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 수요 감소와 중국 악재를 반영한 바닥이 가까워지고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588164</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588164/%eb%b0%98%eb%8f%84%ec%b2%b4-%ec%9e%a5%eb%b9%84%ec%a3%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T08:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 반도체 기업인 텍사스 인스트루먼트 실적을 보는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588161</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588161/%ed%85%8d%ec%82%ac%ec%8a%a4-%ec%9d%b8%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%a3%a8%eb%a8%bc%ed%8a%b8-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T05:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 메타 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 긍정적인 기존 비즈니스, 23년 투자는 지나친 수준]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588149</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588149/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T02:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 리즈 체니의 정치 인생]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75499</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/27/npc_lizcheney/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_lizcheney"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한때 원내 공화당 3인자이자 3선 하원의원이었지만, 지난 대선에서 트럼프가 진 게 맞다며 선거 불복을 내세운 트럼프에 반기를 들다가 당내에서 배척당한 리즈 체니 하원의원이 와이오밍주 공화당 경선에서 패배했습니다. 체니를 누르고 경선에서 승리한 이는 트럼프의 지지를 받은 해리엇 헤이그먼으로, 공화당 지지율이 높은 와이오밍주인 만큼 무난히 하원에 입성할 것으로 예상됩니다. 이번 중간선거에서 트럼프가 지지 선언을 남발하는 것이 겉으로 드러나는 자신의 영향력을 부풀리려는 시도라는 지적도 있지만, 어쨌든 이번 경선 결과는 공화당의 권력을 장악하고 있는 건 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Fedora 37 release-date slip]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912776/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912776/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T22:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora releases have traditionally happened later than their target date,
though the project has done better on that score in recent years.  Ben
Cotton has announced in
Fedora Magazine that the upcoming Fedora 37 release, initially planned
for October 25, won't be happening until November 15.  The
immediate cause is an
impending OpenSSL update which fixes a vulnerability described as
"critical".


	Ironically, Fedora’s openness means we can’t start preparing ahead
	of time. All of our build pipelines and artifacts are open. If we
	were to start building updates, this would disclose the
	vulnerability before the embargo lifts. As a result, we only know
	that OpenSSL considers this the highest level of severity and Red
	Hat’s Product Security team strongly recommended we wait for a fix
	before releasing Fedora Linux 37.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we were looking for a bug in PVS-Studio or 278 GB of log files]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1005/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1005/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here is an interesting story of how our team were looking for a bug in the PVS-Studio analyzer. Well, we make mistakes too. However, we are ready to roll up our sleeves and dive deep into the rabbit hole.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RC4 Is Still Considered Harmful]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/10/rc4-is-still-considered-harmful.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/10/rc4-is-still-considered-harmful.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T19:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By James Forshaw, Project Zero

I've been spending a lot of time researching Windows authentication implementations, specifically Kerberos. In June 2022 I found an interesting issue number 2310 with the handling of RC4 encryption that allowed you to authenticate as another user if you could either interpose on the Kerberos network traffic to and from the KDC or directly if the user was configured to disable typical pre-authentication requirements.

This blog post goes into more detail on how this vulnerability works and how I was able to exploit it with only a bare minimum of brute forcing required. Note, I'm not going to spend time fully explaining how Kerberos authentication works, there's plenty of resources online. For example this blog post by Steve Syfuhs who works at Microsoft is a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Copyright notices (or the lack thereof) in kernel code]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912355/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912355/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T15:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The practice of requiring copyright assignments for contributions to
free-software projects has been in decline for years; the GNU Binutils
project may be the
latest domino to fall in that regard.  The Linux kernel project,
unlike some others, has always allowed contributors to retain their copyrights,
resulting in a code base that has widely distributed ownership.  In such a
project, who owns the copyright to a given piece of code is not always
obvious. Some
developers (or their employers) are insistent about the placement of
copyright notices in the code to document their ownership of parts of the
kernel.  A series of recent discussions within the Btrfs subsystem, though,
has made it clear that there is no project-wide policy on when these
notices are warranted — or even acceptable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern PHP features explained - PHP 8.0 and 8.1 (Laravel News)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912725/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912725/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T15:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
Laravel News article digs into the many enhancements that have found
their way into the PHP language in the last couple of years or so.


	Lovely Enums, the savior of pointless database tables and floating
	constants across the codebases of the world. Enums have quickly
	become one of my favorite features of PHP 8.1 - I can now push my
	roles into Enums instead of keeping them in a table that never
	changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interview with Doug Duhaime, contributor to Google's Dev Library]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/interview-with-doug-duhaime-contributor-to-google-dev-library.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/interview-with-doug-duhaime-contributor-to-google-dev-library.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by the Google Dev Library Team
    

 
Introducing the Dev Library Contributor Spotlights - a blog series highlighting developers that are supporting the thriving development ecosystem by contributing their resources and tools to Google Dev Library. 
We met with Doug Duhaime, Full Stack Developer in Yale University's Digital Humanities Lab, to discuss his passion for Machine Learning, his processes and what inspired him to release his PixPlot project as an Open Source. 
What led you to explore the field of machine learning? 
I was an English major in undergrad and in graduate school. I have a PhD in English literature. My dissertation was exploring copyright history and the ways that changes in copyright law affected the book market. How does the institution of fixed duration copyri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bos: Do we need a "Rust Standard"?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912704/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912704/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T14:54:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mara Bos has written a lengthy
blog post on whether the Rust language needs to be standardized.
The answer is "no" — but she draws a distinction between a "standard"
(maintained by some distant standards body) and a "specification".



	While no official decision has been made yet, there does seem to be
	a general agreement that we should indeed work towards having and
	maintaining an official complete Rust specification from within the
	Rust project. It’s just a lot of work, so I’m afraid we won’t get
	there with just some enthusiastic volunteers, even if we can use
	the Ferrocene specification as a start. We’ll need support and
	funding from the Rust Foundation and interested companies.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding cache placement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476956</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/understanding-cache-placement/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T14:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a memory system, memory access times are less when the data the processor needs are nearer to it. But how does this happen? In...
The post Understanding cache placement appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krishnakanth Katteri Mahadeva Murthy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912688/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912688/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (389-ds-base, bind, expat, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, libksba, and squid), Debian (chromium, libdatetime-timezone-perl, tzdata, and wordpress), Fedora (dbus, dhcp, dotnet3.1, jhead, samba, and strongswan), Mageia (virtualbox), Oracle (device-mapper-multipath), Scientific Linux (device-mapper-multipath and thunderbird), Slackware (curl), SUSE (container-suseconnect, curl, kernel, libmad, libtasn1, libtirpc, qemu, rubygem-puppet, SUSE Manager Client Tools, and telnet), and Ubuntu (curl, linux-intel-iotg, and mysql-5.7).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: I’m running Matter. Now what?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11246</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-im-running-matter-now-what/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We kick off the podcast with more conversation about the planned White House-led cybersecurity label for consumer IoT devices. Contrary to what I wrote last week, it seems that privacy won’t be as big of a focus, which is disappointing. Then we move into a bunch of updated product news, such as the launch of […]
The post Podcast: I’m running Matter. Now what? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[하이닉스 실적과 텍사스 인스트루먼트 실적에서 읽는 인사이트 by barron’s]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588147</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588147/%ed%95%98%ec%9d%b4%eb%8b%89%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%9d%b8%ec%82%ac%ec%9d%b4%ed%8a%b8"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T10:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 스포티파이 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각, 꾸준한 투자는 23년 빛을 보지 않을까]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588142</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588142/222%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%8a%a4%ed%8f%ac%ed%8b%b0%ed%8c%8c%ec%9d%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T09:03:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공공분양 50만호 공급계획: 세 가지 문제점]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87350</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87350"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T07:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“사는 곳이 곧 신분이 되는 현대판 주거 신분사회를 타파하고, 집 걱정 때문에 포기했던 꿈과 희망을 돌려드릴 수 있도록 모든 노력을 다해나가겠다” (원희룡 국토교통부 장관, 2022. 10. 26.) 오늘 정부가 ‘청년·서민 주거안정을 위한 공공분양 주택 50만호 공급계획’을 발표했다. 윤석열 대통령의 대선공약이었던 청년원가주택, 역세권 첫집주택 등을 구체화한 것으로 향후 5년간 나눔형 25만호(시세 70% 이하 분양), 선택형 10만호(6년 […]
The post 공공분양 50만호 공급계획: 세 가지 문제점 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 실적 분석, 클라우드 비즈니스 성장세 둔화]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588140</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588140/%ed%81%b4%eb%9d%bc%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c-%eb%b9%84%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88%ec%8a%a4-%ec%84%b1%ec%9e%a5%ec%84%b8"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T05:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 마이크로소프트 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 일시적인 클라우드 성장 둔화와 강건한 펀더멘탈]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588135</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588135/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%9c%ec%86%8c%ed%94%84%ed%8a%b8-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T04:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인의(仁義)에 대한 도가의 비판]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222911982383</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222911982383"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T02:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유교, 유학, 유가를 비판하는 도가의 주장이 얼마나 타당한지 검토한 논문이 생각보다 별로 없는 것처럼 보인다. 더 찾아보아야 하겠지만, 임헌규의 논문 두 편이 있다. 한 논문은 유가에 대한 노자의 비판, 즉 인의(仁義)가 인위적 외적 강제라고 주장하지만, 그것에 대한 논거가 없다고 지적하고 있다. 오히려 이 점에서 유가가 도가보다 더 엄밀한 인성론을 가지고 있다. 반면 다른 논문은 노자의 <죽간본>에는 인의(仁義)에 대한 비판이 없기에, 유가에 대한 비판은 나중에 덧붙여진 것이라고 주장한다. 나아가 노자와 유가의 입장이 서로 부합한다. 노자(老子)가 유가의 인의예지(仁義禮智)를 비판하는 것은 그것이 강제적이며 자연적.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 알파벳 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선,광고가 아닌 비용절감에서 길을 찾다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588130</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588130/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%8c%ed%8c%8c%eb%b2%b3-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T02:46:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 27, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911875/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911875/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 27, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Office hours and the LLVM community calendar.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2022-10-27-office-hours/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2022-10-27-office-hours/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About a thousand people contribute code to LLVM each year. There are probablymany thousands who work on the LLVM code base in downstream projects. And evenmore people use the LLVM libraries to build other cool projects on top of.
The many LLVM users and contributors have long been communicating with eachother using mailing lists, bugzilla, and more recently,Discourse and githubissues. Next to theseasynchronous communication channels, the LLVM community has also long had moresynchronous communication channels, such asIRC andDiscord. Twice per year, there is the opportunityto communicate synchronously face-to-face with other LLVM-ers from around theworld: at the LLVM developer meetings. The LLVMsocials that happen in various places aroundthe world also provide the opportunity to meet face-to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The LLVM Project Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 패션과 철학]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75494</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/26/npc_fashion/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_fashion"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T22:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[패션은 사람이 살아가는 데 필수적인 3가지 요소를 말하는 의식주 중 첫 번째를 차지합니다. 누군가 멋진 옷을 입고 달라 보일 때 우리는 옷이 날개라고 말하지요. 선녀의 날개옷 만큼은 아니라도 어떤 옷을 입느냐에 따라 사람들이 그를 다르게 대하는 것은 부정할 수 없는 사실입니다. 어떤 개념을 당위적으로 정의하는 것은 말장난에 그칠 때도 있지만 의외로 심오한 의미를 줄 때도 있습니다. 예를 들어 정리(整理)란 있어야 할 것을 있어야 할 곳에 두는 것이라는 식이죠. 좋은 글은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FileChooser Dialog 크기 설정하기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/size-config-for-filechooser-dialog/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/size-config-for-filechooser-dialog/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T22:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[파일을 선택해야 할 때 나오는 다이얼로그 크기가 제각각에 너무 작게 나와서 어떻게 변경하는지 찾아 정리했다. VLC는 QT고 Chrome은 gtk…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] An ordered set for Python?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912353/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912353/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T19:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python has lots of different options for mutable data structures, both
directly in 
the language and in the standard library. Lists, dictionaries (or "dicts"), and
sets are the foundation, but two of those maintain an order based on how
the elements are added, while sets do not.  A recent discussion on the Python Discourse forum raised the
idea of adding an ordered variant of sets; while it does not look like
there is a big push to add the feature, the discussion did show some of
what is generally needed to get new things into the language—and could well
lead to its inclusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Netfilter Workshop 2022 summary]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912540/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912540/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arturo Borrero González has posted a detailed
summary of the Netfilter workshop that was recently held in Seville.
"This year, the number of participants was just eight people, and this
allowed the setup to be a bit more informal. We had kind of an
un-conference style meeting, in which whoever had something prepared just
went ahead and opened a topic for debate."

(Thanks to Paul Wise).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get to know Google’s Coding Competitions]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/get-to-know-googles-coding-competitions.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/get-to-know-googles-coding-competitions.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Julia DeLorenzo, Program Manager, Coding Competitions
   
 
 
Google’s Coding Competitions provide interactive rounds throughout the year to help you grow your skills, challenge yourself, and connect with developers from around the globe. 
Google has three flagship Coding Competitions: Code Jam, Hash Code, and Kick Start. Each competition is unique and offers different types of challenges from algorithmic puzzles to team-based optimization problems. Our Coding Competitions are designed and tested by a team of Google engineers and program managers who craft new and engaging problems for users to tackle. 
Google’s Coding Competitions have been around for quite a while (two decades!) and this passionate group of contributors and fans around the world makes each new season even more …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pile of stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912498/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912498/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T14:16:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.0.4,
5.15.75,
5.10.150,
5.4.220,
4.19.262,
4.14.296, and
4.9.331
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains a relatively
large set of important fixes.  The 6.0.5
update followed about 90 seconds later with a couple of additional
small fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912495/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912495/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T14:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (tomcat9), Oracle (389-ds-base, device-mapper-multipath, firefox, git-lfs, gnutls, kernel, kernel-container, libksba, pki-core, samba, sqlite, and zlib), Red Hat (device-mapper-multipath, kernel, kpatch-patch, libksba, and thunderbird), Slackware (expat and samba), SUSE (bind, buildah, curl, firefox, golang-github-prometheus-node_exporter, grafana, icinga2, python-paramiko, python-waitress, SUSE Manager Client Tools, telnet, and xen), and Ubuntu (glibc, jinja2, libksba, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, and openvswitch).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to give guests control of smart devices in a vacation home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11232</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-give-guests-control-of-smart-devices-in-a-vacation-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a question from our Voicemail hotline from Alan about the connected devices in his vacation home. Alan has Apple HomeKit devices, as well as Samsung SmartThings, in a rental property he owns and he wants to give guests control over the smart products in it. […]
The post How to give guests control of smart devices in a vacation home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded RTOS and hypervisor put AUTOSAR on AURIX MCUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476922</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-rtos-and-hypervisor-put-autosar-on-aurix-mcus/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T12:46:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The EB tresos AutoCore OS and EB tresos embedded hypervisor enable OEMs and tier 1s to more easily develop and deploy automotive E/E architectures based on the AUTOSAR Classic standard.
The post Embedded RTOS and hypervisor put AUTOSAR on AURIX MCUs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Analog IP provides foundation blocks for IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476916</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/analog-ip-provides-foundation-blocks-for-iot/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T10:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six new analog IP blocks wrap round a developers’ choice of processor core and memory to provide all the vital analog functions required to interface between digital and analog.
The post Analog IP provides foundation blocks for IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Single domain controller unifies vehicle wireless connectivity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476906</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/single-domain-controller-unifies-vehicle-wireless-connectivity/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T09:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With wireless connectivity interfaces distributed among many different ECUs in a typical vehicle, this can create wireless coexistence challenges and presents growing security risks.
The post Single domain controller unifies vehicle wireless connectivity appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언론의 조건… 인간의 죽음보다 파리바게뜨 런던 1호점이 먼저였던 언론들]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87342</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87342"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T08:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10월 15일 오전 6시 20분께 경기 평택에 위치한 SPC그룹 계열사 SPL 빵반죽 공장에서 20대 노동자가 기계에 끼어 숨지는 사고가 발생했습니다. 끼임 사고는 기본 안전수칙 준수로 예방 가능한 재래형 사고라는 점에서 안타까움이 컸는데요. 사고 당일 아무런 설명도 하지 않은 SPC그룹이 사고 직후에도 공장 일부를 가동하고, 숨진 노동자 장례식장에 SPC프랜차이즈 파리바게뜨 빵을 보내는 등 부적절한 대응에 시민 […]
The post 언론의 조건… 인간의 죽음보다 파리바게뜨 런던 1호점이 먼저였던 언론들 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[해커 - 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 피상적 유사성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222910989458</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222910989458"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T03:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[해커는 <칸트와 비트겐슈타인 –선험론적 논증의 문제>(2013)에서 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 유사성에 대해서 다음 여섯 가지를 말하고 있다. 첫째, 메타 철학 혹은 철학관이다. 칸트와 비트겐슈타인은 다른 어떤 철학자들보다 철학의 본성과 지위에 대해서 관심을 기울인다. 그리고 그 둘은 철학이 과학과 다르다는 것, 철학은 과학과 연속적일 수 없다는 것을 주장한다. 철학은 이차적이며 반성적 활동이다. (특히 철학과 자연과학의 연속성에 대해서 반대하기 때문에, 철학과 자연과학의 연속성을 주장하는 자연주의 철학, 혹은 철학의 자연화 경향과 대립된다.) 둘째, 이성의 변증론, 즉 개념적 혼동의 논리에 칸트와 비트겐슈타인는 집중.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 구글 실적, 유튜브 역성장으로 구글 실적은 예상치 하회 , 고용을 절반이하로 줄일 계획]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588128</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588128/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T02:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: Stack overflow and other pitfalls of functions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476902</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-stack-overflow-and-other-pitfalls-of-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T01:29:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Often the best way to learn how to avoid something is to experience it. With this in mind, have you experienced a genuinely nasty stack...
The post Programming embedded systems: Stack overflow and other pitfalls of functions appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김진태가 쏘아올린 작은 공의 의미는?]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=83802</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/83802/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-26T00:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김진태가 그렇지 않아도 살얼음판이었던 금융시장에 곡괭이질을 해댔다. 극우정치인으로서 그간의 언행을 보면 그리 새로울 것도 없는 그의 행동이 채무변제에 대한 책임이 있는 지방자치단체의 장의 위치와 연계되는 순간, 그간의 언행과는 차원이 다른 엄청난 파급효과를 가져왔던 것이다. 금융당국은 수수방관하다 뒤늦게 사태의 심각성을 깨닫고는 주말에 부랴부랴 모여서 입바른 소리일 확률이 높은 ‘50조원+α 유동성 공급 프로그램’을 발표했다. 시장은 어느 정도 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are all RTOSes equivalent?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476889</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/are-all-rtoses-equivalent/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T21:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Examining an RTOS’s features, APIs, capabilities, and pitfalls are often overlooked, even sometimes to the detriment of the application’s needs. There’s a rumor circulating amongst...
The post Are all RTOSes equivalent? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0,1,2, Freddy came for Blender]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1004/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1004/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article could have been named "How PVS-Studio prevents rash code changes, example N7". However, naming articles like that becomes boring. So today Freddy Krueger's name is in the title, and you'll find out why.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poettering: Brave new trusted boot world]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912370/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912370/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T19:50:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lennart Poettering has posted a
detailed specification for a new approach to "trusted computing"
systems.


	Central to the proposed design is the concept of a Unified Kernel
	Image (UKI). These UKIs are the combination of a Linux kernel
	image, and initrd, a UEFI boot stub program (and further resources,
	see below) into one single UEFI PE file that can either be directly
	invoked by the UEFI firmware (which is useful in particular in some
	cloud/Confidential Computing environments) or through a boot loader
	(which is generally useful to implement support for multiple kernel
	versions, with interactive or automatic selection of image to boot
	into, potentially with automatic fallback management to increase
	robustness).


This work is evidently the first in a series that will come out of the
newly formed Linux Userspace API
Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building IoT SDLC application security through test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476885</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/building-iot-sdlc-application-security-through-test/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T17:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the security measures designed to enforce encryption, authentication, and protection aren’t enough if the asset isn’t developed securely at every phase of its software...
The post Building IoT SDLC application security through test appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ricardo Camacho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Accessing QEMU storage features without a VM]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911281/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911281/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T17:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The QEMU emulator has a sizable set of
storage features, including disk-image file formats like qcow2, snapshots, 
incremental backup, and storage migration, which are available to virtual
machines. This software-defined storage functionality that is available
inside QEMU has not 
been easily 
accessible outside of it, however. Kevin Wolf and Stefano Garzarella
presented at 
KVM Forum 
2022 on the new qemu-storage-daemon program and the libblkio
library that make QEMU's storage functionality available even when the goal
is not 
to run a virtual machine (VM).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing AppSheet databases: Build data driven apps for Google Workspace]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/introducing-appsheet-databases-build-data-driven-apps-for-google-workspace.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/introducing-appsheet-databases-build-data-driven-apps-for-google-workspace.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Shirley Ng, Product Manager, Google Cloud

 
AppSheet is Google’s platform for building no-code custom apps and workflows to automate business processes. It lets app creators build and deploy end-to-end apps and automations without writing code. 
Over the past year, we’ve added more functionality to AppSheet, extending how it can maximize the power of Google Workspace through integrations with products such as Gmail, Google Drive and Apps Script. To improve the experience for app creators and users, we’re excited to introduce in public preview AppSheet databases, a built-in database for citizen developers to easily and securely manage their data. 
Introducing AppSheet databases
AppSheet databases will give users access to an easy to use, first party database for creating and mana…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912324/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912324/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T14:09:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libbluray and wkhtmltopdf), Fedora (firefox, libksba, libmodsecurity, libxml2, qemu, and xmlsec1), Red Hat (389-ds-base, 389-ds:1.4, git-lfs, gnutls, java-1.8.0-ibm, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, libksba, mysql:8.0, pki-core, postgresql:12, samba, sqlite, and zlib), Scientific Linux (389-ds-base, libksba, and pki-core), SUSE (bluez, firefox, jdom, kernel, libosip2, libxml2, multipath-tools, and python-Mako), and Ubuntu (barbican, mysql-5.7, mysql-8.0, openvswitch, and pillow).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everactive launches dev kit as tech kicks batteries to the curb]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11240</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/everactive-launches-dev-kit-as-tech-kicks-batteries-to-the-curb/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T13:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everactive, a company that has been making energy-harvesting sensors for industrial uses, has launched its first development kit as part of a strategic shift for the 10-year-old company. The kit will be available for sale next month and will let others use Everactive’s proprietary chips and wireless communication protocol to build their own battery-less sensing devices. […]
The post Everactive launches dev kit as tech kicks batteries to the curb appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[넷플릭스 광고가 인기가 있는 이유?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588120</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588120/%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0-%ec%9d%b8%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T10:29:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[막말 부실 맹탕… 윤 정부 첫 국감, 그래도 빛난 우수의원 11명]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87331</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87331"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T07:54:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 10월 4일부터 진행된 국감이 막바지에 이르고 있다. 이번 국감은 윤석열 정부 출범 이후 처음 맞이하는 국감으로 국민들의 기대가 컸다. 정부가 공정과 민생보다는 기득권층과 고소득층을 위한 정책들을 내놓을 것이라는 우려가 현실화되고 있는 현 상황에서 이번 국감의 중요성은 매우 컸다. 부실·맹탕·막말·정쟁·국감  이에 ‘경실련’은 정치권에 민생 안정을 위한 국감에 힘쓰도록 유도하기 위해 지난 9월 29일, ‘민생 안정을 […]
The post 막말 부실 맹탕… 윤 정부 첫 국감, 그래도 빛난 우수의원 11명 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install VMs and Ansible Automation Platform on Mac M1]]></title>
        <id>53808b9c-70a3-46fe-b29a-3b371aa6152c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/25/how-install-vms-and-ansible-automation-platform-mac-m1"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of the time, we create our own Ansible playground to test Playbooks, features of the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform (AAP), and many other things. We create our dedicated environment to test AAP for faster troubleshooting and resolution of customer issues.
Previously, it was a pain to install virtual machines on a Mac with an M1 chip. But now, Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) VMs can be easily installed using UTM, a system emulator and virtual machine host for macOS.
How to install a RHEL VM using UTM
It should take less than two hours to finish the setup, including installation.
To create VMs (RHEL 8.6 for automation controller) on Mac M1 machines using UTM, follow these steps:

	
Download and install UTM.
After installation, click “+” to create a VM.
Select virtualize and click L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Arnav Bhati</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go and Proxy Servers: Part 1 - HTTP Proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/go-and-proxy-servers-part-1-http-proxies/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/go-and-proxy-servers-part-1-http-proxies/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T03:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Proxy servers are an interesting and important part of network programming. This
post is the first in a series describing how to implement simple proxy servers
in Go and how to work with existing proxy servers.</p>
<p>For simplicity, this post focuses on unencrypted HTTP traffic. More advanced
proxying techniques with …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 현상론(phenomenalism)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222909922356</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222909922356"/>
        <updated>2022-10-25T03:23:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글을 읽고 현상론의 논증을 요약해 보라. (가) 현상론 역시 관념론처럼 우리는 오직 감각경험에만 직접 접할 수 있고, 외부 세계에는 결코 접할 수 없다는 생각에 기초한 지각 이론이다. 관념론과 갈라서는 지점은 물리적 대상의 설명이다. 관념론자들이 물리적 대상이라는 개념을 한 그룹의 감각 경험에 대한 줄임말로 보는 반면에, J. S. 밀과 에이어 같은 현상론자들은 물리적 대상을 순전히 ‘현실적이고 가능한 감각 경험의 유형’이라는 용어로 설명할 수 있다고 생각한다. 내 기타에 관한 감각 경험의 가능성은 내가 실제로 그것을 바라보거나 만지고 있지 않을 때에도 계속해서 존재한다. 현상론자들은 물리적 대상에 대한 모든 기.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 선호투표제, 미국 정치 판도 바꿀까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75479</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/24/npc_rankchoicedvoting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_rankchoicedvoting"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[8월 24일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 올린 글입니다. 오는 11월 미국 중간선거를 앞두고 주별, 선거구별로 예비 선거와 (당내) 경선(프라이머리, primary)이 한창입니다. 경선은 주로 화요일에 치러지는데, 어제(23일)는 뉴욕주 하원의원 경선이 치러졌고, 플로리다주 민주당은 공화당의 거물인 드산티스 주지사, 마르코 루비오 상원의원과 맞설 후보를 각각 뽑았습니다. 지난주 화요일(16일)에 치른 경선에서도 많은 뉴스가 나왔습니다. 가장 큰 주목을 받은 건 와이오밍주 공화당 하원의원 경선에서 패배한 리즈 체니 의원일 겁니다. 와이오밍주는 주 전체 인구가 60만 명이 채 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912216/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912216/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
3.11.0 of the Python language has been released.
"In the CPython release team, we have put a lot of effort into making
3.11 the best version of Python possible. Better tracebacks, faster Python,
exception groups and except*, typing improvements and much more."
Among other things, this release claims a 1.22x speedup on the standard
benchmark suite thanks to the Faster
CPython work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Examples of errors that PVS-Studio found in LLVM 15.0]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1003/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1003/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compilers are evolving: they issue more and more warnings. Do developers still need to use static code analyzers like PVS-Studio? Yes, because analyzers are evolving too. In this article you'll see how PVS-Studio can find bugs even in a compiler.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podman expands to the Desktop]]></title>
        <id>9c5e0744-8573-42ae-a2f9-bddc73643f88</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/24/podman-expands-desktop"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T20:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At KubeCon North America 2022, the Podman community unveiled introduced Podman Desktop, a new tool for developers. Podman Desktop allows developers to install, configure, and keep their container engine (Podman) up to date with a GUI. This convenient GUI enables users to interact with containers and pods running in Podman (Figure 1).
Podman Desktop also provides an easy deployment to Kubernetes for developers working with containers on their laptops, allowing a seamless transition from containers to pods and pods to Kubernetes. Podman expands to the desktop to provide a complete experience enabling developers to easily work with containers.

  


          


Motivation for the Podman Desktop initiative
Containers have become a fundamental part of a developer’s workflow. There is no avoidi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stevan Le Meur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shut Down C++ Embedded Systems with Calling the global Destructors]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=35503</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/10/24/shut-down-c-embedded-systems-with-calling-the-global-destructors/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:54:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If using C++ on an embedded target, you depend on the constructors for global objects being called by the startup code. While in many cases an embedded system won’t stop, so you don’t need to call the global C++ destructors, … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How odo 3.0 GA improves the developer experience]]></title>
        <id>46afa612-02b2-4116-97fd-9dcd118a4ca9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/24/odo-v3-ga-improves-developer-experience"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers love command-line productivity. We get that. This article describes how odo, a developer-focused command-line interface (CLI) for Red Hat OpenShift and Kubernetes, simplifies cloud-native development.
odo supports fast, iterative development and lets developers focus on what's most important to them—code. The odo 3.0 GA release provides new and improved user experience and security. This new release also allows developers to automatically detect bindable resources, making it easier to connect applications to services.
6 ways odo v3 GA improves the developer experience
The following sections describe six odo v3 GA features and commands that improve the developer experience.
1. Interactive commands
odo has new interactive commands to help developers with the discoverability of cap…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serena Chechile Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat joins the Backstage.io community]]></title>
        <id>0c8df3ef-d56f-4f8b-bbc8-180dac42e289</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/24/red-hat-joins-backstageio-community"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The concept of platform engineering and the end-to-end developer experience is a burgeoning topic industry wide. Building an IdP (Internal Developer Portal) is extremely complex. This topic is new for many, and there are still a lot of unknowns regarding how to evolve an organization that has no, or a low, concept of internal platforms.
Enter Backstage. Backstage is an open source framework for building developer portals donated to the Cloud Native Computing Foundation by Spotify. Backstage has a vibrant ecosystem that development teams successfully use to streamline and rapidly onboard applications. It provides a portal into an internal developer platform by delivering an application catalog that can aggregate several sources of information regarding applications.
Backstage is becoming a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serena Chechile Nichols</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We’re getting a consumer IoT security label next year!]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11237</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/were-getting-a-consumer-iot-security-label-next-year/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House is moving forward with an IoT security and privacy label, with plans to have a formal label by spring of 2023. To kickstart the effort, it invited officials from government, industry, academia, and consumer organizations to discuss what the label should cover and how to implement any labeling scheme. The White House […]
The post We’re getting a consumer IoT security label next year! appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Would you like signs with those chars?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911914/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911914/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:20:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the many quirks that make the C language so charming is the set of
behaviors that
it does not define; these include whether a char variable is a
signed quantity or not.  The distinction often does not make a difference,
but there are exceptions.  Kernel code, which runs on many different
architectures, is where exceptions can certainly be found.  A recent
attempt to eliminate the uncertain signedness of char variables
did not get far — at least not in the direction it originally attempted to
go.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The final 5.19.x stable kernel release]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912186/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912186/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T15:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 5.19.17 stable kernel. "Note this is the
LAST 5.19.y kernel to be released.  This 
branch is now 
end-of-life.  You should move to the 6.0.y branch at this point in time."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meeting robot power demands with modular designs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476851</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/meeting-robot-power-demands-with-modular-designs/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T14:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Robot designs come in a wide array of power demands, which means many challenges for engineers, one of which is building the robot’s internal power infrastructure: this article looks at the considerations in determining the right approach for the design.
The post Meeting robot power demands with modular designs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gopal Mitra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gaynor: Buffers on the edge: Python and Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912181/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912181/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T14:51:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alex Gaynor examines the
awkwardness that comes when trying to interface Python and Rust code.


	The challenge is that if you want to pass some bytes to a Rust
	library to parse them (or do any other processing for that matter),
	the library almost certainly expects a &[u8], and
	there’s no way to turn a &[ReadOnlyCell<u8>]
	into a &[u8] safely, without allocating and
	copying. And of course, the whole point of the Python buffer
	protocol is to avoid these sorts of inefficiencies.

	Therefore, the regrettable solution is that, right now, there is no
	way to have all three of: efficiency, interoperability, and
	soundness.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912178/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912178/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T14:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bluez, kernel, and lava), Fedora (ckeditor, drupal7, moby-engine, php-Smarty, and wavpack), Mageia (bind, e2fsprogs, epiphany, freerdp, kernel, kernel-linus, libconfuse, libosip2, ntfs-3g, perl-Image-ExifTool, and poppler), Oracle (firefox, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, kernel, kernel-container, and thunderbird), Scientific Linux (firefox, java-1.8.0-openjdk, and java-11-openjdk), SUSE (bluez, firefox, kernel, libxml2, and tiff), and Ubuntu (linux-gcp).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국가의 인권침해 범죄는 공소시효가 없다: 미군 기지촌 사건 (2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87323</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87323"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T08:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 2022년 9월 29일, 대한민국 대법원은 여성인권사에 길이 남을 역사적 판결을 내렸다. 미군 기지촌 ‘위안부’ 제도에 대한 한국정부의 책임을 최종 인정하고 원고 측인 피해자들의 손을 들어 주었던 것이다. 당사자 소송 8년 2개월, ‘기지촌여성인권연대’ 결성 10년만의 쾌거다. 당일 관련 단체들과 소송 당사자들은 대법원 앞에서 기자회견을 개최하고 “미군 위안부에 대한 국가의 책임, 즉 국가에 의한 폭력과 인권침해 […]
The post 국가의 인권침해 범죄는 공소시효가 없다: 미군 기지촌 사건 (2022) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Ansible automates JBoss Web Server updates and upgrades]]></title>
        <id>e026f9bc-6992-4291-a002-2f337893a4a8</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/24/ansible-automates-jws-updates-upgrades"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous article, Automate Red Hat JBoss Web Server deployments with Ansible, I discussed how to fully automate the deployment of Red Hat JBoss Web Server with Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. However, this initial installation and configuration is only the beginning. Once the Java server is in use, it must be maintained and updated. Otherwise, critical bugs could affect its operation, or a security vulnerability might expose it to bad actors.
Fortunately, we can utilize Ansible and the JWS collection to mitigate these concerns, enabling it to fully patch your deployment by automation and to upgrade the server itself. In this article, we will cover, in detail, how to implement such automation.
Note: Before you begin the steps in this article, install JBoss Web Server using the A…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romain Pelisse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use design by contract to build Kubernetes Operators in Java]]></title>
        <id>30c01f48-9df4-4f63-a9ec-330f7b539bee</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/24/use-design-contract-build-kubernetes-operators-java"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes is great at automating the deployment, monitoring, and scaling of applications. Whatever you want Kubernetes to control—a service, deployment, etc.—is called a resource. This article shows you how to extend Kubernetes's capabilities by writing a Custom Resource Definition (CRD) and an Operator in Java.
CRDs specify how to install, monitor, and manage resources, whereas Operators are agents that actually carry all that out. The usual language for writing an Operator is Go. But most Java teams prefer to keep all their code in Java: they want to avoid doing a deep dive into a new language, and to maintain a unified environment without supporting two sets of tools and practices.
This article explains how to create a CRD and Operator in Java, complete with sample Java code and YAML s…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sun Tan, Andrea Peruffo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[애플과 테슬라 비교, 테슬라의 강력한 영업 레버리지 효과로 주가 10배 상승 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588104</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588104/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%98%81%ec%97%85-%eb%a0%88%eb%b2%84%eb%a6%ac%ec%a7%80-%ed%9a%a8%ea%b3%bc"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T03:03:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2100년 한국 인구는 반토막이나 가장 높은 인구 감소국이 된다는 UN 인구 예측]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588100</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588100/2100%eb%85%84-%ed%95%9c%ea%b5%ad-%ec%9d%b8%ea%b5%ac"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T01:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국이 반도체 전쟁을 시작한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588098</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588098/%eb%b0%98%eb%8f%84%ec%b2%b4-%ec%a0%84%ec%9f%81-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T00:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smaller C++20 Features - My Presentation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/talk-smaller-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/talk-smaller-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In September and October, I had the pleasure of running two meetings about C++20 features for my local Cracow C++ User Group!
Here are the slides and additional comments from the presentation.



     
    


Initially I did one presentation using my article on smaller C++ 20 features (20 Smaller yet Handy C++20 Features - C++ Stories). Thanks to many valuable discussions during the talk, we decided to do a split. The first meeting was about language parts, and the second part was about library changes.

While the list of topics is in a similar order as the article, I made a few changes:
There’s a constinit slide with more examples instead of the Default Bitfield initializers.
More examples of various features
Additional links and references



     
    


Here are the slides @Xara:
20_cpp20_features_language
20_cpp20_features_library


And


You can also have a look at my YT channel (the C++ Stories YT channel) and see the shorter version of the presentation (around 1 hour): 20 smaller C++20 features (Improved audio) - YouTube.



     
    


Please join our meetup page if you want to hear more from the Cracow User Group.
https://www.meetup.com/C-User-Group-Cracow/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.1-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912100/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912100/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T23:54:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second 6.1 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Usually rc2 is a pretty quiet week, and it mostly started out
that way too, but then things took a turn for the strange. End result:
6.1-rc2 ended up being unusually large."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 탈레반의 아프가니스탄 수복 ‘벌써 1년’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75468</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/23/npc_talibanafghanistan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_talibanafghanistan"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T22:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 8월 22일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 올린 글입니다.  탈레반이 아프가니스탄의 수도 카불로 진격해오던 2021년 여름, 공항에서 필사적인 탈출을 시도하던 아프간 시민들의 모습은 전 세계에 큰 충격을 주었습니다. 뉴스페퍼민트도 당시 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 관련 기사와 칼럼들을 여러 편 소개했습니다. 위기에 처한 아프간 여학생들과 STEM의 역설 아프가니스탄, 20년 전으로 시계를 돌려보면 아프간 난민과 국내 정치 이후 지난 1년을 돌아보면, 코로나19 팬데믹은 좀처럼 사그라들지 않고 있고, 러시아는 우크라이나를 침공해 전쟁을 일으켰으며, 세계 각지에서 기후 재해가 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Studying the lifetime of Open source]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7181</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/10/23/studying-the-lifetime-of-open-source/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T21:18:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A software system can be said to be dead when the information needed to run it ceases to be available. Provided the necessary information is available, plus time/money, no software ever has to remain dead, hardware emulators can be created, support libraries can be created, and other necessary files cobbled together. In the case of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 테슬라 실적, 일부 기대에는 미흡하나 장기 비전은 유효할듯]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588096</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588096/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T07:21:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국의 중국 기술 통제 시도는 결국 미국 반도체에 해로울 뿐인 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588092</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588092/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad%ec%9d%98-%ec%a4%91%ea%b5%ad-%ea%b8%b0%ec%88%a0-%ed%86%b5%ec%a0%9c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T05:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[29 스피노자의 일즉다(一卽多), 만유재신론(萬有在神論)의 철학]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222907856154</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222907856154"/>
        <updated>2022-10-23T03:27:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(가) <스피노자의 우주관은 이 우주가 신의 자기 표현에 불과하다는 것이다. 우주법계가 불성의 자기 표현이라고 보는 화엄사상과 같이 스피노자는 이 우주를 신의 무한한 자기 표현인 속성과 유한한 자기 표현인 양상들의 전체로 여긴다고 들뢰즈가 해석한다.> 어떤 하나, 혹은 전체가 우주, 혹은 존재하는 전체를 표현하고 있다. 그런데 이런 형이상학적 주장을 믿을 만 한 것인가? 이런 주장에 매력을 느끼는 이유가 무엇인가? 우주는 그냥 물리적이고 자연적 작용이라고 생각하는 것이 더 <건전>하지 않은가? (나) <표현은 두 가지 길을 가고 있는데, 그 두 가지 길이란 신으로부터 다양한 양상들에 이르는 다양의 전개로서의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mourning Wolfgang Denk]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912052/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912052/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T14:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U-Boot list carries
the sad news that Wolfgang Denk, the founder of the U-Boot project, has
passed away.


	Wolfgang was a pioneer and strong supporter of Open Source, in the
	time when Linux for Embedded System started its first steps. In
	many occasions he had strong discussions with customers to explain
	the advantages of Open Source, and he rejected business contracts
	if customer was going against his principles. We will miss him.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[29 성인(成人)과 아이]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222907168929</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222907168929"/>
        <updated>2022-10-22T04:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글을 요약하고, 평가해 보라. 계몽이란 성년이 되는 것, 어린아이의 유치함으로부터 벗어나는 것이다. 우리가 물어야 하는 것은 이 정의 속에서 아직도 충분히 사유되지 않은 채 남아 있는 배후의 구도이다. 이 구도는 이 정의가 당연한 것으로 받아들이고 있는 성년과 미성년, 혹은 어른과 아이의 대립적 개념짝으로 이루어져 있다. 이 개념짝의 자명성을 의심하지 않는 한에서, 또 이 이분법에 기초한 특정한 직관에 의해 지배되고 조직되는 한에서, 이 계몽의 정의는 로고스중심주의의 무의식을 계승하고 있다. 계몽적 인간은 완전하게 된 인간이고, 그런 의미에서 어른이다. 이 어른의 완전성은 지성 사용 능력에 있다. 그러나 왜 지.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Oct. 21, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11226</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-oct-21-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T19:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why Netatmo’s video doorbell won’t support HomeKit Secure Video: Yet another smart home device isn’t getting a previously promised Apple HomeKit feature. This time it’s the Netatmo Video Doorbell. Even though it works with HomeKit, adding the HomeKit Secure Video (HSV) feature has been such a challenge that the company has given up on the problem. […]
The post IoT news of the week for Oct. 21, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] More flexible memory access for BPF programs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910873/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910873/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All memory accesses in a BPF program are
statically checked for safety using the 
verifier, which analyzes the program in its
entirety before allowing it to run. While this allows BPF programs to
safely run in kernel space, it restricts how that program is able to use
pointers. Until recently, one such constraint was that the size of a memory
region referenced by a pointer in a BPF program must be statically known
when a BPF program is loaded. A recent
patch set by Joanne Koong enhances BPF to support loading programs with
pointers to dynamically sized memory regions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 6.0.3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911991/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911991/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T13:54:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.0.3 stable kernel update has been
released; it contains over 800 important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911989/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911989/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T13:52:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (poppler), Oracle (firefox and thunderbird), Red Hat (firefox, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, and java-17-openjdk), SUSE (bind, clone-master-clean-up, grafana, libksba, python3, tiff, and v4l2loopback), and Ubuntu (libreoffice).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: Arm news, 60GHz modules, & ISO 26262 RISC-V CPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476815</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-arm-news-60ghz-modules-iso-26262-risc-v-cpu/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T12:39:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s embedded news features various announcements including Arm’s reorganization, Pharrowtech’s 60GHz wireless board integrated into Renesas’ baseband modem, Andes Technology’s ISO 26262 compliant RISC-V CPU IP, plus more.
The post embedded news: Arm news, 60GHz modules, & ISO 26262 RISC-V CPU appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[치매를 예방하는 14가지 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87302</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87302"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:34:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[치매 예방법을 살펴보기 전에 건망증 문제를 살펴볼 필요가 있습니다. 건망증은 대부분 치매와 무관합니다. 가령 물건 위치를 잊거나 헷갈리는 것과 같은 건망증은 걱정할 필요가 없습니다. 하지만 등장인물을 기억하지 못해 소설을 읽지 못하는 것과 같이 체계적인 기억력 상실은 치매 초기에 자주 일어나는 현상으로 치매를 의심해야 합니다. 1. 술 끊기 리스택 박사는 늦어도 70세 전에는 술을 […]
The post 치매를 예방하는 14가지 방법 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[22년 9월 미국 TV 플랫폼 점유율과 스트리밍 점유율]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588090</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588090/22%eb%85%84-9%ec%9b%94-%ed%94%8c%eb%9e%ab%ed%8f%bc-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T10:23:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RHEL 9 and single node OpenShift as VMs on macOS Ventura]]></title>
        <id>50766fa8-938d-4d7b-aa7c-bf5772221946</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/21/rhel-9-and-single-node-openshift-vms-macos-ventura"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple's Virtualization Framework is gaining new features in the upcoming release of macOS Ventura that will make it easy to run ARM Linux virtual machines natively on the M1 processor or other Apple silicon chips. New features of the framework include EFI bootloader support and the ability to render the desktop GUI in a window.
Red Hat recently took a closer look at a beta release of Ventura to see how easy it would be to run virtualized versions of two key technologies—Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9 and the single node version of the Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform—on Apple silicon. Spoiler alert: it worked great! Read on for the details and two video demos.
Running RHEL 9 on Apple silicon
Developers who use MacBooks or other Apple hardware often find value in utilizing a separate Linux …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Hrivnak, Benjamin Schmaus</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[디지탈 광고, 스냅 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각, 경기침체로 광고 수요 감소 및 똘똘한 기업으로 집중]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588084</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588084/%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%8a%a4%eb%83%85-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T04:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1 내성(內聖)과 신외왕(新外王)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222906277704</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222906277704"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T03:21:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이명휘는 <중국 현대 신유학의 자아전환>(2013)의 <서론>에서 다음처럼 주장한다. <“내성외왕”의 사상 형식은 오늘날에는 단지 새롭게 전면적인 해석을 통하여 전환하는 것이 필요할 뿐이지 버릴 필요는 없는 것이다. 신유가 학자들은 이러한 전환을 위한 매우 훌륭한 사례를 제공하였다. 현대 신유가가 비록 내성외왕의 기초를 인정하지만 결코 간단하게 외왕을 내성의 직접적 확장으로 보지는 않는다.> 이명휘에 의하면, 유학의 생명과 요체는 바로 내성외왕(內聖外王)이다. 이것을 포기한다면 더 이상 유학에 본질적인 것은 존재하지 않는다. 이것을 포기한 유학, 가령 한 동안 논의되었다가 이제는 논의 자체가 사라져 버.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 3분기 테슬라 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 테슬라 목표주가 하향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588079</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588079/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-21T01:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 치매를 피해 봅시다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75459</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/20/npc_dementia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_dementia"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T22:59:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 어떤 인류도 경험해보지 못한 세상을 살고 있습니다. 하루하루는 비슷한 것 같지만, 어딘가에서는 엄청난 기술이 개발되고 있다는 사실을 알고 있습니다. 그래서 몇십 년 전과 지금이 그렇게 다른 것처럼 몇십 년 후의 세상이 지금과 완전히 다를 것이라는 말에도 고개를 끄덕이게 되죠. 그중에 우리가 가장 직접적으로 느끼게 될 진보가 있다면 수명이 길어진다는 사실입니다. 적어도 오늘날의 주요한 사망 원인인 암과 뇌혈관, 심혈관 질환으로 인한 사망은 줄어들고 있고, 교통사고와 같은 사고사도 줄어들고 있습니다. 예를 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in C# 11: overview]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1002/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1002/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C# 11 is coming, so we're going to explore its new features in detail. You may find these new features pretty curious even though there are not that many of them. Today let's take a closer look at the generic math support, raw string literals, the required modifier, the type parameters in attributes, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The Ghost publishing system]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911601/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911601/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T16:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Part of the early appeal of the World Wide Web was the promise that anybody
could create a site and publish interesting content to the world.  A few
decades later, that promise seems to have been transformed into the ability to
provide content for a small number of proprietary platforms run by huge
corporations.
But, arguably, the dream of widespread independent publishing is enjoying a
resurgence.  The Ghost publishing platform
is built around the goal of making publishing technology — and the ability
to make money from it — available with free software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 22.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911899/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911899/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T15:13:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu
22.10 has been released.  "Codenamed 'Kinetic Kudu', this interim
release improves the experience of enterprise developers and IT
administrators. It also includes the latest toolchains and applications
with a particular focus on the IoT ecosystem."  See the
release notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911879/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911879/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr), Red Hat (java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, OpenShift Container Platform 4.9.50 bug fix and, and rh-nodejs14-nodejs), SUSE (buildah, clone-master-clean-up, go1.18, go1.19, helm, jasper, libostree, nodejs16, php8, qemu, and xen), and Ubuntu (libxdmcp, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15,
 linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.15, linux-gkeop,
 linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-oem-5.14, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4,
 linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gkeop,
 linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle,
 linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, linux-oem-5.17, and perl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: ConwaysLaw]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/ConwaysLaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/ConwaysLaw.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty much all the practitioners I favor in Software Architecture are deeply
  suspicious of any kind of general law in the field. Good software architecture
  is very context-specific, analyzing trade-offs that resolve differently across a wide range
  of environments. But if there is one thing they all agree on, it's the importance
  and power of Conway's Law. Important enough to affect every system I've
  come across, and powerful enough that you're doomed to defeat if you try to
  fight it.
The law is probably best stated, by its author, as:  [1]
Any organization that designs a system (defined broadly) will produce a
    design whose structure is a copy of the organization's communication
    structure.
    
-- Melvin Conway
Conway's Law is essentially the observation that the archite…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools – The Raspberry Pi Pico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14429</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/tools-the-raspberry-pi-pico/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:51:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, the Raspberry Pi Pico might not be thought of as a tool for professional embedded software developers. The Pico is a low-cost development board, not what we might consider … Continue reading Tools – The Raspberry Pi Pico
Tools – The Raspberry Pi Pico first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Cortex-based MCU integrates BLE, Zigbee and OTA capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476810</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/arm-cortex-based-mcu-integrates-ble-zigbee-and-ota-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microchip’s new PIC MCU family is said to solve wireless connectivity design challenge by integrating BLE functionality directly, and is supported by comprehensive developer ecosystem.
The post Arm Cortex-based MCU integrates BLE, Zigbee and OTA capabilities appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: This company thinks TinyML will be big]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11221</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-this-company-thinks-tinyml-will-be-big/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TinyML is about to get really big, or at least that’s what a startup thinks as we explain on this week’s podcast. Useful Sensors is the company that’s making inexpensive, low-powered edge sensors in a way that protects privacy. We discuss why we agree with that approach. Next up are our thoughts on fact why […]
The post Podcast: This company thinks TinyML will be big appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 3분기 넷플릭스 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588073</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588073/2022%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do Wyze cameras in Google Home need a hub?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11192</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/do-wyze-cameras-in-google-home-need-a-hub/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T11:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a question from our Voicemail hotline about Wyze cameras and Google Wi-Fi. Our caller has the second-generation Google Nest Wi-Fi routers and is buying a new house. He plans to add a Wyze door lock and some Wyze cameras to his new home and wants […]
The post Do Wyze cameras in Google Home need a hub? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["SPC그룹과 함께 세상은 더 행복해집니다"]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87293</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87293"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T09:22:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 10월 15일 23살 여성 노동자가 샌드위치 소스 배합기계에 앞치마가 빨려 들어가 숨졌다. 이 죽음을 우리는 오래오래 기억해야 한다. 이 죽음은 단순한 산업재해가 아니기 때문이다. 이 죽음은 조직적이고, 체계적이며, 사회 구성원 대다수가 이 죽음에 암묵적으로 공조했다는 의미에서 무엇보다 사회적이다. 2018년 SPC 그룹의 수백억 원대의 임금체불과 제빵사 불법파견 등이 사회적으로 공론화되자, SPC는 한 걸음 물러나 ‘사회적 […]
The post "SPC그룹과 함께 세상은 더 행복해집니다" first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 essentials to mitigating API security risks]]></title>
        <id>9cd9783e-ceb8-4dd2-aa32-f60a10dfdbc2</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/20/10-essentials-mitigating-api-security-risks"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application programming interfaces (APIs) make connections between systems that enable companies to conduct business. APIs are now one of the most popular ways for applications, microservices, and containers to communicate. They offer a wide range of benefits, including reliable communication and data transfer, streamlined development, easy scalability, and cost-effective re-usability. However, as APIs become more prevalent in the cloud-native landscape, they also leave applications vulnerable to many more security risks.
APIs can expose an application and its data, greatly expanding the attack surface and providing a range of new opportunities for attacks. Since APIs are used for communication and data transfer, an insecure API can expose sensitive customer or corporate data, causing reve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vamsi Ravula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The ultimate CI/CD resource guide]]></title>
        <id>32737cb1-c7f6-483b-93bb-6729cb90017c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/20/ultimate-cicd-resource-guide"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You've found the right place for content on continuous integration/continuous deployment (CI/CD). We've gathered our highest-performing articles from the past year on this topic on Red Hat Developer. This article will introduce you to all things related to CI/CD.
What is CI/CD and why is it important for developers?
Continuous integration (CI) and continuous deployment (CD) are development processes making use of automated tools to produce high-quality software.
CI ensures that any code submitted by each developer works together with all other code in the project. Typically, CI works by running regression tests.
CD involves further automation to make sure that the latest accepted versions of a project enter production, and that all the pieces deployed together are compatible.
Numerous tool…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book review: "The Future of Fusion Energy" by J. Parisi and J. Ball]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/book-review-the-future-of-fusion-energy-by-j-parisi-and-j-ball/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/book-review-the-future-of-fusion-energy-by-j-parisi-and-j-ball/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T03:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Fusion research is back in the news again, due to multiple factors. I've been
long interested in this topic and have seen this book mentioned in several
places since it came out in 2019. Now that I finally got it and read it, I'm
really happy I did. I think …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 20, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911046/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911046/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-20T00:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 20, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How PVS-Studio prevents rash code changes, example N6]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1001/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1001/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often make mistakes accidentally, or because they are in a hurry. Wondering how to find such mistakes quickly? Welcome to another article in the "How PVS-Studio prevents rash code changes" series. Today we're talking about the FreeCAD project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay |  Meet app founders helping people around the world]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/weareplay-meet-app-founders-helping-people-around-the-world.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/weareplay-meet-app-founders-helping-people-around-the-world.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Leticia Lago, Developer Marketing
      
There are millions of apps available on Google Play, created by thousands of founders across the world. Each single app is unique and special in its own right, but they all have one thing in common - their purpose is to help. From helping motorhome enthusiasts find somewhere to camp, small business owners manage their finances or waste pickers make a reliable income - in this latest batch of #WeArePlay stories, we celebrate app founders who are helping people across the world in extraordinarily different ways.  
 
 First we begin with Cristian. Originally from Villa Rica in southern Chile, he made his family very proud by being the first to go to university. During his studies in Santiago, he learned about the local waste pickers – people …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The search for the correct amount of split-lock misery]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911219/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911219/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T15:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike many other architectures, x86 systems support atomic operations that
affect more than one cache line.  This support comes at a cost, though, in
terms of overall system performance and, even, security.  Over the last few
years, kernel developers have worked to discourage the use of this sort of
"split-lock" operation.  Now, though, one group of users is feeling
a little too discouraged, leading to a discussion of how much misery can
appropriately be inflicted upon users who use problematic but
architecturally legal operations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911723/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911723/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T14:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bcel, kernel, node-xmldom, and squid), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, dhcp, dokuwiki, firefox, golang, python-joblib, sos, and unzip), Oracle (nodejs and nodejs:16), Red Hat (firefox, kernel, kernel-rt, nodejs, nodejs:14, and thunderbird), Scientific Linux (firefox and thunderbird), Slackware (git and mozilla), SUSE (amazon-ssm-agent, caasp-release, cri-o, patchinfo, release-notes-caasp, skuba, enlightenment, libreoffice, netty, nodejs12, nodejs14, nodejs16, pngcheck, postgresql-jdbc, python-waitress, rubygem-activesupport-5_1, and tcl), and Ubuntu (frr, git, libksba, and linux-azure-4.15).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Negotiate a balanced product investment mix]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html#NegotiateABalancedProductInvestmentMix</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html#NegotiateABalancedProductInvestmentMix"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T12:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rick and Kennedy conclude their article on the bottleneck caused by
      tension between product and engineering. This final section
      addresses balancing between under and over-engineering in the product's
      technical infrastructure.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민주주의 후퇴 징후들: 출근길 문답, MBC 탄압 그리고 ‘윤석열차’ 사건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87280</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87280"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[집권 7개월 차를 맞는 윤석열 정부의 언론 정책에 대한 우려가 커지고 있다. 집권 초부터 연이은 구설수에 이어 청와대 이전, 수해 대응, 외교 논란에 현 정부를 선택하지 않은 유권자도, 지지한 유권자도 당혹스럽기는 마찬가지다. 국민의 이런 실망감은 2008년 미국산 쇠고기 수입 협상 강행으로 곤욕을 치른 이명박 정부 이래 최저 국정운영 지지율에서 나타난다. 여러 문제점이 있지만, 가장 우려스런 […]
The post 민주주의 후퇴 징후들: 출근길 문답, MBC 탄압 그리고 ‘윤석열차’ 사건 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic system design revenue posts highest quarterly rise]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476803</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/electronic-system-design-revenue-posts-highest-quarterly-rise/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T11:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronic Design Market Data report highlights highest quarterly year-over-year revenue increase in over a decade and record quarter for Q2 2022.
The post Electronic system design revenue posts highest quarterly rise appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former Googler creates Tiny ML sensor startup]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11207</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/former-googler-creates-tiny-ml-sensor-startup/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if we could take the internet out of the Internet of Things? Or at least take the internet out of some of the things? That’s the idea behind Useful Sensors, a startup created by Pete Warden, the former technical lead of the TensorFlow Micro team at Google, and previous founder of Jetpac, a deep […]
The post Former Googler creates Tiny ML sensor startup appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open vSwitch: The revalidator process explained]]></title>
        <id>c7147af2-1bce-4304-b987-1015d70a1150</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/19/open-vswitch-revalidator-process-explained"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open vSwitch (OVS) is a rich implementation of software-defined networking (SDN) L2 switch. OVS's revalidator process, invoked by Open vSwitch's ovs-vswitchd daemon, is responsible for the following:
Making sure the installed datapath flows match the configured OpenFlow rules
Updating OpenFlow packet and byte statistics
Removing idle datapath flows
However, the OVS implementation details are not well documented or understood. The goal of this article is to provide insight into the operation of the revalidator.
Revalidator threads
The ovs-vswitchd daemon creates several revalidator threads when the datapath initializes at the creation of the first bridge for the datapath. If you use both the kernel (system) datapath and the userspace (netdev) datapath, two sets of revalidator threads get cr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eelco Chaudron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[순자의 서(恕)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222904377672</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222904377672"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T03:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<순자> 번역판의 <찾아보기>를 찾아보아도 <서(恕)>가 없다. 그런데 순자의 서(恕)에 대한 논문이 <순자>에서 서(恕)가 딱 한 군데 나타난다고 가르쳐 준다. <순자>의 <법행(法行)> 편에 서(恕)에 대한 언급이 나온다. <공자가 말하기를 ‘군자에게는 세 가지 서(恕)가 있다. 군주가 있는데 능히 섬기지 못하고 신하를 두어 그 부리기를 바라는 것은 서(恕)가 아니다. 부모가 있는데 능히 보답을 하지 못하고 자식을 두어 그 효도를 바라는 것은 서(恕)가 아니다. 형이 있는데 능히 공경하지 못하고 아우를 두어 그 이르는 말을 바라는 것은 서(恕)가 아니다. 선비가 이 세 가지 서(恕)에 밝다면, 가히 자.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA 전망, 2023년 초 투자자 항복으로 랠리가 시작될 것으로 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588064</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588064/2023%eb%85%84-%ec%b4%88-%eb%9e%a0%eb%a6%ac-bofa-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-19T01:15:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Soft Skills For Embedded Systems Software Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1470.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1470.php"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T23:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contents:

Introduction

The Skills


Interpersonal


Tips For Interpersonal Skills


Communications


Tips For Speaking

Tips For Writing

Tips For Diagramming


Time Management


Tips For Time...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 알렉스 존스, 음모론과 웰니스 산업의 위험한 결합]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75437</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/18/npc_alexjoneswellness/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_alexjoneswellness"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T22:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난주, 미국 법원은 샌디훅 총기난사 사건의 피해자 유족들이 조작극을 꾸미고 있다고 허위 정보를 퍼뜨린 알렉스 존스에게 10억 달러 가까운 손해배상금을 지급하라고 판결했습니다. 오늘 소개하는 글은 알렉스 존스 같은 음모론과 웰니스 산업의 위험한 결합을 조명한 글로 지난 8월 17일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 올렸던 글입니다. “인포워즈(Infowars)”라는 매체를 운영하며 극우 음모론 전파에 앞장섰던 알렉스 존스(Alex Jones)가 최근 샌디훅 초등학교 총기 난사 사건 희생자 유족들이 제기한 일련의 손해배상 소송에서 패소하면서 5천만 달러 가까운 큰 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.21: GitLab Code Quality, Unreal Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1000/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1000/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.21 has been released. This short note describes the analyzer's main enhancements and lists our recent articles and quizzes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you add a secondary Z-Wave controller for a connected door lock?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11150</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/can-you-add-a-secondary-z-wave-controller-for-a-connected-door-lock/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T16:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a question from Dave on our Voicemail hotline. Dave’s landlord uses a SmartRent mobile app and Aeotec hub that connects to a smart Yale Assure door lock with Z-Wave. Dave wants to add a secondary Z-Wave controller to the Aeotec hub so that he can […]
The post Can you add a secondary Z-Wave controller for a connected door lock? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Identity management for WireGuard]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910766/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910766/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T15:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its inclusion in the Linux kernel, the WireGuard VPN tunnel has become
increasingly popular.  In general, WireGuard is simpler to configure than
other VPNs, but the approach that it takes to authentication can present
some challenges. Each node in a WireGuard network has a cryptographic key
that serves as the node's identity; 
nodes that do not know each other's keys cannot directly communicate.
Keeping
track of these keys and distributing them to the other nodes
in a mesh network quickly becomes a chore as the network grows.
Fortunately, there are now 
several open-source 
tools that can automate the management of these keys and make using
WireGuard easier for both administrators and end users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 106 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911563/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911563/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T14:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
106.0 of the Firefox browser has been released.  There are several new
features, including PDF editing, Firefox
View (an overview of recently closed tabs), and a set of new color
schemes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911562/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911562/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:54:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (glibc and libksba), Fedora (dhcp and kernel), Red Hat (.NET 6.0, .NET Core 3.1, compat-expat1, kpatch-patch, and nodejs:16), Slackware (xorg), SUSE (exiv2, expat, kernel, libreoffice, python, python-numpy, squid, and virtualbox), and Ubuntu (linux-azure and zlib).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating multidisciplinary stream-aligned teams to escape the              product-vs-engineering bottleneck]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html#CreateMultidisciplinaryStream-alignedTeams</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html#CreateMultidisciplinaryStream-alignedTeams"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rick and Kennedy continue explaining how to deal with the lack of 
      collaboration between product and engineering. This installment advises
      creating multidisciplinary stream-aligned teams and establishing team
      working agreements.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NTT envisions a “greener” IoT sensor]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11202</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/ntt-envisions-a-greener-iot-sensor/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my  Oct. 14 weekly IoT newsletter. One of the larger challenges associated with the internet of things is e-waste. Every sensor deployed into the world has a cache of heavy, rare metals and hard-to-recycle electronics inside. Yet the promise of using more sensors to help optimize production in factories or […]
The post NTT envisions a “greener” IoT sensor appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10/18 애플, 아마존, 테슬라에 대한 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588058</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588058/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T09:19:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[성평등전주 ‘성노동’ 사상 검열로 쫓겨난 작가 사랑해와 치명타의 입장]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87263</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87263"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T09:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10월 7일 성평등전주는 공식사과문을 발표하였습니다. “성매매에 대한 다른 입장을 가진 예술가들과 예술제를 준비한다는 것이 그간의 선미촌의 변화 노력과 모순되는 것이라는 판단이 중요하게 작용”했고, “사랑해, 이시마, 치명타 3명의 작가에게 하차를 요구하는 것을 ‘전여문'(전북여성문화예술인연대)에 맡기고 사업의 주최기관인 성평등전주가 직접 작가들에게 상황을 설명하는 등의 적극적인 노력을 기울이지 않았던 것은 너무 안일한 대처”이며, “성평등전주가 예술가들을 민주적이지 않은 절차에 노출시킴으로써 […]
The post 성평등전주 ‘성노동’ 사상 검열로 쫓겨난 작가 사랑해와 치명타의 입장 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An API-first approach to building Node.js applications]]></title>
        <id>d0c6ef97-2223-46db-aef9-292c01f8dc7b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/18/api-first-approach-building-nodejs-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API services are a common component of Node.js applications. This installment of the ongoing Node.js reference architecture series focuses on the development of REST APIs using an API-first approach.
Read the series so far:
Part 1: Overview of the Node.js reference architecture
Part 2: Logging in Node.js
Part 3: Code consistency in Node.js
Part 4: GraphQL in Node.js
Part 5: Building good containers
Part 6: Choosing web frameworks
Part 7: Code coverage
Part 8: Typescript
Part 9: Securing Node.js applications
Part 10: API-first approach to building Node.js applications
The IBM and Red Hat team has provided a comprehensive reference for developers looking to build Node.js applications. The Markdown source file of the reference specification is also available on GitHub under the Apache 2.0 ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wojciech Trocki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알도 레오폴드의 <모래 군의 열두 달> 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222903607561</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222903607561"/>
        <updated>2022-10-18T06:09:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 일광욕하러 외출했다가 눈보라를 만난 얼룩다람쥐는 잠자리로 되돌아가면 그만이다. 그러나 호수의 숨구멍을 찾아서 200마일의 칠흑 같은 밤길을 날아온 모험심 많은 철새 기러기에게는 물러설 곳이 마땅치 않다. 기러기의 도착은 배수의 진을 친 어떤 예언자의 확신 같은 것을 내포한다. (2) 봄철 기러기의 일상을 관찰하다보면, 다른 놈보다 훨씬 여기저기 더 많이 날아다니고 더 많이 울어대는 외톨이들이 적지 않다는 것을 알게 된다. 누구나 이 놈들의 울음소리는 쓸쓸하다고 생각하기 쉽다. 또 이 심한 홀아비이거나 잃어버린 새끼를 찾아 헤매는 어미일 것이라고 지레짐작하기 쉽다. 그러나 경험이 많은 조류학자라면 새들의 행동을 그.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 마침내 통과된 기후변화 대응법, 성공인가 실패인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75429</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/17/npc_inflationreductionact/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_inflationreductionact"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T22:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 8월, 마침내 인플레이션 감축법(Inflation Reduction Act)이 미국 하원의 표결을 통과했습니다. 730쪽에 달하는 법안의 골자를 이루는 건 법안의 이름인 인플레이션과는 무관해 보이는 기후변화 대응과 의료보험 지원 확대 방안입니다. 물론 법안 통과를 환영한다고 밝힌 백악관의 설명에 따르면, 에너지 요금과 의료비를 낮출 수 있다면 치솟은 물가를 안정시킬 수 있습니다. 바이든 대통령은 이번 주에 법안에 서명하겠다고 밝혔는데, 법이 발효되더라도 곧바로 물가가 내리지는 않을 겁니다. 여당인 민주당은 법을 통과시키기 위해 공화당과 협의하는 과정에서 원안의 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Which signal processing technique is right for your device?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476762</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/which-signal-processing-technique-is-right-for-your-device/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T19:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Acoustic signal processing techniques such as beamforming and blind source separation improve intelligibility of captured speech, but which technique is best for which application? In...
The post Which signal processing technique is right for your device? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dave Betts</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tails 5.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911494/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911494/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T18:28:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
5.5 of the Tor-centered Tails distribution is out.  The biggest change
appears to be a significant update to the Thunderbird email client.



	Thunderbird 102 is a major update with many changes to the
	navigation, folder icons, and address book.
	Thunderbird 102 also includes important usability improvements to
	the OpenPGP feature. When composing an email, you can now see
	whether it will be encrypted or not. If encryption is impossible, a
	key assistant helps you solve key issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dev Library Letters: 14th Issue]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/dev-library-letters-14th-issue.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/dev-library-letters-14th-issue.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Garima Mehra, Program Manager
  
   
‘Google Dev Library letters’ is curated to bring you some of the best projects developed with Google tech that have been submitted to the Dev Library platform. We hope this brings you the inspiration you need for your next project!



    
                    
                                    
Android
                            
            
                                    



                                                    
Image-compressor 
by Vinod Baste
                    
Check out Vinod’s Android Image compress library that helps reduce the size of the image by 90% without losing any of its pixels.
                            
            
                                    




SealedX 
by Jaewoong Eum
                    …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two more stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911487/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911487/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T16:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.10.149 and
5.4.219
stable kernel updates have been released.  These small updates contain only a
few more WiFi fixes and one revert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Matter is a key step forward for cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11199</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-matter-is-a-key-step-forward-for-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T16:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my  Oct. 14 weekly IoT newsletter. One of my favorite things about the Matter home interoperability protocol is that even if it doesn’t make it easy to manage my crazy complex smart home right from the beginning — or ultimately, ever — it does mandate some basic security requirements […]
The post How Matter is a key step forward for cybersecurity appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.1 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910608/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910608/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T14:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released
6.1-rc1 and closed the 6.1 merge window on 
October 16; at that point, 11,537 non-merge changesets had been pulled
into the mainline repository.  That is considerably less than the 13,543
changesets pulled during the 6.0 merge window, but quantity is not
everything: there were quite a few significant changes brought in this time
around.  Many of those were part of the nearly 5,800 changesets pulled
since our first 6.1 merge window summary;
read on for a look at some of the work done in the latter part of this
merge window.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GnuPG 2.3.8 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911467/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911467/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T14:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.3.8 of the GNU Privacy Guard is out.  It contains a few new
features but the real purpose is to fix CVE-2022-3515,
an integer overflow vulnerability that can be exploited remotely for code
execution via a, for example, malicious S/MIME attachment.  Note that the
actual vulnerability is in the libksba library, which is
normally packaged separately on Linux systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911461/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911461/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T13:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (kernel, linux-hardened, linux-lts, and linux-zen), Debian (python-django), Fedora (apptainer, kernel, python3.6, and vim), Gentoo (assimp, deluge, libvirt, libxml2, openssl, rust, tcpreplay, virglrenderer, and wireshark), Slackware (zlib), SUSE (chromium, python3, qemu, roundcubemail, and seamonkey), and Ubuntu (linux-aws-5.4 and linux-ibm).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[최근 약세장 랠리에서 얻는 교훈]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588047</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588047/%ec%95%bd%ec%84%b8%ec%9e%a5-%eb%9e%a0%eb%a6%ac-%ea%b5%90%ed%9b%88"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T13:15:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모건스탠리 윌슨, S&P 500 지수는 단기 랠리로 4,150까지 상승 가능하다고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588039</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588039/%eb%aa%a8%ea%b1%b4%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%a0%eb%a6%ac-sp-500-%ec%a7%80%ec%88%98-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T12:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유럽의 미디어 다양성 전략: ‘저작권 지침안 vs. 구글’ 중심으로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87252</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87252"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T10:17:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[앞에서 빅테크와 뉴스미디어의 불균형을 제도적으로 해결하기 위한 유럽 각국의 움직임을 살펴보겠습니다. 유럽연합은 특히 ‘저작권’을 통해서 빅테크 기업을 규제하는 방식을 채택하고 있습니다. 유럽연합은 2019년 3월 20일, ‘디지털 단일시장 저작권 지침안'(이하 ‘저작권 지침안’)을 가결했습니다. 참고: ‘2019 저작권학술대회’ 유럽연합 디지털 단일시장 저작권 지침의 쟁점 및 시사점 저작권 지침안: 개요와 쟁점  저작권 지침안은 2019년 6월 7일 시행되고, 회원국은 2년 […]
The post 유럽의 미디어 다양성 전략: ‘저작권 지침안 vs. 구글’ 중심으로 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 경제학자들의 미국 경제 예측, 내년 경제 침체 가능성 63%와 상반기 마이너스 성장 예상]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588028</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588028/%ea%b2%bd%ec%a0%9c%ed%95%99%ec%9e%90%eb%93%a4%ec%9d%98-2023%eb%85%84-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ea%b2%bd%ec%a0%9c-%ec%98%88%ec%b8%a1"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T09:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get OpenShift Streams for Apache Kafka on AWS Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>9f7ef34c-99e8-45e4-854b-0ef09d06823c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/17/get-openshift-streams-apache-kafka-aws-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Kafka Streams allow you to implement event-driven and event streaming applications in a distributed environment. Red Hat OpenShift Streams for Apache Kafka takes those capabilities to the next level by eliminating the complexity and management involved in implementing and maintaining Kafka instances.
If you're using Amazon Web Services (AWS) to host your Red Hat OpenShift cluster or Red Hat OpenShift Streams for Apache Kafka, you'll be pleased to know that the AWS Marketplace now offers Red Hat OpenShift Streams for Apache Kafka for AWS (Figure 1).

  


          


This Kafka installation is managed by Red Hat, freeing you to focus on developing code instead of maintaining infrastructure. The service also works alongside the Service Binding Operator in OpenShift. Once you install the Operator, connecting your code to a Kafka instance can be as simple as drag and drop (Figure 2).

  


          


The Service Binding Operator also makes it easy to experiment with these technologies by running our Managed Kafka sandbox activity in an existing OpenShift cluster on AWS.
Finally; if you have already created the Sandbox Activity in our sandbox, and want to move it to your AWS cluster, check out the GitOps Primer Operator, which gives you the ability to export all Kubernetes objects within a namespace as a portable zip file that can be easily taken to another cluster.
Happy coding!
Get OpenShift Streams for Apache Kafka on AWS Marketplace appeared first on Red Hat Developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Don Schenck</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to fix issues caused by reusing Go error variables]]></title>
        <id>08db59ca-2473-4722-9329-8eb2c8ccac4e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/17/fix-issues-reusing-go-error-variables"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses issues caused by reusing error variables in Go code. I will begin by illustrating the problem with a fictional company called ACME Corporation and its software engineer Wile E. Then I will present trivial examples to reveal the problem and how to avoid it.
The story of a reused Go error variable
A user opened a new issue to ACME Corporation because he noticed that users could enter any string into the phone number on the contact form. Wile E. is in charge of implementing a fix.
Wile E. examines the code:
func StoreAllContacts() {
  for _, c := range contactsToStore {
    err := legacy.StoreContact(&c)
    if err != nil {
      fmt.Printf("Error storing %v: %v\n", c, err)
    } else {
      fmt.Printf("Contact NAME: %s, SURNAME: %s, PHONE: %s stored successfully!\n", …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Massimiliano Ziccardi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경험의 형이상학]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222902547905</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222902547905"/>
        <updated>2022-10-17T05:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 유사성보다 차이성을 강조하고 있지만, 사실 해커는 그 누구보다 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 유사성을 강조했던 철학자였다. 그의 <통찰과 환상>(1972)의 초판의 부제가 <철학과 경험의 형이상학에 대한 비트겐슈타인>이다. 부제에 사용된 <경험의 형이상학>이란 바로 칸트의 철학을 의미한다. <내가 우선적으로 다루고 있는 주제는 비트겐슈타인의 경험의 형이상학이다. 이 칸트적 용어는 비트겐슈타인의 철학 일반이 보여주고 있는 칸트적 친근성을 탐구하는 중심 주제 중의 하나이다. 비트겐슈타인의 경험의 형이상학은 다음 세 가지 문제로 이루어졌다고 할 수 있다. 자기 의식의 문제, 타인의 마음.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 코로나19 후유증(Long COVID)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75414</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/16/npc_longcovid/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_longcovid"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T23:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 2019년 시작된 코로나19는 세상을 코로나19 이전과 이후로 나누었습니다. 하지만 올해 초만 하더라도 다수가 백신을 맞고, 또 많은 사람이 코로나19에 걸려 자연 면역을 얻으면서 새로운 시대가 시작되는 듯 보였습니다. 하지만 이제 또 다른 변이가 유행하고 있습니다. 물론 여러 전문가가 예상하는 것처럼 앞으로 유행할 새로운 변이는 전파력은 강하더라도 치명률은 낮을 가능성이 있습니다. 그러나 코로나 자체의 증상 외에도 사람들이 이를 두려워하는 다른 문제가 있습니다. 바로 롱 코비드(Long COVID)라고도 불리는 코로나19 후유증입니다. 코로나19 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.1-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911367/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911367/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T23:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.1-rc1 and closed the
merge window for this development cycle.


	This isn't actually shaping up to be a particularly large release:
	we "only" have 11.5k non-merge commits during this merge window,
	compared to 13.5k last time around. So not exactly tiny, but
	smaller than the last few releases. At least in number of commits.

	That said, we've got a few core things that have been brewing for a
	long time, most notably the multi-gen LRU VM series, and the
	initial Rust scaffolding (no actual real Rust code in the kernel
	yet, but the infrastructure is there).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clustering source code within functions]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7167</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/10/16/clustering-source-code-within-functions/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T21:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The question of how best to cluster source code into functions is a perennial debate that has been ongoing since functions were first created. Beginner programmers are told that clustering code into functions is good, for a variety of reasons (none of the claims are backed up by experimental evidence). Structuring code based on clustering […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 C++ conference talks 2019—2022]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0999/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0999/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lots of interesting developer conferences take place in the world. It would be great to invent teleportation so you could attend every talk you're interested in, but let's make things easier. You can watch almost any conference talk on YouTube.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google launches KataOS]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911332/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911332/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T17:26:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced
the existence of yet another new operating system, called KataOS, aimed at
the creation of secure embedded systems.


	As the foundation for this new operating system, we chose seL4 as
	the microkernel because it puts security front and center; it is
	mathematically proven secure, with guaranteed confidentiality,
	integrity, and availability. Through the seL4 CAmkES framework,
	we're also able to provide statically-defined and analyzable system
	components. KataOS provides a verifiably-secure platform that
	protects the user's privacy because it is logically impossible for
	applications to breach the kernel's hardware security protections
	and the system components are verifiably secure. KataOS is also
	implemented almost entirely in Rust, which provides a strong
	starting point for software security, since it eliminates entire
	classes of bugs, such as off-by-one errors and buffer overflows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[넷프릭스 광고(광고 요금제)를 보는 월가의 시선, 새로운 수익 모델 가능성 충분]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588021</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588021/%eb%84%b7%ed%94%84%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0%eb%a5%bc-%eb%b3%b4%eb%8a%94-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%9c%ec%84%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T14:49:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 3]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476759</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-steps-to-designing-an-embedded-software-architecture-step-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:52:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores the third step to designing an embedded software architecture: Decompose the system. The last two articles have explored the five steps to...
The post 5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 3 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling the quantum leap]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476756</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/enabling-the-quantum-leap/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-16T11:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To speed up the quantum leap, wafer testing solutions will need to evolve to keep pace and cater for a shorter time-to-market, which is key...
The post Enabling the quantum leap appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aki Junes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Saturday's stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911272/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911272/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T15:25:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.0.2,
5.19.16,
5.15.74,
5.10.148, and
5.4.218
stable kernel updates have all been released.  Among other things, these
updates contain the fixes for the recently disclosed WiFi vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유가 윤리와 도가 윤리]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222900817304</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222900817304"/>
        <updated>2022-10-15T03:41:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 갑, 을 사상가들의 입장으로 가장 적절한 것은? 갑: 이름을 바로잡는 것[正名]이 정치의 시작이다. 이름이 제대로 서지 않으니 예악이 흥성하지 않고, 예악이 흥성하지 않으니 형벌이 제멋대로 된다. 을: 도(道)는 자연스러움을 본받는다. 인위적인 것을 강제해서는 안 된다. 내버려두면 백성들이 스스로 잘 살게 되고 세상도 잘 돌아간다. ① 갑: 인간이 제정한 규범에서 벗어나 무위(無爲)를 추구해야 한다. ② 갑: 내가 하기 싫은 일을 남에게 시키지 않는 서(恕)를 행해야 한다. ③ 을: 자신의 직분과 지위에 걸맞은 예법을 충실히 따라야 한다. ④ 을: 시비선악(是非善惡)을 구분하여 질서를 바로 세워야 한다. ⑤ 갑, 을: 인(仁)의 시작.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Oct. 14, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11189</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-oct-14-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T19:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft and Mercedes-Benz built up a relationship in the cloud: Microsoft wants to be the IT side of any IT-OT convergences, and a new deal with Mercedes-Benz shows how it has built infrastructure to bring plant data into IT environments for analysis. Mercedes-Benz, meanwhile, has built its MO360 Data Platform to connect 30 passenger car manufacturing plants to Microsoft […]
The post IoT news of the week for Oct. 14, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a STEM culture on campus in Uganda]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/creating-stem-culture-on-campus-in-uganda.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/creating-stem-culture-on-campus-in-uganda.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Muhammad (Auwal) Samu, Developer Communities Regional Lead, Sub-Saharan Africa
 

  


Halimah Bukirwa says she felt like she knew nothing about computers or coding when she started university but threw herself into learning about STEM as much as possible.
“I committed to being the best at it, since I was given this awesome opportunity to actually study it.”  Originally thinking she’d pursue a career in the field of aviation, Halimah joined several developer communities to learn more about engineering. That’s when she found the Google Developer Student Club (GDSC) at her university.  




 Creating a culture of participation on campus
  
She joined the local GDSC chapter as a core team member first, helping out with general logistics and planning, then the next year she applied t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[First RISC-V laptop uses Alibaba TH1520 SoC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476739</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/first-risc-v-laptop-uses-alibaba-th1520-soc/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A project led by RISC-V International with DeepComputing and Xcalibyte has resulted in the first RISC-V laptop. We take a look at the chip behind the laptop and the people behind the project.
The post First RISC-V laptop uses Alibaba TH1520 SoC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The disabling of hardware codecs in community distributions]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910978/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910978/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T15:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software patents affect our systems in many ways, but perhaps most
strongly in the area of codecs — code that creates or plays back audio
or video that has been compressed using covered algorithms.  For this
reason, certain formats have simply been unplayable on many Linux
distributions — especially those backed by companies that are big
enough to be worth suing — without installing add-on software from
third-party repositories.  One might think that this problem could be
worked around by purchasing hardware that implements the patented algorithms,
but recent activity in the Fedora and openSUSE communities shows that life
is not so simple.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911168/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911168/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T13:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (dbus, dhcp, expat, kernel, thunderbird, vim, and weechat), Mageia (libofx, lighttpd, mediawiki, and python), Oracle (.NET 6.0 and .NET Core 3.1), Slackware (python3), SUSE (chromium, kernel, libosip2, python-Babel, and python-waitress), and Ubuntu (gThumb, heimdal, linux-aws, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-aws-hwe, linux-gcp, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, postgresql-9.5, and xmlsec1).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아바타 초보 강좌: 아바타 2를 기다리는 올바른 자세]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87216</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87216"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T11:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자칭 “세상의 왕” 제임스 카메론이 가장 최근에 연출한 작품은, 다큐멘터리를 제외하면, 무려 13년 전 작품 [아바타] (2009)다. 역대 흥행 성적 1위라는 [아바타]의 상업적 성과도 놀랍지만, 전 세계에 걸쳐 아바타 현상을 일으켰던 당시의 ‘영화적 충격’은 그야말로 경악할 만한 것이었다. 하지만 많은 시간이 지났고, 그로 인해 우리 기억은 13년 전 아바타가 우리에게 줬던 충격, 그 사실보다 이 […]
The post 아바타 초보 강좌: 아바타 2를 기다리는 올바른 자세 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>옥토</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[해커 - 칸트, 비트겐슈타인, 선험론적 논증]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222900066425</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222900066425"/>
        <updated>2022-10-14T04:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[해커의 <Insight & Illusion>의 초판은 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 유사성을 상세하게 추구한 책이다. 그런데 재판에서부터 해커는 이 유사성을 거부한다. 물론 칸트와 비트겐슈타인 사이에 유사성이 있지만, 해커에 의하면 그들 사이의 차이성이 더 크며, 이러한 차이성이 더 중요하다. 이런 차이성을 보이는 한 방식으로 해커는 <논리철학논고>에서 칸트적 의미의 선험론적 논증이 전개되고 있지 않다고 주장한다. 어떤 철학자들에 의하면, 후기 비트겐슈타인보다 오히려 <논리철학논고>가 대표적인 선험론적 철학의 모습을 보여주는데, 해커는 바로 이런 생각을 강하게 거부하고 있다. 해커의 <Kant and Wittgenstein: t.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing Machine-Learning Applications on the Raspberry Pi Pico]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14407</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/developing-machine-learning-applications-on-the-raspberry-pi-pico/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T17:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Raspberry Pi Pico is a versatile, low-cost development board that applies to many applications. This course will explore getting up and running with the Raspberry Pi Pico. We’ll mainly … Continue reading Developing Machine-Learning Applications on the Raspberry Pi Pico
Developing Machine-Learning Applications on the Raspberry Pi Pico first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some remotely exploitable kernel WiFi vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911062/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911062/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T14:36:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It would appear that there is a set of
memory-related vulnerabilities in the kernel's WiFi stack that can be
exploited over the air via malicious packets; five CVE numbers have been
assigned to the set.  Fixes are headed toward the
mainline and should show up in stable updates before too long; anybody who
uses WiFi on untrusted networks should probably keep an eye out for the
relevant updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A first look at Rust in the 6.1 kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910762/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910762/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:42:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There have been a lot of significant changes merged into the mainline for
the 6.1 release, but one of the changes that has received the most
attention will also have the least short-term effect for users of the
kernel: the introduction of support for the Rust programming language.  No
system with a production 6.1 kernel will be running any Rust code, but this
change does give kernel developers a chance to play with the language in
the kernel context and get a sense for how Rust development feels.  Perhaps
the most likely conclusion for most developers, though, will be that there
isn't yet enough Rust in the kernel to do much of anything interesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL 15 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911044/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911044/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 15 of the PostgreSQL database management system is out.


PostgreSQL 15 builds on the performance improvements of recent releases with
noticeable gains for managing workloads in both local and distributed
deployments, including improved sorting. This release improves the developer
experience with the addition of the popular
MERGE
command, and adds 
more capabilities for observing the state of the database.


There are a lot of changes in this release; click below for the details,
and see the
release notes for more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Why Roku needs the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11183</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-why-roku-needs-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest news this week is probably the launch of a line of inexpensive smart home products from Roku, the smart TV and set-top box maker. We talk about the products, its deal with Wyze and where you can get them. Then we move on to Matter, specifically when you might get Matter on your […]
The post Podcast: Why Roku needs the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/911042/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/911042/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T12:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libreoffice, rexical, ruby-nokogiri, and squid), Fedora (wavpack), Red Hat (expat), SUSE (gdcm, orthanc, orthanc-gdcm, orthanc-webviewer and rubygem-puma), and Ubuntu (GMP and unzip).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing TIFF image processing using AARCH64 (64-bit) Neon]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:d70a1405-d692-4345-8ab4-0ca6a6f8c4f7</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/optimizing-image-processing-using-aarch64-neon"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This guest blog shows how 64-bit Neon technology can be used to improve performance in image processing applications.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramin Zaghi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공공의대, 이제 더는 미룰 수 없습니다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87209</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87209"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:27:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“대한의사협회 및 현직 의사, 의대생 이외에 공공의대 설립을 반대하는 사람은 아무도 없다. (…중략…) 반대하는 이는 의사면허의 독점적 가치가 하락할 것을 우려하는 현직 의사, 의대생과 대한의사협회 뿐이다.” (나무위키, ‘국립공공보건의료대학/논란’ 중에서) 지난달 서울아산병원 간호사가 근무 중 쓰러졌지만, 응급수술할 의사가 없어 골든타임을 놓치고 말았습니다. 깊은 애도를 표하며, 필수 의료인력을 확보하지 못해 반복되는 참사를 보며 비통함을 금할 수 없습니다. […]
The post 공공의대, 이제 더는 미룰 수 없습니다 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy JBoss EAP applications with OpenShift Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>90ac6b54-9ceb-4cf1-9bc7-403bbc1e97ba</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/13/how-deploy-jboss-eap-applications-openshift-pipelines"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, How to migrate your Java applications to Red Hat OpenShift, you learned about the steps involved with building and deploying Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application Platform applications to OpenShift. This article will extend that scenario by introducing Red Hat OpenShift Pipelines to manage the artifact build process and enable integration with GitHub repositories and other external source control tools. This article will demonstrate that:
OpenShift Pipelines provide powerful, simple-to-use tools to manage Maven builds.
OpenShift Pipelines can be integrated with the JBoss EAP Source-to-Image (S2I) process, preserving the functionality provided by that tooling.
Implementing event triggers enables integration with external systems.
You can find the source code for both …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Hayes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced regex: Capture groups, lookaheads, and lookbehinds]]></title>
        <id>e15fa60e-48f3-4749-872e-ee0929ab2dd5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/13/advanced-regex-capture-groups-lookaheads-and-lookbehinds"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Capture groups, lookaheads, and lookbehinds provide a powerful way to filter and retrieve data according to advanced regular expression matching logic. This article explains capture groups, lookaheads, and lookbehinds, along with the fundamental syntax you need to know in order to write them.
This is the fourth article in a series about regular expressions:
Part 1: A beginner’s guide to regular expressions with grep
Part 2: Regex how-to: Quantifiers, pattern collections, and word boundaries
Part 3: Filter content in HTML using regular expressions in grep
In those articles, you learned about regular characters, metacharacters, quantifiers, pattern collections, and word groups. This article builds on those concepts. As in the previous articles in the series, the sample commands here execute …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Reselman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[메이야수 - 선조적 사실과 실재]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222899243578</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222899243578"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T06:09:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 오늘날의 과학은 - 수정가능한 가설의 자격일지라도 - 최초의 영장류의 출현에 선행하는 생명체 화석의 형성 시기, 지구의 형성 시기, 혹은 천체의 형성 시기, 더 나아가 우주 자체의 나이를 정확하게 규정할 수 있다. (우주의 기원은 135억 년 전, 지구의 형성은 44억 5천만 년 전, 지구의 생명체의 기원은 35억 년 전, 그리고 인간의 기원은 200만 년 전이다.) 그러할 때 우리가 관심을 갖는 질문은 이렇다. 천체물리학자들, 지질학자들, 혹은 고생물학자들이 우주의 나이, 지구의 형성 시기, 인간에 선행하는 어떤 종의 출현 시기, 인간 자체의 출현 시기를 문제 삼을 때, 그들은 무슨 이야기를 하는가? 사유의 출현에 선행하는 것으로, 심.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 13, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910503/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910503/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-13T01:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 13, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is there life without RTTI or How we wrote our own dynamic_cast]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0998/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0998/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There aren't many things left in modern C++ that don't fit the "Don't pay for what you don't use" paradigm. One of them is dynamic_cast. In this article, we'll find out what's wrong with it, and after that — try to find an alternative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] (Re)moving outdated Python tools and scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910898/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910898/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T19:33:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of September, Victor Stinner reported
on a security bug
fix he had been working on for a script from the CPython
Tools/scripts directory.  As part of that work, he realized
that there were 74 scripts in that directory that were potentially
outdated, unused, unmaintained, trivial, buggy, or some combination of all
of those.  It 
is not uncommon for projects to have code that accretes in overlooked
corners of the source tree, but it makes sense to periodically take a look
to see if changes are needed.  Stinner seems to have kicked that off for Python 
with his message.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCUXpresso IDE 11.6.1]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=35484</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/10/12/mcuxpresso-ide-11-6-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T16:24:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week I received the email notification, that NXP has released an update of the MCUXpresso IDE: the version 11.6.1. So I quickly checked it out: It is a maintenance release of the previous IDE 11.6.0, fixing a few issues … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the new Roku Smart Home is a safe bet for the company]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11162</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-the-new-roku-smart-home-is-a-safe-bet-for-the-company/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Add another smart home company to your list: Roku, the digital media streaming brand today introduced Roku Smart Home. The platform initially supports seven types of connected devices with relatively low prices and subscription options. It achieves this through a partnership with Wyze, a maker of capable but inexpensive connected cameras, locks, a video doorbell, […]
The post Why the new Roku Smart Home is a safe bet for the company appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting out of the product-v-engineering bottleneck by identifying              your "first team"]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html#exit</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html#exit"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rick and Kennedy start their discussion of how to break through the
      product-V-engineering bottleneck by getting people to identify and focus
      on their "first team", and to develop a shared understanding of how a
      business creates value.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Arm Cortex-M Intel-Hex (ihex) files]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/?p=3755</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2022/10/understanding-arm-cortex-m-intel-hex-ihex-files/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T14:04:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a flash image
The primary purpose of the ihex file in the embedded space is to create a file that is used to program/reprogram a target system. There are various file formats around, with the Intel Hex (ihex) format being among the most widely used.
The output of the linker stage of a build process is typically to generate a .elf file (Executable and Linkable Format). Many debuggers and programmers can work directly with the ELF file format. However, in many [...] 

The post Understanding Arm Cortex-M Intel-Hex (ihex) files appeared first on Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Cooling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910954/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910954/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.0.1,
5.19.15, and
5.15.73
stable kernels have been released; each contains a relatively small set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910953/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910953/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T13:01:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (mediawiki and twig), Oracle (expat, gnutls and nettle, and kernel), Red Hat (expat, kernel, and kpatch-patch), and Ubuntu (advancecomp and dotnet6).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국의 빅테크 규제 현황: 구글, 애플, 페이스북, 아마존은 민주주의를 위협하는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87189</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87189"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T08:52:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GAFA(구글, 애플, 페이스북=메타, 아마존)로 대표되는 빅테크 기업의 본국이라고 할 수 있는 미국에서도 빅테크를 규제해야 한다는 목소리가 높아지고 있습니다. 이는 빅테크가 시장에서의 공정한 경쟁과 혁신을 저해하고 이용자의 기본권을 침해하며 미디어의 다양성과 민주주의를 위협한다는 것에 대한 공감대가 확대되고 있음을 의미합니다. 미 하원, [디지털 시장의 경쟁 조사] (2004~2017) 2020년 10월, 미 하원 사법위원회 산하 반독점, 상업 및 […]
The post 미국의 빅테크 규제 현황: 구글, 애플, 페이스북, 아마존은 민주주의를 위협하는가 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크론 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588015</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588015/ib%ec%9d%98-22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T08:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to easily generate Helm charts using Dekorate]]></title>
        <id>6c9b52a7-8e74-41ac-ae1d-289cec072fc0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/12/generate-helm-charts-using-dekorate"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Helm is the most popular package manager that finds, shares, and deploys software built for Kubernetes. It would be best if you packaged Java applications as Helm charts containing all of the necessary metadata and resource definitions to configure them for distribution through Helm. This article introduces the Dekorate Helm extension as an easier way to generate and maintain Helm chart resources.
What are Helm charts?
A Helm chart is a collection of files inside a directory. The following files are mandatory:
Chart.yaml: Chart metadata, such as name, version, and developers.
values.yaml: Default configuration values for the chart in YAML.
templates: A directory containing the list of resources that, combined with values.yaml, generate the application when the chart is installed. The resou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jose Carvajal Hilario, Charles Moulliard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 주택 수요 2010년이래 최저치 기록]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588011</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588011/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%a3%bc%ed%83%9d-%ec%88%98%ec%9a%94-%ec%b5%9c%ec%a0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T03:40:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I solved the Dandelions paper-and-pencil game]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2022/10/12/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2022/10/12/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T03:02:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been reading Math Games with Bad Drawings, a great book
well-aligned to my interests. It’s given me a lot of new, interesting
programming puzzles to consider. The first to truly nerd snipe me was
Dandelions (full rules), an asymmetric paper-and-pencil game
invented by the book’s author, Ben Orlin. Just as with British Square two
years ago — and essentially following the same technique — I wrote a
program that explores the game tree sufficiently to play either side
perfectly, “solving” the game in its standard 5-by-5 configuration.
The source: dandelions.c
The game is played on a 5-by-5 grid where one player plays the dandelions,
the other plays the wind. Players alternate, dandelions placing flowers
and wind blowing in one of the eight directions, spreading seeds from all
flowers alon…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[블름버그]채권 수익률 정점은 이머징 투자 신호를 보낸다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588003</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588003/%ec%9d%b4%eb%a8%b8%ec%a7%95-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%ec%8b%a0%ed%98%b8"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T02:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국은 OPEC+ 감산 결정을 매우 happy하게 바라본다, FT 인터뷰 해석]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587996</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587996/%ec%84%9d%ec%9c%a0%ea%b0%90%ec%82%b0%ec%9d%84-%eb%b3%b4%eb%8a%94-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%81"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Wonderfully Terrible World of C and C++ Encoding APIs (with Some Rust)]]></title>
        <id>https://thephd.dev/the-c-c++-rust-string-text-encoding-api-landscape</id>
        <link href="https://thephd.dev/the-c-c++-rust-string-text-encoding-api-landscape"/>
        <updated>2022-10-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last time we talked about encodings, we went in with a C++-like design where we proved that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Pasture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A plan for the kernel Bugzilla]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910740/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910740/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T21:27:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's Bugzilla
instance is largely unloved and ignored, at least as a bug-reporting
tool for the bulk of the upstream kernel. At the recent Maintainers Summit,
Bugzilla was discussed during the regression-handling session led by Thorsten
Leemhuis.  In a followup to that discussion, Leemhuis posted
some ideas for improving the state of bugzilla.kernel.org to the
ksummit-discuss mailing list recently; the resulting discussion helped
clarify a number of problem areas for it—and for the Bugzilla tool itself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patent clouds for the Opus codec]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910848/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910848/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T16:35:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Opus codec is an audio codec that
was designed from the beginning to avoid existing patents in the field and
be royalty-free for all users.  It was standardized by the IETF in 2012 as
RFC 6716.
Now a company called Vectis ("a premier
full-suite IP licensing and consultancy boutique") is collecting
patents that are claimed to read on Opus as a way of demanding
royalties on its use. 
"The planned Opus program will focus on hardware devices and will not be
directed towards open-source software, applications, services, or
content".  (Thanks to Paul Wise).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VirtualBox 7.0.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910833/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910833/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T14:23:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.0.0
of the VirtualBox virtualization system is out.  Changes include support
for fully encrypted virtual machines, a new performance-monitoring tool,
improved theme support, and a number of new devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910828/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910828/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T14:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (connman, dbus, git, isc-dhcp, strongswan, and wordpress), Fedora (rubygem-pdfkit and seamonkey), Red Hat (gnutls,  nettle, rh-ruby27-ruby, and rh-ruby30-ruby), SUSE (libgsasl, python, and snakeyaml), and Ubuntu (graphite2, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15,
 linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-kvm,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-bluefield, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4,
 linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux, linux-dell300x, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2,
 linux-snapdragon, linux-hwe, linux-oracle, openssh, and pcre3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developing User Interfaces for Custom Boards with ESP microcontrollers]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/b8bc2ad04a00</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/developing-user-interfaces-for-custom-boards-with-esp-microcontrollers-b8bc2ad04a00?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:33:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Vilem Zavodny</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get Matter on your devices]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11145</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-get-matter-on-your-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T13:25:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published in my Oct. 7, 2022 newsletter.  The Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA) released version 1 of the Matter smart home interoperability protocol this week, and I and millions (maybe just tens of thousands) of other users are now wondering how we get access to it on our devices. Major smart home companies including […]
The post How to get Matter on your devices appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ensuring SAR compliance in connected consumer devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476734</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ensuring-sar-compliance-in-connected-consumer-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T11:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intelligent proximity sensors enable users of laptops and tablets to provide optimal connectivity and long battery life, but they must meet SAR compliance.
The post Ensuring SAR compliance in connected consumer devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Wong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top three tips for graph technology systems developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476728</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/top-three-tips-for-graph-technology-systems-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T10:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graph technology opens new avenues for obtaining insights from data to make more informed and agile business decisions. Here are three tips to help systems developers make the most of graphs.
The post Top three tips for graph technology systems developers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keshav Pingali</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 반도체 설비투자 전망, YoY 21% 증가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587992</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587992/2022%eb%85%84-%eb%b0%98%eb%8f%84%ec%b2%b4-%ec%84%a4%eb%b9%84%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T10:44:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JP모건, 넷플릭스 광고 비즈니스로 수십억 달러를 벌 수 있다고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587983</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587983/%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0-%eb%b9%84%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88%ec%8a%a4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T09:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[22년 3분기 AMD 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각, 경쟁력은 여전한데 시황이 문제로다..]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587981</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587981/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-amd-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-amd-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T09:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[누구를 위한 ’10년주택’이었나: 서민 쫓겨나고 LH공사 4.25조 이익]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87177</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87177"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T08:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“이 정책은 서민들의 주거 보호에 결국 실패했습니다. (…중략…) 그럼 누가 이득을 봤을까? LH와 민간 건설사 4곳이 분양 전환으로 얻는 시세차익은, LH 1조1천억원, 민간건설사 4곳 1조원, 합쳐서 2조1천억원입니다. 판교 분양에 성공했던 1만3천 세대의 아파트 주인들이 얻은 시세차익은 8조 원으로 추정됩니다. 공공이 강제수용한 땅에서 정작 서민들은 쫓겨나고, 공기업, 건설사들, 그리고 분양받은 소수의 사람들이 돈을 번 셈입니다.” – […]
The post 누구를 위한 ’10년주택’이었나: 서민 쫓겨나고 LH공사 4.25조 이익 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222897503036</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222897503036"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T08:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 소박실재론, 혹은 상식적 실재론의 기본 주장을 다음 세 명제로 표현할 수 있다. 비판해 보라. (가) 우리는 물리적 대상을 직접 지각한다. (나) 물리적 대상들은 우리로부터 독립적으로 존재하고, 공간에서 일정한 위치를 차지한다. (다) 이러한 대상들의 성질은 그 대상들이 현재 그렇게 있다고 지각하는 것과 같은 것이다. ** 비록 물리적 대상을 우리가 직접 지각한다고 할지라도, 우리가 지각하는 모든 것이 물리적 대상이 아니다. 꿈이나 환상에서 물리적 대상이 없는 지각을 우리는 한다. 물 속에서 굽은 것처럼 보이는 막대는 분명히 객관적 현상이지만, 막대의 굽음 혹은 굽은 막대는 사실, 즉 물리적 사실이 아니다. ** 현상과 실재, .......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[File-based Kafka Connect scenarios with end-to-end encryption]]></title>
        <id>690bf52f-bdb5-437c-93a7-5ba68d872b17</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/11/file-based-kafka-connect-scenarios-end-end-encryption"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first article in this series explained the need for client-side, end-to-end encryption for data passing through Apache Kafka. The article also introduced the Kryptonite for Kafka project, which integrates with Apache Kafka Connect to achieve automatic encryption and decryption with no changes to application code.
This article, the second and last in this series, contains more advanced examples that cover a common scenario: File-based data integration between different kinds of storage. I'll show Kryptonite for Kafka features that support fine-grained, field-level encryption in this use case.
To keep things simple in the examples, a local file system serves as the source while the sink is set up in MinIO (Figure 1), an open source object storage service compatible with AWS S3.




     …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hans-Peter Grahsl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in September]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/september-2022-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/september-2022-roundup"/>
        <updated>2022-10-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
September
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build smarter and ship faster with the latest updates across our ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/build-smarter-and-ship-faster-with-the-latest-ecosystem-updates.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/build-smarter-and-ship-faster-with-the-latest-ecosystem-updates.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T22:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeanine Banks, VP/GM, Developer X and DevRel
  
At last week’s Made by Google launch event, we announced several new hardware products including the Pixel 7 and Pixel 7 Pro, Google Pixel Watch, and Google Pixel Tablet—a suite of innovative products that we’re excited about. While sure to delight users, it got me thinking—what will these changes mean for developers? 
It’s hard to build experiences that let users enjoy the best that their devices have to offer. Undoubtedly this brings a level of complexity for developers who will need to build and test against multiple OS updates and new features. That’s the thing about development—the environment is constantly evolving. We want to cut through the complexity and make it simpler to choose the technology you use, whether for an app o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Misbeliefs in programming career or how to survive as a newcomer]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0997/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0997/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is purposed to be in a friendly spirit manner and carries neither mockery, nor snobbery. It intends to protect from unnecessary stress those who are entering the programming world for the first time. If you are learning to sort arrays, parse strings right now and believe in "oh, yes, this is what I'm going to do at work" — keep reading to find out newbies' common misbeliefs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why your smart thermostat might run before its programmed times]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11098</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-your-smart-thermostat-might-run-before-its-programmed-times/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T19:00:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a question from our Voicemail hotline about smart thermostats. This question was specific to the ecobee thermostats, although it could apply to other brands as well. Essentially, the question is why the smart thermostat doesn’t always run at programmed times, instead turning the HVAC on […]
The post Why your smart thermostat might run before its programmed times appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yasmine Evjen shares her passion for Android development and how to get involved at DevFest]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/yasmine-evjen-shares-her-passion-for-android-development-and-how-to-get-involved-at-devfest.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/yasmine-evjen-shares-her-passion-for-android-development-and-how-to-get-involved-at-devfest.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Komal Sandhu - Global Program Manager, Google Developer Groups
 

 

 “I would love to see more stepping out of our comfort zones, playing with technology, and bringing back that joy of what got us into Android development in the first place.”
Learn Android tools and tips from Android Community Lead, Yasmine Evjen, and hear from her first-hand on how to get involved.


Among the many inspiring experts in the Android developer community is Yasmine Evjen, a Googler for over five years who now serves as new Android Developer Relations Community team lead. Read on to see Yasmine’s Evjen’s outlook on her favorite Android tools and Android Developers who inspire her.
What is your role and how long have you been at Google?

     “I began my career at Google as a Design Advocate, support…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bottleneck #03: Product v Engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/03-product-v-engineering.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the third article on the Bottlenecks of Scaleups, Rick Kick and
      Kennedy Collins talk about the bottleneck that occurs when friction
      develops between product and engineering. In this first installment
      they discuss the signs that show this friction is occurring: with finger
      pointing and engineering lacking a sense of product context, as the teams
      communicate but don't collaborate.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Software: Applying Design for Change Principles to the Course Itself]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=22458</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2022/10/10/beyond-software-applying-design-for-change-principles-to-the-course-itself/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10 October 2022 by Phillip JohnstonA phrase that often repeats in my mind is Charlie Munger’s “take a simple idea and take it seriously.” Good ideas can be found in abundance. There are thousands of viable ways to improve your life and your work. What’s in short supply is application. We don’t take the ideas … 
Continue reading "Beyond Software: Applying Design for Change Principles to the Course Itself"
The post Beyond Software: Applying Design for Change Principles to the Course Itself appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A deeper look into the GCC Rust front-end]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909887/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909887/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T14:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philip Herron and Arthur Cohen presented an
update on the "gccrs" GCC front end for the Rust language at the
2022 Kangrejos conference.  Less than
two weeks later — and joined by David Faust — they did it again at the 2022 GNU Tools Cauldron.
This time, though, they were talking to GCC developers and refocused their
presentation accordingly; the result was an interesting look into the
challenges of implementing a compiler for Rust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910724/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910724/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:50:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (knot-resolver and libpgjava), Fedora (booth, dotnet3.1, expat, nheko, php-twig, php-twig2, php-twig3, poppler, python-joblib, and seamonkey), Mageia (colord, dbus, enlightenment, kitty, libvncserver, php, python3, and unbound), Slackware (libksba), SUSE (cyrus-sasl, ImageMagick, and xmlgraphics-commons), and Ubuntu (nginx and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How John Deere built its own cellular network for its factory]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11140</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-john-deere-built-its-own-cellular-network-for-its-factory/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T13:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was originally published in my Oct. 7, 2022 newsletter.  Last week, I made a trip out to Moline, Ill., to tour the more-than 3 million-square-foot factory where John Deere makes its X9 1100 combine, among other equipment, and which it built after spending half a million dollars in 2020 on 50 megahertz of wireless spectrum in […]
The post How John Deere built its own cellular network for its factory appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: Modules, recursion, and the Procedure Call Standard]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476533</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-modules-recursion-and-the-procedure-call-standard/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this lesson, you will see how the distinction between the declaration and the definition allows you to split the program into multiple modules —...
The post Programming embedded systems: Modules, recursion, and the Procedure Call Standard appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top tips on Linux, Rust, Kafka, and more]]></title>
        <id>e8d3ba9b-f454-462b-a9ad-d210d3632f10</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/10/top-tips-linux-rust-kafka-and-more"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[September was another fantastic month of content at Red Hat Developer. Check out some of the articles that our developers have created specifically for you! We've got 101-level learning articles, some articles that dive into technical matters, and we'll round out the month with tips and tricks for your current Linux environment.
Three places to begin your 101 learning
Bob Reselman introduces regular expressions with grep, and shows you how to use them to match patterns in text. His guide covers the basics of how to write a regular expression and gives many examples. Regular expressions are a way to search for patterns of characters within a larger body of text. They can be used to find all instances of the word bat, for instance, or all instances of a word that begins with b and ends with …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All Major C++17 Features You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2017/01/cpp17features/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2017/01/cpp17features/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ISO Committee accepted and published the C++17 Standard in December 2017. In this mega-long article, I’ve built (with your help!) a list of all major features of the new standard.
Please have a look and see what we get!
Language Features

New auto rules for direct-list-initialization
static_assert with no message
typename in a template template parameter
Removing trigraphs
Nested namespace definition
Attributes for namespaces and enumerators
u8 character literals
Allow constant evaluation for all non-type template  arguments
Fold Expressions
Unary fold expressions and empty parameter packs
Remove Deprecated Use of the register Keyword
Remove Deprecated operator++(bool)
Removing Deprecated Exception Specifications from C++17
Make exception specifications part of the type system
Aggregat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] ‘용 나는 개천’의 비결은 ‘부자 친구’ 많이 사귀기?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75386</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/09/npc_friendingbias/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_friendingbias"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T22:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개천에서 나는 용이 귀해진 요즘의 상황은 학계뿐 아니라 어느 분야라도 문제입니다. 다양성이 줄어들고 비슷비슷한 사고를 하는 사람끼리만 모여 있다 보면, 창의력과 역동성이 떨어지고 자연히 혁신도 일어나기 어려워지기 때문이죠. 집단이나 사회는 서로 다른 이들이 함께 섞여 지낼 때 결국 더 좋은 결과를 냅니다. 경제학자들은 ‘계층 이동의 사다리’를 오랫동안 연구해 왔습니다. 형편이 넉넉하지 못한 환경에서 자란 아이라도 성인이 돼서는 좋은 일자리를 얻고 중산층 또는 부유한 계층에 오를 기회가 풍부한 사회가 바람직한데, 그런 사회의 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Printing press+widespread religious behavior: A theory]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7160</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/10/09/printing-presswidespread-religious-behavior-a-theory/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T22:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The book The Weirdest People in the World: How the West Became Psychologically Peculiar and Particularly Prosperous provides an explanation of the processes which weakened the existing social ties of family and tribe; however, the emergence of WEIRD people (Western, Educated, Industrialized, Rich and Democratic) required new social norms to spread and be accepted throughout […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윌리엄스 뉴욕 연준 총재, 4.5%까지 미 금리 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587976</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587976/%ec%9c%8c%eb%a6%ac%ec%97%84%ec%8a%a4-%eb%89%b4%ec%9a%95-%ec%97%b0%ec%a4%80-%ec%b4%9d%ec%9e%ac-%eb%af%b8-%ea%b8%88%eb%a6%ac-4-5-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T06:31:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[28 스피노자의 철학 - 무의식, 신즉자연(神卽自然), 지성적 직관]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222895557611</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222895557611"/>
        <updated>2022-10-09T03:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김형효가 12.1 <스피노자의 신즉자연(神卽自然)으로서의 심즉물(心卽物)의 사유와 철학적 구원>에서 하고자 하는 작업은 스피노자가 유가의 양명학, 도가의 노장사상, 불교의 사상, 에카르트의 신학, 가브리엘 마르셀과 하이데거와 동일한 사유 노선에 서있다는 것을 해명하는 것이다. 그 사유 노선은 이미 우리가 보았듯이 만유재신론(萬有在神論)이고, 일즉다(一卽多)의 사유이다. 스피노자의 철학은 바로 이런 사유 노선에서 <본성의 존재론>에 대해서 말하고 있다. 들뢰즈에 의하면 스피노자의 철학은 데카르트와 같은 자아학이나 의식학이 아니다. 김형효는 자아라는 개념이 인간 이기심과 연결된다고 보고 있다. 우리는 <자.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[28 이성의 공적 사용과 사적 사용]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222894883485</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222894883485"/>
        <updated>2022-10-08T02:27:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 이성의 ‘공적 사용’과 ‘사적 사용’이란 무엇인가? 그 구분에 대해서 평가해 보라. <계몽을 위해서 자유 이외에 다른 것이 필요하지 않다. 자유라고 이름 부를 수 있는 것들 중에서 가장 해가 없는 자유는 모든 측면에서 그의 이성을 공적으로 사용할 수 있는 자유이다. 그러나 사방에서 “따지지 말라”는 소리가 들린다. 장교는 “따지지 말고 그저 훈련하라”고 말하고, 세무원은 “따지지 말고 그저 세금을 납부하라”고 하며, 성직자는 “따지지 말고 그저 믿기만 하라”고 외친다. 도처에 자유에 대한 제한이 존재하고 있다. 그렇다면 어떠한 제한이 계몽에 장애가 되는 것인가? 어떤 것이 계몽에 방해가 되지 않고 그것을 촉진시.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for October 7, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11138</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-october-7-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T17:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s IoT news was compiled and written by Kevin C. Tofel The Pixel Tablet morphs into a Nest Hub: Along with the Pixel 7, Pixel Watch, and new Nest products, Google this week showed off the Pixel Tablet. You can’t buy this Android tablet until next year, and you might not even want an Android […]
The post IoT news of the week for October 7, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Rose Niousha, GDSC Waseda Founder & WTM Ambassador]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/meet-rose-niousha-gdsc-waseda-founder-and-wtm-ambassador.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/meet-rose-niousha-gdsc-waseda-founder-and-wtm-ambassador.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Takuo Suzuki, Developer Relations Program Manager, Japan

   

Rose Niousha wanted to create a community where students could explore their technical interests without being held back by external factors or stereotypes. A passion for inclusion set her on a path to growing her Google Developer Student Clubs chapter and discovering the Women Techmakers (WTM) program.
After majoring in Computer Science at Waseda University, Rose realized many students had difficulty applying what they learned in school to practical environments and internships. Seeing a gap between theory and practice, she aimed to tackle these problems by founding a Google Developer Student Club (GDSC) on her campus. Through her leadership, the club became the largest chapter in Japan, with 177 active members. This…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 5.4.217]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910622/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910622/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T15:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released the 5.4.217
stable kernel with a set of important fixes, as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The first half of the 6.1 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910312/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910312/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T15:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.1 merge window is well underway: since it opened, 5,752 non-merge
changesets have been pulled into the mainline repository.  That is
approximately half of the work that had piled up in linux-next and marks a
good time to look at what has been merged so far.  Some long-awaited core
changes have landed for the next kernel release, but there are likely to be
more significant changes to come.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910606/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910606/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T14:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (dbus, isc-dhcp, and strongswan), Fedora (booth, php, php-twig, php-twig2, and php-twig3), Oracle (expat, prometheus-jmx-exporter, and squid), Red Hat (expat, openvswitch2.11, and squid), Scientific Linux (expat and squid), SUSE (exiv2, LibVNCServer, postgresql-jdbc, protobuf, python-PyJWT, python3, slurm, squid, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (libreoffice).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: Drones challenge for agriculture, plus IDE and BSP news]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476711</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-drones-challenge-for-agriculture-plus-ide-and-bsp-news/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s embedded news features various announcements including NXP’s HoverGames Challenge 3, new IDE and BSP support, the upcoming Hardware Pioneers Max show, plus more.
The post embedded news: Drones challenge for agriculture, plus IDE and BSP news appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How highly skilled engineers manage complexity of embedded systems design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476481</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-highly-skilled-engineers-manage-complexity-of-embedded-systems-design/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The complex nature of embedded systems and applications calls for a diversity of tools and techniques to be employed during the embedded system design life...
The post How highly skilled engineers manage complexity of embedded systems design appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard McCullagh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[성평등전주, ‘성노동자’ 개념 사상 검열로 작가 3인을 내쫓다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87165</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87165"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T07:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 7월 16일과 18일, 전주시가 설치·운영하는 기관인 전주시사회혁신센터 성평등전주(이하 ‘성평등전주’)는 ‘제3회 페미니즘 예술제 [지구탈출]’에 참여 작가로 선정된 10인 중 3인(작가 사랑해, 치명타, 이시마, 이하 ‘작가 3인’)을 이들의 사상과 양심을 이유로 일방적으로 전시에서 배제하였다. 성평등전주가 작가 3인을 전시에서 배제한 근거는 예술제 준비를 위한 비공개 워크숍에서 작가들이 했던 발언이었다. 작가 3인의 발언과 전시예정작품이 예술제 취지인 성평등 혹은 […]
The post 성평등전주, ‘성노동자’ 개념 사상 검열로 작가 3인을 내쫓다 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's inside an RPM .repo file?]]></title>
        <id>dced428e-79ee-490f-9f8f-e410e684dd97</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/07/whats-inside-rpm-repo-file"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The previous article in this series, How does RPM package discovery work?, described how the RPM package management technology discovers and installs an .rpm package on a local computer running the Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Fedora, or CentOS Stream operating system. In that article, you learned that the .repo files stored in the /etc/yum.repos.d directory of the local machine play a critical role in discovering, installing, and managing RPM packages.
This article goes to the next level of detail to describe the format specified for a .repo file.
This article describes not only the format specification for a .repo file but also describes the logic that's applied to a .repo file when managing RPM packages on a given machine. But, before delving in, let's review how RPM discovers a package on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Reselman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving from apt to dnf package management]]></title>
        <id>7989058e-2a55-483d-926e-36cbd5eff3bf</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/07/move-apt-dnf-package-management"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A package manager makes it simple to install GNU/Linux applications on a local computer. Before package management became commonplace, installing applications was a tedious, error-prone undertaking. The ease a package manager brings to installing an application on a Linux computer has been a major factor contributing to the widespread adoption of Linux as a mainstream operating system for both business and home users.
Package management under Linux is divided, however. Two major systems co-exist:
The APT package management system for Debian and its many derivatives, notably Ubuntu. Packages are marked with the .deb suffix and are managed through the apt command-line interface (CLI).
The RPM package management system for Red Hat Enterprise Linux and its derivatives, notably Fedora and CentO…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Reselman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 개인주의적 이성적 자아]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222894150752</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222894150752"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T04:09:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[브라이도티의 <포스트휴먼>은 결론을 제외한 각 장에서 다음과 같은 <제안>을 하고 있다. 첫째, 개인적 자아를 넘어서야 한다. 둘째, 인간중심주의로부터 벗어나야 한다. 단지 인간종의 생명만이 중요한 것이 아니다. 셋째, 삶과 죽음, 인간과 비인간이라는 이분법에서 벗어나야 한다. 넷째, 단지 인간만을 다루는 인문학으로부터 벗어나야 한다. 이렇게 정리된 주장에 대해서 나는 찬동한다. 그렇지만 그녀의 서술 스타일이 논증적이라기 보다는 서사적이고 설명적이며 제안적이기 때문에, 개인적 자아를 넘어서야 한다는 그녀의 첫째 주장도 글자 그대로 단순하게 받아들이기 어렵다. 그녀가 생각하는 극복해야 할 <개인적 자아.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[실리콘밸리의 스타트업 바이블 1 – ‘탁월한 조직이 빠지기 쉬운 5가지 함정’]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2426</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2022/10/07/svbible-1-kr-5dysfunctions-of-a-team/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=svbible-1-kr-5dysfunctions-of-a-team"/>
        <updated>2022-10-07T03:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[친구들과 팀 스포츠 경기를 해보신 분이라면, 원론적으로 당연한 ‘팀워크’를 성공하기가 얼마나 어려운지 실감하실 것 입니다. 하물며, 다 큰 어른들이 각자 세부적으로 다른 성공의 목표를 가지고 있는 회사에서, 시스템과 원칙이 여물지 않은 스타트업이라면 혼란이 더 크리라 예상합니다. 특히, 기존 멤버에서 경력직 멤버가 추가되는 여정, 한국팀 위주로 구성되었다가 글로벌 오피스를 세우며, 외국인 임원들이 입사하며 겪게 되는 입체적Continue reading "실리콘밸리의 스타트업 바이블 1 – ‘탁월한 조직이 빠지기 쉬운 5가지 함정’"
실리콘밸리의 스타트업 바이블 1 – ‘탁월한 조직이 빠지기 쉬운 5가지 함정’ appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 미중 갈등 시대, 각국의 쉽지 않은 균형 잡기]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75393</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/06/npc_pelosiinasia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_pelosiinasia"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 8월 8일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 올린 글입니다. 낸시 펠로시 미국 하원의장이 아시아 지역을 방문하면서 관련 뉴스가 쏟아져 나왔습니다. 대만 방문으로 인한 중국과 미국 사이의 갈등 고조가 가장 큰 주목을 받았지만, 국내에서는 방문지 가운데 한국이 포함되었음에도 휴가 중인 윤석열 대통령이 펠로시 의장을 만나지 않은 것을 두고 공방이 오갔습니다. 미국과 중국 사이에서 균형을 유지하기 위한 전략이라는 분석 이면에 한국 정부가 공항 의전도 제공하지 않은 것에 대한 비판이 일었고, (이후 대통령실이 오보라고 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fingerprinting systems with TCP source-port selection]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910435/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910435/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T17:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in May 2022, a mysterious set of patches titled insufficient TCP
source port randomness crossed the mailing lists and was subsequently
merged (at -rc6) into the 5.18 kernel.  Little information was available at
the time about why significant changes to the networking stack needed to be
made so late in the development cycle.  That situation has
finally changed with the publication of this paper by Moshe Kol,
Amit Klein, and Yossi Gilad.  It seems that the way the kernel chose port
numbers for outgoing network connections made it possible to uniquely
fingerprint users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Next, developer style]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/google-cloud-next-developer-style.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/google-cloud-next-developer-style.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeana Jorgensen, Senior Director, Cloud Product Marketing and Sustainability, Google
  

 
Google Cloud Next is coming up on October 11 - 13. Register at no cost today and join us live to explore what’s new and what’s coming next in Google Cloud. 
You’ll find lots of developer-specific content in the Developer Zone. Here’s a preview of what we’ve curated for you this year. 
A developer keynote to get you thinking about the future
  
For the Next developer keynote we’re going to share our top 10 cloud technology predictions that we believe could come true by the end of 2025.
Hear from our experts who are on the cutting edge of many of these technology trends, whether it's AI, data and analytics, or modern cloud infrastructure:






Jeanine Banks, VP of Developer Products and Comm…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Software Architecture Killers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=14395</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/5-software-architecture-killers/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T14:56:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The chip shortage has forced many embedded systems companies to rethink their software architecture. Many embedded systems have tightly coupled embedded software that makes the hardware-dependent microcontroller code indistinguishable from … Continue reading 5 Software Architecture Killers
5 Software Architecture Killers first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910492/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910492/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T13:20:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bind9 and nodejs), Red Hat (prometheus-jmx-exporter and squid), Slackware (dhcp), SUSE (pngcheck and sendmail), and Ubuntu (isc-dhcp, kitty, and linux-gcp-5.4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Matter is here. Now what?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11133</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/episode-392-matter-is-here-now-what/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T13:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matter is now official after almost three years of waiting, and Kevin and I are super excited. Well, I am. Kevin is more measured, but we talk about what to expect and when to expect Matter to start changing your smart home. In related news, we discuss Google’s new doorbell, mesh router and plans for […]
The post Podcast: Matter is here. Now what? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미 국방부 플랫폼 서비스 ‘플랫폼 원’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87156</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87156"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T09:21:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[현대전에서 소프트웨어의 중요성은 특별히 더 강조할 필요 없을 정도로 모두 공감하고 있다. 상대방의 주요 인프라를 무력화시키는 사이버전뿐만 아니라, 전장에서 싸우는 군인의 전투 능력 향상 및 생존 가능성 증대를 위해서도 소프트웨어에 의존할 수밖에 없는 것이 현대전의 양상이다. 이러한 전투 현장에서의 역량 우위는 궁극적으로 전쟁에서의 전술적 우위를 확보할 수 있는 기반을 제공한다. 전장 상황은 시시각각 변하기 마련이고, […]
The post 미 국방부 플랫폼 서비스 ‘플랫폼 원’ first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make your APIs more discoverable]]></title>
        <id>e4fddd4c-750e-4fe6-911e-0fb458b979a7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/06/how-make-your-apis-more-discoverable"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[API discoverability is a key aspect of any API management initiative. The discoverability of an API directly impacts its adoption and usage. A typical big enterprise with multiple development teams might build hundreds of APIs that they would want to reuse internally or share with partners that build complementary applications. If the teams cannot discover existing APIs, they might build a new API with the same functionality, which leads to duplication of efforts and underutilization of the existing API. It is also an unscalable practice to contact the API developer each time someone wants to use the API.
There needs to be a better and more hands-off way for internal teams and partners to discover and understand the usage of these APIs without directly contacting the developers who built t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vamsi Ravula, Hugo Guerrero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Kubernetes improves developer agility]]></title>
        <id>9d53e549-98cc-4f0c-b8cd-a5da017607d2</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/06/kubernetes-improves-developer-agility"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the first in a series that explains Kubernetes storage on a high level. In the series, I provide information for a programmer or software architect to decide which types of storage meet the requirements for their applications running on Kubernetes. This series provides links to help you go deeper into your chosen technologies but does not dig into YAML syntax or Kubernetes APIs. Whether a novice or experienced with Kubernetes, this overview can guide you toward a storage architecture that is right for your application.
Follow the series:
Part 2:  A developer’s guide to the functions of Kubernetes storage
I explain the concepts of persistent volumes and storage provisioners and how they enable system administrators to manage storage for a Kubernetes cluster.
Part 3:  Why CSI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Lozano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A developer’s guide to Kubernetes storage concepts]]></title>
        <id>5609d0da-8bf2-4c07-b7de-43873612ae51</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/06/kubernetes-storage-concepts"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This second article continues a series discussing Kubernetes storage concepts. I will define the concepts of volumes, persistent volume claims, and storage classes, and why they should matter to a developer. I will also explain how persistent volumes and storage provisioners enable system administrators to manage storage for a Kubernetes cluster while offering developers self-service to storage. You will also discover the special abilities of stateful sets.
Follow the series:
Part 1:  How Kubernetes improves developer agility
The first part of this series explains why storage is essential, even for developers developing "stateless" applications based on microservices architectures. I also explain the role of Kubernetes in managing and providing storage volumes for applications running as p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Lozano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why CSI drivers are essential in Kubernetes storage]]></title>
        <id>a40aab57-d874-4edf-980f-a443d433f8ed</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/06/csi-drivers-essential-kubernetes-storage"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is the third and final part of the series about Kubernetes storage concepts. I will explain how Container Storage Interface (CSI) drivers enable advanced storage features necessary for production environments and CI/CD pipelines. This article also underscores the need for storage products designed for Kubernetes versus storage designed for traditional physical and virtual data centers or Infrastructure-as-a-Service (IaaS) clouds.
Follow the series:
Part 1:  How Kubernetes improves developer agility
The first part of this series explains why storage is important, even for developers who are developing stateless applications based on microservices architectures. I describe the unique needs of containerized applications. It also explains the role of Kubernetes in managing and pro…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Lozano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 6, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909801/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909801/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-06T01:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for October 6, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] NVIDIA and nouveau]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910343/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910343/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T21:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of source code for NVIDIA
graphics hardware was perhaps something of a surprise; at least at a quick
glance, it seems
like that could lead to an in-tree, officially supported driver.  For many
years, though, the nouveau
project has been working on an upstream driver for NVIDIA hardware, so an
obvious question is what happens with nouveau in light of the NVIDIA
announcement.  Kernel graphics maintainer Dave Airlie gave a talk at the
2022 Linux Plumbers Conference (LPC) to
help shed some light on that subject.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you plan to take on .NET MAUI? Get ready for an adventure with NullReferenceException]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0996/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0996/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Multi-platform App UI is a framework written by professionals. However, the code of some of its functions looks like the developers could have forgotten what null reference dereferencing could lead to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OPEC+ 대규모 감산을 발표한 후 유가 전망 by Market Watch]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587967</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587967/opec-%ea%b0%90%ec%82%b0-%eb%b0%9c%ed%91%9c-%ed%9b%84-%ec%9c%a0%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T20:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Favorite Software AND Hardware Tools for Embedded Systems Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1473.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1473.php"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T17:07:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, at the Embedded Online Conference, we interviewed the speakers and asked them what were some of their favorite software and hardware tools for Embedded development.  



We aggregated all their answers in one insightful video that you can watch here.

Although you should...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter 1.0 spec aims for interoperable smart home IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476675</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/matter-1-0-spec-aims-for-interoperable-smart-home-iot/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T17:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matter 1.0 specification helps alleviate the challenges of having different device ecosystems, products and protocols communicate by offering one unified standard for device makers to follow for many smart home applications.
The post Matter 1.0 spec aims for interoperable smart home IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Thorny Problem of Keeping the Internet’s Time (New Yorker)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910418/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910418/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T15:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The New Yorker has a
lengthy article on the Network Time Protocol and its creator David
Mills.


	Coders sometimes joke, morbidly, about the “bus factor.” How many
	people need to get hit by a bus before a given project is
	endangered? It’s difficult to determine the bus factor for N.T.P.,
	and time synchronization more broadly, especially now that
	companies such as Google have developed their own N.T.P.-inspired
	proprietary code. But it seems reasonable to say that N.T.P.’s bus
	factor is rather small.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Al-Qudsi: Implementing truly safe semaphores in rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910417/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910417/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T15:26:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mahmoud Al-Qudsi provides
extensive details on what it takes to implement a safe semaphore type
in the Rust language.


	The problem is that with n > 1, there’s no concept of a
	“privileged” owning thread and all threads that have “obtained” the
	semaphore do so equally. Therefore, a rust semaphore can only ever
	provide read-only (&T) access to an underlying resource,
	limiting the usefulness of such a semaphore almost to the point of
	having no utility. As such, the only safe “owning” semaphore with
	read-write access that can exist in the rust world would be
	Semaphore<()>, or one that actually owns no data and can
	only be used for its side effect of limiting concurrency while the
	semaphore is “owned,” so to speak.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910396/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910396/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T14:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.19.14,
5.15.72,
5.10.147,
5.4.216, and
4.19.261
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910395/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910395/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T14:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (barbican, mediawiki, and php-twig), Fedora (bash, chromium, lighttpd, postgresql-jdbc, and scala), Mageia (bash, chromium-browser-stable, and golang), Oracle (bind, bind9.16, and squid:4), Red Hat (bind, bind9.16, RHSSO, and squid:4), Scientific Linux (bind), SUSE (cifs-utils, libjpeg-turbo, nodejs14, and nodejs16), and Ubuntu (jackd2, linux-gke, and linux-intel-iotg).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Applying Machine Learning to Biology is Hard – But Worth It]]></title>
        <id>https://future.com/?p=7114</id>
        <link href="https://future.com/why-applying-machine-learning-to-biology-is-hard-but-worth-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jimmy Lin is CSO of Freenome, which is developing blood-based tests for early cancer detection, starting with colon cancer. He is a pioneer in developing computational approaches to extract insights from large-scale genomic data, having spearheaded the computational analyses of the first genome-wide sequencing studies in multiple cancer types.  Lin talked to Future about the... Read More
The post Why Applying Machine Learning to Biology is Hard – But Worth It appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jimmy Lin and Nicole Neuman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제프리스, 흥청망청한 아마존 투자 전략은 반독점 규제를 겨냥한 두더지 잡기((whack-a-mole) 전략이라고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587943</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587943/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T11:21:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 S&P 500 전망, 약세장 반등 후 더 하락할 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587941</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587941/sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-4"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T11:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The state of driver monitoring systems (DMS) today]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476666</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-state-of-driver-monitoring-systems-dms-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T10:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Advances in technology and new safety regulations and legislation are accelerating the adoption of driver monitoring systems (DMS) into passenger vehicles, a feature expected to become mandatory in new cars in many countries by the end of the decade.
The post The state of driver monitoring systems (DMS) today appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Pluemer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빅테크(GAFAM)가 미디어 다양성에 미치는 영향]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87143</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87143"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T08:55:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[전 세계적으로 GAFAM(Google, Apple, Facebook, Amazon,Microsoft)의 독점과 불공정한 지위 남용으로 기울어진 운동장의 형태를 보이고 있습니다. 특히, 빅테크(디지털 플랫폼)가 온라인 소통의 중심으로 부상하면서 뉴스 미디어는 위기에 직면했습니다. 이 글에서는 ‘빅테크와 뉴스 미디어’ 사이의 불균형을 살펴보았습니다. 빅테크로 인해 어떻게 뉴스가 소비되는지, 그 소비패턴의 변화와 현황에 주목하여 문제점을 짚어보았습니다. 빅테크가 광고 비즈니스 독점과 어떤 관계가 있는지, 어떤 관점으로 […]
The post 빅테크(GAFAM)가 미디어 다양성에 미치는 영향 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Filter content in HTML using regular expressions in grep]]></title>
        <id>4bc5a4ab-1f48-4233-b219-a86d2df9ae9a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/05/filter-content-html-using-regular-expressions-grep"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article is a third in a series about executing regular expressions using the grep executable that ships with Linux operating systems. The grep command filters content in a file or as output from stdout.
The first article in this series described the basics of using metacharacters and regular characters to create regular expressions. The second discussed working with quantifiers, pattern collections, groups, and word boundaries in regular expressions. This article uses the features described in the previous articles, along with new ones, to match and filter content in HTML files.
Matching and retrieving text from HTML is a common task for a broad variety of IT professionals, particularly when troubleshooting issues in web pages. Thus, being able to apply regular expressions to HTML fil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Reselman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유심론, 관념론, 내적 초월주의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222892357702</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222892357702"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T04:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[식(識)은 주관적 마음 상태이다. 반면에 경(境)은 대상들이다. 식과 경, 어느 것이 우선적인가? 유식학은 이 문제에 대해 유식무경(唯識無境), 즉 식만 있으며, 식을 떠난 경은 존재하지 않는다고 주장한다. 그런데 우선성에 대한 질문 자체가 정당한가? <식을 떠난 경이 존재하지 않는다>는 표현이 애매하다. 그것은 경, 즉 대상은 식에 의존한다는 것을 의미한다. 또한 존재하는 대상에 대해서 우리가 알기 위해서 그것이 원리적으로 우리의 인식 대상이 되어야 한다는 것을 의미한다. 원리적으로 우리가 절대로 알 수 없는 대상의 존재라는 개념은 어떤 의미에서 공허하다. <개체적인 물질 또는 보편적인 관념은 그것을 인식하는 주.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to build a WaitGroup from a 32-bit integer]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2022/10/05/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2022/10/05/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T03:19:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go has a nifty synchronization utility called a WaitGroup, on which
one or more goroutines can wait for concurrent task completion. In other
languages, the usual task completion convention is joining threads doing
the work. In Go, goroutines aren’t values and lack handles, so a WaitGroup
replaces joins. Building a WaitGroup using typical, portable primitives is
a messy affair involving constructors and destructors, managing lifetimes.
However, on at least Linux and Windows, we can build a WaitGroup out of a
zero-initialized integer, much like my 32-bit queue and 32-bit
barrier.
In case you’re not familiar with it, a typical WaitGroup use case in Go:

var wg sync.WaitGroup
for _, task := range tasks {
    wg.Add(1)
    go func(t Task) {
        // ... do task ...
        wg.Done()
    }(tas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[장기적으로 K-방산 전망이 밝은 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587939</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587939/k-%eb%b0%a9%ec%82%b0-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-05T00:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 인생의 중요한 결정을 데이터를 기반으로 내릴 수 있을까요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75375</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/04/npc_datadecision/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_datadecision"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T22:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사람들은 항상 거짓말을 합니다. 누구도 지켜보지 않을 때를 제외하면 말이죠. 그리고 무언가를 궁금해 할 때도 사람들은 솔직하게 자신의 의도를 드러냅니다. 이 두 가지 조건이 모두 만족하는 순간이 있습니다. 바로, 검색 엔진에 무언가를 찾아볼 때입니다. 구글의 데이터과학자였던 세스 스티븐스 다비도위치는 사람들이 구글에 무엇을 검색하는지를 바탕으로 2017년 ‘모두 거짓말을 한다’를 썼고, 이 책은 베스트셀러가 되었습니다. 그는 이 책에서 사람들이 남들에게는 밝히지 않는 성적 취향과 같은 사람의 진짜 속마음을 구글 검색에는 어떻게 드러내는지 보였고, 이런 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does RPM package discovery work?]]></title>
        <id>84e44017-4068-4bde-8e8d-be86a9e1a5fd</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/04/how-does-rpm-package-discovery-work"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T22:44:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RPM package management system is used to install Linux applications on computers running the Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Fedora, and CentOS Stream operating systems. With RPM, users can install an application from a terminal window by executing nothing more than a single command:
dnf install 



Or:
yum install 



Most users never need to go beyond using the dnf or yum install commands, which we reviewed in an earlier article, Move from apt to dnf package management. These commands hide the complexity of what's going on underneath the covers during the installation process. But when things go wrong with an installation, it's useful to understand how RPM goes about locating and installing applications, at least for debugging purposes.
You'll learn about those details in this article. You…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Reselman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A discussion on printk()]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909980/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909980/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T20:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's print function, printk(), has been the target of
numerous improvement efforts over the years for a
variety of reasons.  One persistent problem with printk() has been
that its latency is unacceptably high for the realtime Linux kernel; at
this point, printk() represents the last piece needing changes
before the 
RT_PREEMPT patches can be fully merged.  So there have been efforts
to rework printk() for latency and lots of other reasons, but
those have not made it into the mainline; a recent discussion at
the 2022 Linux Plumbers Conference (LPC)
seems to have paved the way for new solution to land in the mainline before
too long.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ekstrand: Introducing NVK]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910319/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910319/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T16:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Ekstrand announces
a new Vulkan driver for NVIDIA hardware on the Collabora blog.  It
seems to be off to a good start, but there is some work yet to do:


	Normally, I would have submitted the merge request long ago. There
	are far more alpha-quality drivers already in Mesa. The problem is
	that we really need a new kernel uAPI to support Vulkan properly
	and I don't want to be stuck supporting the current nouveau uAPI
	for the next five years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter is now official!]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11115</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/matter-is-now-official/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T16:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Connectivity Standards Alliance has certified and released the first version of the Matter smart home interoperability protocol Tuesday and I couldn’t be happier. This means that member companies can now put their devices through the certification protocol and get a badge showing that their products are Matter compliant. Matter is an application level protocol […]
The post Matter is now official! appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel update 5.19.13 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910313/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910313/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T15:43:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.19.13 stable kernel update is out.
"This release is to resolve a regression on some Intel graphics
	systems that had problems with 5.19.12.  If you do not have this
	problem with 5.19.12, there is no need to upgrade."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google preps Google Home for Matter, adds new gear]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11105</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/google-preps-google-home-for-matter-adds-new-gear/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T15:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has launched two new devices for the smart home and is revamping its Google Home app all in preparation for Matter and the third wave of innovation it believes the smart home is set to undergo. The search giant explained its vision for the smart home, launched a new router designed for Wi-Fi 6E, […]
The post Google preps Google Home for Matter, adds new gear appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Left on the Cutting Room Floor]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=22456</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2022/10/04/left-on-the-cutting-room-floor/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T14:50:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[4 October 2022 by Phillip JohnstonThere is always a gap between the creation and the creator’s initial vision. At some point, you need to call your work “done”. You need to overcome the perfectionistic urge and leave some of your material on the cutting room floor. But it is painful to accept that some of … 
Continue reading "Left on the Cutting Room Floor"
The post Left on the Cutting Room Floor appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH 9.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910301/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910301/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T14:06:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH 9.1 has been released.  It is advertised as a bug-fix release (and
it addresses a few low-priority memory-safety bugs), but
there's also a new option to set the minimum RSA key size for
authentication, a few sftp extensions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910300/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910300/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T14:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (barbican), Fedora (libdxfrw, librecad, and python-oauthlib), Oracle (bind), Red Hat (bind and rh-python38-python), SUSE (bind, chromium, colord, libcroco, libgit2, lighttpd, nodejs12, python, python3, slurm, slurm_20_02, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (linux-azure, python-django, strongswan, and wayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제프리스, 아마존 주가는 너무 저렴해서 아마존 주식 투자는 매력적이라고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587937</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587937/%eb%a7%a4%eb%a0%a5%ec%a0%81%ec%9d%b8-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T13:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockley Photonics puts lasers on a chip for medical sensors]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11093</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/rockley-photonics-puts-lasers-on-a-chip-for-medical-sensors/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my Sept. 30 newsletter.  Rockley Photonics, which began its life using photonics for communications between computers, has been building chips to manage light for the past nine years. With photonics, light is used instead of electricity to send data. After being used to send data (as in fiber networks) […]
The post Rockley Photonics puts lasers on a chip for medical sensors appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[10/4] 3분기 테슬라 판매량를 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=587926</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/587926/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89-%eb%b0%8f-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T08:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부동산 가격 폭등의 진짜 원인: 다주택자·법인 소유 1,000만 채의 ‘투기적 가수요’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87135</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87135"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T08:21:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난해 연말과 올해 초 압도적 다수의 미디어와 자칭 타칭 전문가들은 2022년 주택시장이 상승할 것이라고 예견했다. 이들이 주택시장 상승을 전망하면서 내놓은 주된 근거는 신규주택 공급 부족이다. 그러나 주택시장이 대세 하락을 본격화한 지금 신규주택 공급이 부족하다는 목소리는 찾을 길이 없다. 어째서 이런 일이 벌어진 것일까? 재고 주택시장 공급량, 주택시장 가격 좌우 기억을 복기해보면 금방 알 일인데, ‘신규주택 […]
The post 부동산 가격 폭등의 진짜 원인: 다주택자·법인 소유 1,000만 채의 ‘투기적 가수요’ first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김형효의 전기 하이데거와 유식학(唯識學)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222891506405</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222891506405"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T06:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김형효는 <하이데거와 마음의 철학>(2000)에서 전기 하이데거, 즉 <존재와 시간>의 하이데거를 불교의 유식학(唯識學)의 관점에서 해명하고 있다. 그는 하이데거와 유식학의 유사성을 세 가지 관점에서 지적하고 있는데, 그 첫 번째가 현존재와 세상, 또는 마음과 세상의 관계이다. <현존재는 바로 마음의 존재이다. 현존재는 마음에 현시되어 있는 진리이다. 따라서 마음의 존재가 곧 진리이다. 현존재의 Da는 심식(心識)이다. 심식은 마음의 현상화이며, 그 현상화가 마음의 상분(相分)으로서 세상이다. 그래서 <Da>는 견분(見分)으로 보면 마음의 관심이고, 상분(相分)으로 보면 세상이다. 그 세상은 세상에 존재함으로.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocket article: Debugging ccache misses]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/ccache-debugging</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/ccache-debugging"/>
        <updated>2022-10-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides a few tips and tricks for diagnosing ccache misses, to
keep your C/C++ build nice and snappy!
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List in C#: implementation and features]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0995/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0995/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[List is one of the most used collections in C#. Let's inspect the features of List and look at how some of its parts are implemented.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.38 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910213/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910213/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T20:19:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.38.0 of the Git distributed version-control  system has been released.  It comes with lots of new features and bug fixes, some of the former are described in a GitHub blog post by Taylor Blau.  Highlights include the promotion of the scalar addition for large repositories into Git core, improvements to multi-branch rebase operations with --update-refs, performance improvements, a bash prompt indication for unmerged indexes, and lots more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Netdev 0x16 accepted sessions announced]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910210/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910210/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T20:02:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The accepted sessions for the upcoming Netdev 0x16 have been posted.  The conference will be held virtually and in-person in Lisbon, Portugal October 24-28.  In addition, early-bird registration rates have been extended to October 4.

Netdev 0x16, like all the previous netdev conferences, is a conference of the netdev community, by the netdev community, for the netdev community. Linux kernel networking and user space utilization of the interfaces to the Linux kernel networking subsystem are the focus. If you are using Linux as a boot system for proprietary networking, then this conference _may not be for you_.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing functionally safe RTD systems: Certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476367</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/implementing-functionally-safe-rtd-systems-certification/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article in a two-part series on implementing functionally safe RTD systems, we describe certification, the need to review the system for potential...
The post Implementing functionally safe RTD systems: Certification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mary McCarthy and Wasim Shaikh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some 6.0 development statistics]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/909625/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/909625/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T17:55:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released
the 6.0 kernel on October 2.  There were 15,402 non-merge
changesets pulled into the mainline for this release, growing the kernel by
just over 1.1 million lines of code.  As usual, a lot went into the
creation of this kernel release; read on for a look at where some of that
work came from.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/910161/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/910161/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T14:24:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium, gdal, kernel, libdatetime-timezone-perl, libhttp-daemon-perl, lighttpd, mariadb-10.3, node-thenify, snakeyaml, tinyxml, and tzdata), Fedora (enlightenment, kitty, and thunderbird), Mageia (expat, firejail, libjpeg, nodejs, perl-HTTP-Daemon, python-mako, squid, and thunderbird), Scientific Linux (firefox and thunderbird), SUSE (buildah, connman, cosign, expat, ImageMagick, python36, python39, slurm, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial and linux-gke-5.15).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Somalytics turns paper into cheap proximity sensors]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11090</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/somalytics-turns-paper-into-cheap-proximity-sensors/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T14:19:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my Sept. 30 newsletter.  This week’s newsletter is all about sensors. When I evaluate technology, I often look at whether or not it changes the cost, power consumption, or performance of a typical process by a significant factor. One of the easiest ways to do that is through new […]
The post Somalytics turns paper into cheap proximity sensors appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing a power-saving solenoid driver: Design implementation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476335</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/designing-a-power-saving-solenoid-driver-design-implementation/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article concludes a two-part series, describing implementation of a dual power-saving solenoid driver that can achieve huge power savings for two solenoids in a...
The post Designing a power-saving solenoid driver: Design implementation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maicon Bruno Hofmann</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting UX right for household appliances]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/quality/getting-ux-right-household-appliances/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/quality/getting-ux-right-household-appliances/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T09:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UX (user experience) is a fundamental part of product design that is often overlooked in many industries, from medical devices to […]
The post Getting UX right for household appliances appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoe Griffiths</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lumotive and Gpixel launch 3D lidar reference design platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4476662</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/lumotive-and-gpixel-launch-3d-lidar-reference-design-platform/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-03T09:39:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies partner to offer 3D lidar sensor reference design platform for mobility and industrial applications.
The post Lumotive and Gpixel launch 3D lidar reference design platform appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Sustainable Refillable Active Coal Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=13198</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2022/09/20/build-a-sustainable-refillable-active-coal-filter/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T12:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever used air filters to keep smells, fumes and dust at a low level in your workshop, you for sure came in contact with these expensive throwaway active coal filters. While throwing-away the used active coal seems to be unavoidable, all the thrown away plastic and packaging of the filter can easily be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE): A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://novelbits.io/?p=22402</id>
        <link href="https://novelbits.io/bluetooth-low-energy-ble-complete-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T11:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet of Things (IoT) has been a buzzword for decades, but today this market is far from theoretical. There are over 10 billion active IoT devices globally, and one of the key technologies enabling this market growth is Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE).  Introduced in 2012, this flexible protocol provides wireless connection for many of […]
The post Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE): A Complete Guide appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammad Afaneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extreme Integers – Doom from Below]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=13025</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2022/09/04/extreme-integers-doom-from-below/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T09:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a beginner or immediate C++ programmer, you heard never mixing unsigned and signed integer types or avoiding unsigned integers at all. There was also this talk about undefined behaviour. Yet, in embedded software development, there is no way around unsigned integers – so what is behind all these warnings? Wonderful that you strive to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a BLE Module for Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://novelbits.io/?p=22320</id>
        <link href="https://novelbits.io/how-to-choose-ble-module-for-your-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T14:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a way to add BLE connectivity to your project, you have many options. So how do you know which module is right for you? We’ll help you understand the options available and make the best decision for your needs. How to select a BLE module There are a few key considerations […]
The post How to Choose a BLE Module for Your Project appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nthatisi Hlapisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>