<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2022-11-26T20:15:00.909Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[도(道)와 언어]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222938729876</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222938729876"/>
        <updated>2022-11-26T07:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I. <정확히 말하면 나의 언어의 한계는 나의 세계의 한계가 되는 것이다. 이처럼 언어는 세상의 것을 대상화하고 구성함으로써 세상을 표현한다. 그러나 인간의 언어는 정말로 세계를 있는 그대로 묘사하고 있는 것일까. 아마 수없이 제기되었던 문제였을 것이다.> 두 가지 생각이 구분 없이 섞여 있다. 하나는 전기 비트겐슈타인의 사유이다. 전기 비트겐슈타인에 의하면, 우리 언어는 그림 언어이며 표상 언어이다. 그것은 바로 세계를 있는 그대로 묘사하고 서술하는 언어이다. 전기 비트겐슈타인은 이런 언어가 어떻게 가능한지 탐구하고 있다. 그런 언어는 논리적 형식, 표상적 형식, 그림 형식 때문에 가능하다. 그렇지만 이런 그림.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More stable kernels released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915991/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915991/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T22:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released the 5.10.156, 5.4.225, 4.19.267, 4.14.300, and 4.9.334 stable kernels.  As usual, they
contain important fixes throughout the kernel tree.

Update: 6.0.10 and 5.15.80 were released on November 26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eliyan eliminates silicon interposer to advance D2D chiplet connect for HPC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477388</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/eliyan-eliminates-silicon-interposer-to-advance-d2d-chiplet-connect-for-hpc/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T21:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eliyan's chiplet interconnect technology enables connection of homogeneous & heterogenous architectures on a standard organic chip substrate.
The post Eliyan eliminates silicon interposer to advance D2D chiplet connect for HPC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 25, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11414</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-25-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T18:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony Semiconductor offers a new, power-efficient cellular modem for the IoT: Sony has a new modem that lets IoT devices connect via cellular, Low-Power Wide-Area Networks such as LoRa, satellite or hybrid communication channels. The chip, called the ALT1350, is optimized to reduce power consumption by 80% in standby mode when compared to the current generation and by 85% when using […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 25, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915984/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915984/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (firefox), Mageia (dropbear, freerdp, java, libx11, and tumbler), Slackware (ruby), SUSE (erlang, grub2, libdb-4_8, and tomcat), and Ubuntu (exim4, jbigkit, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sony launches low power multi-protocol 5G LPWA IoT chipset]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477382</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/sony-launches-low-power-multi-protocol-5g-lpwa-iot-chipset/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T11:11:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sony said its new chip is a game changer for the IoT chipset market, with its multiple ultra-low power connectivity options and low-power processing on the edge.
The post Sony launches low power multi-protocol 5G LPWA IoT chipset appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빅테크(메타, 구글, 애플, 아마존) 독점력 남용, 세계 각국은 어떻게 대응하고 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87591</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87591"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T09:17:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[메타, 구글 등 빅테크가 시장에서의 독점적 지위를 남용하여 자사 서비스에 비해 경쟁업체를 차별하거나 과도한 수수료를 요구하는 등 불법 행위를 하여 빅테크의 플랫폼을 사용하는 업체 및 이용자의 피해가 발생하고 있습니다. 각국의 규제기관이 반독점 소송을 제기하거나 시정요구를 하고 있지만, 빅테크는 소송으로 맞서고 있죠. 관련 시장을 어떻게 볼 것인지, 독점적 지위에 있는지, 불법 행위를 했는지 등 해결해야 할 […]
The post 빅테크(메타, 구글, 애플, 아마존) 독점력 남용, 세계 각국은 어떻게 대응하고 있을까 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[31 자기 복종]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222937895860</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222937895860"/>
        <updated>2022-11-25T05:02:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 칸트는 <계몽이란 무엇인가>의 마지막 부분에서 다음처럼 말한다. 칸트 주장의 의미를 분명히 하고, 그것에 대해 평가해 보라. <종교상의 문제에 있어 국민에게 어떠한 것도 규정하지 않고 그들에게 완전한 자유를 허용하는 것을 의무로 생각하는 군주, 따라서 관용이라는 존대한 호칭도 사양하는 군주야말로 스스로 계몽된 사람이며, 적어도 정부 측에서 인류를 미성년에서 해방하여 양심에 관한 모든 사항에서 각자 자신의 이성을 사용할 것을 허락한 최초의 사람으로서, 은혜를 아는 당대와 후대 사람들에게 찬양 받아 마땅한 사람이다. 그러한 군주 치하에서는 존경 받을 만한 성직자들에게 학자의 자격으로서 자신의 직무상의 의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 수리남 바우테르서 전 대통령의 그림자]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75580</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/24/npc_suriname/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_suriname"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T22:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[9월 21일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 올린 글입니다.   화제의 넷플릭스 드라마 “수리남”에 관해 수리남 정부가 넷플릭스와 드라마 제작사를 상대로 법적 절차를 밟는 방안을 검토하고 있다고 밝히면서 창작물로 인해 발생할 수 있는 애꿎은 피해와 표현의 자유 등에 관해 많은 이야기가 나오고 있습니다. 각색하거나 창작한 부분도 있지만, 기본적으로 실화를 바탕으로 만든 드라마이며, 주요 등장인물도 실존 인물을 모티프로 삼았다고 알려지면서 수리남의 내용 가운데 어디까지가 실화고, 어디부터 창작인지를 둘러싼 기사들도 많은 관심을 받고 있습니다. 오늘은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling autonomous safety in autonomous systems with MCUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477374</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/enabling-autonomous-safety-in-autonomous-systems-with-mcus/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T15:04:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microcontrollers (MCUs) offer a solution for implementing safety co-processors at the heart of today’s new generation of autonomous systems.
The post Enabling autonomous safety in autonomous systems with MCUs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bob Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915929/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915929/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T14:38:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (vim), Fedora (drupal7-context, drupal7-link, firefox, xen, xorg-x11-server, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Oracle (container-tools:ol8, device-mapper-multipath, dotnet7.0, firefox, hsqldb, keylime, podman, python3.9, python39:3.9, thunderbird, and xorg-x11-server), SUSE (exiv2-0_26, keylime, libarchive, net-snmp, nginx, opensc, pixman, python-joblib, strongswan, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (expat, imagemagick, mariadb-10.3, mariadb-10.6, and xorg-server, xorg-server-hwe-16.04, xorg-server-hwe-18.04, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Alexa’s drama and our holiday gift guide]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11409</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-alexas-drama-and-our-holiday-gift-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T14:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The biggest news in the internet of things this week was the staggering story about Amazon’s Alexa business being responsible for the majority of an estimated $10 billion loss in the year ahead. So Kevin and I discuss what Amazon pulling back on Alexa might look like and what it means for voice and the […]
The post Podcast: Alexa’s drama and our holiday gift guide appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using edge AI processors to boost embedded AI performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477367</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/using-edge-ai-processors-to-boost-embedded-ai-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T13:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at Kinara's accelerator and NXP processors which combine to deliver edge AI performance capable of delivering smart camera designs  
The post Using edge AI processors to boost embedded AI performance appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rehan Hameed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인텍플러스 4분기 전망 및 2023년 전망 by 상상인증권]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588573</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588573/%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%8d%ed%94%8c%eb%9f%ac%ec%8a%a4-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T11:33:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[소프트웨어 교육시장에 대한 이해]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=11975</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2022/11/24/software-edu-market/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T10:57:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제목이 조금 거창합니다.엄밀히 말하면 “소프트웨어 교육”과 “개발자 양성”은 다릅니다만,아직 혜안이 부족해 그냥 적어봅니다. 많은 사람들이 궁금해 합니다. “소프트웨어 교육, 어떻게 해야 할까” 최근 교육 언저리에 3년 정도 있었습니다.그러다보니 “교육산업”에 대해 약간은 이해하게 되었습니다. 몇 개 글을 더 쓸테지만, 우선 교육시장에 대해 서술을 해봅니다. 01. 초.중.고등학교 교육 초등학교 6년 + 중학교 3학년 + 고등학교 3학년 =... Continue Reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10.29 참사 유족 기자회견, 왜 ‘흐리고'(TV조선) ‘어둡게'(JTBC) 처리했을까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87578</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87578"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T09:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10.29 이태원 참사가 발생한 후 처음으로 유가족이 공개 입장을 밝혔습니다. 11월 22일, 민주사회를위한변호사모임(민변) 대회의실에서 ‘이태원 핼러윈 참사’ 유가족 입장 발표 기자회견이 열렸는데요. 희생자를 기리는 묵념을 마친 후 6명의 유가족은 10.29 이태원 참사에 대한 심경과 입장에 대해 밝혔습니다. ‘10.29 참사’ 대응 테스크포스(TF)팀장인 윤복남 변호사는 △윤석열 대통령과 정부의 진정한 사과 △성역 없는 진상·책임 규명 △피해자 참여 보장 […]
The post 10.29 참사 유족 기자회견, 왜 ‘흐리고'(TV조선) ‘어둡게'(JTBC) 처리했을까 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET, Go, Kamelets, and more: Top articles from November 2022]]></title>
        <id>8a3c16cc-51fd-42d2-bf3d-741065b76de7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/24/net-go-kamelets-and-more-top-articles-november-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you'll soon be signing off for a fall November break or working through the end of the month, take a moment to check out Red Hat Developer's latest top-performing articles. We've highlighted the tutorial guides and announcements that our developer community has engaged with the most.
Announcements

	
.NET 7 now available for RHEL and OpenShift: This short overview from John Clingan discusses what you need to know about .NET 7. The .NET 7 release is now available, targeting Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8.7, RHEL 9.1, and Red Hat OpenShift.
Intros, deep dives, and announcements: Our best of October 2022: Here are some highlights from Red Hat Developer for October 2022, organized by product announcements, topic roundups, learning guides, and advanced deep dives
Tutorials

	
3 ways …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 모종삼 철학에서 “물자체” 개념]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222937162184</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222937162184"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T06:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[모종삼은 칸트에 대해서 다음과 같은 주장을 하고 있다. (i) 현상과 물자체, 혹은 현상과 본체의 구분은 필수적이다. (ii) 인간은 유한하다. 혹은 인간은 지적 직관 능력을 갖고 있지 못하다. (iii) 물자체, 혹은 이명휘가 이체(理體)라고 부르는 본체, 지사물(智思物)은 지식론적 의미가 아니라, 가치 의미를 가진 개념이다. 즉 도덕적 영역에서 적용되는 개념이다. (iv) 도덕의 영역에서 매우 중요한 것이 칸트가 주장한 것처럼 자유, 자유의지, 자율이다. (v) 그런데 칸트는 (ii) 때문에 자유의지의 위상을 위태롭게 만들고 있다. 특히 우리의 자유의지가 단순하게 예설(預設) 혹은 가설이 되고 만다. 따라서 칸트는 (iii)의 의미를 정확하게.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전문 유통점 베스트바이 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각, 기대 이상으로 목표주가 상향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588561</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588561/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%b2%a0%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%b0%94%ec%9d%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T06:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanksgiving!  I have much to be thankful for]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2022/11/24/thanksgiving.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2022/11/24/thanksgiving.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We started a tradition in my family, years ago, of naming the things we are
thankful to God for on each Thanksgiving.
This year, I would like to share with you those things that I am thankful
for.  The three primary things I am thankful to God for this year are
my salvation, my family, and the business that He has given me.  In many
ways, these blessings are the natural result of the service I’ve chosen
to give to God.  (Heb 11:6)
For this reason, I’d also like to take a short moment to walk through some
verses, and to try to describe the results of my attempts to follow the same.
Salvation
The salvation Jesus Christ offers is easily summarized in this verse:
Kiss the Son, lest he be angry, and ye perish from the way, when his wrath
is kindled but a little.  Blessed are all they that put t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quiz #23: Can this assertion fail?]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/quiz/2022/11/24/quiz23.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/quiz/2022/11/24/quiz23.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At one time I thought that swapping the assumptions regarding the inputs
of a design with the assertions over the outputs was a good
approach to handling
complexity.  Then
I came across this example.
What do you think?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모건스탠리 S&P 500 전망, ’23년 1분기 저점 3000 터치 후 반등해 연말 3900 레벨에 이를 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588554</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588554/%eb%aa%a8%ea%b1%b4%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%a0%eb%a6%ac-sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T03:45:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 굳이 암호화폐를 사용할 이유가 뭐냐는 질문]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75776</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/23/npsp_ftxcrypto/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_ftxcrypto"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T02:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난해 최고의 해를 보냈던 암호화폐 업계는 올해 최악의 해를 보내고 있습니다. 지난 5월에는 루나-테라 사태로 수십조 원의 가치가 사라져 전 세계 암호화폐 관계자들을 망연자실하게 했죠. 이어 이달 초에는 가장 인기 있고 거래량이 많은 거래소 중 하나인 FTX가 그들이 보유한 자산에 대한 의문을 담은 기사 하나가 올라온 지 단 며칠 만에 파산 신청을 하고 말았습니다. 암호화폐에 비판적인 태도를 보이는 대표적인 경제학자이자 노벨상 수상자인 폴 크루그먼은 이번 FTX 사태가 암호화폐 업계의 끝이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 주가 폭락을 보는 월가의 시각, 지나친 하락과 새로운 기회]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588544</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588544/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80%ed%8f%ad%eb%9d%bd%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a7%a4%ec%88%98-%ea%b8%b0%ed%9a%8c"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T01:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s the future of voice in an economic downturn?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11391</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/whats-the-future-of-voice-in-an-economic-downturn/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-24T00:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice has been one of the most successful technologies of the last decade, especially when it comes to the smart home. Thanks to innovations in natural language processing (NLP) during the 2012-2015 time period, voice became ubiquitous on our phones and in our homes. But now, with news that Amazon is downsizing its Alexa business […]
The post What’s the future of voice in an economic downturn? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 rules for a right first time ASIC specification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477322</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/7-rules-for-a-right-first-time-asic-specification/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T17:12:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at seven most common problems in developing ASIC specifications, which if unquestioned could lead to problems further down the line in product development. 
The post 7 rules for a right first time ASIC specification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Morris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 4.19.266]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915772/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915772/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T14:58:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 4.19.266 stable kernel update has been
released; it consists entirely of backported fixes for
speculative-execution vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915802/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915802/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T14:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (heimdal, libarchive, and nginx), Fedora (varnish-modules and xterm), Red Hat (firefox), Scientific Linux (firefox, hsqldb, and thunderbird), SUSE (Botan, colord, containerized-data-importer, ffmpeg-4, java-1_8_0-ibm, krb5, nginx, redis, strongswan, tomcat, and xtrabackup), and Ubuntu (apr-util, freerdp2, and sysstat).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[If a Matter company stops paying license fees, what happens?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11374</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/if-a-matter-company-stops-paying-license-fees-what-happens/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T12:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a Matter question during our Voicemail hotline segment. This particular question was submitted via email by Jon, and since it was such a good question, we decided to tackle it. Jon asked: What intrigued me about the Matter initiative was the hope that it would […]
The post If a Matter company stops paying license fees, what happens? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공공의대 법안 표류… 국회는 의사 편입니까, 국민 편입니까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87569</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87569"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T10:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“대한의사협회 및 현직 의사, 의대생 이외에 공공의대 설립을 반대하는 사람은 아무도 없다. (…중략…) 반대하는 이는 의사면허의 독점적 가치가 하락할 것을 우려하는 현직 의사, 의대생과 대한의사협회 뿐이다.” (나무위키, ‘국립공공보건의료대학/논란’ 중에서) 의사 부족으로 인한 안타까운 죽음이 반복되고 있습니다. 그럼에도 국회 보건복지위원회 법안심사소위에서 필수·공공의료 의사 확충을 위한 공공의대법제정안 상정이 국민의힘 반대로 불투명한 상황이죠. 국민의 생명을 누구보다 우선해야 할 여당이 강 […]
The post 공공의대 법안 표류… 국회는 의사 편입니까, 국민 편입니까 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OECD 세계경제 전망 및 한국경제 전망(’22년 11월 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588536</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588536/oecd-%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84%ea%b2%bd%ec%a0%9c-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T10:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존 광고 비즈니스의 성장성에도 채용을 동결하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588534</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588534/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0-%eb%b9%84%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88%ec%8a%a4-%ec%b1%84%ec%9a%a9-%eb%8f%99%ea%b2%b0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T07:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Next.js applications to Red Hat OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>eeff6449-d837-4fc1-bc79-4a7a8fdd9434</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/23/how-deploy-nextjs-applications-red-hat-openshift"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js is a popular framework for deploying sites based on Node.js. You can read about many popular Node.js frameworks in part 6 of the Red Hat Developer series on the Node.js reference architecture.
In this article, you'll learn how to deploy Next.js applications using the ubi8/nodejs-16 and ubi8/nodejs-16-minimal containers available from Red Hat.
If you are a Red Hat customer with support, then you'll want to use the UBI or RHEL containers; this article was inspired in part because one of our customers asked us how to do that with Next.js. Even if you are not a customer yet, ubi8 containers are free to use and a great choice; we've seen their usage continue to grow.
Once you've seen how to build a Next.js application on top of the UBI containers, we'll show you how you can do the build…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[소니 혼다 모빌리티 사장, 테슬라 극복할 소니 계획 공개]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588530</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588530/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ea%b7%b9%eb%b3%b5%ed%95%a0-%ec%86%8c%eb%8b%88-%ea%b3%84%ed%9a%8d"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T06:03:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[암호화페 FTX 사태 정리에서 배우는 세가지 포인트]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588526</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588526/ftx-%ec%82%ac%ed%83%9c-%ec%a0%95%eb%a6%ac"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T05:25:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주목해야 할 에듀테크 트렌드 5가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588516</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588516/%ec%97%90%eb%93%80%ed%85%8c%ed%81%ac-%ed%8a%b8%eb%a0%8c%eb%93%9c"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T04:35:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[최근 테슬라 주가 폭락, 이제 다시 진입할 시점일까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588507</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588507/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ed%8f%ad%eb%9d%bd%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a7%a4%ec%88%98-%ec%8b%9c%ec%a0%90"/>
        <updated>2022-11-23T02:12:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 수십 년째 줄어들던 미국 범죄율의 불안한 반등 조짐]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75570</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/22/npc_ushomicides/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_ushomicides"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T22:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 9월 19일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 쓴 글입니다.   2022년 상반기 미국의 범죄 실태 조사 결과에서 불길한 변화가 감지되고 있습니다. 미국 주요 도시에서 살인 범죄는 감소하고 있지만, 폭력 범죄 전체 건수는 1월 초부터 6월 말 사이, 작년 동기 대비 4.2% 증가했기 때문입니다. 2019년 같은 조사와 비교하면 살인은 50%, 가중 폭행은 35% 증가했습니다. 액시오스(Axios) 기사가 인터뷰한 검찰 관계자는 노숙, 중독, 정신 건강 등 팬데믹과 관련된 사회경제적 이슈가 범죄의 증가로 나타났다고 분석합니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mind the Gap]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/mind-the-gap.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/mind-the-gap.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T21:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url('https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=OPeqXG-QxW3ZD8BtmPikfA');.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-0>li:before{content:"\0025cf  "}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-6{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-7{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-4{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-5{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-2{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-3{list-style-type:none}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf  "}ul.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-1{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0  "}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf  "}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb  "}.lst-kix_9apzkelodq30-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb  "}.lst-kix_9a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Holy C++]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1010/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1010/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'll try to list all things that we can throw out of C++ without remorse. This won't cost us anything but will reduce the standard (and our headaches), take the burden off the compiler developers and students who learn this language — and thus will eliminate the memetic potential of the C++ enormity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PTC will acquire ServiceMax for $1.46B]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11388</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/ptc-will-acquire-servicemax-for-1-46b/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T17:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story ran in the Friday, Nov. 16, 2020 issue of my weekly newsletter.  PTC has agreed to acquire ServiceMax in an all-cash deal valued at $1.46 billion. The deal combines PTC’s earlier efforts in digital manufacturing with software that can dispense service technicians to solve problems that get detected. So if a predictive maintenance […]
The post PTC will acquire ServiceMax for $1.46B appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asahi Linux November 2022 progress report]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915725/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915725/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T15:47:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those who are waiting for Linux on Apple hardware, the Asahi Linux
project has put out a detailed
report on progress toward a working kernel and distribution.


	This kind of safety model is not new: it is already commonplace on
	Android phones, where it is usually implemented in DSP
	firmware. But of course, the desktop Linux ecosystem doesn’t even
	have a speaker EQ database framework yet, nevermind safety models!
	The eternal lagging behind of Linux audio strikes again. What’s the
	plan? While this isn’t settled yet, our current idea is to
	implement the safety model in a stand-alone daemon that captures
	the voltage/current feedback data from the ALSA device, and drives
	the mixer volume itself as as means of implementing soft power
	limits, together with some kind of “safety watchdog interlock” with
	the kernel that only enables higher volume limits when the daemon
	is active and running]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Etsy's observability and ML infrastructure teams moving to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/etsy-cloud-scale.html#TheChallengesOfObservingEverything</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/etsy-cloud-scale.html#TheChallengesOfObservingEverything"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim Cochran and Keyur Govande
      continue their account of how Etsy used the cloud to scale up by
      describing the journey of two teams: observability and ML
      infrastructure
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome Stéphane Guillou, new QA Analyst for LibreOffice (Document Foundation)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915711/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915711/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:31:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Document Foundation has announced
the hiring of a quality-assurance analyst, bringing its staff up to 13
people.


	A lot of my time will be spent on triaging the issues users report
	on Bugzilla – our bug-reporting platform. There is a lot of
	activity on Bugzilla, and classifying and testing the reports is
	fundamental for us to focus on the most pressing issues, help the
	work developers are doing, and keep improving the software for
	everyone! Part of the work will also be to analyse and summarise
	the wealth of data available to help us see the bigger picture and
	make better decisions when allocating resources.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915708/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915708/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T14:10:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ntfs-3g), Fedora (krb5 and samba), Gentoo (firefox-bin, ghostscript-gpl, pillow, sudo, sysstat, thunderbird-bin, and xterm), Red Hat (firefox, hsqldb, and thunderbird), SUSE (cni, cni-plugins, and krb5), and Ubuntu (isc-dhcp and sqlite3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Psychological safety in the workplace]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/?p=12683</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/people/psychological-safety-in-the-workplace/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T09:57:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Psychological safety in the workplace revolves around employee engagement and disengagement. Often, business leaders may believe that psychological safety in their […]
The post Psychological safety in the workplace appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily King</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[수원 봉녕사 만추 풍경]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588482</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588482/%ec%88%98%ec%9b%90-%eb%b4%89%eb%85%95%ec%82%ac-%eb%a7%8c%ec%b6%94"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T09:55:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빈곤 포르노가 아니면 무엇인가: 언론이 본 김건희 캄보디아 연출 사진 논란]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87555</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87555"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T09:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 대통령의 4박 5일간 동남아 해외순방에 동행한 김건희 여사는 주최국이 준비한 각국 정상 배우자 프로그램 참여 대신 개인 일정을 소화했습니다. 김 여사는 캄보디아 프놈펜에서 12일(현지 시각)에 선천성 심장질환 환아를 방문했는데요. 대통령실이 공개한 김 여사가 아이를 안고 찍은 사진이 언론을 통해 보도되면서 과거 소말리아 유니세프를 방문한 오드리 햅번을 연상시킨다는 이야기와 함께 ‘빈곤 포르노’라며 비판하는 여론이 일었습니다. […]
The post 빈곤 포르노가 아니면 무엇인가: 언론이 본 김건희 캄보디아 연출 사진 논란 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pipenv and S2i: A better way to manage Python dependencies in containers]]></title>
        <id>2d93abd9-3ece-4c43-9d58-45431685588e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/22/pipenv-and-s2i-better-way-manage-python-dependencies-containers"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing the many libraries and packages used by an application is complex and has some hidden risks. The difficulties increase when you want to run an application in a container, because you need to manage a development environment when creating a different set of libraries and packages for the containerized application. This article discusses some of the common problems Python developers face when containerizing Python applications, and how Pipenv and Source-to-Image (S2I) can help to resolve those problems. We will build a simple Python application on the Red Hat OpenShift container platform using those tools.
Shortcomings of pip
Pip is the nearly universal tool employed by Python programmers to install dependent packages. Pip is incredibly simple and powerful. But that simplicity creat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Trevor Royer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I developed a faster Ruby interpreter]]></title>
        <id>d5200cd6-1ab5-4212-8e66-fda53f090fe1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/22/how-i-developed-faster-ruby-interpreter"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will describe my efforts to implement a faster interpreter for CRuby, the Ruby language interpreter, using a dynamically specialized internal representation (IR). I believe this article will interest developers trying to improve the interpreter performance of dynamic programming languages (e.g., CPython developers).
I will cover the following topics:

	
Existing CRuby interpreter and just-in-time (JIT) compilers for Ruby—MJIT, YJIT, and the MIR-based CRuby JIT compiler at the very early stages of development—along with my motivation to start this project and my initial expectations for the project outcome.
The general approach to performance improvement by specialization and the specializations used in my project to implement a faster CRuby interpreter. I will describe a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vladimir Makarov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유통업체 실적을 보는 월가의 시각]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588475</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588475/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%9c%a0%ed%86%b5%ec%97%85%ec%b2%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T06:26:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사실과 요청]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222935283533</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222935283533"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T05:39:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 이명휘는 <모종삼 철학에서 ‘물자체’의 개념>에서 다음처럼 말한다. <모종삼의 견해에 의하면 칸트는 단지 도덕의 길을 따라 신학을 세웠을 뿐으로 “도덕적(道德的) 신학(神學)”은 있지만 “도덕 형이상학”은 없는데, 그 핵심은 칸트가 의지적 자유는 인간의 의식 속에서 드러날 수 있다는 점을 받아들이지 않고 단지 “요청”(Postulat)으로 보았기 때문이다.> 이것이 칸트를 공박하는 모종삼의 핵심 논제이다. (2) 이 구절을 읽으면서 나는 모종삼이 틀렸다고 생각했다. 칸트는 의지적 자유를 <요청>이라기 보다는 <사실>로 간주했다고 생각했다. 그러나 칸트에게 있어서 자유의지는 도덕이 가능하기 위한 요.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[스티펠, 연준 기준금리는 9%에 이를 수 있다고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588468</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588468/%ec%97%b0%ec%a4%80-%ea%b8%b0%ec%a4%80%ea%b8%88%eb%a6%ac-9-%ec%a3%bc%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T03:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 인텍플러스 실적, 매출과 이익 감소 속 4분기를 기대하라]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588464</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588464/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%8d%ed%94%8c%eb%9f%ac%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-2"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T02:06:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[카타르 월드컵 32개국 몸값 순위]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588462</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588462/%ec%b9%b4%ed%83%80%eb%a5%b4-%ec%9b%94%eb%93%9c%ec%bb%b5-%eb%aa%b8%ea%b2%82-%ec%88%9c%ec%9c%84"/>
        <updated>2022-11-22T00:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 문화 현상이 된 ‘사랑의 언어’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75565</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/21/npc_lovelanguage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_lovelanguage"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T22:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 8월 27일 뉴욕타임스에는 ‘여섯 번째 사랑의 언어는 존재하지 않는다’는 제목의 기사가 올라왔습니다. 글쎄요, 어지간하면 제목으로 글의 내용을 유추할 수 있는 수준에 올랐다고 생각했는데, 이 글이 무슨 내용일지는 전혀 감이 잡히지 않았습니다. 그래서 읽기 시작했습니다. 낚시가 성공한 것이죠. 아니, 흥미롭게 읽었고 생각할 거리를 얻었으니 낚시가 아니라 글 제목을 잘 지었다고 해야겠네요. 기사는 1992년, 50대의 목사이자 상담전문가였던 개리 챕맨(Gary Chapman)이 20년간 여러 부부와 연인들을 상담하며 그들의 이야기를 정리해 펴낸 ‘다섯 가지 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sonos eyes hardware subscriptions to broaden customer base]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11383</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/sonos-eyes-hardware-subscriptions-to-broaden-customer-base/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T18:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Janko Roettgers  Sonos is giving hardware subscriptions another look, at least if a new job listing is any indication. Based on the details of that listing, the company appears to be on the cusp of expanding its Flex subscription program, which lets people rent Sonos speakers for a fixed monthly fee. Expanding the program […]
The post Sonos eyes hardware subscriptions to broaden customer base appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915623/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915623/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T15:08:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (graphicsmagick and krb5), Fedora (dotnet6.0, js-jquery-ui, kubernetes, and xterm), Gentoo (php and postgresql), Mageia (php-pear-CAS, sysstat, varnish, vim, and x11-server), Red Hat (thunderbird), SUSE (389-ds, binutils, dpkg, firefox, frr, grub2, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, kernel, kubevirt stack, libpano, nodejs16, openjpeg, php7, php74, pixman, python-Twisted, python39, rubygem-loofah, sccache, sudo, thunderbird, tor, and tumbler), and Ubuntu (flac, git, linux-azure-fde, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-raspi-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, and linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke-5.15, linux-intel-iotg, linux-raspi).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: Structures in C and CMSIS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477267</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-structures-in-c-and-cmsis/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In embedded systems, structs can provide an elegant, intuitive, and efficient way of accessing hardware registers. The latter property of structs is the foundation of...
The post Programming embedded systems: Structures in C and CMSIS appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How augmented reality could improve CNC machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477264</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-augmented-reality-could-improve-cnc-machines/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T13:12:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying augmented reality technology in computer numerical control (CNC) machines can enable improvements in CNC education, error reduction, and more. Augmented reality (AR) is becoming...
The post How augmented reality could improve CNC machines appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공정한 선거보도 심의? 전 세계 유례 없는 검열제도]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87540</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87540"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T11:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[언론이 선거보도에서 공정성을 추구해야 한다는 것은 당연한 저널리즘의 가치입니다. 이 가치를 확보하기 위해 심의제도를 확대하는 것이 바람직한가에 관해서 이야기해야 하는데요. 토론 주제로 전달받은 것은 심의제도의 활성화 방안이었는데, 이에 관해선 다른 분들이 설명해주셨으니 저는 다른 관점에서 심의대상을 일반 인터넷상 표현물로까지 확대하려는 논의가 있는 움직임이 바람직한 것인지 심의제도 자체에 대해 비판적인 관점에서 접근하려고 합니다. 가장 원론적인 이야기죠. […]
The post 공정한 선거보도 심의? 전 세계 유례 없는 검열제도 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>손지원</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 월마트와 타겟 실적을 가른 4가지 월마트와 타겟 차이]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588454</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588454/%ec%9b%94%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8%ec%99%80-%ed%83%80%ea%b2%9f-%ec%b0%a8%ec%9d%b4"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T07:25:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 타겟 실적을 보는 월가의 시각, 당분간 마진 회복은 어려워 주가 상승은 제한적]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588452</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588452/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%83%80%ea%b2%9f-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T07:12:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why GPUs are essential for AI and high-performance computing]]></title>
        <id>452b1181-0613-4a56-8cf6-16ca8e55a3f5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/21/why-gpus-are-essential-computing"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Graphics processing units (GPU) have become the foundation of artificial intelligence. Machine learning was slow, inaccurate, and inadequate for many of today's applications. The inclusion and utilization of GPUs made a remarkable difference to large neural networks. Deep learning discovered solutions for image and video processing, putting things like autonomous driving or facial recognition into mainstream technology.
The connection between GPUs and OpenShift does not stop at data science. High-performance computing is one of the hottest trends in enterprise tech. Cloud computing creates a seamless process enabling various tasks designated for supercomputers, better than any other computing power you use, saving you time and money.
How GPUs work
Let’s back up and make sure we understand …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Audrey Reznik, Troy Nelson, Kaitlyn Abdo, Christina Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[일론 머스크식 ‘언론의 자유’는 민주주의를 위협한다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75769</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/21/npsp_musktwitter/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_musktwitter"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T05:30:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라의 창업자 일론 머스크가 트위터를 인수한 뒤 안팎으로 잡음이 끊이지 않고 있습니다. 스브스 프리미엄에 올린 이번 글에서는 뉴욕타임스 인도 특파원을 지낸 리디아 폴그린의 칼럼 “일론 머스크(의 트위터)가 위험한 진짜 이유가 궁금하면 미국 밖을 보라”를 옮겼습니다. 이어 일론 머스크가 이해하는 ‘언론의 자유’가 왜 위험한지를 짚은 주장과 분석을 정리했습니다. 일론 머스크식 ‘언론의 자유’는 민주주의를 위협한다]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.1-rc6]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915547/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915547/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.1-rc6 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	 I'm still waffling about whether there will be an rc8 or not,
	 leaning a bit towards it happening. We'll see - it will make the
	 6.2 merge window leak into the holidays, but maybe that's fine and
	 just makes people make sure they have everything lined up and
	 ready *before* the merge window opens, the way things _should_
	 work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Measure String SSO Length with constinit and constexpr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/sso-cpp20-checks/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/sso-cpp20-checks/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is SSO 
  




     
    


Just briefly, SSO stands for Short String Optimization. It’s usually implemented as a small buffer (an array or something similar) occurring in the same storage as the string object. When the string is short, this buffer is used instead of a separate dynamic memory allocation.
See a simplified diagram below:

The diagram illustrates two strings and where they “land” in the string object. If the string is long (longer than N characters), it needs a costly dynamic memory allocation, and the address to that new buffer will be stored in ptr. On the other hand, if the string is short, we can put it inside the object in the buf[N]. Usually, buf and ptr might be implemented as union to save space, as we use one or the other, but not both simultaneously.
Let’s star…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stochastic rounding reemerges]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7283</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/11/20/stochastic-rounding-reemerges/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T23:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just like integer types, floating-point types are capable of representing a finite number of numeric values. An important difference between integer and floating types is that the result of arithmetic and relational operations using integer types is exactly representable in an integer type (provided they don’t overflow), while the result of arithmetic operations using floating […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Energy Crisis in Europe: Optimizing a Building from 4.5 to 2.4 MWh]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=35531</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/11/20/energy-crisis-in-europe-optimizing-a-building-from-4-5-to-2-4-mwh/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T18:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the war in the Ukraine, energy prices in Europe reached new record levels. This initially affected the gas price which does not affect my directly. But it had a bit impact on the price for electrical energy too. In … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peripheral Interaction Without a Linux Device Driver Using Spidev]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1485.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1485.php"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T17:29:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview
When integrating a new peripheral onto an embedded Linux platform, we might think we always need to implement a kernel module to serve as a device driver. However, as we all know, absolutes such as “always” and “never” are rarely true. The same is true in this case. Implementing a device driver in kernel space on an embedded Linux platform should only be undertaken if the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Memoriam: Frederick P. Brooks, Jr. and The Mythical Man-Month]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1484.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1484.php"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T16:47:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is with some sadness that I have read that Fred Brooks has passed away. Brooks (1931 - 2022) worked at IBM and managed a large team developing the IBM System/360 computers in the early 1960s. Brooks was thirty years old at the start of this project. He founded the Computer Science Department at UNC Chapel Hill in 1964,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[메이야수 – 절대자에 대한 요구]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222933527464</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222933527464"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T08:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[메이야수의 <유한성 이후>를 읽는 것이 내 철학적 사유에 도움을 주는가? 내가 일종의 칸트주의자이기 때문에, 이런 칸트주의를 비판하는 그의 사유가 부정적인 의미에서 도움을 줄 수 있다. 그럼에도 불구하고 그의 책을 읽어나가는 것이 무척 고역이다. 그것은 그가 내가 보기에는 말장난 같은 철학적 사유를 보여주기 때문이다. 그런데 그는 말장난이 아니라, 그가 보여주는 사유 방식이 바로 철학적 사유의 한 전형이라고 생각하고 있는 것 같다. 메이야수의 <유한성 이후> 2장 <형이상학, 신앙절대론, 사변>은 다음과 같은 것을 주장하고 싶어 한다. <선조성을 사유하는 것은 <사유 없는 세계>, 즉 <세계의 소.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SSH port forwarding with Go]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/ssh-port-forwarding-with-go/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/ssh-port-forwarding-with-go/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-20T03:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This post shows how to set up SSH port forwarding (&quot;tunnels&quot;) - both local and
remote - using the extended Go standard library.</p>
<div class="section" id="setup">
<h2>Setup</h2>
<p>While you <em>could</em> set up <tt class="docutils literal">localhost</tt> forwarding for testing, to discuss a more
realistic scenario I would recommend spinning up a basic <a class="reference external" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Virtual_private_server">VPS</a>. For the purpose of
writing …</p></div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477260</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-steps-to-designing-an-embedded-software-architecture-step-5/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T16:02:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article closes out the series by examining the last step; Simulate, iterate, and scale. The last several articles have explored the five steps to...
The post 5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 5 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고궁의 가을을 느끼며, 경복궁 가을, 창덕궁 가을을 만나다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588389</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588389/%ea%b3%a0%ea%b6%81%ec%9d%98-%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%84"/>
        <updated>2022-11-19T12:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 18, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11370</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-18-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T20:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Twilio launches asset tracking service as part of IoT platform expansion: Twilio, which put a toehold into the IoT with its acquisition of Electric Imp back in July 2020, and the creation of a new IoT platform two months later, has finally launched another IoT product. This week, it introduced a customizable asset tracker that […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 18, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET, Go, Kamelets, and more: Top articles from November 2022]]></title>
        <id>8a3c16cc-51fd-42d2-bf3d-741065b76de7</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/18/net-go-kamelets-and-more-top-articles-november-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T19:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you'll soon be signing off for a fall November break or working through the end of the month, take a moment to check out Red Hat Developer's latest top-performing articles. We've highlighted the tutorial guides and announcements that our developer community has engaged with the most.
Announcements

	
.NET 7 now available for RHEL and OpenShift: This short overview from John Clingan discusses what you need to know about .NET 7. The .NET 7 release is now available, targeting Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8.7, RHEL 9.1, and Red Hat OpenShift.
Intros, deep dives, and announcements: Our best of October 2022: Here are some highlights from Red Hat Developer for October 2022, organized by product announcements, topic roundups, learning guides, and advanced deep dives
Tutorials

	
3 ways …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Averting excessive oopses]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914878/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914878/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T16:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even a single kernel oops is never a good thing; it is an indication that something has
gone badly wrong in the system somewhere and a straightforward
recovery is not possible.  But it seems that oopsing a large number
of times has the potential to be even worse.  To head off problems that
might result from repeated oopsing, there
is currently work afoot to put an upper limit on the number of times that
the kernel can be allowed to oops before just giving up and rebooting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Review: GIMP 2.99.14 (Libre Arts)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915388/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915388/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T15:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Libre Arts looks at
the GIMP as the 3.0 release approaches.



	Releases like this are too rare to disregard and thus all the more
	to treasure. In one swift motion the team is doing away with
	floating selections and bringing strokes/outlines for text. But
	this has been a bumpy road]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source community split over offer of 'corporate' welfare for critical
dev tools (Register)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915385/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915385/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T15:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Register looks
at the discussion around the GNU Tools Infrastructure proposal.


	Sourceware, a volunteer group that has been supporting various
	critical FOSS developer tools for more than two decades, is being
	courted by The Linux Foundation's Open Source Security Foundation
	(OpenSSF). The OpenSSF aims to improve open source software
	security by providing Sourceware projects with more modern IT
	infrastructure.

	But some members of the Sourceware community fear that accepting
	the help of the OpenSSF would give the corporate Linux world more
	leverage over FOSS developer tools. They would prefer to seek
	support from the Software Freedom Conservancy, a charitable
	non-profit that they believe is better aligned with software
	freedom.


LWN covered this discussion back in
September.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Embedded Teams in the Modern Era]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=22946</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2022/11/18/building-embedded-teams-in-the-modern-era/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T15:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[18 November 2022 by Phillip JohnstonEmbedded Artistry and Memfault are joining forces to host a quarterly embedded discussion panel that is focused on the technical aspects of building embedded systems at scale. We will be featuring guest panel members who are at the cutting edge of embedded development. Our goal is to spread beneficial techniques and practices throughout … 
Continue reading "Building Embedded Teams in the Modern Era"
The post Building Embedded Teams in the Modern Era appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915378/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915378/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T14:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (asterisk, firefox-esr, php-phpseclib, phpseclib, python-django, and thunderbird), Fedora (grub2, samba, and thunderbird), Mageia (firefox, sudo, systemd, and thunderbird), Slackware (freerdp), SUSE (firefox, go1.18, go1.19, kernel, openvswitch, python-Twisted, systemd, and xen), and Ubuntu (expat, git, multipath-tools, unbound, and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you use a DIY Matter product? Yes, but…]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11330</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/can-you-use-a-diy-matter-product-yes-but/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a Matter question on our Voicemail hotline. Our caller is interested in the process of getting DIY devices Matter certified, which is an excellent question. To understand the answer, you need to know about the certification requirements, as well as the provisions for non-certified devices. […]
The post Can you use a DIY Matter product? Yes, but… appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Installing eGit into CodeWarrior Development Studio for MCU v11.1]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=36119</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/11/18/installing-egit-into-codewarrior-development-studio-for-mcu-v11-1/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T12:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Git is the standard version control system these days. And it even can be installed and used in older legacy IDEs, for example the Freescale (now NXP) CodeWarrior for MCU Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[감사원 선생님, 지금 대통령 눈치 보십니까? (ft. 대통령집 이사 의혹 등 국민감사 촉구)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87531</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87531"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T11:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주요 경과: 감사원의 ‘시간 끌기’   1. 참여연대와 시민들의 감사청구 (10.12)  참여연대는 지난 10월 12일 700여 명의 국민이 자필 서명해 국민감사청구인으로 참여한 ‘대통령실⋅관저의 이전과 그 비용 등 관련 불법 의혹에 대한 국민감사청구서’ (이하 ‘국민감사청구‘)를 감사원에 제출했습니다. 국민감사청구 요건인 300명의 두 배가 넘는 수치죠. 2. 감사원, 보완 요구 (10.25)  감사원은 지난 10월 25일 국민감사청구에 대해 […]
The post 감사원 선생님, 지금 대통령 눈치 보십니까? (ft. 대통령집 이사 의혹 등 국민감사 촉구) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[일론 머스크 업무원칙 6가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588428</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588428/%ec%9d%bc%eb%a1%a0-%eb%a8%b8%ec%8a%a4%ed%81%ac-%ec%97%85%eb%ac%b4%ec%9b%90%ec%b9%99"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T07:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernize at scale with the new migration toolkit for applications]]></title>
        <id>f8db9619-4659-4a29-819c-b34658a17249</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/18/modernize-scale-new-migration-toolkit-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The migration toolkit for applications from Red Hat equips developers with tools to assess, prioritize, and modernize Java applications across the hybrid cloud on Red Hat OpenShift. Version 6 of the toolkit is now generally available—and it's a major step up from the previous version, offering new capabilities to accelerate large-scale application modernization efforts. Read on to explore the new toolkit and see a demo.
Based on the open source Konveyor project, the migration toolkit for applications provides insights and alignment for project leads and migration teams as they move to Red Hat OpenShift for a single application or a portfolio of applications. These insights are a huge boost for developers and organizations looking to modernize and migrate from their legacy platforms to the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 월마트 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 경기침체에도 점유율과 매출 이익 상승 가능]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588420</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588420/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9b%94%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T04:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[See My New Book: C++ Initialization Story]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/cpp-init-book/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/cpp-init-book/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m happy to announce that my new book on C++ Initialization is published!
Have a look at the background story and how to get it.
Updates: Go to the latest updates from 18th Nov here, 30 new pages added!
Note: Initially, the book was called “Data Member Initialization in Modern C++”, but in September 2022, I updated it heavily and changed the title.



     
    


As for my other books, I used the Leanpub platform for the PDF/Epub generation. Here’s the book’s website:

C++ Initialization Story @Leanpub 


And also have a look at Goodreads: C++ Initialization Story by Bartłomiej Filipek and leave youre review.



     
    


Initialization in C++ is a hot topic. With each C++ Standard, we’ll get some updates to the syntax, rules, and new capabilities. With this book, I wanted to clarify …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 중간선거에서 ‘붉은 파도’가 없었던 이유는]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75751</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/17/npsp_noredwave/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_noredwave"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T22:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난주 치른 미국 중간선거에 관해 스프에 쓴 두 번째 분석입니다. 예년 같은 중간선거였다면 야당인 공화당이 큰 승리를 거둬 상원과 하원을 모두 석권하는 게 당연해 보였지만, 이번 중간선거는 그렇지 않았습니다. 그 이유를 투표용지 효과(downballot effect)를 바탕으로 풀어봤습니다. 미국 중간선거에서 ‘붉은 파도’가 없었던 이유는 함께 읽어보실 만한 뉴욕타임스 칼럼으로, 미셸 골드버그가 쓴 “Republicans Did Not Read the Room”를 번역했습니다. 분위기 파악에 실패한 공화당]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rust in the 6.2 kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914458/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914458/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T15:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The merge window for the 6.1 release brought in basic support for writing kernel code in Rust
— with an emphasis on "basic".  It is possible to create a "hello world"
module for 6.1, but not much can be done beyond that.  There is, however, a
lot more Rust code for the kernel out there; it's just waiting for its turn to be
reviewed and merged into the mainline.  Miguel Ojeda has now posted the next
round of Rust patches, adding to the support infrastructure in the
kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the cloud to scale Etsy]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/etsy-cloud-scale.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/etsy-cloud-scale.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Etsy is a well-known marketplace for craft items. The pandemic led to a
      huge spike in growth, growing from 46 million buyers to 90 million buyers
      in two years. Etsy coped with this, with no bottlenecks in the business.
      One aspect of how they did this was a shift to Google cloud. Tim
      Cochran and Keyur Govande begin this story by
      describing the strategic principles that guided this effort and the
      incremental federated approach that they took.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Bluetooth bets on 6 GHz and TP-Link hops on Wi-Fi 7]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11361</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-bluetooth-bets-on-6-ghz-and-tp-link-hops-on-wi-fi-7/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T14:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has started laying off workers, including some working on Alexa and in Amazon’s devices business. We discuss this as well as IBM following in Google’s footsteps and shutting down its IoT cloud business. We move from bad news to innovation with the news that the Bluetooth Special Interest Group is investing in new Bluetooth […]
The post Podcast: Bluetooth bets on 6 GHz and TP-Link hops on Wi-Fi 7 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915245/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915245/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T13:57:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr and thunderbird), Fedora (expat, xen, and xorg-x11-server), Oracle (kernel, kernel-container, qemu, xorg-x11-server, and zlib), Scientific Linux (xorg-x11-server), Slackware (firefox, krb5, samba, and thunderbird), SUSE (ant, apache2-mod_wsgi, jsoup, rubygem-nokogiri, samba, and tomcat), and Ubuntu (firefox and linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-dell300x, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LH 수도권 공공주택, 얼마나 올랐을까 (ft. ‘적자사업’ 주장의 허구성)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87523</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87523"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LH(한국토지주택공사)가 수도권에 보유한 공공주택의 규모와 시세를 보고 있노라면 그야말로 가슴이 웅장해진다. 경실련이 분석한 결과는 다음과 같다(출처: 박주현 전 국회의원, LH 임대주택 자산보유현황 – 2016년말 기준). 보유한 수도권 공공주택 수 22.7만호  취득 시점(2016년 말) 가액은 27.2조 원 현 시세(2022년) 64.6조 원 (약 2.4배 증가)  LH는 서민 주거 안정을 위해 세워진 주택공기업이다. 그 본연의 업무는 공공주택 을 […]
The post LH 수도권 공공주택, 얼마나 올랐을까 (ft. ‘적자사업’ 주장의 허구성) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[volatility3를 활용한 메모리 분석 (3) - macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13424833</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13424833"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:35:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[앞서 volatility3 를 활용하여 windows 및 linux에서 메모리 분석이 가능함을 확인했다.
https://cpuu.postype.com/post/9993241https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11807930

이제 마지막으로 macOS 환경도 volatility 이용한 메모리 포렌식이 가능한지?에 대한 실험 결과이다.
실험을 진행하기 이전에 몇가지 제약사항이 있었고 아직까지 해결하지 못한 부분이 많다. 그 내용들을 몇가지 요약하자면..
1) 현재 최신 macOS 환경에 대한 메모리 포렌식은 volatility 에서 지원하지 않는다. 
2) 2021년 이후 출시되고 있는 Apple Silicon 이 탭제된 Mac 컴퓨터에 대해서는 우선 현시점에서는 불가능한 것으로 판단된다. 공식 Volatility 에서는 지원이 되지 않고, 비공식적으로 arm64를 지원하기 위한 패치를 개발하는 개개인이 존재하는 것으로 보인다. 


그렇다면 macOS 메모리 포렌식 분석을 위해 메모리 덤프, 프로파일 생성, 볼라틸리티3 사용 등을 순서대로 살펴보자.


macOS 환경에서 메모리 덤프 추출
일반적으로 윈도우는 FTK Imager 를 이용해서 쉽게 추출할 수 있고, Linux는 lime이나 avml이 존재한다. 
macOS에서는 우선 오픈소스로는 osxpmem이 있다. osxpmem 은 https://github.com/Velocidex/c-aff4/releases 에서 Release 3.2 에 해당하는 파일을 다운받으면 된다. 알려진 바로는 10.8 부터 10.15 사이의 Intel x64 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New features in OpenMP 5.1 and OpenMP 5.2]]></title>
        <id>176803c8-6ac5-4f9c-82c7-4512bce9c230</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/17/new-features-openmp-51-and-openmp-52"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses recent features implemented in the GCC compiler version 12, the latest stable release. The new features were implemented as a joint effort between Red Hat and CodeSourcery, now a part of Siemens EDA.
OpenMP is an API consisting of compiler directives and library routines that implement high-level parallelism in C and C++ as well as Fortran. OpenMP version 5.1 was released in November 2020, and version 5.2 was released in November 2021. Support for various OpenMP 5.1 features has been added. But GCC 12 does not yet have complete support for OpenMP 5.0, and work is ongoing in GCC 13.
C++11 attribute syntax
Traditionally, the OpenMP directives were expressed in C++ using a pragma syntax, #pragma omp ... or _Pragma("omp ..."). Now the directives can use the C++11 omp::di…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jakub Jelínek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarking improved conntrack performance in OvS 3.0.0]]></title>
        <id>97deb5b4-748c-4ad1-93c3-722f5f8e2381</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/17/benchmarking-improved-conntrack-performance-ovs-300"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open vSwitch (OvS), an open source tool for creating virtual Layer 2 networks, relies in some use cases on connection tracking. The recent 3.0.0 release of OvS included this patch series to improve multithread scalability, which makes connection tracking more efficient when OvS is run on multiple CPUs. This article shows how to measure the performance of connection tracking with OvS.
What is connection tracking and why is it critical?
Connection tracking, or conntrack, maintains an internal table of logical network connections (also called flows). The table identifies all packets that make up each flow so that they can be handled consistently.
Conntrack is a requirement for network address translation (NAT)—in IP address masquerading, for example (described in detail in RFC 3022). Conntrac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robin Jarry</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 17, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914359/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914359/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-17T00:27:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 17, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 엘리자베스 2세 서거와 영국 왕실]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75561</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/16/npc_ukroyal/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_ukroyal"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:59:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 9월 14일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 쓴 글입니다.   지난 주말, 영국 여왕 엘리자베스 2세가 96세의 나이로 세상을 떠났습니다. 재임 기간이 무려 70년이었고, 그 기간 영국의 실질적인 국가 지도자 자리인 수상직을 거친 인물이 15명이니, 마치 영국의 군주는 늘 엘리자베스 여왕이어야 할 것만 같은 착각이 드는 것도 무리는 아닙니다. 지구촌의 유명 인사 순위에서 빠지기 어려운 인물임이 틀림 없죠. 한편, 영국 왕실 관련 소식이 전해질 때마다 지금의 정치제도, 또 현대인으로서의 감각과 도무지 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Networking and high-frequency trading]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914992/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914992/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T22:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The high-frequency-trading (HFT) industry is rather tight-lipped about what
it does 
and how it does it, but PJ Waskiewicz of Jump Trading came to the Netdev 0x16 conference to try
to demystify some of that, especially with respect to its use of
networking.  He 
wanted to contrast the needs of HFT with those of the traditional networking
as it is used outside of the HFT space.  He also has some thoughts on what
the Linux kernel could do to help address those needs so that HFT companies
could move away from some of the custom code that is currently being
developed and maintained by multiple firms in the industry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple TV 4K 2022 review: Getting more for less]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11347</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/apple-tv-4k-2022-review-getting-more-for-less/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T16:24:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, it can be challenging to review a product, especially if it’s the first generation. Other times, like with the new Apple TV 4K, reviewing an iterative device simple. Everything about it is usually a little bit better or faster. This is the case with the latest Apple TV 4K introduced last month. Apple’s new […]
The post Apple TV 4K 2022 review: Getting more for less appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using CWs]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html#using-cws</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html#using-cws"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the new features on Mastodon for a recovering twitterer is the
      CW field for new posts. CW stands for Content Warning. When I’m composing
      a post, if I press the CW button, I have the option of putting a short
      phrase into a dialog. Readers will initially only see that short phrase,
      and need to click a button to see more. But there's a lot of strong
      opinions on when and how to use it - how do I navigate that?
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta's Sapling source-code management system]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915104/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915104/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T15:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has announced
the open-source release of part of its internal source-code management
system, called Sapling.


	Sapling began 10 years ago as an initiative to make our monorepo
	scale in the face of tremendous growth. Public source control
	systems were not, and still are not, capable of handling
	repositories of this size. Breaking up the repository was also out
	of the question, as it would mean losing monorepo’s benefits, such
	as simplified dependency management and the ability to make broad
	changes quickly. Instead, we decided to go all in and make our
	source control system scale.

	Starting as an extension to the Mercurial open source project, it
	rapidly grew into a system of its own with new storage formats,
	wire protocols, algorithms, and behaviors. Our ambitions grew along
	with it, and we began thinking about how we could improve not only
	the scale but also the actual experience of using source control.


At this point, only the client side of the system has been released; the
company "hopes to" release the rest later.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three more stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915098/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915098/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.0.9,
5.15.79, and
5.10.155
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/915097/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/915097/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T14:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (grub2, nginx, and wordpress), Red Hat (389-ds-base, bind, buildah, curl, device-mapper-multipath, dnsmasq, dotnet7.0, dpdk, e2fsprogs, grafana-pcp, harfbuzz, ignition, Image Builder, kernel, keylime, libguestfs, libldb, libtiff, libvirt, logrotate, mingw-zlib, mutt, openjpeg2, podman, poppler, python-lxml, qt5, rsync, runc, samba, skopeo, toolbox, unbound, virt-v2v, wavpack, webkit2gtk3, xorg-x11-server, xorg-x11-server-Xwayland, and yajl), SUSE (389-ds, bluez, dhcp, freerdp, jackson-databind, kernel, LibVNCServer, libX11, nodejs12, nodejs16, php7, php8, python-Mako, python-Twisted, python310, sudo, systemd, and xen), and Ubuntu (mako).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Does agile work with embedded software?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477199</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/does-agile-work-with-embedded-software/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with embedded software teams, I found several common reasons I’m often fed why Agile is not going to work. Agile has taken the...
The post Does agile work with embedded software? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Securing smart home energy management systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477194</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/securing-smart-home-energy-management-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:02:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data governance, privacy protection and security principles must be integrated into the fabric of how smart devices communicate to create true smart home and city...
The post Securing smart home energy management systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julian Durand</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using SDRs as a GPS/GNSS simulator]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477206</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/using-sdrs-as-a-gps-gnss-simulator/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software defined radios offer the performance and flexibility needed to help GPS/GNSS manufacturers test existing equipment. Editor’s Note: This is the first article in a...
The post Using SDRs as a GPS/GNSS simulator appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammad Usman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[봄이 아름답다는 마곡사, 가을도 아름답다, 공주 마곡사 단풍 기행]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588401</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588401/%eb%a7%88%ea%b3%a1%ec%82%ac-%eb%8b%a8%ed%92%8d-%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OSS Supply-chain Security: What Will It Take?]]></title>
        <id>3570923</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3570923"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T12:22:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10.29 참사 희생자 명단 공개에 관한 짧은 생각]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87520</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87520"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T11:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어느 때보다 조심스러운 마음입니다. 그 마음이 글에 온전히 담기길 바랍니다. 혹여 그렇지 못했다면, 어떤 비판도 겸허하게 감수하겠습니다. 제가 감히 10.29 참사 희생자라고 생각해봤습니다. 저는 제 이름을 공개하고 싶지 않을 것 같습니다. 다른 이유는 없습니다. 그게 저라는 사람입니다. 세상의 관계들, 의미들에서 이제 그만 해방되길 바랄 것 같습니다. 생이 얼마나 소중하고, 얼마나 간절했는와는 상관없이, 또 때론 얼마나 […]
The post 10.29 참사 희생자 명단 공개에 관한 짧은 생각 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.1]]></title>
        <id>2b053bfb-3418-4d0f-a338-e2dda781d6ab</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/16/whats-new-red-hat-enterprise-linux-91"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.1 brings new features and enhancements that deliver a more secure and consistent foundation for open, hybrid cloud environments and allow organizations to deliver workloads, applications, and services faster and more efficiently. Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.1 can be downloaded at no cost as a part of the Red Hat Developer Subscription for Individuals.
This article summarizes some of the ways Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9.1 further improves the developer experience.
The latest language runtimes and tools
Many of the most popular languages in enterprise and web development have seen upgrades.
Ruby 3.1 is a new release that includes a new experimental in-process just-in-time (JIT) compiler. The JIT achieves both a fast warmup time and performance improvements on most re…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Mungale, Alex Krikos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why OpenShift is essential for containerized applications]]></title>
        <id>a25d4e10-1e44-4cf3-a171-72afae277888</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/16/openshift-essential-containerized-applications"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few decades, application development has been evolving from bare metal hosting to virtualization to containers, leading to the adoption of the Kubernetes orchestration platform. This article traces these developments and explains how Red Hat OpenShift provides the next level of application support.
There has been an explosion in the modernization of application development and deployment over the past few years. Several publications such as Forbes and Business Wire quoted IDC's prediction that between 2018 to 2023 more than 500 million logical applications will be developed, which is equal to the number of applications built over the previous 40 years. In addition, businesses expect faster changes to applications.
Virtualization and the cloud
A great shift has taken place dur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공자가 죽어야 나라가 산다]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222930174266</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222930174266"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T04:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<공자가 죽어야 나라가 산다>는 1999년에 출간되었다. 벌써 20년이 지났다. 이 책이 전문적인 학술서도 아니고, 또 깊은 울림을 주는 교양서도 아니다. 그럼에도 어떤 사람에게는 여전히 이 책이 영향력을 주고 있는 것처럼 보인다. 책 <머리말>에 공자에 대해서 다음처럼 말한다. <현란한 수식어에도 불구하고 공자의 도덕은 사람을 위한 도덕이 아니라 정치를 위한 도덕이었고, 남성을 위한 도덕이었고, 어른을 위한 도덕이었고, 기득권자를 위한 도덕이었고, 심지어 주검을 위한 도덕이었다. 때문에 공자의 도덕을 딛고 선 유교 문화는 정치적 기만과 위선, 남성적 우월, 젊음과 창의성의 말살, 그리고 주검 숭배가 낳은 우울.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[금단의 땅, 서산 용유지 만추 풍경]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588394</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588394/%ec%84%9c%ec%82%b0-%ec%9a%a9%ec%9c%a0%ec%a7%80-%eb%a7%8c%ec%b6%94"/>
        <updated>2022-11-16T02:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 바이든 행정부 ‘산업정책’ 주도하는 상무부의 핵심 레이몬도 장관]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75553</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/15/npc_uscommercedep/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_uscommercedep"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T22:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 9월 12일 네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 쓴 글입니다. 로드아일랜드주 스미스필드라는 작은 마을의 이탈리아계 미국인 가정에서 태어났다. 아버지는 불로바(Bulova) 시계 공장에서 일했는데, 56세 때 공장이 해외로 이전하면서 일자리를 잃었다. 하버드 학부, 예일 로스쿨을 졸업한 뒤 로즈 장학생으로 옥스포드에서 수학했다. 나중에 싱글맘에 관한 논문으로 사회학 박사 학위를 받았다. 로드아일랜드주 최초의 벤처캐피털 회사를 차렸다. 2011년부터 주 재무장관을 지냈고, 2015년엔 로드아일랜드주 역사상 최초의 여성 주지사가 됐다. 주지사 재임 시절 주요 이력은 감세, 규제 완화, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Scaling the KVM community]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914638/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914638/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T21:23:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The scalability of Linus Torvalds was a
recurring theme during Linux's early years; these days maintainer struggles
are a recognized problem within open-source
communities in general.  It is thus not surprising that Sean Christopherson
gave a talk at Open Source Summit Europe (and KVM Forum) with the title
"Scaling KVM and its community".  The talk mostly focused on KVM for the
x86 architecture—the largest and most mature KVM architecture—which
Christopherson 
co-maintains.  But it was not a technical talk: most of the content can be
applied to other KVM architectures, or even other Linux subsystems, so that
they can avoid making the same kinds of mistakes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What 's new in .NET 7?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1009/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1009/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[.NET 7 is now available, which means that we can enjoy all sorts of new features and enhancements. Let's talk about the most interesting improvements: C# 11, containers, performance, GC, and so on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora 37 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914960/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914960/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T14:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 37
of the Fedora family of distributions has been released, a few weeks later
than originally intended.


	With Fedora Linux 37, we’re adding two new Editions. Fedora CoreOS
	is the successor to what you may remember as Atomic Host. Drawing
	from Project Atomic and the original CoreOS work, it provides an
	automatic update mechanism geared toward hosting container-based
	workloads. With atomic updates and easy rollback, it adds peace of
	mind to your infrastructure.
	
What's
new in Fedora 37 in Fedora Magazine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The industrial IoT is getting the IT treatment]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11343</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/the-industrial-iot-is-getting-the-it-treatment/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T14:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Marvell has launched a line of chips designed to bring Ethernet to factory and industrial settings. The chips include several security features as well as time-sensitive networking. And because Marvell believes the time is ripe for the IIoT to get a dose of Internet Protocol (IP), it has integrated these features into one module, lowering […]
The post The industrial IoT is getting the IT treatment appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914952/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914952/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T13:51:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (kernel and webkit2gtk3), Red Hat (dhcp, dovecot, flac, freetype, fribidi, frr, gimp, grafana, guestfs-tools, httpd, kernel-rt, libtirpc, mingw-gcc, mingw-glib2, pcs, php, protobuf, python3.9, qemu-kvm, redis, speex, and swtpm), SUSE (chromium, containerized-data-importer, jhead, kubevirt stack, nodejs14, nodejs16, python-Werkzeug, and xen), and Ubuntu (golang-1.13, nginx, and vim).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.0 alpha 2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/11/python-3120-alpha-2-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2022/11/python-3120-alpha-2-released.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.12 alpha 2.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3120a2/
This is an early developer preview of Python 3.12.


Major new features of the 3.12 series, compared to 3.11


Python 3.12 is still in development. This release, 3.12.0a2 is the second of seven planned alpha releases.


Alpha releases are intended to make it easier to test the current state of new features and bug fixes and to test the release process.


During the alpha phase, features may be added up until the start of the beta phase (2023-05-08) and, if necessary, may be modified or deleted up until the release candidate phase (2023-07-31). Please keep in mind that this is a preview release and its use is not recommended for production environments.


Many new features for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Literate Executables]]></title>
        <id>3570938</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3570938"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T11:10:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[그 아이가 위험하다: 태아산재법의 문제점]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87508</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87508"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T09:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아마도 이 글을 읽는 많은 분들에게는 ‘태아산재’라는 말이 생소할 것 같다. 일터의 위험 때문에 노동자가 일하다가 아프게 되면, 우리는 이것을 산재라고 부른다. 그런데 어떤 위험은 노동자 본인이 아니라 노동자의 아이를 아프게 한다. 이 경우를 우리는 태아산재라고 부른다. 태아산재의 법적인 용어는 ‘건강손상자녀’이고, 태아산재법 또한 별도의 법이 아니라 관련한 산재보험법 개정 내용을 일컫는 말이다. 다만 이에 […]
The post 그 아이가 위험하다: 태아산재법의 문제점 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>반올림</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Knative broker GA enhances Kafka on OpenShift Serverless]]></title>
        <id>61871045-e5e6-407e-b8ce-826e1bb03a83</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/15/knative-broker-enhances-kafka-openshift-serverless"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Kafka is greatly enhanced by the Knative broker, which reduces overhead for message delivery.  Red Hat OpenShift has its own Knative implementation, introduced as a Tech Preview earlier this year. Our Knative implementation has reached General Availability now with the 1.25 release of Red Hat Openshift Serverless.
How Knative enhances Kafka message delivery
Knative is integrated with Apache Kafka as an optimized, native broker that stores and routes events to interested consumers. The incoming cloud events are directly stored on a configurable Kafka topic and read from the same topic for message delivery when the messages are routed to a registered subscriber using a Trigger API. Integrating the broker and its trigger APIs directly into Apache Kafka has enormous benefits over other,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Wessendorf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to categorize C programs by behavior]]></title>
        <id>bb47bd70-8885-4eda-b25b-9f30e4c240dc</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/15/how-categorize-c-programs-behavior"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Most of us who write C and C++ code intuitively understand why some programs might behave differently when compiled with different compilers or different compiler options, or when running under particular conditions. We're also aware of the dangers of undefined behavior and usually try to avoid it in our code. But not all of us appreciate the many useful (and often unavoidable) aspects of undefined behavior. This article explains the kinds of behavior the C standard uses to categorize programs and their subtle, sometimes unexpected, impacts on compilers, libraries, other standards, and programmers themselves.
Programmers are rarely familiar with the subtle nuances of undefined behavior. Nor do programmers pay as close attention to the other kinds of behavior that C programs are subject to,…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Sebor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알도 레오폴드의 <모래 군의 열두 달> 4]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222929275151</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222929275151"/>
        <updated>2022-11-15T04:52:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 나는 작은 시내를 거슬러 올라가다 버려진 농가와 마주쳤다. 옛 밭을 가로질러 늘어선 어린 뱅크스소나무의 나이를 통해, 나는 얼마나 오래 전에 이 불운한 농부가 모래 평원에서는 곡식이 아니라 고독만이 자랄 뿐이라는 사실을 깨닫게 되었을까 추정하려고 해본다. 그러나 뱅크스소나무는 조심성 없는 사람에게는 허풍을 떤다. 왜냐하면 이 나무는 해마다 한 번이 아니라 여러 번의 돌려나기를 생성하기 때문이다. 이 나무보다는 지금 헛간 문을 가로막고 있는 어린 느릅나무를 통해 헤아려보는 것이 더 정확하다. 느릅나무의 나이테는 가물었던 1930년으로 거슬러 올라간다. 그 해 뒤로는 어느 누구도 이 헛간에서 우유를 실어내지 않았다.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 기층 유권자들의 이탈 부른 민주당 엘리트의 선택]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75726</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/14/npsp_elites/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_elites"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뉴스페퍼민트는 이번 주 새로 닻을 올린 SBS의 프리미엄 콘텐츠 채널 스프(스브스 프리미엄)에 글을 씁니다. 뉴욕타임스 칼럼 한 편을 번역해 소개하고, 해당 칼럼의 주제와 관련한 기사, 분석, 칼럼, 팟캐스트를 참고해 해설을 덧붙여 주에 두 편씩 글을 씁니다. 뉴스페퍼민트에는 스프에 글이 발행되는 시점에 맞춰 글에 대한 간략한 소개와 링크를 첨부해 올릴 계획입니다. 스프 채널에 가입만 하면 뉴스페퍼민트의 큐레이션 칼럼과 함께 다양한 정보, 콘텐츠를 제한 없이 보실 수 있습니다. 지난주 치른 미국 중간선거에 관한 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon is building robots at scale in Massachusetts]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11339</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/amazon-is-building-robots-at-scale-in-massachusetts/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T18:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has built a fleet of robots to help workers get packages from its warehouses to your door, and on Thursday it showed off two new ones. The first is Sparrow, a machine designed to pick up items (not packages) from a container and place them in a different container. The second is a concept […]
The post Amazon is building robots at scale in Massachusetts appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using final in C++ to improve performance]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/?p=3760</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2022/11/using-final-in-c-to-improve-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic polymorphism (virtual functions) is central to Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). Used well, it provides hooks into an existing codebase where new functionality and behaviour can (relatively) easily be integrated into a proven, tested codebase.
Subtype inheritance can bring significant benefits, including easier integration, reduced regression test time and improved maintenance.
However, using virtual functions in C++ brings a runtime performance overhead. This overhead may appear inconsequential for individual calls, but in a non-trivial real-time embedded application, these overheads may build up and [...] 

The post Using final in C++ to improve performance appeared first on Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Cooling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open-source software vs. the proposed Cyber Resilience Act (NLnet Labs)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914840/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914840/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NLnet Labs has put up a
blog entry warning about the possible effects of the "Cyber Resilience
Act" proposal in the European Commission.


	We feel the current proposal misses a major opportunity. At a high
	level the 'essential cybersecurity requirements' are not
	unreasonable, but the compliance overhead can range from tough to
	impossible for small, or cash-strapped developers. The CRA could
	bring support to open-source developers maintaining the critical
	foundations of our digital society. But instead of introducing
	incentives for integrators or financial support via the CRA, the
	current proposal will overload small developers with compliance
	work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Block-device snapshots with blksnap]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914031/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914031/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T16:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a general rule, one need not have worked in the technology industry for
long before the value of good data backups becomes clear.  Creating a
backup that is truly good, though, can be a challenge if the filesystem in
question is actively being changed while the backup process runs.  Over the
years, various ways of addressing this problem have been developed, ranging
from simply shutting down the system while backups run to a variety of
snapshotting mechanisms.  The kernel may be about to get another approach
to snapshots should the blksnap
patch set from Sergei Shtepa find its way into the mainline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet Bluefruit’s new EOT trustees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/?p=12652</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/people/meet-bluefruits-new-eot-trustees/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T15:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an employee-owned company, it is important that everyone at Bluefruit Software has their voice heard. We recently held a company-wide […]
The post Meet Bluefruit’s new EOT trustees appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914811/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914811/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T14:03:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (dropbear, php7.4, pixman, sysstat, and xorg-server), Fedora (mingw-expat, mingw-libtasn1, and mingw-pixman), Mageia (binutils/gdb, chromium-browser-stable, exiv2, libtiff, nodejs, pcre, pixman, wayland, and webkit2), Red Hat (device-mapper-multipath and libksba), SUSE (autotrace, busybox, libmodbus, php72, python-numpy, rustup, samba, varnish, xen, and xterm), and Ubuntu (thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 하필 출퇴근길에 시위하냐고요? 비장애인이 불편해야 장애인 목소리를 들으니까요…]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87491</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87491"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T10:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2021년 4월 초의 어느 날 오후, ‘전장연’ 회원들은 사무실 인근의 한 노선버스 정류장에서 집회를 진행했다. 이들은 장애인의 이동권 보장을 요구하는 문구를 적은 피켓을 목에 걸고 집회하던 중 마침 정류장에 도착한 버스 앞으로 나가 구호를 외치면서 버스의 운행을 막았다. 이날 전장연 회원들이 집회를 벌인 시간은 총 20분 남짓이며, 이 중 노선버스를 막아선 시간은 15분 정도에 불과했다. […]
The post 왜 하필 출퇴근길에 시위하냐고요? 비장애인이 불편해야 장애인 목소리를 들으니까요… first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 ways to embed a commit hash in Go programs]]></title>
        <id>f2546d72-10b9-4d83-a762-cf5c44656bf6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/14/3-ways-embed-commit-hash-go-programs"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you are using Go to write a simple console-based utility or a fancy web application, it is always helpful to reference the previous version of your software. This information is essential, especially for developers. They need to know what the source code looked like in previous versions, so they can debug any issues introduced at specific points in time.
To do that, you need a system that can control and manage different versions of the source code, such as git. Whenever you want to capture a snapshot of the program's current codebase, you run a git commit command that saves the code at that point in time. To make sure you do not overwrite a previously saved record, git creates (by default) a unique identifier, hashed with the SHA-1 algorithm, for every commit.
Usually, when a dece…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Panagiotis Georgiadis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[철학적 포스트휴머니즘의 전제들]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222928304185</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222928304185"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T04:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[페란도의 <철학적 포스트휴머니즘>(2021)은 포스트휴머니즘에 대한 만물상과 같은 책이다. 포스트휴머니즘에 대한 전체적 지형도를 그려주고 있으므로 (비록 그녀의 박사논문을 중심으로 작성되었다고 하지만) 논쟁적 의미에서 깊이가 있다고 할 수 없는 책이다. 포스트휴머니즘과 관련되어 아주 많은 책을 읽고, 어떤 의미에서 잡다하게 혹은 종합적으로 철학적 포스트휴머니즘의 주장과 과제에 대해서 이야기하고 있다. 철학적 포스트휴머니즘은 다음과 같은 주장을 하고 있다. (1) 대립적인 이원론과 위계적 질서에 대해서 반대한다. 즉 탈이원론의 철학이다. (2) 탈인간주의 또는 탈인류중심주의이어야 한다. 인간을 담론의 중심에서 탈.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of Non-Regular Data Members in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2022/non-regular-members/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2022/non-regular-members/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you have a class with a regular data member like an integer or string, you’ll get all special member functions out of the box. But how about different types? In this article, we’ll look at other categories of members like unique_ptr, raw pointers, references, or const members.



     
    


In my book on “C++ Initialization” I recently wrote a chapter about so-called non-regular data members.
Here’s a definition based on cppreference - regular concept
A type is regular, that is, it is copyable, default constructible, and equality comparable. It is satisfied by types that behave similarly to built-in types like int, and that are comparable with ==.
For example:
class Product {
public:    
    Product() = default;
    explicit Product(std::string name, unsigned id)
    : name_(std::move…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.1-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914747/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914747/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T23:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.1-rc5 for testing.


	But we'll see. If things don't start calming down, this may be one
	of those releases that need an extra week. It wasn't a particularly
	big merge window, but I don't particularly like how the rc's keep
	being on the bigger side.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some human biases in conditional reasoning]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7232</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/11/13/some-human-biases-in-conditional-reasoning/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T22:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tracking down coding mistakes is a common developer activity (for which training is rarely provided). Debugging code involves reasoning about differences between the actual and expected output produced by particular program input. The goal is to figure out the coding mistake, or at least narrow down the portion of code likely to contain the mistake. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[위기의 이연을 위한 양적완화가 초래한 결과]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=83914</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/83914/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T11:25:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[경제학자들은 통화당국이 상업은행에 단기 준비금을 제공하고 장기 국채를 매입함으로써 중앙은행의 채권매입 프로그램이 사실상의 재정정책의 하나였다는 것에 동의한다. 최근까지 이건 괜찮은 비즈니스처럼 보였다. 채권은 기술적으로 수익이 거의 없는 반면 조달비용이 무척 저렴했기 때문에(예를 들어 유로존에서는 -0.5%) 중앙은행은 어쨌든 이익이 났다. 그러나 많은 나라에서 물가가 두자릿수에 이를만큼 치솟음에 따라 중앙은행은 정책금리를 급하게 올릴 수밖에 없었다. 이로 인해 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[루소 형제 어셈블: 그들의 10억불 스튜디오 ‘아그보AGBO’ 스토리 (번역)]]></title>
        <id>http://ebadak.news/?p=3646</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2022/11/13/joe-anthony-russo-agbo/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-13T04:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[루소 형제는 2017년, 파트너 프로듀서인 마이크 라로카와 함께 독립적이며 아티스트 친화적인 스튜디오 아그보AGBO를 설립했습니다. 그들만의 크리에이티브를 만드는데 전념하기 시작했죠.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A first lesson in sales pitches: Honesty]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2022/11/12/honesty.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2022/11/12/honesty.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I seem to be getting quite a few requests from those who would wish to help
me on this blog.  These tend to fall into a couple of categories:
Search Engine Optimization (SEO) offers
Web redesign
Requests to submit an (irrelevant) article
Requests for me to link to an article somewhere
For all those to whom it may concern, therefore, let me offer the following
advice: 1) do your homework, and 2) be honest!
ZipCPU Funding
First and foremost, few of these cold e-mailers bother to look through the web
site to see how it is funded.  If they did, they might notice that
zipcpu.com doesn’t (currently)
advertise, it doesn’t
offer promotions, nor are there any links to click on to purchase ZipCPU
merchandise.
The closest thing to blog funding is a Patreon
link on the left of every page which people …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노자와 순자]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222926694236</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222926694236"/>
        <updated>2022-11-12T03:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 고대 동양 사상가 갑, 을 모두가 부정의 대답을 할 질문으로 가장 적절한 것은? (2022) 갑 : 무엇을 하고자 하는 사람[爲者]은 실패하고, 움켜잡는 사람은 잃는다. 그런 까닭에 성인(聖人)은 아무 것도 함이 없으므로 [無爲] 실패함이 없고, 움켜잡음이 없으니 잃음이 없다. 을 : 그릇은 옹기장이의 작위[僞]로 생기는 것이지 그 사람의 본성에서 생기는 것이 아니다. 예의(禮義)는 성인의 작위로 생기는 것이지 그 사람의 본성에서 생기는 것이 아니다. ① 인격 수양을 위해 후천적 노력이 필요한가? ② 하늘[天]이 부여한 도덕적 본성에 따라 살아가야 하는가? ③ 사람의 귀천과 상하를 구분하여 나라를 다스려야 하는가? ④ 성인은 예의를 제.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 11, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11326</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-11-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T19:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexa better get to work: Brace yourselves, Alexa owners. Amazon is looking at cost-cutting, according to a report in the Wall Street Journal, and Alexa looks like a target. The WSJ reports that the business unit has a reported loss of $5 billion a year. This being Amazon, a loss isn’t something to be ashamed of as long as […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 11, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Git evolve: tracking changes to changes]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914041/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914041/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T16:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Git source-code management system exists to track changes to a set of
files; the stream of commits in a Git repository
reflects the change history of those files.  What is seen in Git, though, is the
final form of those commits; the changes that the patches themselves went
through on their way toward acceptance are not shown there.  That history
can have value, especially while changes are still under consideration.
The proposed git
evolve subcommand is a recognition that changes themselves go
through changes and that this process might benefit from tooling support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914571/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914571/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T13:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and exiv2), Fedora (curl, device-mapper-multipath, dotnet6.0, mediawiki, mingw-gcc, and php-pear-CAS), Gentoo (lesspipe), Slackware (php), SUSE (git, glibc, kernel, libarchive, python, python-rsa, python3-lxml, rpm, sudo, xen, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (wavpack).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[은행나무와 짙은 안개가 신비로웠던 문광저수지 아침 안개 풍경]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588347</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588347/%eb%ac%b8%ea%b4%91%ec%a0%80%ec%88%98%ec%a7%80-%ec%95%88%ea%b0%9c"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T11:42:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기억을 기억하라: 10.29 이태원 참사를 함께 기억하는 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87485</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87485"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T08:51:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[투명사회를 위한 정보공개센터와 참여연대는 11월 10일(목)부터 시민의 알권리에 기반한 ‘기록과 기억을 위한 10.29 이태원참사 정보공개운동’을 시작한다. 정부발표와 언론보도 등으로 많은 정보가 쏟아지지만, 사실관계를 정확하게 보여주는 자료는 많지 않은 실정이며, 시민들이 제대로 알아야 참사의 진상을 규명하고 책임을 물을 수 있어 정보공개운동을 시작한다고 말했다. 일단 향휴 계획은 다음과 같다. 대통령실과 행정안전부, 서울시청과 용산구청, 경찰청과 소방청 등 모든 […]
The post 기억을 기억하라: 10.29 이태원 참사를 함께 기억하는 방법 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 로블록스 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각, 잘했지만 아직 기대에는 미치지 못해]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588361</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588361/%eb%a1%9c%eb%b8%94%eb%a1%9d%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a1%9c%eb%b8%94%eb%a1%9d%ec%8a%a4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T05:28:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[후기 비트겐슈타인의 선험론적 논증]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222925748247</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222925748247"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 해커는 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 차이를 형이상학적 진리와 표상이나 언어 서술의 규칙의 차이로 규정하고 있다. 칸트나 전기 비트겐슈타인은 모두 논리와 기호적 표상에 의해 선제되는 형이상학적이고 필연적 진리에 천착하고 있었다. 그러나 후기 비트겐슈타인은 이것을 포기한다는 것이 해커의 주장이다. 후기 비트겐슈타인이 강조하는 표상의 규칙은 추론적 규칙이다. 그러한 규칙은 우리가 사용하는 언어 의미에 구성적인 것이다. 따라서 가령 ‘빨간색’, ‘분홍색’, ‘더 어둡다’ 등의 단어의 의미를 잘 알면, 이것으로부터 ‘빨강색이 분홍색보다 더 어둡다’는 것을 추론할 수 있다. 따라서 빨강색이 분홍색보다 더 어둡다는 것을 아.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588355</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588355/%ec%bf%a0%ed%8c%a1-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T02:26:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 대안이라던 리비안 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각, 모든 문제가 해결되고 중장기 밝은 전망이 보인다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588348</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588348/%eb%a6%ac%eb%b9%84%ec%95%88-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a6%ac%eb%b0%94%ec%95%88-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T01:56:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SW보안약점 진단원 시험 후기]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13370786</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/13370786"/>
        <updated>2022-11-11T01:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국인터넷진흥원의 사이버보안인재센터(https://academy.kisa.or.kr/main.kisa) 에서는 매년 다양한 보안 관련 교육이 개설된다. 그 중에서 "SW 개발보안 교육"이라는 항목이 있다. 
기본적으로 SW개발보안 기본과정(개발자 대상, 공무원 대상)이 있고, SW보안약점 진단원 양성과정, SW보안약점 진단원 보수교육 등으로 이루어진다. 예전에는 개발단계 교육과 설계단계 교육 등도 있었는데 코로나19 이후로 교육들이 많이 축소되고 온라인 비대면으로 전환되면서 조금씩 커리큘럼이 바뀐듯하다.


일단 이번 글에서 설명할 것은 "SW보안약점 진단원" 이라는 일종의 자격증에 대한 설명과, 시험 후기이다.


1. SW보안약점 진단원 이란?
기본적으로 행정안전부고시 제2022-31호(행정기관 및 공공기관 정보시스템 구축운영 지침)에 따르면, 소프트웨어 보안약점이 남아있는지 진단하여 조치방안을 수립하고 조치결과 확인 등의 활동을 수행하는 사람이라고 되어있다. 이러한 업무를 하기위해서는 '자격증'이 있어야 하고, 자격증 시험에 합격하더라도 매년 일정시간동안 보수교육을 이수해야 한다.


우선 양성교육을 듣기 위해서는 6년 이상의 유관 개발경력 또는 3년 이상의 보안 업무 경력이 요구된다. 
기본적으로 "진단원 양성과정" 교육을 수료하면 총 3번의 응시 기회가 주어진다. 2022년 기준으로는 일정이 대략 6~9월 사이에 교육이 개설되고, 그 교육이 종료되는 시점에 시험이 있다. 나의 경우에는 2021년에 교육을 들었으나 2021년에 응시기회 2번을 사용하여 불합격했다. 그래서 2022년에 마지막 기회를 사용…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A round of stable-kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914423/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914423/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T20:12:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.4.224,
4.19.265,
4.14.299, and
4.9.333
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.

Note that 6.0.8,
5.15.78,
5.10.154
went into the review process at the same time, but have not yet been released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of new LWN site features]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914410/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914410/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T18:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have finally added a set of dark mode defaults to the customization options for the site for
those who prefer the dark side.  Thanks to all the readers who have asked
for this; apologies for taking so long to do it.  The defaults seem good,
but we are not dark-mode users, so please let us know if you have
suggestions for improvements.

Another new feature that has been requested for some time is the ability to
receive feature articles via email.  These emails are currently available
to subscribers at the "Project Leader" level and higher; interested
subscribers can sign up for the "Features" list on the mailing-lists page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Class action against GitHub Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914150/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914150/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T15:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GitHub Copilot
offering claims to assist software developers through the application of
machine-learning techniques.  Since its inception, Copilot has been
followed by controversies, mostly based on
the extensive use of free software to train the machine-learning engine.  The announcement of a
class-action lawsuit against Copilot was thus unsurprising.  The lawsuit
raises all of the expected licensing questions and more;
while some in our
community have welcomed this attack against Copilot,
it is not clear that this action will lead to good results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914347/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914347/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T14:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libjettison-java and xorg-server), Slackware (sysstat and xfce4), SUSE (python3 and xen), and Ubuntu (firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Arduino Opta adds a little IT to the OT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11320</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-arduino-opta-adds-a-little-it-to-the-ot/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T14:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show kicks off with a discussion of the lawsuit between Arm and Qualcomm amid accusations that Arm is changing its licensing model. We cover what has been said, and what it might mean for the IoT before heading into some industrial news. Arduino has announced a programmable logic controller (PLC) in conjunction with […]
The post Podcast: Arduino Opta adds a little IT to the OT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Split Your Overwhelmed Teams]]></title>
        <id>3570920</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3570920"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T13:34:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MBC 기자는 전용기 못 타!’ 대통령실에서 문자 통보]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87481</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87481"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T07:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 정부의 언론자유에 대한 인식 수준이 바닥을 치고 있다. 윤석열 대통령이 취임식에서부터 그토록 강조한 ‘자유’는 공영방송에 대한 언론탄압으로 이미 거짓임이 분명해졌다. MBC 기자의 전용기 탑승 불허는 그 언론탄압 방식조차 치졸한 수준으로 전락하고 있음을 드러냈다. 대통령실은 윤석열 대통령 동남아 순방 이틀을 앞둔 11월 9일 밤 MBC 기자들의 대통령 전용기 탑승 불가를 문자로 통보했다. 최근 MBC의 외교 […]
The post ‘MBC 기자는 전용기 못 타!’ 대통령실에서 문자 통보 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전기차 리비안 주가 폭등, 긍정적인 생산 예측이 촉매제]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588345</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588345/%eb%a6%ac%eb%b9%84%ec%95%88-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a6%ac%eb%b9%84%ec%95%88-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T07:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement a Rest API application with MongoDB using SBO]]></title>
        <id>668d4ce3-5724-4dc0-ab1a-f06a94845d7d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/10/implement-restapi-application-mongodb-using-sbo"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article concludes a two-part series about deploying a REST API application and binding it to a MongoDB using odo and a Service Binding Operator. Part 1, Set up an OpenShift cluster to deploy an application in odo CLI, explained the value of odo in managing a cluster and the applications in it. In that article, we installed both odo and the Service Binding Operator. Now you will learn how those tools easily create an instance of a database and a binding (connection) between the application and database.
Set up the application and database in 7 steps
Previously, we completed the prerequisites. Now we will demonstrate how to use odo to bind the REST application to the MongoDB database through the Service Binding Operator.
Follow these 7 steps:
Step 1: Get the application sources
Clone th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Ilario</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set up an OpenShift cluster to deploy an application in odo CLI]]></title>
        <id>99cd9947-0cf8-487c-9e3d-9cf898d48fcb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/10/set-openshift-cluster-deploy-application-odo-cli"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binding is the task of finding a backing service and connecting it to an application, such as a database. There are several ways to bind applications to cloud services in Kubernetes and Red Hat OpenShift. The odo command-line interface (CLI) consolidates steps that developers normally have to perform manually, and abstracts away Kubernetes and OpenShift background concepts.
With odo, you can concentrate on creating applications instead of administering the cluster. The odo tool automates deployment configurations, build configurations, service routes, and other Kubernetes and OpenShift elements.
The Service Binding Operator, employed by odo, makes the application developer's life a lot easier by providing a consistent and declarative Service Binding method.
This two-part series demonstrate…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francesco Ilario</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10/10 테슬라를 보는 월가의 시각]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588330</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588330/%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T05:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[학문적 양심]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222925039777</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222925039777"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T04:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[생태, 환경, 생명에 대한 노자 논문을 찾다가 우연하게 노자와 관련된 어떤 최근 논문을 하나 본다. 두 사람이 쓴 논문인데, 한 사람은 대학원생이다. 아마 짐작하건데 그가 논문을 쓰고 다른 사람 하나는 거기에 이름만 올려놓았을 것이다. (아니라면 참으로 다행이지만, 예전에는 이것이 거의 관례였다. 지금도 이러한 관례가 계속되는가?) 내가 다른 사람과 함께 논문을 쓴 경우가 딱 두 번 있었다. 당연하게 내가 썼고 그들은 그냥 이름만 얹었다. 그래도 하나는 연구비의 반을 주었지만, 다른 하나는 다 독식했다. 부당했지만, 그래도 괜찮았다. 이런 기회 덕분에 강제적으로 논문을 쓸 수 있었기 때문이다. 이런 경험 때문에 두 명 이상의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go and Proxy Servers: Part 2 - HTTPS Proxies]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/go-and-proxy-servers-part-2-https-proxies/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/go-and-proxy-servers-part-2-https-proxies/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T03:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is the second post in a series about proxy servers and Go. Here is a list
of posts in the series:</p>
<ul class="simple">
<li><a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/go-and-proxy-servers-part-1-http-proxies/">Part 1 - HTTP Proxies</a></li>
<li>Part 2 - HTTPS Proxies (this part)</li>
</ul>
<p>The previous part is an overview of proxy servers and presents some basic Go
implementations, as well as …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[디즈니 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각, 내년이 불안해..]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588321</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588321/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%94%94%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T03:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시가 총액의 89% 가 증발, 트윌리오와 B2B 스타트업 매출 총이익 관리의 중요성]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2453</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2022/11/10/twilio-and-importance-of-gross-margin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=twilio-and-importance-of-gross-margin"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T02:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 금요일은 IPO 혹은 창립 이후 트윌리오에게 악몽과도 같은 날이었습니다. 회사의 주가가 11월 4일 금요일 거래에서 하루만에 약 35% 이상 폭락하였기 때문입니다. 하루 전 3분기 재무 결과에서 4억 8,230만 달러의 순 손실이 보고된 직후 입니다. 트윌리오 (Twilio)는 고객과 관련된 모든 커뮤니케이션 관련 제품을 제공하는 클라우드 API/ SaaS 스타트업으로, 우리가 서비스 가입시 받아보게 되는 인증문자에 해당하는Continue reading "시가 총액의 89% 가 증발, 트윌리오와 B2B 스타트업 매출 총이익 관리의 중요성"
시가 총액의 89% 가 증발, 트윌리오와 B2B 스타트업 매출 총이익 관리의 중요성 appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 10, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913641/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913641/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-10T00:45:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 10, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Moving past TCP in the data center, part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914030/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914030/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T21:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of our earlier article on John
Ousterhout's talk at Netdev 0x16, he had concluded
that TCP was unsuitable for data-center environments for a variety of
reasons.  He also argued that there was no way to repair TCP so that it
could serve the needs of data-center networking.  In order for software to
be able 
to use the full potential of today's networking hardware, TCP needs to be
replaced with a protocol that is different in almost every way, he said.
The second 
half of the talk covered the Homa
transport protocol that he and others at Stanford have been working on
as a possible replacement for TCP in the data center.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Pass Converter for Mobile Wallets]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/11/open-source-pass-converter-for-mobile-wallets.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/11/open-source-pass-converter-for-mobile-wallets.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T17:19:00.017Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Stephen McDonald, Developer Programs Engineer, and Nick Alteen, Technical Writer, Engineering, Wallet
    

 
Each of the mobile wallet apps implement their own technical specification for passes that can be saved to the wallet. Pass structure and configuration varies by both the wallet application and the specific type of pass, meaning developers have to build and maintain code bases for each platform. 
As part of Developer Relations for Google Wallet, our goal is to make life easier for those who want to integrate passes into their mobile or web applications. Today, we're excited to release the open-source Pass Converter project. The Pass Converter lets you take existing passes for one wallet application, convert them, and make them available in your mobile or web application f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded forum at electronica 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477147</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-forum-at-electronica-2022-agenda/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T16:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[electronica 2022 is back in person in Munich on 15-18 November 2022. AspenCore Media will again host the embedded forum where we’ll explore various aspects of edge intelligence and AI, sustainability, HPC, and safety critical systems.
The post embedded forum at electronica 2022 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914221/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914221/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:17:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (vim, webkit2gtk, and wpewebkit), Fedora (mingw-python3, vim, webkit2gtk3, webkitgtk, and xen), Mageia (389-ds-base, bluez, ffmpeg, libtasn1, libtiff, libxml2, and mbedtls), Red Hat (kpatch-patch and linux-firmware), SUSE (conmon, containerized data importer, exim, expat, ganglia-web, gstreamer-0_10-plugins-base, gstreamer-0_10-plugins-good, gstreamer-plugins-base, gstreamer-plugins-good, kernel, kubevirt, protobuf, sendmail, and vsftpd), and Ubuntu (libzstd, openjdk-8, openjdk-lts, openjdk-17, openjdk-19, php7.2, php7.4, php8.1, and pixman).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why aren’t there any Matter smoke alarms?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11302</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-arent-there-any-matter-smoke-alarms/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T14:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a question on our Voicemail hotline from Sam. Given all of the recent Matter news, Sam is wondering if there are any smoke detectors that support Matter right now. It’s a good question because some people aren’t clear about what the first device types will […]
The post Why aren’t there any Matter smoke alarms? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역차별? 무상승차? 결국 독점과 협상의 문제 (ft. 넷플릭스 vs. SKB 1심 분석)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87460</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87460"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T11:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[소위 ‘망사용료’를 둘러싼 논란이 확대되고 있다. 이 논란은 2020년 4월, 넷플릭스가 서울중앙지방법원에 SK브로드밴드(이하 ‘SKB’)를 상대로 채무 부존재 확인 소송을 제기하면서 시작되었다. SKB는 넷플릭스에 망사용료 지급을 요구한 반면, 넷플릭스는 망사용료를 지급할 의무가 없다고 주장했다. 오징어 게임이 쏘아올린 ‘망 무임승차방지법’ 넷플릭스의 국내 트래픽이 급증하고, 넷플릭스 드라마 ‘오징어 게임’이 폭발적인 성공을 거두면서 해외 ‘콘텐츠 제공자'(Content Provider, 이하 CP)들이 막대한 […]
The post 역차별? 무상승차? 결국 독점과 협상의 문제 (ft. 넷플릭스 vs. SKB 1심 분석) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How static application security testing improves software security]]></title>
        <id>bd669d29-5afa-4243-9978-b13072135c19</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/09/how-static-application-security-testing-improves-software-security"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static application security testing (SAST) is one of the most effective techniques to improve application security. The term covers a variety of testing techniques that analyze an application's source, bytecode, or binary code for security vulnerabilities. Typically, developers complete this analysis during the software development lifecycle of an application. Many SAST tools are mature, and the techniques have become central to secure coding. Source code is the most common target of SAST, but you can also utilize SAST on bytecode and binary code.
Binary scanning analyzes the binary itself or the result of disassembling or decompiling it. Scanning binaries can add a benefit, unlike source code scanning, which identifies vulnerabilities created by the compiler. On the other hand, the report…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Florencio Cano Gabarda</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Mastodon Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html#multiple-mastodon-accounts</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html#multiple-mastodon-accounts"/>
        <updated>2022-11-09T00:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The usual Twitter convention is to follow the whole person, meaning one
      Twitter account for a person would tweet on many different subjects. In
      the Fediverse, however, that's not encouraged, so we'll see many people
      having multiple Mastodon (and other) accounts.s
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A software bug captured Apple and other huge companies]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1008/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1008/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We collected some hot stories about programming errors for you to have a little fun and learn something new. Keep reading to find out how one programmer broke the Internet by deleting a tiny piece of code and see other not-so-obvious errors.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Communities: Q3 ‘22 highlights and achievements]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/MLCommunities2022Q3.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/MLCommunities2022Q3.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T18:00:00.011Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nari Yoon, Hee Jung, DevRel Community Manager / Soonson Kwon, DevRel Program Manager
           

 
Let’s explore highlights and accomplishments of vast Google Machine Learning communities over the third quarter of the year! We are enthusiastic and grateful about all the activities by the global network of ML communities. Here are the highlights!


 
TensorFlow/Keras
  




  
Load-testing TensorFlow Serving’s REST Interface by ML GDE Sayak Paul (India) and Chansung Park (Korea) shares the lessons and findings they learned from conducting load tests for an image classification model across numerous deployment configurations. 
TFUG Taipei hosted events (Python + Hugging Face-Translation+ tf.keras.losses, Python + Object detection, Python+Hugging Face-Token Classification+tf.keras.…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Using certificates for SSH authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913971/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913971/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T17:49:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SSH is a
well-known mechanism for accessing remote computers in a
secure way; thanks to its use of cryptography, nobody can alter or
eavesdrop on the  
communication. Unfortunately,  SSH is somewhat
cumbersome when  
connecting to a host for the first time;  it's also tricky for a
server administrator to provide time-limited access to the server. SSH
certificates can solve these problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET 7 now available for RHEL and OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>b684ba57-1243-4e26-84fe-89001bd7f4a0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/08/net-7-now-available-rhel-and-openshift"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a quick overview of what developers need to know about this new major release. The .NET 7 release is now available, targeting Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8.7, RHEL 9.1, and Red Hat OpenShift.
.NET 7 includes 7 new features
These are the seven new features included in the new .NET 7 release:
IBM Power support: .NET is available for the following architectures: 

	
ppc64le (64-bit IBM Power) architecture for RHEL 8 and RHEL 9
x86_64 architecture (64-bit Intel/AMD)
ARM64 (64-bit ARM)
s390x (64-bit IBM Z)

	
C# updated to C#11: New language version C# 11 included.
New build support: Supports building completely native console applications.
Performance improvements: Many performance improvements were made throughout the base libraries, GC and JIT. A new source generator for regular …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Clingan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Texinfo 7.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914120/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914120/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T14:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 7.0 of Texinfo, the GNU Project's documentation system, has been
released.  There are a number of changes here, the biggest of which may be
the ability to produce output in the EPUB format.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914119/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914119/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T14:30:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (pixman and sudo), Fedora (mingw-binutils and mingw-gdb), Red Hat (bind, bind9.16, container-tools:3.0, container-tools:4.0, container-tools:rhel8, dnsmasq, dotnet7.0, dovecot, e2fsprogs, flatpak-builder, freetype, fribidi, gdisk, grafana, grafana-pcp, gstreamer1-plugins-good, httpd:2.4, kernel, kernel-rt, libldb, libreoffice, libtiff, libxml2, mingw-expat, mingw-zlib, mutt, nodejs:14, nodejs:18, openblas, openjpeg2, osbuild, pcs, php:7.4, php:8.0, pki-core:10.6 and pki-deps:10.6, poppler, protobuf, python27:2.7, python38:3.8 and python38-devel:3.8, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9, qt5, redis:6, rsync, unbound, virt:rhel, virt-devel:rhel, wavpack, webkit2gtk3, xmlrpc-c, xorg-x11-server, xorg-x11-server-Xwayland, and yajl), SUSE (exiv2, expat, rubygem-nokogiri, sudo, and vsftpd), and Ubuntu (isc-dhcp, libraw, sqlite3, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내장산 단풍 관광, 진 단풍이 더 아름답더라.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588258</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588258/%eb%82%b4%ec%9e%a5%ec%82%b0-%eb%8b%a8%ed%92%8d-%ea%b4%80%ea%b4%91"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T11:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A visual guide to deploying JBoss EAP on AWS]]></title>
        <id>a6b608d6-7c51-4345-8c73-94b1967d0705</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/08/visual-guide-deploying-jboss-eap-aws"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat recently launched a new offering for Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application Platform (JBoss EAP), an efficient and comprehensive Java platform on the Amazon Web Services marketplace. This offering allows you to deploy certified Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) equipped with Red Hat Enterprise Linux (fully supported by Red Hat) and JBoss EAP.  
Note: You are not required to have an existing JBoss EAP subscription from Red Hat prior to utilizing this service. This is a pay-as-you-go offering. Amazon will bill you for the service.
6 Steps to deploy a JBoss EAP on AWS
The following six steps guide you through provisioning, running, and connecting to JBoss EAP on AWS.
Step 1: Prerequisites set up
Set up the following prerequisites:
Sign up for an Amazon Web Services account.
Install the Amazo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Hayes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11/8 아마존, 메타 등 테크 기업을 보는 월가의 시선,]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588293</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588293/11-8-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80-%eb%93%b1-%ed%85%8c%ed%81%ac-%ea%b8%b0%ec%97%85%ec%9d%84-%eb%b3%b4%eb%8a%94-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%9c%ec%84%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T08:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이태원 참사 국정조사와 이상민, 윤희근, 박희영 사퇴가 필요한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87453</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87453"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T08:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“경찰이나 소방 인력을 미리 배치함으로써 해결될 수 있었던 문제는 아니었던 것으로 파악하고 있다.” (이상민 행정안전부 장관, 2022년 10월 30일) “이건 축제가 아닙니다. 축제면 행사의 내용이나 주최 측이 있는데 내용도 없고 그냥 할로윈 데이에 모이는 일종의 어떤 하나의 ‘현상’이라고 봐야 되겠죠.” (박희영 용산구청장, 2022년 10월 31일, 합동분향소에서 분향을 마친 후) 이태원 참사를 수사하는 경찰청 특별수사본부로부터 수사 […]
The post 이태원 참사 국정조사와 이상민, 윤희근, 박희영 사퇴가 필요한 이유 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to debug events: Learn how to use breakpoints]]></title>
        <id>84e3ee15-4367-4b75-aef8-1d3d5751cee2</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/08/introduction-debug-events-learn-how-use-breakpoints"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous articles on Red Hat Developer, I introduced you to the GNU Debugger (GDB) and explained what every developer should know about debuginfo. This article begins a series that will cover the expansive topic of debug events—that is, all the events to which GDB can respond. These include signals, breakpoints, watchpoints, syscalls, exceptions, and more. I'll be covering the commands and convenience variables and functions that will aid you in your endeavors to stop GDB at the right place at the right time.
A breakpoint is the most useful of these events, so let me start there.
What is a breakpoint?
A breakpoint instructs the debugger to stop at a particular code location in the user's program, returning control of the debugger to them. The user may then inspect the application's stat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keith Seitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국 코로나 봉쇄로 아이폰 공급 차질을 보는 월가의 시각]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588288</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588288/%ec%a4%91%ea%b5%ad-%ec%bd%94%eb%a1%9c%eb%82%98-%eb%b4%89%ec%87%84-%ec%95%84%ec%9d%b4%ed%8f%b0-%ea%b3%b5%ea%b8%89-%ec%b0%a8%ec%a7%88"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T06:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노자의 생태담론]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222923220550</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222923220550"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T04:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[머레이 북친이 다음처럼 이야기한다. <동양의 현인들이 심오하게 사유하고 느꼈다는 사실이 “그들의 저서가 모호하다”는 비판으로부터 그들을 구원해 주진 못한다. ... 서구의 동양사상 신봉자들은 가끔 자신들의 우월성을 입증하기 위해서 이러한 모호성을 애용하기도 하고, 자신들의 자가당착적 주장을 지성적인 것으로 만들기 위해 동양 현인들의 은유를 차용하기도 한다. 이러한 모호성은 그 자체로 좋은 장점이 되지 못한다. 왜냐하면 이것은 명료화와 해명을 요구하기 때문이다.> 나는 북친의 이런 주장에 공감한다. 나아가 생태, 환경, 생명 문제에 대해서 동양의 현인들의 사유에 대한 과도한 형이상학적 과장을 나는 좋아하지 않.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경제적 해자를 강화하는 아마존,아마존 프라임 혜택을 늘려 성장성 강화 추진]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588285</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588285/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ed%94%84%eb%9d%bc%ec%9e%84-%ea%b0%95%ed%99%94"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T02:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Two Cents #55] Web3 일반; Web3 시장 현황; 블록체인 L1 L2; De-Fi, NFT, 게임 메타버스, DAO, dApp; 인프라, 제도 규제, 생각할 꺼리들;]]></title>
        <id>https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-55-web3-web3-l1-l2-de-fi</id>
        <link href="https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-55-web3-web3-l1-l2-de-fi"/>
        <updated>2022-11-08T01:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Web3 개념] Blockchains are cities. Will we live in a multi-chain world, or… | by Haseeb Qureshi | Dragonfly Research | Medium (’22.1) L1을 (네트워트가 아닌) ‘도시’, multi-chain world을 multi-city world로 비유하면, 그 차이, 관련 개념을 이해하기 조금 쉬워짐 Utility Tokens From Real Businesses Will Drive Next Wave of Crypto Adoption — Tascha Labs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin Ho Hur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: Standard integers  and mixing integer types]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477124</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-standard-integers-and-mixing-integer-types/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T21:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All safer C language subsets like MISRA-C:2012 have a whole category of rules for integer arithmetic. Interestingly, these tend to be the most frequently violated...
The post Programming embedded systems: Standard integers <stdint.h> and mixing integer types appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter offers promise of single ecosystem for smart homes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477102</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/matter-offers-promise-of-single-ecosystem-for-smart-homes/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T20:43:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA) launched Matter with great fanfare in Amsterdam to showcase members’ solutions for smart homes devices that can talk to each other using a single language.
The post Matter offers promise of single ecosystem for smart homes appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the COVID-19 pandemic drove the move to rapid point of care testing technology]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477096</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-the-covid-19-pandemic-drove-the-move-to-rapid-point-of-care-testing-technology/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T20:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Testing manufacturers are turning to smaller, automated, cost-effective versions of lab-based systems. Such devices would help evolve the medical testing landscape from its current centralized...
The post How the COVID-19 pandemic drove the move to rapid point of care testing technology appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aileen Cleary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How microservices enhance agility in embedded systems development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477089</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-microservices-enhance-agility-in-embedded-systems-development/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T19:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By applying concepts from modern software development, embedded development can be faster and easier. Despite the increased use of embedded devices, development techniques remain in...
The post How microservices enhance agility in embedded systems development appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Rabault</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your organization should run its own Mastodon server]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/your-org-run-mastodon.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/your-org-run-mastodon.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T17:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest crisis at Twitter has led to a big surge of interest in
      Mastodon and the broader Fediverse of open social media platforms. My
      colleague Julien
      Deswaef has long been an advocate of the Fediverse. Here he explains
      why organizations should take control of their own social media platform
      by running their own Mastodon server.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter only solves about one of the smart home core issues]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11307</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/matter-only-solves-about-one-of-the-smart-home-core-issues/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T16:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Connectivity Standards Alliance (CSA) held a launch event for the Matter home interoperability specification on Thursday, and amid the flurry of self-congratulations there was a bit of Matter news and a ton of release information detailing when devices would get updated to Matter and how. Most notably, new releases will come out twice a year and […]
The post Matter only solves about one of the smart home core issues appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Better CPU selection for timer expiration]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913568/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913568/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T15:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the surface, the kernel's internal timer mechanism would not appear to
have changed much in a long time; the core API looks quite similar to the
one present in the 1.0 release.  Underneath the API, naturally, quite a bit
of complexity has been added over the years.  The implementation of this
API looks to become even more complex — but faster — if and when this 
patch set from Anna-Maria Behnsen finds its way into the mainline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전주 한옥마을을 다녀오다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588260</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588260/%ec%a0%84%ec%a3%bc-%ed%95%9c%ec%98%a5%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%84"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T14:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/914012/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/914012/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T13:44:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ffmpeg, libxml2, python-django, python-scciclient, and xen), Fedora (ghc-cmark-gfm, java-latest-openjdk, and vim), Mageia (expat, ntfs-3g, and wkhtmltopdf), Oracle (kernel), Slackware (sudo), and SUSE (expat, libxml2, rubygem-loofah, and xmlbeans).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KISDI 망사용료법 신중론의 의의와 한계: 문제는 ‘발신자 종량제’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87441</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87441"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T09:04:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[본문으로 들어가기 전에 논의에 사용되는 용어와 그 기본 개념을 짚고 넘어가자. (이하 ‘편집자’) 인터넷 접속료 ≠ 망사용료 망사용료 논의를 처음 접하는 독자는 ‘망사용료를 당연히 내야지?’라고 착각할 수 있는데, 망사용료 논의의 출발점은 망사업자(SKT 등)가 자신의 고객인 콘텐츠 제공자(네이버 등)가 이미 내고 있는 ‘인터넷 접속료’라는 망사용료 외의 별도 대가를 종량제와 같은 별도 형태로 받는 것을 의미한다. 즉, […]
The post KISDI 망사용료법 신중론의 의의와 한계: 문제는 ‘발신자 종량제’ first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build reactive apps on Kubernetes using Camel K]]></title>
        <id>8af1019a-6265-4caf-9789-cd3425b5b3dc</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/07/build-reactive-apps-kubernetes-using-camel-k"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reactive application meets modern requirements for customer-facing services. Reactive applications are message-driven, elastic, responsive, and resilient. Common traits of reactive applications include:
An event-driven architecture
Data integration
Distributed integration
Function-as-a-Service (FaaS)
Events play a major role in these types of applications. Events are not new, but event-driven architectures are gaining in popularity and use asynchronous message queue technologies such as RabbitMQ, Apache ActiveMQ, WebLogic, and IBM MQ. In this article, you'll learn how Apache Camel K can make it easier to develop reactive applications on Kubernetes by integrating data sources, Apache Kafka brokers, and Knative for event management.
Why choose Camel K?
Apache Camel K is a Kubernetes-native…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumit Mukherjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 유아론과 사적 언어]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222922266883</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222922266883"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T04:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 물리적 대상이란 흄이 주장하듯이 지각의 다발 혹은 묶음이다. 이것이 현상론의 기본 주장이다. 물리적 대상에 대한 언어가 감각 소여에 대한 언어로 번역되거나 환원될 수 있다고 현대적으로 표현할 수 있다. * 번역 가능성에 대해서 두 가지 비판이 제기되었다. 첫째, 그 번역이 무한하게 길어진다는 것이다. 둘째, 번역과정에서 물리적인 것에 대한 개념이 남아 있을 수밖에 없다는 것이다. 이런 의미에서 환원적 번역은 실패할 수밖에 없다. * 다음 글을 요약해 보라. <물리적 사물을 한 사람의 마음 혹은 한 관찰자의 경험들로 이루어진 구성물로 해석하려는 현상주의는 어떤 형태를 취하던 간에 기껏해야 약간 변형된 유아주의로 귀결.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[자동차 딜러의 아마존, 카바나 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588248</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588248/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%b9%b4%eb%b0%94%eb%82%98-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T04:37:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.1-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913980/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913980/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T04:35:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.1-rc4 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "So as hoped for (and expected), things seem to be starting to calm
down, and rc4 is a pretty normal size for this stage in the process".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘자동차 딜러의 아마존’ 카바나 몰락을 보는 두 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588246</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588246/%ec%9e%90%eb%8f%99%ec%b0%a8-%eb%94%9c%eb%9f%ac%ec%9d%98-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%b9%b4%eb%b0%94%eb%82%98-%eb%aa%b0%eb%9d%bd"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T03:19:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트위터 광고 매출은 일론 머스크 이전에 감소하고 있었다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588242</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588242/%ed%8a%b8%ec%9c%84%ed%84%b0-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-07T02:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evidence-based Software Engineering book: two years later]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7210</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/11/06/evidence-based-software-engineering-book-two-years-later/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T23:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two years ago, my book Evidence-based Software Engineering: based on the publicly available data was released. The first two weeks saw 0.25 million downloads, and 0.5 million after six months. The paperback version on Amazon has sold perhaps 20 copies. How have the book contents fared, and how well has my claim to have discussed […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 미국 대법원 돕스 판결, 중간선거 뒤흔들까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75537</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/06/npc_dobbsmidterm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_dobbsmidterm"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T22:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국 대법원은 지난 여름 로 대 웨이드(Roe v. Wade) 판결을 뒤집었습니다. 이로써 반세기 동안 미국 헌법이 보장해 온 여성의 임신중절권은 더는 헌법상의 권리가 아니게 됐습니다. 앞서 5월 유출된 판결문 초안에서 로 대 웨이드(Roe v. Wade) 판결은 근본적으로 잘못됐다고 강하게 비판했던 사무엘 앨리토 대법관은 6월 실제 판결문에서도 임신 중절은 대법원이 옳고 그름을 가릴 사안이 아니라 시민이 선출한 정부가 결정할 일이라고 못을 박았습니다. 로 대 웨이드를 폐기한 이른바 돕스(Dobbs) 판결의 의미와 영향은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make sure no Dynamic Memory is used]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=36000</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/11/06/how-to-make-sure-no-dynamic-memory-is-used/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T17:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to disable heap (dynamic memory allocation) in an embedded application? This article goes into the details of linker files and how to detect dynamic memory allocation. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 신인합일(神人合一)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222921257570</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222921257570"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T05:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 신이라는 실체는 자연이다. 즉 신즉자연(神卽自然)이다. 그것은 필연의 법칙이다. 즉 존재하는 모든 것이 신 안에 있고, 신은 우연적인 것이 아니다. 신은 필연적 방식으로 존재한다. 그러나 이렇게 필연적으로 존재한다고 주장되는 신이 진짜 있는 것인지 나는 모르겠다. (2) 필연의 법칙으로서 신은 인격적 신이 아니다. 신은 자유의지를 상징하지 않는다. 오히려 신은 우주적 필연의 법이면서 본성이다. 스피노자가 사용하는 <의지>라는 개념은 신적인 오성과 동의어이다. 따라서 그것은 자유의지가 아니라 필연적 원인이라는 개념이다. 신이 필연적으로 있다. 그리고 신은 필연적 법이다. 이 두 주장이 서로 다른 주장이다. 그럼에.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세계화 혹은 ‘공간의 압축’이 만들어 놓은 세계]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=83867</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/83867/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-06T00:11:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[노동자들의 단결은 대공업에 의해 만들어지는, 서로 다른 지방의 노동자들 상호간에 연계를 맺어주는 교통수단의 증대에 의해 촉진된다. 그런데, 이러한 연계만 맺어지면 어디서나 동일한 성격을 띠고 있는 허다한 지방적 투쟁들은 하나의 전국적 투쟁, 하나의 계급투쟁으로 집중할 수 있다. 그리고 모든 계급투쟁은 정치 투쟁이다. 지방도로를 갖고 있던 중세의 시민들이 수세기를 필요로 했던 단결을, 철도를 갖고 있는 현대 프롤레타리아들은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap 4.8 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913908/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913908/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T23:32:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.8 of the SystemTap tracing tool is out.  "Enhancements to this release include: kernel runtime improvements
on multi-CPU systems, python3 tapset support through python3.11,
tapset and template script for cve livepatching, bpf backend
embedded-code assembler improvements".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 4, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11299</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-4-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T19:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xerox is spinning out its predictive maintenance technology: Xerox’s Palo Alto Research Center (PARC) has spun out Novity, a predictive maintenance technology startup. Like other predictive maintenance software, Novity uses equipment sensors and proprietary algorithms to help manufacturers keep an eye on anomalous data in their plant operations that might cause future problems. A Xerox release […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 4, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Very Powerful Clipboard: Analysis of a Samsung in-the-wild exploit chain]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/a-very-powerful-clipboard-samsung-in-the-wild-exploit-chain.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/a-very-powerful-clipboard-samsung-in-the-wild-exploit-chain.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maddie Stone, Project Zero

Note: The three vulnerabilities discussed in this blog were all fixed in Samsung’s March 2021 release. They were fixed as CVE-2021-25337, CVE-2021-25369, CVE-2021-25370. To ensure your Samsung device is up-to-date under settings you can check that your device is running SMR Mar-2021 or later.

As defenders, in-the-wild exploit samples give us important insight into what attackers are really doing. We get the “ground truth” data about the vulnerabilities and exploit techniques they’re using, which then informs our further research and guidance to security teams on what could have the biggest impact or return on investment. To do this, we need to know that the vulnerabilities and exploit samples were found in-the-wild. Over the past few years there’s been tremendo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Two performance-oriented patches: epoll and NUMA balancing]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913291/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913291/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T15:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The search for better performance from the kernel never ends.  Recently
there has been a stream of smaller patches that promise incremental
performance gains, at least for some types of applications.  Read on for an
overview of two of those patches, which make changes to the epoll system
calls and to NUMA balancing.  This work shows where developers are looking
for performance improvements — and that not everybody measures performance
the same way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When your favorite devices will get Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11296</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/when-your-favorite-devices-will-get-matter/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T15:00:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welp, 2023 will be the year of Matter updates. Although there are already 190 devices that have (apparently) been certified so far, only a handful of them are available today. With only a few weeks left in 2022, and the initial release of the specification taking place just a month ago, it’s clear that the […]
The post When your favorite devices will get Matter appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: Mid-air haptics, Silex sells security biz, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477076</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-mid-air-haptics-silex-sells-security-biz-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T13:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s embedded news features various announcements including, Silex Insight selling its security business, Ultraleap new ultrasound transducer to scale up adoption of mid-air haptics and more.
The post embedded news: Mid-air haptics, Silex sells security biz, and more appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913849/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913849/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T13:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (clickhouse, distro-info-data, and ntfs-3g), Fedora (firefox), Oracle (kernel), Slackware (mozilla), and SUSE (python-Flask-Security-Too).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노란봉투법의 진실: 불법파업은 어떻게 만들어지는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87432</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87432"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T10:51:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 정부 첫 국정감사가 끝나고 민생법안 개정 논의가 본격화되는 가운데 노동조합 및 노동관계조정법(노조법) 2조와 3조 개정안인 일명 ‘노란봉투법’을 둘러싼 논란이 치열하다.   노란봉투법 비난 하는 정부여당과 보수 언론  더불어민주당이 노조법 개정을 정기국회 7대 입법 과제로 선정하자 정부 여당은 일찌감치 대통령 거부권 행사까지 예고했다. 여당 원내대표였던 권성동 의원은 “노란봉투법은 불법파업을 조장하는 ‘황건적보호법’에 불과하다”라고 주장했고, 김문수 […]
The post 노란봉투법의 진실: 불법파업은 어떻게 만들어지는가 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intros, deep dives, and announcements: Our best of October 2022]]></title>
        <id>35a5fa3e-a047-464f-890a-c2fc334a3f87</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/04/intros-deep-dives-and-announcements-our-best-october-2022"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've gathered up the most popular content from Red Hat Developer for October 2022, and we hope you find it informative and helpful. We've divided them into product announcements, topic roundups, learning guides, and advanced deep dives.
Get started with product announcements
Red Hat is joining the Backstage.io community to improve the developer experience on Red Hat OpenShift. In this announcement, Serena Chechile Nichols describes how OpenShift and Kubernetes are critical to Red Hat's customers, and how Red Hat aims to provide tools that make it easier and more productive for teams to build services and applications.
At KubeCon North America 2022, Stevan Le Meur and Tim deBoer highlighted how the Podman community unveiled and introduced Podman Desktop. This convenient GUI enables users t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Heiker Medina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[펌글]스트라이프 정리해고에서 얻는 시사점]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588240</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588240/%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b4%ed%94%84-%ec%a0%95%eb%a6%ac%ed%95%b4%ea%b3%a0"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T05:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제프리 건들락, 연준 금리인상은 4.5%에서 멈출 것이며 미국채와 신흥시장 투자를 제안]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588234</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588234/%ec%97%b0%ec%a4%80-%ea%b8%88%eb%a6%ac-%ec%9d%b8%ec%83%81-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T05:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 논증과 해명]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222919424308</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222919424308"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T03:09:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 다음 글을 논증으로 요약해 보라. 어른이 어린이의 권리에 참여할 수 있는 것은 어린 시절이 있었다는 것에 정당한 이유가 있다. 철학자의 어린이는 가상적(假想的) 사유의 주체이지만, 소설가 생텍쥐베리의 어린이는 합리적 사유 저편에 있는 초자연적 사유의 주체이다. 소설가의 관점에서 어린 시절의 기억은 우리가 극복하고 넘어서야 하는 장애가 아니라, 우리가 합리적 사유 안에서 망각하고 있는 본래적 사유의 길잡이다. 그 기억 속에 어린 시절은 다시 태어나야 하고 변신을 거듭해야 할 고향이다. 왜냐하면 진리와 행복은 어린 아이의 눈에만 나타나기 때문이다. 어른이 된다는 것은 기원의 원초적 순수성을 상실하는 것이고, 자연의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 퀄컴 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 스마트폰 수요 악화의 직격탄이 커질 듯]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588228</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588228/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%80%84%ec%bb%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T02:36:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 에어비앤비 실적을 읽는 월가의 시각,4분기 및 2023년 전망의 불확실성에 주목]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588221</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588221/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%97%90%ec%96%b4%eb%b9%84%ec%95%a4%eb%b9%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-04T01:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913771/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913771/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T19:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (pypy3), Fedora (drupal7, git, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, and php), Oracle (kernel, lua, openssl, pcs, php-pear, pki-core, python3.9, and zlib), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, lua, openssl-container, pcs, php-pear, pki-core, python3.9, and zlib), Scientific Linux (kernel, pcs, and php-pear), SUSE (EternalTerminal, hsqldb, ntfs-3g_ntfsprogs, privoxy, rubygem-actionview-4_2, sqlite3, and xorg-x11-server), and Ubuntu (ntfs-3g, python3.10, and sqlite3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A report from the 2022 Image-Based Linux Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912774/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912774/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T18:38:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first Image-Based Linux Summit was
held in Berlin on October 5 and 6, 2022. The main goal of this summit was to
agree on common concepts and tooling for how to build, deploy, and run modern,
secure, image-based Linux distributions — a project that that the organizers,
Christian Brauner, Luca Boccassi, and Lennart Poettering, have been working on
for some time.  The result was a more refined vision of how Linux systems
can be built and deployed securely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From a personal notebook to 100k YouTube subscriptions: How Carlos Azaustre turned his notes into a YouTube channel]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/11/from-personal-notebook-to-100k-youtube-subscriptions-carlos-azaustre.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/11/from-personal-notebook-to-100k-youtube-subscriptions-carlos-azaustre.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kevin Hernandez, Developer Relations Community Manager
 

 




Carlos Azaustre with his Silver Button Creator Award from YouTube




When Carlos Azaustre, Web Technologies GDE, finished university, he started a blog to share his personal notes and learnings to teach others about Angular and JavaScript. These personal notes later evolved into tutorials that then turned into a blossoming YouTube channel with 105k subscriptions at the time of this writing. With his 10 years of experience as a Telecommunications Engineer focused on front end development, he has a breadth of experience that he shares with his viewers in a sea of competing content currently on YouTube. Carlos has successfully created a channel focused on technical topics related to JavaScript and has some valuable adv…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today's crop of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913679/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913679/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T16:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.0.7, 5.15.77, 5.10.153, 5.4.223, 4.19.264, 4.14.298, and 4.9.332 stable kernels.  As usual, they
contain important fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.65.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913635/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913635/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T15:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.65.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Improvements include
generic associated types, a new let...else statement, and the
ability to break from labeled blocks:


	Plain block expressions can now be labeled as a break
	target, terminating that block early. This may sound a little like
	a goto statement, but it's not an arbitrary jump, only
	from within a block to its end. This was already possible with
	loop blocks, and you may have seen people write loops that
	always execute only once, just to get a labeled break.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Here’s when you’ll get Matter on your devices]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11287</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-heres-when-youll-get-matter-on-your-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T14:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s episode kicks off what I hope is a flurry of news from vendors about their Matter plans. We hear when and how vendors such as Amazon, Eve, Nanoleaf, and Schneider Electric plan to roll out Matter to new and old devices. We also call out companies that haven’t yet shared information and what […]
The post Podcast: Here’s when you’ll get Matter on your devices appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[임대인이 ‘실거주 갱신거절’ 거짓말로 1,250만원 물어낸 사연]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87423</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87423"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T09:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2020년 7월과 8월 국회에서 이른바 ‘임대차 3법’(계약갱신청구권, 전월세 인상율 상한제, 전월세 신고제)이 통과됐다. 임차인의 ‘안심하고 살 권리’ vs. 임대인의 갱신거절권  그 중에서도 계약갱신청구권은 주택임대차에 있어서 임차인(세입자)이 2년의 임대기간이 끝났을 때 임대인(집주인)에게 2년 더 살겠다고 먼저 요구할 수 있는 권리를 처음으로 인정한 것이었다. 이전까지는 법에서 보장하는 임대기간이 불과 2년이었기 때문에 임차인으로서는 그 기간이 다 되었을 […]
The post 임대인이 ‘실거주 갱신거절’ 거짓말로 1,250만원 물어낸 사연 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Node.js Reference Architecture, Part 10: Accessibility]]></title>
        <id>05737025-a2df-4580-b548-c78f89eb648a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/03/nodejs-reference-architecture-part-10-accessibility"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Making applications accessible to disabled users is both good business and often required by law. We must develop the Node.js components that are part of these applications in a way that facilitates accessibility. This installment of the ongoing Node.js Reference Architecture series covers the key questions that Node.js developers need to understand about accessibility:
Do Node.js developers need to worry about accessibility?
Are there standards and guidelines for accessibility?
What do I need to do as a Node.js developer?
Read the series:
Part 1: Overview of the Node.js reference architecture
Part 2: Logging in Node.js
Part 3: Code consistency in Node.js
Part 4: GraphQL in Node.js
Part 5: Building good containers
Part 6: Choosing web frameworks
Part 7: Code Coverage
Part 8: Typescript
Par…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Next-10 project supports the future of Node.js]]></title>
        <id>153c9186-0f9d-40b3-8655-9b0802fb2180</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/03/how-next-10-project-supports-future-nodejs"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Node.js community is working on an effort to ensure the Next-10 project is just as successful over the next ten years as it was in the first ten. This large open source project is the basis for many backend web applications and offers lessons for other open source communities. This article discusses the project's goals and progress.
Why open source planning is difficult
Many open source projects find it difficult to plan upgrades and set roadmaps because nobody is in charge of telling people what to do. The collaborative process can be a difficult mind shift for people coming from teams that have done internal development.
Roadmaps are easier for projects sponsored mainly by a single organization. Although the single organization project is open, a lead from that organization can more …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블름버그, 월가는 파월의 논평에서 ‘악마의 흥정’을 봅니다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588216</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588216/11%ec%9b%94-fomc-%ed%9a%8c%ec%9d%98"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T06:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 모종삼의 삼통설(三統說)]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222918505989</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222918505989"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T04:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 모종삼은 삼통설(三統說)에 대해서 주장한다. 삼통(三統)은 도통(道統), 정통(政統), 학통(學統)이다. 도통(道通)은 내성의 학문, 즉 유학이며, 정통(政統)은 민주정치이고, 학통(學統)은 과학지식이다. 이 세 가지에 대해서 모종삼은 도통이 정통과 학통을 통섭(統攝)한다고 주장한다. (2) 도통이 하는 통섭의 기능은 구성적, 구조적인 것이 아니라, 규제적이다. 따라서 가령 도통은 정통이나 학통을 집어 삼키는 것을 의미하지 않는다. 이런 의미에서 삼통설(三統說)은 환원주의가 아니며, 범도덕주의도 아니다. (3) 과학과 민주라는 중국 현대화가 추구해야 할 두 가지 목표에서 주의할 것이 있다. 하나가 과학주의, 혹은 과학일층론(科學.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 AMD 실적을 보는 월가의 시각, 바닥을 다지고 있다?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588206</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588206/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-amd-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T03:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Replacing my home desktop computer]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/replacing-my-home-desktop-computer/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2022/replacing-my-home-desktop-computer/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-03T03:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After 9 years, it's time to retire my <a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2013/11/23/a-new-ubuntu-machine-for-home/">old and faithful home Linux machine</a>. It
has served me extremely well, by far the longest time I've used a home computer
without any replacements. The fans were starting to show their age, to the
extent that the CPU fan sometimes needs …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 3, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912698/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912698/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T23:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 3, 2022 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Modernizing Fedora's C code]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913505/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913505/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is not often that you see a Fedora change proposal for a version of the
distribution that will not be available for 18 months or so, but that
is exactly what was recently posted to the mailing list. 
The change targets the C source code in the myriad of packages that the
distribution ships; it would fix code that uses some ancient compatibility
features that were removed by the C99 standard but are still supported by
GCC.  As might be guessed from the 
long runway proposed, there is quite a bit of work to do to get there.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catastrophic backtracking: how can a regular expression cause a ReDoS vulnerability?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1007/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1007/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular expressions come in handy when you need to search for and replace text. However, in some cases, they may cause the system to slow down or even make vulnerable to ReDoS attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new crop of malicious modules found on PyPI]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913555/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913555/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T18:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phylum has posted an
article with a detailed look at a set of malicious packages discovered
by an automated system they have developed.


	Similar to this attacker’s previous attempts, this particular
	attack starts by copying existing popular libraries and simply
	injecting a malicious __import__ statement into an otherwise
	healthy codebase. The benefit this attacker gained from copying an
	existing legitimate package, is that because the PyPI landing page
	for the package is generated from the setup.py and the README.md,
	they immediately have a real looking landing page with mostly
	working links and the whole bit. Unless thoroughly inspected, a
	brief glance might lead one to believe this is also a legitimate
	package.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An appeal to Americans who aren't inclined to vote in the midterm              elections]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2022-midterm-vote.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2022-midterm-vote.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the United States, we have midterm elections coming up. Many people
      aren't interested in politics, or feel there is nobody worthwhile to vote
      for. If you're an American inclined to skip voting in these midterms, I'd
      appreciate it if you read my appeal.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extending support for App Engine bundled services (Module 17)]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/extending-support-for-app-engine-bundled-services-module-17.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/extending-support-for-app-engine-bundled-services-module-17.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T17:00:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Wesley Chun (@wescpy), Developer Advocate, Google Cloud
 

 
Background
 App Engine initially launched in 2008, providing a suite of bundled services making it convenient for applications to access a database (Datastore), caching service (Memcache), independent task execution (Task Queue), Google Sign-In authentication (Users), or large "blob" storage (Blobstore), or other companion services. However, apps leveraging those services can only run their apps on App Engine. 
To increase app portability and help Google move towards its goal of having the most open cloud on the market, App Engine launched its 2nd-generation service in 2018, initially removing those legacy services. The newer platform allows developers to upgrade apps to the latest language runtimes, such as moving from…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Nest Wifi Pro review: Matter ready and good for the money]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11272</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/google-nest-wifi-pro-review-matter-ready-and-good-for-the-money/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T15:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has finally brought WiFi 6 and WiFi 6E to its router lineup with the new Nest Wifi Pro. This mesh networking system is relatively inexpensive with one-, two- and three-packs of units priced at $199.99, $299.99, and $399.99 respectively. I’ve been using a trio of Nest Wifi Pro units and expected a wireless performance […]
The post Google Nest Wifi Pro review: Matter ready and good for the money appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913504/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913504/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T14:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ffmpeg and linux-5.10), Fedora (libksba, openssl, and php), Gentoo (openssl), Mageia (curl, gdk-pixbuf2.0, libksba, nbd, php, and virglrenderer), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, libksba, and openssl), SUSE (gnome-desktop, hdf5, hsqldb, kernel, nodejs10, openssl-3, php7, podofo, python-Flask-Security, python-lxml, and xorg-x11-server), and Ubuntu (backport-iwlwifi-dkms, firefox, ntfs-3g, and openssl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twitter feed now cross-posts to Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html#twitter-feed-to-mastodon-is-now-working</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html#twitter-feed-to-mastodon-is-now-working"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the main things I wanted to do with Mastodon was to replicate my
      twitter feed there, so that folks who would rather follow me on Mastodon
      could get everything. To do this, I used moa.party.
      You have to give it credentials to access both your Twitter and Mastodon
      feeds, which is a little worrisome, but my Mastodon-aware colleagues have
      used it without problems. It allows cross-posting in either or both
      directions, but I've set it up to just go from Twitter to Mastodon. It's
      pretty simple and seems to be working. So if you'd like to follow my
      twitter feed from Mastodon, you can now do so.
I'll be monitoring the follower count for the Mastodon account. If lots
      of people follow me on Mastodon, I'll probably do more with it. So
      following my Mastodon feed is vote for me to put more effort into it. But
      for the moment, I expect it to be a simple copy of what I post on
      Twitter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gregor Samsa: Exploiting Java's XML Signature Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/gregor-samsa-exploiting-java-xml.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2022/11/gregor-samsa-exploiting-java-xml.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T11:41:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Felix Wilhelm, Project Zero

Earlier this year, I discovered a surprising attack surface hidden deep inside Java’s standard library: A custom JIT compiler processing untrusted XSLT programs, exposed to remote attackers during XML signature verification. This post discusses CVE-2022-34169, an integer truncation bug in this JIT compiler resulting in arbitrary code execution in many Java-based web applications and identity providers that support the SAML single-sign-on standard. 
OpenJDK fixed the discussed issue in July 2022. The Apache BCEL project used by Xalan-J, the origin of the vulnerable code, released a patch in September 2022. 

While the vulnerability discussed in this post has been patched , vendors and users should expect further vulnerabilities in SAML.

From a security resea…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미래의 농업: 스마트팜, 어그테크, 정밀농업을 위한 클라우드 서비스]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87410</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87410"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T10:52:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[스마트 팜, 어그테크, 정밀농업  스마트 팜은 농림축산식품부의 정의에 따르면 ‘비닐하우스·유리온실·축사 등에 IoT, 빅데이터·인공지능, 로봇 등 4차 산업혁명 기술을 접목하여 작물과 가축의 생육환경을 원격·자동으로 적정하게 유지·관리할 수 있는 농장’이며 원격 제어 단계의 1세대, 데이터 기반 정밀 생육 관리 단계의 2세대, 인공지능· 무인 자동화 단계인 3세대로 구분한다. 이 가운데에서 2세대 모델부터는 기본 구성에서 클라우드서비스를 고려하고 있으며 […]
The post 미래의 농업: 스마트팜, 어그테크, 정밀농업을 위한 클라우드 서비스 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인간중심적 윤리학 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222917523686</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222917523686"/>
        <updated>2022-11-02T04:41:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222907856154 인간중심주의라는 개념이 다의적이다. 따라서 어떤 인간중심주의는 용인할 수 없지만, 어떤 인간중심주의는 그 설득력을 따져 보아야 한다고 생각한다. 윤리학의 경우, 인간중심적 윤리학을 다음처럼 묘사하고 있다. 쉽게 인정할 수 없는 인간중심주의적 윤리학은 다음과 같은 주장을 하고 있다. 즉 <오직 인간만이 도덕적 가치를 갖는다.> 따라서 자연에 대해서 우리는 직접적 책임을 갖는 것이 아니라, 간접적 책임을 갖는다. 그러나 오직 인간만이 도덕적 가치를 갖지 않는다. 인간에게만 적용되었던 도덕적 가치를 충분히 확장할 수 있다. 따라서 가령 동물도 도덕적 가치 혹은 생명적 가.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913392/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913392/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T23:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.4.222,
4.19.263, and
4.14.297
stable kernel updates have been released.  The first two contain a single
patch for a Clang compilation error; 4.14.297, instead, has a number of
fixes and speculative-execution mitigations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Moving past TCP in the data center, part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913260/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913260/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T23:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the recently concluded Netdev
0x16 conference, which was held both in Lisbon, Portugal and virtually,
Stanford professor John Ousterhout gave his personal views on where
networking in data centers needs to be headed.  To solve the problems that
he sees, he suggested some "fairly significant changes" to those
environments, including leaving behind the venerable—ubiquitous—TCP
transport protocol.  While LWN was unable to attend the conference itself,
due to scheduling and time-zone conflicts, we were able to view the video of
Ousterhout's keynote talk to bring you this report.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 정체성과 얼굴]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75518</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/11/01/npc_identity/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_identity"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T22:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정체성은 한 사람을 다른 사람과 구별 짓는 특성입니다. 영어 단어로는 “identity”가 정체성을 뜻하죠. 한 사람의 정체성이 어디에 있는가는 철학적인 질문이지만, 매우 현실적인 질문이기도 합니다. 오늘날 우리는 이 질문에 답하는 데 필요한 다양한 기술을 가지고 있습니다. 곧 내가 나임을 증명하는 기술입니다. 우리는 스마트폰을 열기 위해 지문이나 얼굴을 이용하며, 인터넷으로 송금하기 위해서는 기억 속의 비밀번호를 이용합니다. 국가가 발행하는 신분증은 여전히 중요한 기술이지만, 그리 오래되지 않았습니다. 영화 “마틴 기어의 귀향”은 몇백 년 전만 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Mastodon]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-mastodon.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I've been a heavy user of Twitter over the last decade, and while
      Musk's purchase of Twitter hasn't got me running for the exit, it has
      prompted me to take a look at possible alternatives should Twitter change
      into something no longer worthwhile for me. The obvious alternative is for
      me to explore the fediverse with a Mastodon account. As I explore using
      Mastodon, I'll make some notes here so that others can learn from my
      explorations.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSL 3.0.7 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913370/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913370/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T16:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The much-anticipated OpenSSL 3.0.7 release, which fixes some high-risk
security problems, is available.  The release
notes list two vulnerabilities (CVE-2022-3786 and CVE-2022-3602) that
have not yet been documented on the OpenSSL
vulnerabilities page.  LWN commenter mat2 has provided the relevant information, though.  It
is worth updating quickly, but many sites do not appear to be at immediate
risk.

Update: the associated security
advisory is now available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Developer Journey: November 2022]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/developer-journey-november22.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/developer-journey-november22.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lyanne Alfaro, DevRel Program Manager, Google Developer Studio
  
 
Developer Journey is a new monthly series to spotlight diverse and global developers sharing relatable challenges, opportunities, and wins in their journey. Every month, we will spotlight developers around the world, the Google tools they leverage, and the kind of products they are building. 
We are kicking off #DevJourney in November to give members of our community the chance to share their stories through our social platforms. This month, it’s our pleasure to feature four members spanning products including Google Developer Expert, Android, and Cloud. Enjoy reading through their entries below and be on the lookout on social media platforms, where we will also showcase their work. 
 

Sierra OBryan, Google Deve…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913352/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913352/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T14:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (python3.7), Gentoo (android-tools, expat, firefox, libjxl, libxml2, pjproject, sqlite, thunderbird, and zlib), Oracle (compat-expat1), Slackware (php8 and vim), SUSE (kernel, libtasn1, podman, and pyenv), and Ubuntu (libtasn1-6).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perygee is bringing no-code ease to OT cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11263</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/perygee-is-bringing-no-code-ease-to-ot-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T13:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published on Friday Oct. 28, 2022 in my weekly IoT newsletter.  This week, a three-year-old security startup called Perygee raised $4.75 million from investors that include some significant names in cybersecurity. The company says it has created a no-code cybersecurity platform that brings in data from devices on a network and marries that […]
The post Perygee is bringing no-code ease to OT cybersecurity appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Loading Multiple (Binary) Files with GDB]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=35641</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2022/11/01/loading-multiple-binary-files-with-gdb/"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T11:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A typical debugging session involves just one ELF/Dwarf binary or executable. But what if I need to program multiple binary files with gdb? Things like loading both the bootloader and the application binary? Or I have a an on-chip file … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[망사용료 주장의 9가지 약점 (ft. 영국 오프콤 보고서)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87399</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87399"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T10:05:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[망사용료법(전기통신사업법 개정안)은 합리적인 정책인가. 망사용료법은 일반 이용자를 위한 법안인가 아니면 망사업자를 위한 법안인가. 정치권에서 추진 중인 망사용료법에 관한 판단에 참고가 될 영국 오프콤 보고서가 지난 10월 24일 발표됐다. 오프콤 보고서의 내용을 확인하기 전에 우선 몇 가지 용어와 개념을 짚고 넘어가자. 1. 오프콤 » 방송통신위원회 오프콤(Ofcom)은 영국의 방송통신규제기구다. 정식 명칭은 커뮤니케이션청(Office of Communications)이다. 영국의 방송, […]
The post 망사용료 주장의 9가지 약점 (ft. 영국 오프콤 보고서) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오픈넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트위터 인수는 일론 머스크와 트위터 모두에게 하방 위험이다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588198</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588198/%ed%8a%b8%ec%9c%84%ed%84%b0-%ec%9d%b8%ec%88%98-%ec%9c%84%ed%97%98"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T07:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Kamelets simplify Camel integrations on Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>21c2c77b-e4dc-4e1e-a818-58d4aee3d5bf</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/11/01/how-kamelets-simplify-camel-integrations-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Modern applications, rarely coded from scratch, are formed by combining software components (known as subsystems) into a single system. This process is called integration. Typical subsystems include databases and web services. This article explains how Apache Camel and Kubernetes support easy integration of such services through Kamelets.
How Kamelets make Camel integration easy
Apache Camel is a popular open source integration framework based on known Enterprise Integration Patterns (EIPs). Camel is a complete, production-ready framework with a built-in set of patterns you can use in your integration flows. These patterns are based on design patterns and help connect different systems.
Developers build many frameworks on Apache Camel. This article focuses on Camel K, but several other fra…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammadi Iram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quiz #22: Handling cover failures]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/quiz/2022/11/01/quiz22.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/quiz/2022/11/01/quiz22.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A failed formal cover check can be one of the most challenging things to debug.
All you know is that the formal tool failed to be able to make the covered
expression true.  You have no trace to work with to show you how close
you managed to get to making the expression true before ultimately failing.
Where would you even start to debug something like this?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring the Steps to Design Checkoff]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/formal/2022/11/01/design-checkoff.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/formal/2022/11/01/design-checkoff.html"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve recently had the opportunity to rebuild a NAND flash
controller for Arasan Chip
Systems, Inc.
The purpose of this redesign was to upgrade an existing flash controller
so that it can process flash requests and commands at even faster speeds than
ever before.  Indeed, this new controller is designed to handle flash chips
that operate at speeds of up to 1.6GB/s while being backwards compatible with
all previous speeds.  Those who know my typical design goals will already
know my personal goals for this design: throughput, throughput, throughput!
What I wanted to discuss today, however, was a basic management problem I
came across while working on this project.  At one time, during development,
I was asked by Arasan’s management team where I
was at in the project, and how much longer the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in October]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/october-2022-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/october-2022-roundup"/>
        <updated>2022-11-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
October
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 252 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913287/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913287/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T22:45:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd version 252 has been released.  As usual, the list of changes is
long.  It includes a new systemd-measure tool for the calculation of PCR
values and a bunch of infrastructure to use the result for disk encryption:


	Net effect: if you boot a properly prepared kernel, TPM-bound disk
        encryption now defaults to be locked to kernels which carry PCR
          signatures from the same key pair. Example: if a hypothetical distro
          FooOS prepares its UKIs like this, TPM-based disk encryption is now –
          by default – bound to only FooOS kernels, and encrypted volumes bound
          to the TPM cannot be unlocked on kernels from other sources.


There's a lot more; see the announcement for all of the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lifetime extension of temporary objects in C++: common recommendations and pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1006/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1006/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After reading this article, you will learn the following: ways to extend the lifetime of a temporary object in C++, various tips and tricks; pitfalls of the lifetime extension that a C++ programmer may face, and that I have already faced myself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lifetime extension of temporary objects in C++: common recommendations and pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1006/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1006/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After reading this article, you will learn the following: ways to extend the lifetime of a temporary object in C++, various tips and tricks; pitfalls of the lifetime extension that a C++ programmer may face, and that I have already faced myself.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Still waiting for stackable security modules]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912775/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912775/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T18:20:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux security module (LSM) mechanism was created as a result of the first Kernel Summit in 2001; it was
designed to allow the development of multiple approaches to Linux security.
That goal has been met; there are several security modules available with
current kernels.  The LSM subsystem was not designed, though, to allow
multiple security modules to work together on the same system.  Developers
have been working to rectify that problem almost since the LSM subsystem
was merged, but with limited success; some small security modules can be
stacked on top of the "major" ones, but arbitrary stacking is not possible.
Now, a full 20 years after
security-module support went into the 2.5 development kernel series, it
looks like a solution to the stacking problem may finally be getting
closer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How does Matter handle IoT device security?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11252</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-does-matter-handle-iot-device-security/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T18:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode, we took a question from our Voicemail hotline from Greg. He’s asking how Matter handles IoT device security, which is a great question. It’s also a timely one as we expect to see Matter-certified device availability soon. And thankfully, the Matter specification does provide universal, robust security […]
The post How does Matter handle IoT device security? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913261/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913261/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T17:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (batik, chromium, expat, libxml2, ncurses, openvswitch, pysha3, python-django, thunderbird, and tomcat9), Fedora (cacti, cacti-spine, curl, mbedtls, mingw-expat, and xen), Gentoo (apptainer, bind, chromium, exif, freerdp, gdal, gitea, hiredis, jackson-databind, jhead, libgcrypt, libksba, libtirpc, lighttpd, net-snmp, nicotine+, open-vm-tools, openexr, rpm, schroot, shadow, sofia-sip, tiff, and xorg-server), Mageia (libreoffice), Oracle (expat), Red Hat (device-mapper-multipath), and SUSE (cacti, cacti-spine, chromium, exim, jhead, kernel, libmad, opera, and pdns-recursor).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Kinlan shares his passion for web development and how to get involved at DevFest]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/paul-kinlan-shares-his-passion-for-web-development-and-devfest.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2022/10/paul-kinlan-shares-his-passion-for-web-development-and-devfest.html"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by  Komal Sandhu - Global Program Manager, Google Developer Groups
  

 
“The pace of technology is changing so quickly that it’s impossible sometimes to know where to start and how. What are the things I need to focus on? It’s just too hard to work out. I’m motivated to give developers a clear direction that cuts through a lot of this challenge.”
Learn Chrome tools and tips from Chrome Lead, Paul Kinlan, and hear from him first-hand on how to get involved.


Among the many inspiring experts in the Chrome developer community is Paul Kinlan, a Googler who serves as the Lead Chrome & Web Platform Developer Relations team. Read on to see Paul’s outlook on his favorite Chrome tools and the Chrome developers that inspire him.
Tell us about yourself: 

“My name is Paul Kinlan, and I lead …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart cities should focus on sustainability not safety]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11260</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/smart-cities-should-focus-on-sustainability-not-safety/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T15:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published on Friday Oct. 28, 2022 in my weekly IoT newsletter.  Cities adopt technology for two primary reasons: safety and cost savings. Both of these are driven by a need to please constituents who want lower taxes and the perception of safer streets. Thus, we’ve seen cities adopt LED lighting to […]
The post Smart cities should focus on sustainability not safety appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU Make 4.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913253/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913253/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T15:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.4 of the GNU make utility is out.  There is a long list of
changes and a fair number of potential compatibility issues; see the
announcement text for all the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top smart home trends plus: is Matter the key to interoperability?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477042</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/top-smart-home-trends-plus-is-matter-the-key-to-interoperability/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T14:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinciding with the launch of Matter and World Smart Home Day 2022, engineers from ByteSnap Design highlight trends to watch in smart homes, including the rise of Matter, homes powering the move to off-grid, and consumption dictated by energy suppliers.
The post Top smart home trends plus: is Matter the key to interoperability? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Partnership looks at embedding quantum computing in classical]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477037</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/partnership-looks-at-embedding-quantum-computing-in-classical/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T14:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As part of German Aerospace Center’s quantum computing initiative, partnering companies will pool expertise from across industry to enable rapid advances in quantum computing and help roll out scalable and marketable solutions.
The post Partnership looks at embedding quantum computing in classical appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C to C++: 3 Reasons to Migrate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1478.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1478.php"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T13:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve recently written several blogs that have set the stage with a simple premise: The C programming language no longer provides embedded software developers the tools they need to develop embedded software throughout the full software stack. Now, don’t get me wrong, C is a powerhouse, with over 80% of developers still using it; however, as embedded systems have reached unprecedented...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why you need living documentation for software projects (and how to do it)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/why-need-living-documentationsoftware-projects-how-to-do-it/</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/processes/why-need-living-documentationsoftware-projects-how-to-do-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T11:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Documentation is often the most neglected area of software projects. It can be time-consuming and sometimes tedious, and keeping on top […]
The post Why you need living documentation for software projects (and how to do it) appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jane Orme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[48. X-윈도우와 Wayland]]></title>
        <id>https://joone.net/?p=4342</id>
        <link href="https://joone.net/2022/10/31/48-x-%ec%9c%88%eb%8f%84%ec%9a%b0%ec%99%80-wayland/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T08:26:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[실리콘 그래픽스 GLX와 OpenGL 개발 실리콘 그래픽스는 3D 그래픽에 특화된 워크스테이션 제조사로서 1980년대 부터 2000년대 초반까지 쥬라기 공원, 터미네이터2와 같은 영화 제작, 캐드 등 전문 분야에서 많이 사용되었다. 실리콘 그래픽스는 당시 IRIX라는 유닉스 계열 운영체제를 갖고 있었는데, Unix System V에 BSD 확장을 기반으로 개발되었다. 1991년 IRIX4.0을 발표하면서 X 윈도우를 도입했고, 3D 그래픽스가 가능하도록 GLX라는 X […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>joone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 플렉세라 보고서: 클라우드 동향과 시사점]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87378</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87378"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:37:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[플렉세라(Flexera)는 주로 IT 운영과 관련된 기업 맞춤형 컨설팅 및 서비스를 제공하는 회사로, 매년 클라우드 동향 조사 보고서를 발간하고 있다. 보고서 개요  2022년에도 총 753명의 기술 및 사업을 담당하는 전문가를 통해 클라우드 활용 현황과 향후 전략에 대한 조사를 벌였다. 조사 대상 기업의 규모도 1만 명 이상 직원을 둔 대기업부터 100명 이하의 소기업까지 다양하며, […]
The post 2022 플렉세라 보고서: 클라우드 동향과 시사점 first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices for application shutdown with OpenSSL]]></title>
        <id>043f762e-53b8-4d20-b470-c1a30f2f3b5a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2022/10/31/best-practices-application-shutdown-openssl"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSL is an essential library for securing web traffic. This article offers simple procedures for initializing and terminating applications using OpenSSL. Modern applications that are more complex than "Hello, world!" usually require several external libraries like OpenSSL, which in turn often need to be properly initialized on startup and deinitialized on shutdown.
OpenSSL libraries are set up internally during program initialization. At this time, they load the configuration file, allocate resources, and handle FIPS mode, among many other tasks.
The OpenSSL API function for initialization is OPENSSL_init_crypto. This function accepts a variety of options with reasonable defaults. Initialization should be performed before any other OpenSSL function is used, though some OpenSSL functions…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dmitry Belyavskiy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[크레딕트 스위스 2022년 글로벌 자산 보고서에서 읽는 투자 전략]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588192</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588192/2022%eb%85%84-%ea%b8%80%eb%a1%9c%eb%b2%8c-%ec%9e%90%ec%82%b0-%eb%b3%b4%ea%b3%a0%ec%84%9c-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%8b%9c%ec%82%ac%ec%a0%90"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T04:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[상관주의 혹은 초월론(transcendentalism)의 모순]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222915587684</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222915587684"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T03:55:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[메이야수에 의하면, 선조적 진술의 실재적 의미가 궁극적 의미이다. 그런데 상관주의는 이 주장을 받아들일 수 없다. 그것은 상관주의가 <소여에 선행하는 존재의 소여>를 인정하지 않기 때문이다. 메이야수는 <소여, 혹은 현시(manifestation)에 선행하는 존재의 소여>라는 표현을 사용하고 있는데, 나는 이런 수사적 표현이 진짜 싫다. 존재 혹은 실재가 소여되었다. 이때 소여된 것은 존재적 의미 혹은 메이야수의 주장처럼 선조적 의미에서 소여이다. 반면에 상관주의가 주장하는 소여는 인식적 소여이다. 우리 마음이나 사유가 존재하지 않는다면, 인식적 소여는 주어지지 않는다. 그의 지적처럼 <시간 자체는 인간과 세계의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 인텔 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 두려워했던 것보다 낫다, 장기적으로 파운드리 경쟁력을 갖출 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588183</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588183/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%94-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T00:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.1-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/913122/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/913122/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-31T00:02:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.1-rc3 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	So while rc2 was just _way_ bigger than usual, rc3 is only a bit
	larger than an average rc3 release is. But it's still on the
	largish side. I hope that things start calming down, and we'll
	start seeing the size of these rc's shrink. Please?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A study of deceit when reporting information in a known context]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7194</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2022/10/30/a-study-of-deceit-when-reporting-information-in-a-known-context/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T23:05:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A variety of conflicting factors intrude when attempting to form an impartial estimate of the resources needed to perform a task. The customer/manager, asking for the estimate wants to hear a low value, creating business/social pressure to underestimate; overestimating increases the likelihood of completing the task within budget. A study by Oey, Schachner and Vul […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[필진 칼럼] 비행 에티켓 (2022년 판)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=75514</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2022/10/30/npc_flyingetiquette/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_flyingetiquette"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T22:59:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난주 여름 일정을 마치고 런던에서 뉴욕으로 돌아오는 비행기 안에서 일어난 일입니다. 제 뒷자리에 앉은 승객이 비행 내내 제 의자를 발로 툭툭 차고, 의자 너머로 다리를 뻗으려다 제 팔을 자꾸 쳤습니다. 녹음해둔 팟캐스트 편집하려고 소음 차단 헤드폰을 꼈는데도 희미하게 떠드는 소리가 들릴 만큼 옆 사람과 나누는 대화의 데시벨도 컸습니다. 참다못해 잔뜩 찌푸린 표정으로 뒤돌아서 조용히 하고 발도 그만 차 달라고 말했습니다. 마뜩잖은 표정으로 알았다고 답했지만, 10분쯤 지났을까요? 발차기와 시끄러운 대화는 다시 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 애플 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588181</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588181/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T11:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[브라이도티의 반휴머니즘]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222914622845</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222914622845"/>
        <updated>2022-10-30T03:49:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 나는 휴머니즘이나 그것이 암암리에 옹호하는 인간/휴먼 개념을 그다지 좋아하지 않는다. 반휴머니즘은 내 가족의 배경과 나의 지적, 개인적 계보의 많은 부분을 차지하고 있다. 그래서 나에게 휴머니즘의 위기는 진부하기까지 한 이야기다. ... 내가 유럽중심적이고 제국주의적인 경향을 지닌 휴머니즘의 역사적 쇠락이라는 개념을 반기는 이유는 주로 정치적이고 철학적인 이유에 근거한다. 물론, 역사적 맥락도 관련이 많다. 나는 제2차 세계대전 이후 격랑기에 지적으로 정치적으로 성인이 되었고, 이때는 휴머니즘적 이상이 근본에서부터 문제가 된 시기다. 1960년대와 1970년대 내내 페미니즘, 탈식민주의와 반인종주의, 반핵운동과 평.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912992/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912992/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T13:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.10.151 kernel was released on
October 28 with a small fix to the PAHOLE_FLAGS in the kernel
build.  October 29 saw the release of the 6.0.6, 5.15.76, and 
5.4.221 stable kernels, each with the usual
collection of important fixes throughout the tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 아마존 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 23년 본 궤도를 회복할 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588170</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588170/22%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T10:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알도 레오폴드의 <모래 군의 열두 달> 3]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222913853680</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222913853680"/>
        <updated>2022-10-29T02:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(1) 군청 장부에는 이 방목지가 당신 것으로 적혀 있는지 모르겠지만, 긴꼬리물떼새 녀석은 그런 사소한 법적 사항 따위는 가볍게 웃어넘긴다. 녀석은 인디언 시대부터 소유해온 자신의 권리를 거듭 주장하기 위해 아르헨티나에서부터 4천 마일을 날아 이제 막 돌아왔다. 그리고 새끼들이 날 수 있을 때까지 이 방목지는 녀석의 것이며, 어느 누구도 녀석의 저항 없이 이 곳을 통과할 수는 없다. (2) 선선한 팔월 밤, 다시 한 번 미주 대륙이 예로부터 하나였음을 증명하기 위해 긴꼬리물떼새가, 남미 팜파 초원을 향해 날개를 펼 때, 우리는 놈들의 휘파람 신호소리를 들을 수 있다. 남과 북의 연대가 정치인들에게는 새롭겠지만, 이 날개 달린.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 4]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477025</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-steps-to-designing-an-embedded-software-architecture-step-4/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T22:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores the fourth step to designing an embedded software architecture: defining task components and their interfaces. The last three articles have explored the...
The post 5 Steps To Designing An Embedded Software Architecture, Step 4 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic associated types in Rust 1.65]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912932/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912932/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T20:28:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust Types Team announces
that the long-awaited generic associated types feature will be stable in Rust 1.65.


	At its core, generic associated types allow you to have generics
	(type, lifetime, or const) on associated types. Note that this is
	really just rounding out the places where you can put generics: for
	example, you can already have generics on freestanding type aliases
	and on functions in traits. Now you can just have generics on type
	aliases in traits (which we just call associated types).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Oct. 28, 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=11268</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-oct-28-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T15:56:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LoRa networks for private messages? Although this article doesn’t get into actual implementation, I’m surfacing it because I think the idea is spot-on. In fact, when Amazon’s Sidewalk network was introduced in 2019, I suggested the use of LoRa networks for a private messaging service. By using LoRa instead of cellular or Wi-Fi, you’d have end-to-end […]
The post IoT news of the week for Oct. 28, 2022 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Packaging Rust for Fedora]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912202/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912202/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T15:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux distributions were, as a general rule, designed during an era when
most software of interest was written in C; as a result, distributions
are naturally able to efficiently package C applications and the libraries
they depend on.  Modern languages, though, tend to be built around their
own package-management systems that are designed with different goals in
mind.  The result is that, for years, distributors have struggled to find
the best ways to package and ship applications written in those languages.
A recent discussion in the Fedora community on the packaging of Rust
applications shows that the problems have not yet all been solved.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: Synaptics buys Emza, 6G RIS trials, plus more]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4477028</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-synaptics-buys-emza-6g-ris-trials-plus-more/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s embedded news features various announcements including Synaptics’ acquisition of Emza Visual Sense, various announcements from Cadence, Siemens, and Synopsys, plus Rohde & Schwarz’s evaluation and trial of RIS for 6G, and more.
The post embedded news: Synaptics buys Emza, 6G RIS trials, plus more appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/912873/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/912873/"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T13:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (expat, ruby-sinatra, and thunderbird), Fedora (glances), Mageia (cups, firefox, git, heimdal, http-parser, krb5-appl, minidlna, nginx, and thunderbird), Oracle (389-ds:1.4, device-mapper-multipath, firefox, mysql:8.0, postgresql:12, and thunderbird), SUSE (dbus-1, libconfuse0, libtasn1, openjpeg2, qemu, and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (dbus, linux-azure-fde, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MS의 B2B 전략 ‘초자동화 통한 생산성의 극대화’ (이그나이트 2022)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=87361</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/87361"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T09:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마이크로소프트는 매년 세 가지의 가장 크고도 중요 이벤트를 개최한다. 채널 파트너들을 위한 인스파이어(Inspire)와 개발자를 위한 빌드(Build)와 함께 이 모두를 포함하는 최종 사용자를 위한 이그나이트(Ignite)와 함께 매년 개최한다. 그 이유로 이그나이트는 마이크로소프트의 제품 전략과 로드맵을 볼 수 있기에 특히 기업에서 차기 비즈니스 전략을 준비하는 중요 정보로 사용할 수 있다. 올해는 10월 12일에서 14일까지 사흘간 진행되었으며, 100개가 […]
The post MS의 B2B 전략 ‘초자동화 통한 생산성의 극대화’ (이그나이트 2022) first appeared on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반도체 장비주 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 수요 감소와 중국 악재를 반영한 바닥이 가까워지고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=588164</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/588164/%eb%b0%98%eb%8f%84%ec%b2%b4-%ec%9e%a5%eb%b9%84%ec%a3%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2022-10-28T08:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build a Sustainable Refillable Active Coal Filter]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=13198</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2022/09/20/build-a-sustainable-refillable-active-coal-filter/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-20T12:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you ever used air filters to keep smells, fumes and dust at a low level in your workshop, you for sure came in contact with these expensive throwaway active coal filters. While throwing-away the used active coal seems to be unavoidable, all the thrown away plastic and packaging of the filter can easily be...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE): A Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://novelbits.io/?p=22402</id>
        <link href="https://novelbits.io/bluetooth-low-energy-ble-complete-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-06T11:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet of Things (IoT) has been a buzzword for decades, but today this market is far from theoretical. There are over 10 billion active IoT devices globally, and one of the key technologies enabling this market growth is Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE).  Introduced in 2012, this flexible protocol provides wireless connection for many of […]
The post Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE): A Complete Guide appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammad Afaneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extreme Integers – Doom from Below]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=13025</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2022/09/04/extreme-integers-doom-from-below/"/>
        <updated>2022-09-04T09:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a beginner or immediate C++ programmer, you heard never mixing unsigned and signed integer types or avoiding unsigned integers at all. There was also this talk about undefined behaviour. Yet, in embedded software development, there is no way around unsigned integers – so what is behind all these warnings? Wonderful that you strive to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Choose a BLE Module for Your Project]]></title>
        <id>https://novelbits.io/?p=22320</id>
        <link href="https://novelbits.io/how-to-choose-ble-module-for-your-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T14:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a way to add BLE connectivity to your project, you have many options. So how do you know which module is right for you? We’ll help you understand the options available and make the best decision for your needs. How to select a BLE module There are a few key considerations […]
The post How to Choose a BLE Module for Your Project appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nthatisi Hlapisi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>