<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2021-12-19T20:18:58.820Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[매년 안 맞아도 되는 독감 백신 만들 수 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73949</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/12/19/npc_fluvaccine/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_fluvaccine"/>
        <updated>2021-12-19T20:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 백신 이전에도 현대 의학과 공중보건에서 백신은 수많은 목숨을 구했습니다. 대표적인 것이 매년 추워지기 전에 맞는 독감(influenza) 백신이죠.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key-Value pairs in FLASH Memory: file-system-less minINI]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=34100</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/12/19/key-value-pairs-in-flash-memory-file-system-less-minini/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-19T11:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many embedded systems application need to store some kind of data in a persistent way: calibration values, settings or log information. For a smaller amount of data, using an external memory or file system is an overkill. In many system … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대단한 철학자 모종삼]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598995619</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598995619"/>
        <updated>2021-12-18T19:19:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[모종삼이 대단한 철학자이다. 아마 그는 근현대 중국철학의 최고봉일 것이다. 내가 묻는다. 무엇이 그렇게 대단한가? 그가 모종삼의 학문적 이력에 대해서 쭉 설명해 준다. 그러나 그런 발생적, 학술적 배경이 중요한 것이 아니다. 그의 개인적 학술적 과거가 중요한 것이 아니다. 그가 <논리철학논고>를 번역했고, 칸트의 저술을 번역했다는 것은 그의 번역적 공헌을 말하는 것이지, 그의 철학적이며 학문적 성취에 대해서 이야기해 주는 것이 아니다. 내가 듣고 싶은 것은 다음과 같은 것이다. 도대체 그가 무엇을 주장했는가? 그리고 그 주장이 가진 철학적 의의에 대해서 이야기해야 그의 철학적 독창성이나 가치에 대해서 말할 수 있.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전기 하이데거의 언어철학 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598578169</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222598578169"/>
        <updated>2021-12-18T06:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[게오르크 W. 베르트람의 <언어, 의미, 그리고 철학>은 <언어철학에서 해석학적 전회>라는 제목으로 헤르더와 하이데거의 언어철학을 이야기하고 있다. 베르트람에 의하면 ‘해석학적 전회’의 가장 분명한 특성이 반심리주의이다. 베르트람에 의하면, 정신은 언어와 상관없이 구성되어 있다는 주장이 심리주의의 주장이다. 해석학적 전회가 주장하는 반심리주의는 언어와 정신 사이에 근본적 연관이 있다는 주장이다. 즉 <화자의 정신에 들어 있는 표상들이 곧 언어적 표현의 의미가 아니다.> 베르트람은 콩디약에 대한 헤르더의 비판에서 볼 수 있는 반심리주의를 다음처럼 요약한다. <콩디약은 언어는 정신적 방식으로 세.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The container throttling problem]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/cgroup-throttling/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/cgroup-throttling/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an excerpt from an internal document David Mackey and I co-authored in April 2019. The document is excerpted since much of the original doc was about comparing possible approaches to increasing efficency at Twitter, which is mostly information that's meaningless outside of Twitter without a large amount of additional explanation/context.
At Twitter, most  CPU bound services start falling over at around 50% reserved container CPU utilization and almost all services start falling over at not much more CPU utilization even though CPU bound services should, theoretically, be able to get higher CPU utilizations. Because load isn't, in general, evenly balanced across shards and the shard-level degradation in performance is so severe when we exceed 50% CPU utilization, this makes the prac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[뉴욕타임스 올해의 인물 이름 맞히기 퀴즈]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73931</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/12/17/nyt2021notablepeople/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=nyt2021notablepeople"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T22:59:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[네이버 프리미엄 콘텐츠에 주로 글을 쓰느라 하반기에는 뉴스페퍼민트에 많은 글을 올리지 못했습니다. 그와 관련해서는 조만간 새로운 글 업로드 방침을 공지할 계획입니다. 조금만 기다려주시기를 부탁드리며, 연말을 맞아 뉴욕타임스가 꼽은 올해의 인물 이름 맞히기 퀴즈 함께 풀어보시죠. 퀴즈 풀기 점수가 너무 낮을까봐 걱정하시는 분들을 위해 부끄럽지만, 제 점수를 공개합니다. (퀴즈를 푸실 분은 먼저 퀴즈부터 풀고 봐주세요!)         저는 특히 문화예술계 유명인을 거의 못 맞혔습니다. 정치 뉴스만 주로 보는 편식이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for December 17, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9480</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-december-17-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T21:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Radar-based health monitoring startup scores $10M: Toronto-based Xandar Kardian has closed a $10 million Series A funding round led by Phoenix Venture Partners, Portfolia Active Aging & Longevity Fund, and Taronga Ventures after a busy year for the startup. Xandar Kardian, which I profiled back in February, makes a device that uses radar to monitor patients’ breathing rates and heartbeats, […]
The post IoT news of the week for December 17, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCompris Releases Version 2.0 (KDE.news)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879058/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879058/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T19:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Just in time for the upcoming holidays, "KDE's educational suite of more than 170 activities and pedagogical games", GCompris, has released version 2.0.  It includes new and updated games and activities, including:

Getting back to numeracy activities, GCompris 2.0 includes a wide range of activities that mimic basic manipulation math games, allowing young players to experiment with elements, grouping them in sets of up to ten items. This helps them build a clear concept of the decimal system, and, as with many GCompris activities, an educator can gradually increase the difficulty level, allowing the activities to be used with children of ages between 3 and 10. Once they grasp the concept of the decimal system, the addition and subtraction activities, also based on math manipulation, help practice arithmetic.

Along with other classics, like chess, align four, and checkers, fans of strategy games will enjoy Oware, a game that requires forethought and, again, numeracy skills. Oware is originally a traditional African pastime and can be played against a friend or against Tux, offering unlimited hours of fun.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding the Impact of Apache Log4j Vulnerability (Google)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879052/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879052/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Security Blog looks
into the ripple effects of the Log4j vulnerability.


	Most artifacts that depend on log4j do so indirectly. The deeper
	the vulnerability is in a dependency chain, the more steps are
	required for it to be fixed. The following diagram shows a
	histogram of how deeply an affected log4j package (core or api)
	first appears in consumers dependency graphs. For greater than 80%
	of the packages, the vulnerability is more than one level deep,
	with a majority affected five levels down (and some as many as nine
	levels down). These packages will require fixes throughout all
	parts of the tree, starting from the deepest dependencies first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] SA_IMMUTABLE and the hazards of messing with signals]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878768/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878768/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T17:36:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are some parts of the kernel where even the most experienced and
capable developers fear to tread; one of those is surely the code that
implements signals.  The nature of the signal API almost guarantees that
any implementation will be full of subtle interactions and complexities,
and the version in Linux doesn't disappoint.  So the inclusion of a
signal-handling change late in the 5.16 merge window might have been
expected to have the potential for difficulties; it didn't disappoint
either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Work is Not Corporate — It’s DAOs and Crypto Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2769</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-future-of-work-daos-crypto-networks/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T16:57:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the future, it’s likely that the average person will not work for a company. Instead, people will earn income in non-traditional ways by taking actions such as playing games, learning new skills, creating art, or curating content. This kind of shift in how we work is not unusual or unexpected — the idea that... Read More
The post The Future of Work is Not Corporate — It’s DAOs and Crypto Networks appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ben Schecter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.15.10, 5.10.87, and 5.4.167]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879022/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879022/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T15:18:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 5.15.10, 5.10.87, and 5.4.167 stable kernels.  These are fairly
small updates, but, unlike yesterday's single
self-test bug fix updates, do contain important fixes throughout the tree; users
should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/879020/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/879020/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T14:45:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel), Fedora (dr_libs, libsndfile, and podman), openSUSE (fetchmail, log4j, log4j12, logback, python3, and seamonkey), Oracle (go-toolset:ol8, idm:DL1, and nodejs:16), Red Hat (go-toolset-1.16 and go-toolset-1.16-golang, ipa, rh-postgresql12-postgresql, rh-postgresql13-postgresql, and samba), Slackware (xorg), SUSE (log4j, log4j12, and python3), and Ubuntu (apache-log4j2 and openjdk-8, openjdk-lts).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EXPLIoT Named IoT Security Champion Award Winner 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21439</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/expliot-named-iot-security-champion-award-winner-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T09:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pictured (left to right): Tom White Paratus People, Jenny Devoy IoTSF, John Moor IoTSF & Piers Linney, Guest Speaker  EXPLIoT has been announced as the 2021 IoT Security Champion of the Year by the IoT Security Foundation The award was presented by business entrepreneur and "Dragon's Den" star Piers Linney at the TechWorks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>-</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[차별금지법 제안 14년, 무슨 논의가 더 필요한가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83145</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83145"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T08:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“충분한 논의와 국민적 합의에 이르러야 한다는데 전적으로 동의한다. 우리사회가 앞으로 가야 할 방향을 잡는 지침 같은 것이라서 일방통행식의 처리는 바람직하지 않다. 이 문제는 우리 사회구성원들의 높은 시민의식에 기초해 왜곡되거나 잘못된 적용을 배제하고, 이 문제에 대해서 충분한 논의와 토론을 통해 얼마든지 사회적 합의에 이를 수 있다.” “헌법 정신에 따라 모든 영역에 있어서 차별이 없어야 한다는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[하고 싶은 일 100가지 쓰기, 버킷리스트를 만나다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83129</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83129"/>
        <updated>2021-12-17T00:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“과장님은 왜 그렇게 회사 생활을 힘들어하세요?”  지금으로부터 6, 7년 전, 직장 생활에서 큰 고비를 마주한다는 10년 차 때의 일이다. 막 과장으로 진급했을 때였다. 오랜 대리 딱지를 떼고, 바라던 승진도 했는데 마냥 기쁘지만 않았다. 누군가에게는 배부른 소리처럼 들릴 수도 있겠지만, 당시 나는 회사 생활이 너무 힘겨웠다. 입사 후 처음으로 맛본 승진의 기쁨이었는데 허무하다는 생각밖에 들지 않았다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최호진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1000 eyes that don't want to check open-source code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0900/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0900/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a myth that open-source software is better and safer that the closed one. This was reasonably questioned many times. People regularly find epic vulnerabilities in the open source code. These vulnerabilities have been there for a long time. I think the project quality depends on how the development managers arrange the process and what methodologies/tools are used. It has nothing to do with the project being open source or closed source.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fostering an inclusive tech community with Evelyn Mendes #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/iamagde-evelyn-mendes.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/iamagde-evelyn-mendes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T19:02:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
  
Evelyn Mendes, the first transgender Google Developer Expert, is based in Porto Alegre, Brazil, and has worked in technology since 2002. “I've always loved technology!” she exclaims, flashing a dazzling smile. As a transgender woman, Evelyn faced discrimination in the tech world in Brazil and relied on her friends for emotional support and even housing and food, as she fought for a job in technology. Her excruciating journey has made her a tireless advocate for diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI), as she works toward her vision of a world of empathy, acceptance, and love. 
Meet Evelyn Mendes, Google De…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878897/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878897/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T18:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.15.9, 5.10.86, and 5.4.166 stable kernels have been
released. "Only change here is a permission setting of a netfilter
selftest file. 
No need to upgrade if this problem is not bothering you."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021 Assistant Recap]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/2021-assistant-recap.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/2021-assistant-recap.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jessica Dene Earley-Cha, Mike Bifulco and Toni Klopfenstein, Developer Relations Engineers for Google Assistant
 We've reached the end of the year - and what a year it's been! Between all of our live (virtual) events including I/O, developer summits, meetups and more, there are a lot of highlights for App Actions, Smart Home Actions and Conversational Actions. Let's dive in and take a look.  

App Actions
 App Actions allows developers to extend their Android App to Google Assistant. App Actions integrates more cleanly with Android using new Android platform features. With the introduction of the beta shortcuts.xml configuration resource, expanding existing Android features and our latest Google Assistant Plug App Actions is moving closer to the Android platform. 
App Actions Ben…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Lessons from Log4j]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878570/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878570/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T16:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, most readers will likely have seen something about the Log4j 
vulnerability that has been making life miserable for system administrators
since its disclosure on December 9.  This bug is relatively easy to
exploit, results in remote code execution, and lurks on servers all across
the net; it is not hyperbolic to call it one of the worst vulnerabilities
that has been disclosed in some years.  In a sense, the lessons from Log4j
have little new to teach us, but this bug does highlight some problems in
the free-software ecosystem in an unambiguous way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Come for the Tool, Stay for the Exchange: Bootstrapping Liquidity in the Private Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2742</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/liquidity-private-market-exchanges/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T15:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past 20 years, there has been a dramatic shift in capital flow from the public to private markets. Since 2000, private market assets have grown over 10 times, representing over $6 trillion globally. This trend has been driven by a variety of factors, including low interest rates, companies staying private longer, the need... Read More
The post Come for the Tool, Stay for the Exchange: Bootstrapping Liquidity in the Private Markets appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Haber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878844/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878844/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T14:07:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache-log4j2 and mediawiki), Fedora (libmysofa, libolm, and vim), Oracle (httpd), Red Hat (go-toolset:rhel8), and Ubuntu (apache-log4j2 and mumble).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Smart homes in the metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9476</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-smart-homes-in-the-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T14:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What happens when the smart home meets the metaverse? We talk about the potential for better user interfaces and home mapping if we build digital twins of the home in a metaverse, while also discussing the potential of UWB to expand the amount of information contained in that digital twin. Then we discuss an excellent […]
The post Podcast: Smart homes in the metaverse appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 16, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878143/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878143/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T01:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 16, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크로소프트의 메타버스 전략 (ft. 팀즈용 메시)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83113</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83113"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T01:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나 대유행 이후에 새로운 트렌드를 이끌어 가기 위해 요즘 빅테크 IT 기업들은 너나 할 것 없이 ‘메타버스’를 각자 관점으로 바라보고 있다. 마이크로소프트 역시 어느 기업 못지 않게 메타버스에 투자하고 있다. 특히, 지난 10월에 진행했던 마이크로소프트 이그나이트 개발자 행사에서 ‘위드 코로나’ 시대에 사람들이 어떻게 업무 생산성에 재미있게 높일 수 있을지 보여줬다. 이것은 페이스북이 메타버스에 대한 미래를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Wrangling the typing PEPs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878675/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878675/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-16T00:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When last we looked in on the great typing PEP
debate for Python, back in August, two PEPs were still being
discussed as alternatives for handling annotations in the language.
The steering council was considering the issue after deferring on a
decision for the Python 3.10 release, but the question has been
deferred again for Python 3.11.  More study is needed and the council
is looking for help from the Python community to guide its
decision.  In the meantime, though, discussion about the deferral has led
to the understanding that annotations are not a general-purpose feature,
but are only meant for typing information.  In addition, there is a growing
realization that typing information is effectively becoming mandatory
for Python libraries.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹이 테크 산업을 어떻게 바꾸고 있는가?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73915</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/12/15/%ed%8c%ac%eb%8d%b0%eb%af%b9%ec%9d%b4-%ed%85%8c%ed%81%ac-%ec%82%b0%ec%97%85%ec%9d%84-%ec%96%b4%eb%96%bb%ea%b2%8c-%eb%b0%94%ea%be%b8%ea%b3%a0-%ec%9e%88%eb%8a%94%ea%b0%80/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=%25ed%258c%25ac%25eb%258d%25b0%25eb%25af%25b9%25ec%259d%25b4-%25ed%2585%258c%25ed%2581%25ac-%25ec%2582%25b0%25ec%2597%2585%25ec%259d%2584-%25ec%2596%25b4%25eb%2596%25bb%25ea%25b2%258c-%25eb%25b0%2594%25ea%25be%25b8%25ea%25b3%25a0-%25ec%259e%2588%25eb%258a%2594%25ea%25b0%2580"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T22:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(이코노미스트) 원문보기   클라우드, 하드웨어, 경쟁이라는 세 가지 변화가 테크 산업을 강타했습니다. 최근 테크 업계가 연일 호황입니다. 지난 2분기 실적 하락에 따른 우려는 3분기 실적 발표를 계기로 사라졌습니다. 구글(Google)의 모회사인 알파벳(Alphabet), 아마존(Amazon), 페이스북(Facebook), 애플(Apple), 마이크로소프트(Microsoft) 등 서부의 5대 빅테크의 실적이 급증했습니다. GAFAM이라 불리는 다섯 기업의 매출은 지난 해 3분기보다 40% 증가했고, 이익은 90%나 뛰었습니다. S&P 500 정보통신(IT) 지수는 연일 신고가를 기록하며 상승하고 있습니다. 그러나 최근 실적이 정점이라고 보는 전문가들도 많습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20: linker surprised by four lines of code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0899/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0899/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine that you are a student learning modern C++ features. And you have to complete a task concerning concepts/constraints. The teacher, of course, knows the proper way to do it – but you don't. You've already written spaghetti code that does not work. (And you keep adding more and more overloads and templates specializations to solve escalating compiler claims).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mold (linker) 1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878759/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878759/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.0 of the mold linker has been released.


	mold 1.0 is the first stable and production-ready release of the
	high-speed linker. On Linux-based systems, it should "just work" as
	a faster drop-in replacement for the default GNU linker for most
	user-land programs. If you are building a large executable which
	takes a long time to link, mold is worth a try to see if it can
	shorten your build time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve seen the future of the UWB smart home and I want it now]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9468</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/ive-seen-the-future-of-the-uwb-smart-home-and-i-want-it-now/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T18:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine using a single app to control everything in your smart home. I don’t mean the apps of today which show your devices in groups or rooms. I’m talking about a context-aware interface that intelligently surfaces a specific device, and its controls when you point your phone at it. That’s the future of the smart […]
The post I’ve seen the future of the UWB smart home and I want it now appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Idea to Impact: How a team from Solution Challenge launched an environmentally-focused social enterprise]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/from-idea-to-impact-how-a-team-from-solution-challenge.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/from-idea-to-impact-how-a-team-from-solution-challenge.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T16:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Merve Isler, Regional Developer Relations Community Manager, Turkey
                
Some challenges affect everyone regardless of borders or nationality, and combating climate issues is no different. Aysu Keçeci, a student in Turkey with an avowed reverence for the sea, found herself increasingly distressed by the growing amount of plastic in the world’s oceans. She notes, “As an Aegean, the seas are a big part of my life, Unfortunately, I have grown up observing that our waters are polluted daily, and I know that plastics now make up 80% of marine garbage, and if we don't take precautions, there will be more plastic in our seas than fish in 2050. That's why plastic pollution has always been a problem I wanted to address.” 
As part of a global community, Google Developer Student…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878749/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878749/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T16:06:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (libopenmpt), openSUSE (icu.691, log4j, nim, postgresql10, and xorg-x11-server), Red Hat (idm:DL1), SUSE (gettext-runtime, icu.691, runc, storm, storm-kit, and xorg-x11-server), and Ubuntu (xorg-server, xorg-server-hwe-18.04, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the advice process works in practice]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#HowThisTypicallyWorksInPractice</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#HowThisTypicallyWorksInPractice"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T15:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew finishes his article on how to scale software architecture by
      looking at how this technique works in practice, and also outlines how
      things can go wrong.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Selecting the right software defined radio solution for your application]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471871</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/selecting-the-right-software-defined-radio-solution-for-your-application/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T13:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SDRs are available in a wide range of performance, form factor and cost, so choosing the right SDR for your application can be a challenge....
The post Selecting the right software defined radio solution for your application appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brendon McHugh and Kaue Morcelles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘승무원 룩북’ 성상품화가 문제? 편승하는 언론이 더 문제!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83108</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83108"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T10:31:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국경제가 12월 13일 오전 [“속옷부터 보정 없이…” 승무원 룩북 영상, 성상품화 논란[영상] ] (김소연 기자)을 보도했습니다. 한 유튜버가 채널에 승무원 유니폼을 착용하는 영상을 올렸는데, 선정적이라 성상품화 논란이 일고 있다는 기사입니다. 한국경제 보도 이후, 다른 언론도 앞다퉈 ‘승무원 룩북 영상으로 성상품화 논란이 일고 있다’는 기사를 내놨습니다. 그런데 이런 언론보도가 오히려 해당 유튜브 영상을 더욱 확산시키고 있습니다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["충청의 아들" "강릉의 외손" 지역주의 조장 그만하시라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83101</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83101"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T09:58:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제20대 대통령선거가 90일도 채 남지 않았습니다. 그러나 후보별 정책을 집중 조명하고 평가하는 보도는 찾아보기 힘듭니다. 대신 후보들이 유권자 표심을 잡기 위해 전국 각지를 방문해 내놓는 발언을 보도의 주된 내용으로 삼고 있습니다. 그중에서도 선거철만 다가오면 어김없이 등장하는 보도가 있습니다. 바로 후보 연고와 지연을 강조하는 보도입니다. ‘지연 강조’ 보도가 늘고 있다 민주언론시민연합은 대통령선거 D-100인 11월 29일부터 12월 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter: Bridge for Non-Matter Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d3b7f003a004</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-bridge-for-non-matter-devices-d3b7f003a004?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-15T06:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #4]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shu Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kdenlive 21.12 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878696/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878696/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T23:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
21.12 of the Kdenlive video editor is out.


	The last and most exciting release of Kdenlive this year is out and
	brings long awaited features like Multicam Editing and Slip
	trimming mode, all of which drastically improve your editing
	workflow.  This version also comes with a new deep-learning based
	tracking algorithm, an auto-magical noise reduction filter and
	support for multiple Project Bins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Adding fs-verity support for Fedora 36?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878281/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878281/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T22:36:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding fs-verity file-integrity information
to RPM packages for Fedora 36 is the 
topic of a recent discussion on the Fedora devel mailing list.  The feature
would provide a means to install files from RPM packages as read-only files
that cannot be read or otherwise operated on if the data in the files changes
at any point.  The proposal is mostly about making the plumbing available
for use cases that are not particularly clear—which has led to some
questions and skepticism among those participating in the thread.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Promote your Google Workspace Marketplace apps with the new badge for developers]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/promote-your-google-workspace-marketplace-apps.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/promote-your-google-workspace-marketplace-apps.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Elena Kingbo, Program Manager
 Recently, Google Workspace Marketplace launched new features for developers to improve the application search and evaluation experience in the Marketplace for our Google Workspace admins and end users.  
Continuing with updates to further improve the developer experience, we are excited to announce Google Workspace Marketplace badges.  
The new badges will allow developers to promote their published Google Workspace Marketplace applications on their own websites. Users will be taken directly to the Marketplace application listing, where they can review application details, privacy policy, terms of service, and more. These users will then be able to securely install applications directly from the Google Workspace Marketplace. 
This promotional tool c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878630/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878630/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T15:51:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.15.8, 5.10.85, 5.4.165, 4.19.221, 4.14.258, 4.9.293, and 4.4.295 have been released.  As usual there
are important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878629/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878629/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T15:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libsamplerate and raptor2), Fedora (pam-u2f and python-markdown2), openSUSE (chromium, fetchmail, ImageMagick, and postgresql10), Oracle (samba), SUSE (fetchmail, postgresql10, python-pip, python3, and sles12sp2-docker-image), and Ubuntu (apache-log4j2, flatpak, glib, and samba).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Treat integration as strategic to your business]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#TreatIntegrationAsStrategicToYourBusiness</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#TreatIntegrationAsStrategicToYourBusiness"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T14:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brandon finishes his article on how we should look at
      integration by arguing that it is a strategic element of an enterprise's
      infrastructure. You can buy the best products in the world but "none of it
      will make you competitive in a digital world if you continue to treat
      integration as a tactical nuisance to overcome so you take advantage of
      those new systems."
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This chipmaker could change the air quality monitoring game]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9460</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/this-chipmaker-could-change-the-air-quality-monitoring-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are y’all sick of me writing about air quality yet? I view the monitoring of indoor air quality and management of in-home energy as the two biggest trends to emerge from the last year or so, so I’m very focused on them these days. To that end, this week I met a startup called Piera Systems, which […]
The post This chipmaker could change the air quality monitoring game appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[양심적 병역거부과 십자가 밟기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83094</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83094"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T09:49:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2018년, 양심적 병역거부자에 대한 대체복무제를 규정하지 않은 병역종류 조항은 양심의 자유를 침해한다는 취지의 헌법재판소 결정과 진정한 양심에 따른 병역거부는 병역법 제88조(입영의 기피) 제1항에 정한 ‘정당한 사유’에 해당한다는 대법원의 전원합의체 판결이 나오며 우리 사회에 존재했던 또 하나의 뒤틀린 정의가 바로잡혔다. 하지만 기존 논의가 ‘여호와의 증인’을 중심으로 이루어진 결과, 종교적 신념이 아닌 비폭력·평화주의 신념에 따른 양심적 병역거부자들은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선험주의와 본래적 자기]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222595435215</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222595435215"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T09:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기농이 그렇게 자세하게 분석하고 있지 않지만, 로티와 테일러의 논의가 두 가지 논점에서 대립하고 있다고 본다. 첫째, 선험주의, 혹은 선험적 논증의 문제이다. 둘째, 자아의 본래성의 문제이다. 비트겐슈타인이나 하이데거를 충분히 실행적 혹은 실천적 선험주의로 이해할 수 있다고 생각한다. 그런데 이 입장이 논리적이고 문법적이며 개념적인 것이 실행적인 것을 통해 구성될 수 있다는 주장을 의미한다면, 그것은 문제가 있다고 생각한다. https://blog.naver.com/sellars/221100870499 https://blog.naver.com/sellars/220763474930 https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222240665508 분명히 비트겐슈타인이나 하이데거에게서 본래성이 문제.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논증의 다섯 가지 요소: 일상 대화에서 찾는 논증의 원리]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83078</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83078"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T08:50:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 다른 사람과 대화하는 과정에서 아이디어를 떠올리는 경험을 자주 한다. 질문하고 대답하는 과정에서 자신도 미처 깨닫지 못하고 있던 가치있는 주장을 발견하기도 하고, 주장을 뒷받침하는 이유와 근거를 즉흥적으로 떠올리기도 한다. 관심 있는 주제를 놓고 대화하다 보면 누구나 경험할 수 있는 일이다. 논증이란 무엇인가  글을 쓸 때도 마찬가지다. 글을 쓴다는 것은 혼자 자신이 아는 것을 쏟아내는 것이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘몰카’가 아니라 ‘불법 촬영 범죄’다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83069</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83069"/>
        <updated>2021-12-14T07:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[12월 8일 MBC가 [단독/‘골프장’·‘기독교 언론사’ 대표 아들‥불법 촬영물 62개] (이문현 기자)를 보도했습니다. “유명 골프장 리조트와 언론사를 운영하는 기업 회장의 아들이 여러 여성과 성관계하는 장면을 불법 촬영”했고 이를 여성 이름과 나이순으로 정리해둔 것이 수백 개에 달한다는 내용입니다. 취재진은 “확보한 모든 자료와 증언을 서울지방경찰청 여성청소년범죄수사대에 제출”했다면서, 경찰은 보도 당일 저녁 “미국 LA로 출국하려던 (피의자) 권 씨를 공항 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio checks Umbraco code for the third time]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0898/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0898/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six years ago, we first checked Umbraco with the PVS-Studio static analyzer for C#. Today, we decided to go where it all started and analyze the Umbraco CMS source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Digging into the community's lore with lei]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878205/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878205/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T18:25:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email is often seen as a technology with a dim future; it is slow, easily
faked, and buried in spam.  Kids These Days want nothing to do with it, and
email has lost its charm with many others as well.
But many development projects are still dependent on it, and even
non-developers still cope with large volumes of mail.  While development
forges show one possible path away from email, they are not the only one.
What if new structures could be built on top of email to address some of
its worst problems while keeping the good parts that many projects depend
on?  The "lei" system recently launched by Konstantin Ryabitsev is a hint
of how such a future might look.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878520/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878520/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T15:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (chromium, firefox, gitlab, grafana, grafana-agent, thunderbird, and vivaldi), Debian (apache-log4j2, privoxy, and wireshark), Fedora (firefox, grub2, mariadb, mod_auth_openidc, rust-drg, rust-tiny_http, and rust-tiny_http0.6), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, curaengine, fetchmail, firefox, libvirt, log4j, opencontainers-runc, python-django, speex, and thunderbird), openSUSE (clamav, firefox, glib-networking, glibc, gmp, ImageMagick, log4j, nodejs12, nodejs14, php7, python-Babel, python-pip, webkit2gtk3, and wireshark), Red Hat (mailman:2.1 and samba), and SUSE (bcm43xx-firmware, firefox, glib-networking, ImageMagick, kernel-rt, and python-pip).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EFF: Chrome Users Beware: Manifest V3 is Deceitful and Threatening]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878454/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878454/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T15:32:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Electronic Frontier Foundation warns
against Manifest V3, a set of changes coming to a Chrome browser near
you.


	Manifest V3, or Mv3 for short, is outright harmful to privacy
	efforts. It will restrict the capabilities of web
	extensions—especially those that are designed to monitor, modify,
	and compute alongside the conversation your browser has with the
	websites you visit. Under the new specifications, extensions like
	these– like some privacy-protective tracker blockers– will have
	greatly reduced capabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A tech landscape and current climate sensing tool - Your own Tech Radar]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#4.ATechLandscapeAndCurrentClimateSensingTool-YourOwnTechRadar</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#4.ATechLandscapeAndCurrentClimateSensingTool-YourOwnTechRadar"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T15:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew's fourth supporting element for the Advice Process is using a
      tech radar to capture and map out your local version of the technology
      trends you see across your organization. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sharing a smart home with multiple digital assistants isn’t bad]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9458</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/sharing-a-smart-home-with-multiple-digital-assistants-isnt-bad/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T14:01:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re finally approaching the end of 2021! I don’t know about you, but perhaps the biggest change I made to my smart home this past year was transitioning to Apple HomeKit. When I started out on my digital assistant journey a few years back, it was with the Amazon Alexa platform. Then once Google got into the market, I moved over to […]
The post Sharing a smart home with multiple digital assistants isn’t bad appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Develop boards remotely, in real time with new hardware-as-a-service]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471812</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/develop-boards-remotely-in-real-time-with-new-hardware-as-a-service/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T10:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New service from MIKROE claims to be embedded industry’s first hardware-as-a-service offer that enables remote embedded hardware design from $4 a day.
The post Develop boards remotely, in real time with new hardware-as-a-service appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022 대선은 2030이 결정한다 (ft. 2030 공약 비교)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83050</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83050"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T09:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[왜 20대 대통령선거를 90여 일 앞두고 정치권은 여야 구분 없이 2030 청년 세대를 호명하는가? 지금까지 그래왔듯이 이러한 호명은 대선을 코앞에 둔 각 정당과 대선 후보자들의 표몰이에 그칠 것인가? 이용·소비·동원되는 2030, 선거 핵심 캐스팅 보터 얼마 전 이재명 더불어민주당 대선 후보는 18세 고등학생을 광주 공동선대위원장에 임명하고, 과학 분야 2030세대 전문가 4명을 선대위원으로 영입했다. 윤석열 국민의힘 대선 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Examples of 7 Handy Functions for Associative Containers in Modern C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/handy-map-functions/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/handy-map-functions/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’d like to show you examples of several handy “map” functions from Modern C++. Associative containers like std::map, std::set, and their “unordered” counterparts are essential for many algorithms and techniques. With this new functionality, you can save the creation of temporary objects, write smaller and, what’s more, safer code.
Background code
To illustrate all the mechanics of a map, especially in terms of what happens with our objects, I have the following helper custom class:
struct User {
    std::string name {"default"};
    
    User() {
        std::cout << "User::User() " << name << '\n';
    }

    explicit User(std::string str) : name(std::move(str)) {
        std::cout << "User::User(std::string str) " << name << '\n';
    }

    ~User() {
        std::cou…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT News of the week for Dec. 10, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9456</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-dec-10-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T05:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A different perspective on the Matter standard: I don’t spend a lot of time thinking about TVs in part because I don’t spend much time watching one. This isn’t a snob thing, just a function of my family spending more time watching shows on an iPad and not spending much time with TV in general. But for […]
The post IoT News of the week for Dec. 10, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch  5.16-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878418/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878418/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T00:10:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc5 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


Do give it a good testing - with the holidays coming up, things are
probably going to slow down both on the development and testing front,
and as a result I expect that I will also extend the rc series by
another week not because it's necessarily needed (too early to tell,
but doesn't feel that way), but simply because nobody will want to
open the next merge window immediately in the new year.


One small change of note in this -rc is that the default limit for the
number of pages that can be locked into memory by an unprivileged process
has been raised to
8MB; see this article for a summary of the
discussions leading up to this change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I think about writing]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/writing-non-advice/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/writing-non-advice/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I see a lot of essays framed as writing advice which are actually thinly veiled descriptions of how someone writes that basically say "you should write how I write", e.g., people who write short posts say that you should write short posts. As with technical topics, I think a lot of different things can work and what's really important is that you find a style that's suitable to you and the context you operate in. Copying what's worked for someone else is unlikely to work for you, making "write how I write" bad advice.
We'll start by looking at how much variety there's been in what's worked1 for people, come back to what makes it so hard to copy someone else's style, and then discuss what I try to do in my writing.
If I look at the most read programming blogs in my extended social circles2 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘아랍의 봄’ 그 자리에 남은 절망: 27살 아델 케드리가 분신한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82892</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82892"/>
        <updated>2021-12-12T23:43:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[폴 쉠은 북아프리카 특파원으로 모로코의 수도 라바트에서 근무했다. ‘아랍의 봄’(2010년 12월 튀니지 혁명로 촉발된 아랍권의 민주화 시위. 튀니지, 이집트, 예멘의 정권이 교체되었고, 2011년에 절정, 그 후 소강 상태다.)이 터지기 직전 그의 사무실 벽에는 카다피 포스터가 걸려있었고, 거리는 시위로 늘 시끄러웠다. ‘낙타’ 이야기보다 독자의 관심받지 못한 ‘아랍의 봄’  그는 매일 기사를 써서 보냈지만, 아무도 관심을 갖지 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Log4j mess]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878390/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878390/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-12T16:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those who have not yet seen it, this
advisory from Apache describes a nasty vulnerability in the widely used
Log4j package.


	Apache Log4j2 <=2.14.1 JNDI features used in configuration, log
	messages, and parameters do not protect against attacker controlled
	LDAP and other JNDI related endpoints. An attacker who can control
	log messages or log message parameters can execute arbitrary code
	loaded from LDAP servers when message lookup substitution is
	enabled. From log4j 2.15.0, this behavior has been disabled by
	default.


Updating this package is, of course, necessary, but that will only help so
much; it is bundled into a lot of other deployed products.
For more information see
this
Ars Technica article or, for desperate cases,
the Logout4Shell
utility.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 유사성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222593614037</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222593614037"/>
        <updated>2021-12-12T10:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[찰스 기농(구글은 ‘기논’이라고 부르고 있다)은 <비트겐슈타인과 하이데거 이후의 철학>이라는 논문에서 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 유사성에 대해서 이야기하고 있다. 기농은 예전에 칸트 없이 철학을 할 수 없었더라면, 마찬가지로 이제 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거 없이 철학을 할 수 없을 것이라는 로티의 말을 빌려 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 중요성에 대해서 암시하고 있다. 비트겐슈타인과 하이데거의 차이에도 불구하고 그들은 다음과 같은 유사성을 보여준다. 첫째, 그들은 모두 실천적, 실행적 삶을 강조한다. 이것은 이성이나 세계에 대한 탈시간적 진리를 강조하는 것에 반대된다. 둘째, 그들은 세계에 대한 표상주의적 혹은 재.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[표상과 대상]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222592608038</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222592608038"/>
        <updated>2021-12-11T00:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[통각이 대상을 구성하는가, 아니면 표상을 구성하는가? 이것에 답변이 되는 칸트의 말이 금방 눈에 띠지 않는다. <지성은 인식의 능력이다. 인식들은 주어진 표상들이 한 객관, 즉 대상들과 일정하게 관계 맺는데에서 성립한다. 그러나 객관, 즉 대상이란 주어지는 직관의 잡다가 그 개념 안에 통합되어 있는 바로 그것이다. 그런데 표상들의 모든 결합은 표상들의 종합에서 의식의 통일성을 필요로 한다. 따라서 의식의 통일은 표상들이 한 대상과 관계 맺음을, 그러니까 표상들의 객관적 타당성을, 따라서 표상들이 인식이 되는 것을 결정하는 바로 그것이며, 그 위에 따라서 지성의 가능성조차 의거한다.> (B 137) 인식 자체가 표상과 대.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mourning Fredrik "Effbot" Lundh]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878325/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878325/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T21:13:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Guido van Rossum has posted the sad news that longtime Python
contributor Fredrik Lundh has died.


	Fredrik was an early Python contributor (e.g. Elementtree and the
	're' module) and his enthusiasm for the language and community were
	inspiring for all who encountered him or his work. He spent
	countless hours on comp.lang.python answering questions from
	newbies and advanced users alike.

	He also co-founded an early Python startup, Secret Labs AB, which
	among other software released an IDE named PythonWorks. Fredrik
	also created the Python Imaging Library (PIL) which is still THE
	way to interact with images in Python, now most often through its
	Pillow fork. His effbot.org site was a valuable resource for
	generations of Python users, especially its Tkinter documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How ‘Hyperscalers’ are Innovating — and Competing — in the Data Center]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2730</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/how-hyperscalers-are-innovating-and-competing-in-the-data-center/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T20:27:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Innovation in the data center has been constrained by the traditional model of suppliers providing fixed-function chips that limit how much the biggest data center operators can differentiate. But programmable chips have emerged that allow these companies to not only increase performance, but innovate throughout the pipeline, from operating system to networking interface to user... Read More
The post How ‘Hyperscalers’ are Innovating — and Competing — in the Data Center appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick McKeown, Martin Casado and Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[drgn: How the Linux Kernel Team at Meta Debugs the Kernel at Scale (Meta)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878309/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878309/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T18:55:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "Meta for Developers" blog has an
introduction to the drgn kernel debugger.


	drgn (pronounced “dragon”) is a debugger that exposes the types and
	variables in a program for easy, expressive scripting in
	Python. The Linux kernel team at Meta originally built drgn to make
	it easier to investigate the kinds of difficult Linux kernel bugs
	that the team encounters at Meta. The team has since added further
	use cases for it, like monitoring and userspace memory profiling.


LWN reported on drgn in 2019.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Joel Humberto Gómez]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/iamagde-joel-humberto-gomez.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/iamagde-joel-humberto-gomez.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Developers Experts program is a global network of highly experienced technology experts, influencers, and thought leaders who actively support developers, companies, and tech communities by speaking at events and publishing content.
Joel Humberto Gómez is an application developer at IBM, writing applications that improve the performance of IBM’s internal organization. While his job focuses on frontend development using React, he also has experience with web development using JavaScript. He has held many technical lead roles, in which he makes technical decisions and product delivery plans. Joel has a Computer Science degree from Universidad Veracruzana and has familiarity with databases, mobile development, web development, networks, and servers. He is a GDE in Web Technologies …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Stochastic bisection in Git]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877964/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877964/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regressions are no fun; among other things, finding the source of a
regression among thousands of changes can be a needle-in-the-haystack sort
of problem.  The git
bisect 
command can help; it is a (relatively) easy way to sift through 
large numbers of commits to find the one that introduces a regression.  When it
works well, it can quickly point out the change that causes a specific
problem.  Bisection is not a perfect tool, though; it can go badly wrong in
situations where a bug cannot be reliably reproduced.  In an attempt to
make bisection more useful in such cases, Jan Kara is proposing to add "stochastic
bisection" support to Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878279/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878279/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T14:37:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (python-babel), Fedora (golang-github-opencontainers-image-spec and libmysofa), openSUSE (hiredis), Oracle (firefox and thunderbird), Red Hat (thunderbird and virt:8.2 and virt-devel:8.2), Scientific Linux (thunderbird), SUSE (kernel-rt and xen), and Ubuntu (firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[직장 내 괴롭힘 신고로 해고된 ‘3개월 기간제’ 노동자의 싸움]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=83010</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/83010"/>
        <updated>2021-12-10T11:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[나는 2021. 2. 15. 장슬기 조합원 이하 신청인 및 서울청년유니온 집행부와의 상담을 기점으로 직장 내 괴롭힘 신고로 인한 부당해고 건을 수임했다. 청년유니온 자문노무사로서 노동위원회 부당해고 구제신청 사건과 고용노동부 직장 내 괴롭힘 진정사건을 대리하기로 하였으며 그 중 부당해고 구제신청 사건이 중앙노동위원회에서 초심 취소(인용)라는 쾌거를 이루며 마무리되었다. 이하 100장이 훌쩍 넘는 이유서와 50쪽에 달하는 입증자료를 제출해가며 치열하게 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>청년유니온</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Web3 Playbook: Using Token Incentives to Bootstrap New Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2716</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-web3-playbook-using-token-incentives-to-bootstrap-new-networks/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T23:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The killer app of the internet is networks. The web and email are networks. Social apps like Instagram and Twitter are networks. Marketplaces like Uber and Airbnb are networks. Networks get more valuable with more participants, which is great when they are at scale, but cuts the other way when starting out. This is the... Read More
The post The Web3 Playbook: Using Token Incentives to Bootstrap New Networks appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Dixon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.16, expanding the horizons: MISRA C, Visual Studio 2022, .NET 6]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0897/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0897/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the latest release of PVS-Studio in 2021. With it, the PVS-Studio team accomplishes several important goals. Now, PVS-Studio supports Visual Studio 2022, the .NET 6 platform and C# 10.0. We implemented all diagnostics categorized as Mandatory in MISRA C.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Haas: Surviving Without A Superuser - Part One]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878206/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878206/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T19:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostgreSQL developer Robert Haas has begun
a blog series on what would be needed to allow database administrators
to safely delegate superuser powers.


	Consider, for example, the case of a service provider who would
	like to support a database with multiple customers as tenants. The
	customers will naturally want to feel as if they have the powers of
	a true superuser, with the ability to do things like create new
	roles, drop old ones, change permissions on objects that they don't
	own, and generally enjoy the freedom to bypass permission checks at
	the SQL level which superusers enjoy. The service provider, who is
	the true superuser, also wants this, but does not want the
	customers to be able to do the really scary things that a superuser
	can do, like changing archive_command to
	rm -rf / or deleting the 
	entire contents of pg_proc so that the system crashes and the
	database in which the operation was performed is permanently
	ruined.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon’s latest FCC filing hints at Sidewalk expansion plans]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9444</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/amazons-latest-fcc-filing-hints-at-sidewalk-expansion-plans/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T17:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has asked the FCC to approve an outdoor Sidewalk-capable device called the Amazon Sidewalk Ring Bridge Pro, which is designed for professional installation as opposed to being a consumer-oriented technology. This signals that Amazon is planning to take its Sidewalk network to the next level by either providing more robust coverage in areas where […]
The post Amazon’s latest FCC filing hints at Sidewalk expansion plans appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Team-sourced Architectural Principles]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#3.ALightToIlluminateAUnifiedGoalTeam-sourcedArchitecturalPrinciples</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#3.ALightToIlluminateAUnifiedGoalTeam-sourcedArchitecturalPrinciples"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Having architectural principles is not new, but in a world of
      highly-autonomous-teams they become essential because they are the means
      by which an aligned delivery direction is achieved without the need for
      control. In the latest installment, Andrew talks about what makes a good
      principle, and how they work with the Advice Process.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Blocking straight-line speculation — eventually]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877845/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877845/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T15:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Spectre class of vulnerabilities was given that name because, it was
thought, these problems would haunt us for a long time.  As the fourth
anniversary of the disclosure of Meltdown and
Spectre approaches, there is no reason to doubt the accuracy of that
name.  One of 
the more recent Spectre variants goes by the name "straight-line
speculation"; it was first disclosed in June 2020, but fixes are still
trying to find their way into the compilers and the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use commercial integration tools to simplify implementation concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#UseCommercialIntegrationToolsToSimplifyImplementationConcerns</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#UseCommercialIntegrationToolsToSimplifyImplementationConcerns"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thus far, Brandon has has explained why general purpose languages are
      better for integration. In this latest installment he
      explains that there are cases when commercial integration tools make
      sense
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878142/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878142/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T14:31:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (firefox, libopenmpt, matrix-synapse, vim, and xen), Mageia (gmp, heimdal, libsndfile, nginx/vsftpd, openjdk, sharpziplib/mono-tools, and vim), Red Hat (java-1.8.0-ibm), Scientific Linux (firefox), SUSE (kernel-rt), and Ubuntu (bluez).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Lexmark shares how to manage millions of connected devices]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9426</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-lexmark-shares-how-to-manage-millions-of-connected-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s show is our 350th episode, so we start off with a little bit of celebration before hitting half a dozen pieces of Amazon-related news, including the AWS outage that took out many smart home services, and a newly submitted FCC listing that could be a big deal for those needing a low-power wide-area network. […]
The post Podcast: Lexmark shares how to manage millions of connected devices appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AIoT enables smart traffic solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471808</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-aiot-enables-smart-traffic-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T13:09:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Major advancements in AI and IoT, largely driven by an increased emphasis on digital transformation in a post-pandemic world, could be the key to eliminating...
The post How AIoT enables smart traffic solutions appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ravi Kiran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘국힘’ 노재승 망언을 대하는 언론의 태도]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82996</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82996"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T09:37:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[국민의힘은 12월 5일 공동선거대책위원장으로 노재승·함익병·박주선 씨를 내정했습니다. 이후 함익병 씨의 “박정희 독재가 큰 역할을 했다” “여자는 4분의 3만 권리를 행사해야 한다” 등 독재 찬양, 여성비하 발언이 논란이 되자 국민의힘은 곧바로 내정을 취소했습니다. 함익병 씨뿐만 아니라 노재승 씨 역시 과거 SNS에서 극우적 주장을 한 것이 뒤늦게 알려졌는데요. 노재승 씨의 부적절한 발언은 정당 선거대책위원장이란 중책을 맡길 수 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[sureCore register file delivers 50% power reduction]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471803</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/surecore-register-file-delivers-50-power-reduction/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T09:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MiniMiser register file architecture gives developers a new way of optimizing the power envelope for their design, supporting a wide operating voltage range and capability to deliver high performance needed by AI applications.
The post sureCore register file delivers 50% power reduction appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 9, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877424/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877424/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T01:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 9, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[프랑스, ‘클라우드 주권’ 위해 4년간 18억 유로 투입]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82984</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82984"/>
        <updated>2021-12-09T00:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[프랑스 정부가 자국의 클라우드 컴퓨팅 산업을 육성하기 위해 향후 4년 동안 18억 유로를 투입해 다양한 연구 과제를 지원하겠다고 지난 11월 3일에 발표했다. 이 발표는 프랑스에서 최근 상장한 클라우드 기업인 OVH 클라우드의 파리 사무실에서 디지털부 장관인 세드릭 오(Cedric O, 한국계)가 직접 발표했다. 이는 특히 아마존, 마이크로소프트, 구글 등에 의해 유럽 특히 프랑스 클라우드 시장이 주도되고, 남은 공간이 거의 없음을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11.0a3 is available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/12/python-3110a3-is-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/12/python-3110a3-is-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T23:54:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You can tell that we are slowly getting closer to the first beta as the number of release blockers that we need to fix on every release starts to increase  But we did it! 
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3110a1/


Major new features of the 3.11 series, compared to 3.10
Among the new major new features and changes so far:


PEP 657 – Include Fine-Grained Error Locations in Tracebacks
PEP 654 – PEP 654 – Exception Groups and except*


The Faster Cpython Project is already yielding some exciting results: this version of CPython 3.11 is ~19% faster on the geometric mean of the performance benchmarks, compared to 3.10.0.
(Hey, fellow core developer, if a feature you find important is missing from this list, let Pablo know.)

The next pre-release of Python 3.11 will be 3.11.0a3, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[그들이 누구인가]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222590657907</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222590657907"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T23:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[박정희는 독재자였다. 전두환은 박정희를 흉내 내어 체육관에서 선거를 통해 대통령이 되었다. 박정희가 대통령이었을 때, 매스 게임이나 카드 섹션 같은 전체주의적 폭력이 일상적이었다. 머리가 길다고 잡아가고, 고등학생에게 군사 훈련을 시키고, 어떤 의미에서 ‘김일성’ 같은 놈이었다. 지금 어느 정당의 뿌리를 찾아가면 바로 여기에 맞닿아 있다. 그 뿌리가 이렇기 때문에 그 정당을 지지할 수 없다는 것이 아니다. 그렇게 생각하는 것이 발생적 오류이다. 오히려 그 뿌리가 보여주듯이 그 내용이 동일하다. 이런 의미에서 어떻게 그 정당을 지지할 수 있는가? 특정 지역에 사는, 주로 나이 먹은 늙은이들이 내 눈에는 아주 한심해 보일.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python discusses deprecations]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877957/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877957/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T22:42:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feature deprecations are often controversial, but many projects find it
necessary, or desirable, to lose some of the baggage that has accreted over
time.  A mid-November request to get rid of three Python standard library
modules provides a case in point.  It was initially greeted as a good idea
since the modules had been officially deprecated starting with
Python 3.6; there are better ways to accomplish their
tasks now.  But, of course, removing a module breaks any project that uses
it, at least without the project making some, perhaps even trivial,
changes.  The cost of that is not insignificant, and the value in doing so
is not always clear, which led to higher-level conversation about deprecations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first static analysis report: the key problems and how to address them]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0896/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0896/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The main purpose of the static analyzer is to detect and report errors in code - so that you can fix them afterwards. However, reporting errors is not as simple as it may seem. Those just starting out to work with static analysis - and even experienced developers - may encounter a number of problems. In this article I'll talk about these problems and how to deal with them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels for all]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878039/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878039/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T16:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.15.7, 5.10.84, 5.4.164, 4.19.220, 4.14.257, 4.9.292, and 4.4.294 have been released.  They all contain
important fixes and users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/878038/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/878038/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T16:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (nss), Fedora (rubygem-rmagick), openSUSE (xen), Red Hat (firefox and nss), SUSE (kernel and xen), and Ubuntu (mailman and nss).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you limit who voice controls your Google Home devices?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9421</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/can-you-limit-who-voice-controls-your-google-home-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T15:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Jonathan called in to our voicemail hotline with a smart home question. He uses Google Home along with various smart lights. And his sons keep turning off the lights in Jonathan’s bedroom. So he’s wondering: Is there a way to limit who can voice control his smart home devices? […]
The post Can you limit who voice controls your Google Home devices? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Equity: From Lottery Ticket to Financial Wedge]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2643</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/equity-compensation-in-tech/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T15:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A decade ago, equity compensation — paying employees with company stock — was a perk reserved solely for executives. The practice was largely deployed by companies as a way to optimize retention while keeping their balance sheets clean. Since then, equity compensation has expanded quickly. Within the next 10 years, it’s estimated that public companies... Read More
The post Rethinking Equity: From Lottery Ticket to Financial Wedge appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niya Dragova</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[길드의 시대 / 진보의 시대]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82961</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82961"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T09:51:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[19세기 말 미국은 분야별 거대산업이 정치에 막강한 영향력을 미치고 있었다. 위 삽화는 철강, 식품, 석유 등 분야별 산업을 독점한 조합들이 정당과 의회 배후에서 자신들이 의도한 대로 법을 주무르던 당시 부패를 단적으로 보여준다. 마크 트웨인은 이 시대를 미국 자본주의의 추악한 정경유착 시대로 비난하며 ‘길드의 시대’(The Gilded age; 조합의 시대)로 규정하기도 했다. 130년 후 한국, 여전히 유효한 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘업계 로비스트’를 그린피스 ‘창립자’로 둔갑시킨 조선일보 인터뷰]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82964</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82964"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T08:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[조선일보는 12월 6일 탈원전 정책을 비판하는 패트릭 무어 박사 이메일 인터뷰를 두 건의 기사로 보도했습니다. 특히 패트릭 무어를 ‘그린피스 창립자’로 소개하고, 그린피스 이력을 강조했는데요. 이어 사설에선 문재인 정부 탈원전 정책을 강도 높게 비판하며 ‘탈원전정책 철회’를 주장했습니다. 민주언론시민연합은 조선일보가 환경분야 권위자로 소개한 패트릭 무어 이력에 사실과 다른 점은 없는지, 조선일보가 주장하는 ‘탈원전 정책 철회’ 근거에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter: Device-to-Device Automations]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/bdbb32365350</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-device-to-device-automations-bdbb32365350?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-08T06:40:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hrishikesh Dhayagude</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] FIPS-compliant random numbers for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877607/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877607/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T20:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux random-number generator (RNG) seems to attract an outsized amount 
of attention (and work) for what is, or seemingly should be, a fairly small
component of the kernel.  In part that is because random numbers, and
their quality, are extremely important to a number of security
protections, from unpredictable IP-packet sequence numbers to cryptographic
keys.  A recent post of
version 43 of the Linux Random Number 
Generator (LRNG) by Stephan Müller is not likely to go any further than its
predecessors, but the discussion around it may lead to support for a
feature that some distributions need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전기 하이데거의 언어철학 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222589598675</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222589598675"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T19:55:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<언어, 의미, 그리고 철학>은 하이데거의 전기 언어철학을 해명해 주고 있다. 거기에 하이데거의 <존재와 시간>에 나온 한 구절을 다음처럼 번역하고 있다. (A) <양해라는 것의 의미 전체는 낱말로 표현된다. 낱말이 자라서 의미가 된다. 하지만 낱말들이라는 것이 의미로 오해되지 않을 것이다.>(§ 34) 다른 번역판은 이 구절을 다음처럼 번역하고 있다. (B) <이해 가능성의 의미부여 전체가 낱말로 오게된다. 뜻들이 자라서 낱말이 된다. 단어라는 물건에 뜻들이 부착되어 있는 것이 아니다.> (C) <이 이해 가능성의 의의 전체가 언어로 나타나게 되지만, 그렇다고 여러 가지 단어가 여러 가지 뜻을 부여받는 것은.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manipulating C strings safely]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471785</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/manipulating-c-strings-safely/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T17:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s a simple mechanism to prevent software from manipulating an invalid string with well-known string functions. A software failure due to an invalid string of...
The post Manipulating C strings safely appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Leandro Francucci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Menta launches eFPGA soft IP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471780</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/menta-launches-efpga-soft-ip/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T17:30:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eFPGA soft IP allows hardware to be reconfigured after manufacturing, enabling more upgradeability and longer life cycles, and acts as “design insurance” for SoCs and ASICs that include algorithms evolving faster than chip manufacturing cycles.
The post Menta launches eFPGA soft IP appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 95.0 and Firefox ESR 91.4.0]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877950/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877950/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 95.0 is now
available.  With this version the RLBox
sandboxing technology is enabled on all platforms, as is the Site
Isolation security architecture, which protects against side-channel
attacks.

Firefox ESR
91.4.0 is also available with various security
fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination launches RISC-V CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471765</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/imagination-launches-risc-v-cpus/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T16:40:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New RISC-V CPUs target heterogenous compute architectures, with its microcontrollers already shipping in automotive GPUs.
The post Imagination launches RISC-V CPUs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877945/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877945/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T15:57:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (nss), Debian (roundcube and runc), openSUSE (aaa_base, brotli, clamav, glib-networking, gmp, go1.16, hiredis, kernel, mozilla-nss, nodejs12, nodejs14, openexr, openssh, php7, python-Babel, ruby2.5, speex, wireshark, and xen), Oracle (kernel and nss), Red Hat (kpatch-patch, nss, rpm, and thunderbird), SUSE (brotli, clamav, glib-networking, gmp, kernel, mariadb, mozilla-nss, nodejs12, nodejs14, openssh, php7, python-Babel, and wireshark), and Ubuntu (busybox, mariadb-10.3, mariadb-10.5, python-django, and samba).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use a general purpose language to manage the interface evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#UseAGeneralPurposeLanguageToManageTheInterfaceEvolution</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#UseAGeneralPurposeLanguageToManageTheInterfaceEvolution"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many commercial integration tools market their ability to own the
      integration landscape and call out to general purpose languages as needed.
      While I can appreciate the marketing behind such messaging — it promotes
      product penetration and lock-in — as architectural guidance, it is exactly
      backwards. Instead, we should almost always manage the interface evolution
      in a general purpose language for at least two reasons: so we can better
      manage the complexity of maintaining a clean interface, and so that we
      avoid the gravitational pull of our tool's mental model when making
      strategic integration decisions.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can PassiveLiFi make batteries for IoT obsolete?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9431</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/can-passivelifi-make-batteries-for-iot-obsolete/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T14:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m always on the lookout for technologies that helps reduce the use of batteries for the IoT. With that in mind, I’m bullish on energy-harvesting sensors and radios, and excited to see more investment in wireless power at a distance. So this week, I dug into a paper from researchers at Universidad Carlos III de […]
The post Can PassiveLiFi make batteries for IoT obsolete? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speculating on Apple’s self-driving car initiative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471858</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/speculating-on-apples-self-driving-car-initiative/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T12:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s not a question of “if” but rather “when” Apple’s Titan initiative hits the road. Speculation concerning an Apple’s self-driving car received a jolt in...
The post Speculating on Apple’s self-driving car initiative appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Egil Juliussen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Neuromorphic vision takes on diverse applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471854</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/neuromorphic-vision-takes-on-diverse-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event-based vision company Prophesee has showcased some interesting applications for its vision sensors from around the world, spanning biotech, scientific analysis, robotics and space technologies....
The post Neuromorphic vision takes on diverse applications appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Ward-Foxton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASIC enables broad access to space-based mobile network]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471851</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/asic-enables-broad-access-to-space-based-mobile-network/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T12:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cellular ASIC from Ensilica to enable any unmodified handset to connect to AST SpaceMobile’s space-based cellular broadband network. U.K. custom design house Ensilica has announced...
The post ASIC enables broad access to space-based mobile network appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 이것은 논증이고, 저것은 논증이 아닌가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82941</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82941"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T08:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[비판적 사고를 뒷받침하기 위한 수단으로 논증을 활용할 때, 세 단계에 걸쳐 질문을 던져야 한다. 주장이 무엇인지 묻는 단순한 질문에서, 그런 생각을 하게 된 ‘토대’에 관해 묻는 까다로운 질문까지 나아간다. 논증은 질문에 답하는 것이다 논증은 다음과 같은 ‘검증’ 단계를 ‘통과’해야 한다. 1단계. 주장-이유-근거 당신의 주장은 무엇인가? 그것은 어떻게 뒷받침할 수 있는가? 막연한 느낌이나 감정에서 나오는 의미없는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[건강상 이유로 콘텐츠 업뎃이 중단되고 있습니다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584466</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584466/%ea%b1%b4%ea%b0%95%ec%83%81-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0%eb%a1%9c-%ec%bd%98%ed%85%90%ec%b8%a0-%ec%97%85%eb%8e%83%ec%9d%b4-%ec%a4%91%eb%8b%a8%eb%90%98%ea%b3%a0-%ec%9e%88%ec%8a%b5%eb%8b%88%eb%8b%a4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T01:50:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10.1 is available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/12/python-3101-is-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/12/python-3101-is-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-07T00:07:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I hope you like bug fixes, because we have a whole shipment of them! Python 3.10.1 is the first maintenance release of Python 3.10 as we have packed more than 330 commits of fixes and general improvements. You can get it here:

https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3101/

This is the first maintenance release of Python 3.10


Python 3.10.1 is the newest major release of the Python programming language, and it contains many new features and optimizations.


Major new features of the 3.10 series, compared to 3.9
Among the new major new features and changes so far:


PEP 623 – Deprecate and prepare for the removal of the wstr member in PyUnicodeObject.

PEP 604 – Allow writing union types as X | Y

PEP 612 – Parameter Specification Variables

PEP 626 – Precise line numbers for debug…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Foundation 2021 annual report]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877844/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877844/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T23:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those who would like to catch up on what the Linux Foundation has been
doing, the 2021
annual report is available as an 87-page PDF file.


	In 2021, The Linux Foundation continued to see organizations
	embrace open collaboration and open source principles, accelerating
	new innovations, approaches, and best practices. As a community, we
	made significant progress in the areas of cloud-native computing,
	5G networking, software supply chain security, 3D gaming, and a
	host of new industry and social initiatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[원작자가 말하는 ‘듄’의 메시지: ‘리더가 늘 옳다고 절대 믿지 마라’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82932</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82932"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T22:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[짧게 끝나긴 했지만, 단계적 일상 회복이 진행되면서 거리에 사람이 많아졌다. 사람들은 빠르게 이전의 삶으로 돌아가고 있었고, 나도 이 분위기에 질 수 없다는 마음으로 요즘 뜸했던 영화관을 찾았다. 먼저 보고 온 지인들이 그토록 칭찬해 마지않던 영화 [듄]을 보기 위해서였다. 좋아하는 감독, 좋아하는 배우, 좋아하는 세계관. 사회적 거리두기가 일상이 된 이후 ‘오랜만에 극장에서 영화를 본다면 이런 영화여야 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 Ranges — Complete Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0895/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0895/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++20 Ranges, also known as STL v2, effectively replaces existing STL algorithms and facilities. In this article, I will guide you through the changes that Ranges introduce, talk about Views, which are a new composable approach to algorithms and show examples of FizzBuzz using three different methods, all utilizing some aspects of Ranges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kickstarting Network Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2676</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/kickstarting-network-effects/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T20:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network effects can be found powering almost every major technology company, from messaging apps and workplace collaboration tools, like Slack and Zoom, to marketplaces, like Airbnb and Instacart to even the internet itself. In this podcast, we look at the role of network effects creator-driven social platforms, with Alexis Ohanian, cofounder from Reddit, Paul Davison,... Read More
The post Kickstarting Network Effects appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Davison, Alexis Ohanian, Andrew Chen and Das Rush</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A reference-count tracking infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877603/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877603/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T18:28:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reference counts are a commonly used mechanism for tracking the life cycle
of objects in a computing system.  As long as every user of an object
correctly maintains its references by incrementing and decrementing the
reference count, that object will persist for as long as it
is needed
and will be properly destroyed once the last user is done.  The "correctly"
in that sentence is important, though; things do not work
as well in the presence of reference-counting errors.  Networking
developer Eric Dumazet is working on a
reference-count tracking system that could prove useful for finding
these errors in the networking subsystem and, someday, throughout the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877821/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877821/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T16:06:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (isync, lib32-nss, nss, opera, and vivaldi), Debian (gerbv and xen), Fedora (autotrace, chafa, converseen, digikam, dmtx-utils, dvdauthor, eom, kxstitch, libsndfile, nss, pfstools, php-pecl-imagick, psiconv, q, R-magick, rss-glx, rubygem-rmagick, seamonkey, skopeo, synfig, synfigstudio, vdr-scraper2vdr, vdr-skinelchihd, vdr-skinnopacity, vdr-tvguide, vim, vips, and WindowMaker), Mageia (golang, kernel, kernel-linus, mariadb, and vim), openSUSE (aaa_base, python-Pygments, singularity, and tor), Red Hat (nss), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (aaa_base, kernel, openssh, php74, and xen), and Ubuntu (libmodbus, lrzip, samba, and uriparser).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon tries to sell distributed-not-decentralized computing]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9428</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/amazon-tries-to-sell-distributed-not-decentralized-computing/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T14:56:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I initially thought that my overview of the AWS re:Invent conference would focus on the details of a bunch of new features and services. But on Thursday morning, Amazon CTO Werner Vogels took the stage and proceeded to outline a future of computing that’s utterly distributed and tailor-made for the internet of things, yet still […]
The post Amazon tries to sell distributed-not-decentralized computing appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a DevSecOps approach improved security in iris recognition systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471756</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-a-devsecops-approach-improved-security-in-iris-recognition-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T14:23:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at DevSecOps best practice and use of static application security testing (SAST) as part of the software development lifecycle at Iris ID, who provide iris recognition for state-of-the-art access control and sensitive biometric authentication applications. 
The post How a DevSecOps approach improved security in iris recognition systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jun Hong</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trends in embedded development: a Mouser perspective]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471746</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/trends-in-embedded-development-a-mouser-perspective/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T13:18:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the trends in embedded systems design, including greater system integration , connected devices, and the 'virtual' revolution.
The post Trends in embedded development: a Mouser perspective appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Patrick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous integration with Go and GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/ci-with-go-and-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/ci-with-go-and-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T09:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this post we're going to walk through how to use GitHub Actions to create a continuous integration (CI) pipeline that automatically tests, vets and lints your Go code.
For solo projects I usually create a pre-commit Git hook to carry out these kinds of checks, but for team projects or open-source work — where you don't have control over everyone's development environment — using a CI workflow is a great way to flag up potential problems and help catch bugs before they make it into production or a versioned release.
And if you're already using GitHub to host your repository, it's nice and easy to use their built-in functionality to do this without any need for additional third-party tools or services.
To demonstrate how it works, let's run through a step-by-step example.
If you'd like to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[필터 버블과 팬덤 정치: 대선 후를 더 우려하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82917</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82917"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T09:23:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 대통령선거를 앞둔 현재 상황은 여러 측면에서 예외적인 모습을 띤다. 치열하게 각축하고 있는 양대 정당의 후보들은 중앙정치 경험이 없고, 당직 경험이 없는 ‘아웃사이더’로서 정당 내부보다는 외부의 지지에 힘입어 소속 정당의 경선을 통과했다.(1) 또한, 양대 정당 이외의 제3의 후보들이 존재하지만, 과거와 달리 그 영향력은 미미하다.(2) 더불어 자신에 대한 낮은 호감도가 자신이 유권자에게 그다지 매력적인 대안으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Links #6: C++23 Progress, Command Line, Containers, and more!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cpplinksdec/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cpplinksdec/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 6th episode of C++ Links available for C++ Stories subscribers.
See the best C++ stories from the past month.
Here’s the plan for today:
C++23 progress
Parsing Command Line Arguments
3 New articles at C++stories in November
+ 8 Hot C++ News
How to write a custom iterator in C++20
Read till the end to see an additional bonus :)
Let’s start!
🚧 C++23 ISO Progress
At the end of October, there was a cool episode at C++ Cast with Bryce Adelstein Lelbach about the progress of C++23.
Notes:
Everything is moving to Clang - is that good? It’s now lagging with the latest C++ features, probably because of its growth. In GCC, they started using  C++ for the compiler, so it looks like it speeds up things.
Networking has no consensus - TS is probably not worth putting into the Standard  w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Links #6: C++23 Progress, Command Line, Containers, and more!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cplinksdec/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/cplinksdec/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the 6th episode of C++ Links available for C++ Stories subscribers.
See the best C++ stories from the past month.
Here’s the plan for today:
C++23 progress
Parsing Command Line Arguments
3 New articles at C++stories in November
+ 8 Hot C++ News
How to write a custom iterator in C++20
Read till the end to see an additional bonus :)
Let’s start!
🚧 C++23 ISO Progress
At the end of October, there was a cool episode at C++ Cast with Bryce Adelstein Lelbach about the progress of C++23.
Notes:
Everything is moving to Clang - is that good? It’s now lagging with the latest C++ features, probably because of its growth. In GCC, they started using  C++ for the compiler, so it looks like it speeds up things.
Networking has no consensus - TS is probably not worth putting into the Standard  w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some latency measurement pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/latency-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/latency-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a pseudo-transcript (actual words modified to be more readable than a 100% faithful transcription) of a short lightning talk I did at Twitter a year or two ago, on pitfalls of how we use latency metrics (with the actual service names anonymized per a comms request). Since this presentation, significant progress has been made on this on the infra side, so the situation is much improved over what was presented, but I think this is still relevant since, from talking to folks at peer companies, many folks are facing similar issues.
We frequently use tail latency metrics here at Twitter. Most frequently, service owners want to get cluster-wide or Twitter-wide latency numbers for their services. Unfortunately, the numbers that service owners tend to use differ from what we'd like to meas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in November]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/november-2021-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/november-2021-roundup"/>
        <updated>2021-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
November.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877724/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877724/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-05T23:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fourth 5.16 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Nothing looks all that scary, although I certainly hope
the kvm side will calm down".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AP 특파원의 ‘소름 끼치는 임무’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82896</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82896"/>
        <updated>2021-12-05T23:20:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AP 특파원은 전투 결과를 정확하게 전달하기 위해 현장에 직접 들어가 시체를 하나씩 센다. 아마도 AP 특파원이 수행하는 가장 기본적이면서도 위험한 임무일 것이다. 정부가 발표하는 정보에는 왜곡이 많기 때문에 기자는 직접 현장에 가서 사실을 확인하고 기사의 신빙성을 높여야 한다. 물론 이러한 경험은 상당한 트라우마를 남긴다. 1980년 광주, 테리 앤더슨   테리 앤더슨(Terry Anderson)은 이런 일을 두 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advent Calendar for 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=34006</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/12/05/advent-calendar-for-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-05T20:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Switzerland got a snow cover, part of it melted away again. But with more snow coming the next days. December started, and so did the Advent season. Similar to last year, we wanted to create a special advent calendar, which … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가능성과 불가능성의 이중성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222587108307</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222587108307"/>
        <updated>2021-12-04T23:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[재현 관계, 혹은 표상 관계는 이항 관계이다. 그러나 재현 관계는 그것이 어떻게 가능할 수 있는지 스스로 묻지 못한다. 이것이 재현적 혹은 표상적 사유의 한계이다. 재현적 사유를 가능하게 하는 것이 무엇인가? 그것을 가능하게 하는 제3항이 무엇인가? 그것을 타자의 욕망이라고 주장한다. 그러나 타자의 욕망이, 혹은 대타자의 욕망이 재현이나 표상 관계를 가능하게 하는가? 오히려 내 욕망과 내 욕망 대상의 관계를 가능하게 만든다고 주장해야 한다. 욕망은 어떻게 가능한가? 타자의 욕망 때문에 가능하다. 그러나 이것은 순환적이다. 욕망의 가능성을 설명하는데 이미 타자의 ‘욕망’을 전제하고 있다. 내 욕망은 어떻게 가능한가? 그.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fast CSV processing with SIMD]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/04/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/12/04/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-04T01:13:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article was discussed on Hacker News.
I recently learned of csvquote, a tool that encodes troublesome
CSV characters such that unix tools can correctly process them. It
reverses the encoding at the end of the pipeline, recovering the original
input. The original implementation handles CSV quotes using the
straightforward, naive method. However, there’s a better approach that is
not only simpler, but around 3x faster on modern hardware. Even more,
there’s yet another approach using SIMD intrinsics, plus some bit
twiddling tricks, which increases the processing speed by an order of
magnitude. My csvquote implementation includes both
approaches.
Background
Records in CSV data are separated by line feeds, and fields are separated
by commas. Fields may be quoted.

aaa,bbb,ccc
xxx,"yyy",zzz…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Minutes: Inside the GameStop Drama; U.S. Constitution, Auctioned]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2662</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/16-minutes-inside-the-gamestop-drama-u-s-constitution-auctioned/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T20:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to 16 Minutes, our show on the a16z podcast network where we talk about tech trends that are dominating news headlines, industry buzz, and where we are on the long arc of innovation.  Today’s episode actually features a look back at the GameStop saga — the stock market drama that some headlines described as... Read More
The post 16 Minutes: Inside the GameStop Drama; U.S. Constitution, Auctioned appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Andreessen and Ken Griffin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Dec. 3, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9418</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-dec-3-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T18:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some things I just learned about Matter: During a recent pre-CES chat with the folks from Eve, I learned that the company is planning to upgrade most of its devices either via firmware or, in the case of Eve’s light switch and motion sensor, through new devices to Matter. But because a firmware update is so complicated, once […]
The post IoT news of the week for Dec. 3, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adoption picks up for IIoT, IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471774</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/adoption-picks-up-for-iiot-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T17:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a sluggish start, notably in Europe, the pace of adoption of industrial internet of things (IIoT) networks and the IIoT’s more consumer-facing relative, the...
The post Adoption picks up for IIoT, IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Walko</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#BazelCon 2021 Wrap Up]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/bazelcon-2021-wrap-up.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/12/bazelcon-2021-wrap-up.html"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Joe Hicks, Product Manager, Core Developer
   

          
The apps, platforms, and systems that the Bazel community builds with Bazel touch the lives of people around the world in ways we couldn’t have imagined. Through BazelCon, we aim to connect Bazel enthusiasts, the Bazel team, maintainers, contributors, users, and friends in an inclusive and welcoming environment. At BazelCon, the community demonstrates the global user impact of the community—with some quirky and carefully crafted talks, a readout on the State-of-Bazel, an upfront discussion on “Implicit Bias Mitigation,” and community sharing events that remind us that we are not alone in our efforts to build a better world, one line of code at a time.  
     

   
At BazelCon, the community shared over 24 technical sessio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing CentOS Stream 9]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877599/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877599/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T15:56:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The CentOS blog has announced the release of CentOS Stream 9:

CentOS Stream is a continuous-delivery distribution providing each point-release of Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL). Before a package is formally introduced to CentOS Stream, it undergoes a battery of tests and checks—both automated and manual—to ensure it meets the stringent standards for inclusion in RHEL. Updates posted to Stream are identical to those posted to the unreleased minor version of RHEL. The aim? For CentOS Stream to be as fundamentally stable as RHEL itself.

To achieve this stability, each major release of Stream starts from a stable release of Fedora Linux—In CentOS Stream 9, this begins with Fedora 34, which is the same code base from which RHEL 9 is built. As updated packages pass testing and meet standards for stability, they are pushed into CentOS Stream as well as the nightly build of RHEL.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A filesystem for namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877308/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877308/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T14:40:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It is natural, when looking at the kernel development process, to focus on
patches that find their way to acceptance and become a part of future
kernels.  But there can be value in looking at work that doesn't clear the
bar; in failing, these patches often reveal things about the kernel and the
community that creates it.  Such is the case with the proof-of-concept
namespacefs
patch series recently posted by Yordan Karadzhov.  One should not
expect to see namespacefs in a future kernel but, in failing, this work
showed a real use case and why it is hard to satisfy that use case in the
kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877582/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877582/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (krb5 and mailman), Debian (gmp and librecad), Fedora (php-symfony4 and wireshark), Mageia (bluez, busybox, docker-containerd, gfbgraph, hivex, nss, perl/perl-Encode, and udisks2/libblockdev), openSUSE (permissions), Oracle (mailman and mailman:2.1), Red Hat (mailman, mailman:2.1, and nss), Scientific Linux (mailman and nss), and SUSE (nodejs14).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[검찰의 ‘보복기소’를 ‘공소권 남용’으로 처음 막아내다 (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82884</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82884"/>
        <updated>2021-12-03T08:45:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 대법원은 소위 ‘서울시 공무원 간첩’ 사건으로 무죄가 선고된 피고인에게, 이미 수년 전에 조사가 마무리됐던 다른 사건을 추가로 기소한 검사의 공소제기가 위법하다는 판결을 확정하였다. 그가 구속(2013.2.~2013.10.)되고 법정에 선 지 약 8년 6개월만의 일이다. 대법원 판결의 의의   위 판결은 오랫동안 고통받아 온 피고인을 위해 너무나도 다행스러운 결과이고, ‘교과서’에 있던 “검사가 자의적으로 공소권을 행사하여 피고인에게 실질적인 불이익을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언어는 존재의 집이다.]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222585519094</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222585519094"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T21:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[하이데거가 <이정표>에 있는 <휴머니즘 서간>에서 다음처럼 말한다. <언어는 존재의 집이다. 언어라는 가옥 안에 인간은 거주한다. 사유가와 시인은 이러한 가옥의 파수꾼이다. 그들의 파수 행위는 그들이 존재의 개방 가능성을 그들의 말행위를 통해 언어로 가져오고 언어 안에 보존하는 한, 존재의 개방 가능성을 완성하는 것이다. 사유로부터 하나의 결과가 비롯됨에 의해, 혹은 사유가 응용됨에 의해, 사유가 비로소 작용케 되는 것이 아니다. 사유는 사유하는 동안, 이미 행위하고 있는 것이다. 아마도 이러한 행위는 가장 단순 소박한 것이면서도 또한 동시에 가장 지고한 것인데, 그 까닭은 이러한 행위는 존재와 인간의 관.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Even small projects have bugs, or how PVS-Studio checked Blend2D]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0894/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0894/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often check large projects because it's easier to find bugs there. What if we try PVS-Studio on a small project? In this article we analyze Blend2D — a library for vector 2D graphics. Let's look at what we found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Detecting missing memory barriers with KCSAN]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877200/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877200/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T19:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Writing (correct) concurrent code that uses locking to avoid race
conditions is difficult enough.  When the objective is to use lockless algorithms, relying on memory
barriers instead of locks to eliminate locking overhead, the problem
becomes harder 
still.  Bugs are easy to create and hard to find in this type of code.
There may be some help on the way, though, in the form of this
patch set from Marco Elver that enhances the Kernel
Concurrency 
Sanitizer (KCSAN) with  the ability to detect some types of missing
memory barriers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LPDDR5X memory targets low-power devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471770</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/lpddr5x-memory-targets-low-power-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Micron’s LPDDR5X based on its 1-alpha node reduces power consumption on several fronts. Micron Technology’s latest memory technology aimed at smartphones offers a potential triple...
The post LPDDR5X memory targets low-power devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gary Hilson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.57.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877422/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877422/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T15:24:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.57.0 of the Rust language is out.  "Rust 1.57 brings panic! to
const contexts, adds support for custom profiles to Cargo, and stabilizes
fallible reservation APIs."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This shouldn't have happened: A vulnerability postmortem (Project Zero blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877420/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877420/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Project Zero blog, Tavis Ormandy has a lengthy postmortem on a vulnerability that he found in the Network Security Services (NSS) cryptography library.  The vulnerability is a bog-standard buffer overflow that has existed in the library since 2012 despite various kinds of static analysis, testing, and fuzzing that Mozilla and others have applied to it over the years.  He found it with a new fuzzing technique:

To solve this problem, I’ve been experimenting with monitoring the call stack during execution.

The naive implementation is too slow to be practical, but after a lot of optimization I had come up with a library that was fast enough to be integrated into coverage-guided fuzzing, and was testing how it performed with NSS and other libraries.

[...] The fuzzer I was using is able to isolate and extract interesting new ASN.1 OIDs, SEQUENCEs, INTEGERs, and so on. Once extracted, it can then randomly combine or insert them into template data. This isn’t really a new idea, but is a new implementation. I'm planning to open source this code in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: AWS overload and Libelium embraces the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9414</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-aws-overload-and-libelium-embraces-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T14:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show kicks off with a bunch of IoT-related news from Amazon’s re:Invent conference happening this week in Las Vegas. We cover the launch of a fleet management service, a digital twin service, an easy way to securely connect hardware to Amazon’s cloud, a way to manage massive robot deployments, and the launch of […]
The post Podcast: AWS overload and Libelium embraces the cloud appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877410/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877410/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T13:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (kernel, openssh, and rpm), Debian (nss), Fedora (seamonkey), Mageia (glibc), openSUSE (go1.16, go1.17, kernel, mariadb, netcdf, openexr, poppler, python-Pygments, python-sqlparse, ruby2.5, speex, and webkit2gtk3), Oracle (nss), Red Hat (nss), SUSE (clamav, glibc, gmp, go1.16, go1.17, kernel, mariadb, netcdf, OpenEXR, openexr, openssh, poppler, python-Pygments, python-sqlparse, ruby2.1, ruby2.5, speex, webkit2gtk3, and xen), and Ubuntu (nss and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 2, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876363/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876363/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-02T00:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 2, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동아·TV조선, 국정원 간첩 조작 편승 사건 (2014)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82862</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82862"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T22:25:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2013년 국가정보원 간첩 조작 사건은 군사독재 시절에나 있을 법한 일이라고 생각했던 용공 조작 사건이 얼마든지 다시 벌어질 수 있음을 보여준 대표적인 사건입니다. 국가정보원은 한 개인을 간첩으로 몰기 위해 탈북민 출신 서울시 공무원 유 모 씨 동생을 잡아 폭행과 고문 위협을 가하며 허위 자백을 받아냈고, 중국 공문서를 위조해 외교 마찰까지 불렀습니다. 결국, 탈북민 출신 서울시 공무원 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fedora revisits the Git-forge debate]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877240/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877240/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T22:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A seemingly straightforward question aimed at candidates for the in-progress
Fedora
elections led to a discussion on the Fedora devel mailing list that
branched into a few different directions.  The question was related to a
struggle that the distribution has had before: whether using non-free Git
forges is appropriate.  One of the
differences this time, though, is that the focus is on where source-git (or src-git)
repositories will be hosted, which is a separate question from where the dist-git repository
lives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SFC: First Update on the Vizio lawsuit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877294/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877294/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T17:57:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Software Freedom Conservancy provides
an update on its suit against Vizio for
copyleft license violations.  Vizio's response was not to release the
source code:

Instead, Vizio filed
a request to "remove" the case from California State Court (into US federal
court), which indicates Vizio's belief that consumers have no
third-party beneficiary rights under copyleft! In other words, Vizio’s
answer to this complaint is not to comply with the copyleft licenses, but instead imply that Software Freedom Conservancy — and all other purchasers of the devices who might want to assert their right under GPL and LGPL to complete, corresponding source — have no right to even ask for that source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[November 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d75a402cb216</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/november-2021-d75a402cb216?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:44:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/38ccf1d60bcd</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-38ccf1d60bcd?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matter is an initiative of the Connectivity Standards Alliance, and developed through collaboration amongst all the leaders of the IoT…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877285/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877285/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:16:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.15.6, 5.10.83, 5.4.163, and 4.19.219 have been released. They all contain
important fixes throughout the tree.  Users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877284/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877284/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T16:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (rsync, rsyslog, and uriparser), Fedora (containerd, freeipa, golang-github-containerd-ttrpc, libdxfrw, libldb, librecad, mingw-speex, moby-engine, samba, and xen), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, and samba), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.11, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.11, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.11, linux-hwe-5.11, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.11, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-kvm, linux-oem-5.13, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, and linux-oem-5.14).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A thinking and recording tool: Decision Records]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#1.AThinkingAndRecordingToolDecisionRecords</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html#1.AThinkingAndRecordingToolDecisionRecords"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Advice Process works when supported by four elements. Andrew
      describes the first of these, Decision Records, which act as a tool for
      thinking about and recording the decision process.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Put most of your energy into building clean interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#PutMostOfYourEnergyIntoBuildingCleanInterfaces</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html#PutMostOfYourEnergyIntoBuildingCleanInterfaces"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While we have historically drawn up our project plans and costs around
      the boxes—the digital products we are introducing—the lines are the
      hidden and often primary driver of organizational tech debt. They are the
      reason that things just take longer now than they used to. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Allegion Ventures creates $100 million fund]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9405</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/allegion-ventures-creates-100-million-fund/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:48:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Allegion has created a second venture fund with $100 million in capital to invest in IoT-related startups. The company, which is the parent of Schlage branded locks, plans to continue investing in software startups that provide cybersecurity and privacy services. The corporate venture fund will also look for investments in construction and property and asset […]
The post Allegion Ventures creates $100 million fund appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the future of embedded software lies in containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471731</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/why-the-future-of-embedded-software-lies-in-containers/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are becoming increasingly important in IoT, industrial, and automation applications, which often require regular refreshes of many different components over long time periods. In...
The post Why the future of embedded software lies in containers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Till Adam</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julia 1.7 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877242/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877242/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T15:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.7 of the Julia programming language has been released.  The list of
new features is long; see the release announcement and this LWN article for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter: Clusters, Attributes, Commands]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/82b8ec1640a0</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/matter-clusters-attributes-commands-82b8ec1640a0?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T09:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Sovani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Genetics of a Modern IoT Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21401</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/genetics-of-a-modern-iot-attack/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T09:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to IoT attacks and malware, there is a perceptible pattern in which most intrusions manifest. It is good practice to study such patterns and draw conclusions so that we may extrapolate to future attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[영국 정부의 디지털 콘트롤 타워 ‘GDS’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82841</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82841"/>
        <updated>2021-12-01T08:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[세 차례 칼럼을 통해 ‘플랫폼으로서의 정부'(GaaP: Government as a Platform) 개념 및 속성, 그리고 실행전략을 소개했다. 앞서 소개한 내용은 완전히 새로운 개념이라기보다는 지난 수십 년 동안 정부가 디지털 기술을 도입하는 과정에서 터득한 바람직한 디지털 정부의 모습을 체계적으로 정의한 것이다. 공공 디지털 서비스 분야에서 자주 인용되는 사례 중 하나가 영국 정부의 디지털 전환 거버넌스 체계다. 이 중심에는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python identifiers, PEP 8, and consistency]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877115/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877115/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T22:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While there are few rules on the names of variables, classes, functions,
and so on (i.e. identifiers) in the Python language, there are some
guidelines on how those things should be named.   But, of course, those
guidelines were not always followed in 
the standard library, especially in the early years of the project.  A
suggestion to add aliases to the standard library for
identifiers that do not follow the guidelines seems highly unlikely to go
anywhere, but it led to an interesting 
discussion on the python-ideas mailing list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Checking Chromium after three years. How's it going?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0893/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0893/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We dust off the irregular series of articles about the Chromium project check. Let's look at the code quality in the latest Chromium release and check the new features of the PVS-Studio analyzer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Personalize user journeys by Pushing Dynamic Shortcuts to Assistant]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/personalize-user-journeys-by-pushing-dynamic-shortcuts.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/personalize-user-journeys-by-pushing-dynamic-shortcuts.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T17:57:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jessica Dene Earley-Cha, Developer Relations Engineer
 Like many other people who use their smartphone to make their lives easier, I’m way more likely to use an app that adapts to my behavior and is customized to fit me. Android apps already can support some personalization like the ability to long touch an app and a list of common user journeys are listed. When I long press my Audible app (an online audiobook and podcast service), it gives me a shortcut to the book I’m currently listening to; right now that is Daring Greatly by Brené Brown.  
Now, imagine if these shortcuts could also be triggered by a voice command –    and, when relevant to the user, show up in Google Assistant for easy use. 
 Wouldn't that be lovely? 
  
Dynamic shortcuts on a mobile device
 Well, now you can…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Machine Learning for COVID-19 helpline with Krupal Modi #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/Iamagde-krupal-modi.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/Iamagde-krupal-modi.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T17:03:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
In college, Krupal Modi programmed a robot to catch a ball based on the ball’s color, and he enjoyed it enough that he became a developer. Now, he leads machine learning initiatives at Haptik, a conversational AI platform. He is a Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning and recently built the MyGov Corona Helpdesk module for the Indian government, to help Indians around the country schedule COVID-19 vaccinations. He lives in Gujarat, India. 
Meet Krupal Modi, Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning.
   
GDE Krupal Modi
    
The early days
Krupal Modi didn’t set out to become a developer, but when he …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877186/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877186/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T16:12:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (samba), Fedora (kernel), openSUSE (netcdf and tor), SUSE (netcdf and python-Pygments), and Ubuntu (imagemagick).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How will the IoT be used to prevent drunken driving?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9399</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-will-the-iot-be-used-to-prevent-drunken-driving/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T15:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Brian called into our voicemail hotline with a question about the Build Back Better legislation recently passed in the U.S. House of Representatives. There’s a provision in the current bill that requires new vehicles to prevent drunken driving. Specifically, Brian wants to know how this might be implemented. […]
The post How will the IoT be used to prevent drunken driving? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can't Buy Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/cant-buy-integration.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T14:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Build versus buy” decisions are everywhere today, and rightly so.
      Building software is risky and expensive, and software product companies
      can spread that risk and expense across multiple customers. But my
      colleague Brandon Byars argues that the kinds
      of tools that are available to buy for systems integration are not
      products that directly solve a business problem. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling the Practice of Architecture, Conversationally]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/scaling-architecture-conversationally.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many modern software architects, Andrew Harmel-Law struggles with
      the need to scale architectural thinking to larger organizations while
      allowing teams to be as autonomous as possible. The approach he's
      currently using is the "Advice Process", that encourages and supports
      these teams to be engaged in broader architectural decision making. In
      this first installment, Andrew describes this advice process, later
      installments will dig into four supporting elements that help make it work.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경마 중계식 ‘대선 지지율’ 보도, 이제 좀 작작 해라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82834</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82834"/>
        <updated>2021-11-30T07:37:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지금까지 한국 대선 보도에서 찾아볼 수 없었지만 이번 선거부터라도 새로운 판세 조사를 할 수는 없을까? 선거 때만 되면 늘 봐오던 지지율 조사와 보도가 올해도 여전히 정당이나 후보자 중심으로 이뤄지고 있다. 지지하는 후보와 선호하는 정당 조사는 물론이고 후보 간 대결구도를 가상으로 설정해서 누구를 지지하는지를 묻고 있다. 심지어는 누가 될 것 같은지도 질문하여 결과를 발표하고 있다. 언론은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[ 책 소개 ] 기하급수적인 기술 발전과 급변하는 세상을 다루는 두 권의 책]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73847</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/11/29/two-new-books-explore-the-impact-of-accelerating-technology/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=two-new-books-explore-the-impact-of-accelerating-technology"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T22:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자율주행차, 메타버스, NFT 등 최근 유튜브를 달구는 영상들을 보고 있자면 현기증 나는 속도로 변하는 세상의 흐름에 멀미가 날 정도입니다. 불과 10년 전과 비교해도 우리가 사는 세상이 얼마나 변했는지 깜짝 놀랄 때가 많습니다. 기술과 산업이 발전하는 속도와 급변하는 세상을 다루는 책 3권을 소개합니다. 기하급수적으로 성장하는 기술이 사회와 경제를 뒤흔들고 있으며, 격변기의 승리자들은 엄청난 과실을 누리고 있습니다. 과연 인류는 엄청난 속도로 발전하는 기술을 발판으로 벽을 깰 수 있을까요? 답을 찾아봅시다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A different approach to BPF loops]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877062/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877062/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T22:02:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the key features of the extended BPF virtual machine is the verifier
built into the kernel that ensures that all BPF programs are safe to run.
BPF developers often see the verifier as a bit of a mixed blessing, though;
while it can catch a lot of problems before they happen, it can also be
hard to please.  Comparisons with a well-meaning but rule-bound and picky
bureaucracy would not be entirely misplaced.  The bpf_loop()
proposal from Joanne Koong is an attempt to make pleasing the BPF
bureaucrats a bit easier for one type of loop construct.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인의 사적 언어]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222582453332</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222582453332"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T21:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(A) 우리는 자기 자신을 격려하고, 명령하고, 복종하고, 비난하고, 자기 자신을 벌줄 수 있다. 그는 자기에게 질문을 던지고 그것에 대답할 수 있다. 우리는 오직 독백으로 이야기하는 인간을 상상할 수 있다. 그는 그의 활동에 혼잣말을 덧붙인다. - 이런 사람을 보고 그들이 말하는 것을 듣는 관찰자는 그들의 언어를 자기 언어로 번역할 수 있을 것이다. (따라서 그는 그렇게 독백으로 말하는 사람의 행동을 올바르게 예측할 수 있다. 그는 그들이 결단하고 결심하는 것도 들을 수 있다.) 그러나 우리는 마찬가지로 그의 사적 사용을 위해 그의 내적 경험에, 즉 그의 감정, 기분 등에 언어적 표현을 주는 그런 언어를 상상할 수 있는가? - 우.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wide bandgap devices enhance motor control design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471799</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/wide-bandgap-devices-enhance-motor-control-design/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T18:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Motor control systems consist of software and hardware components, including IGBTs, WBG semiconductors, and MCUs, which are becoming increasingly more complex. Motor control plays an...
The post Wide bandgap devices enhance motor control design appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maurizio Di Paolo Emilio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IPOs and Beyond: A Guide to Exit Options for Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2625</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/ipos-and-beyond-a-guide-to-exit-options-for-companies/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T18:32:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exit options for startups, and their investors, were relatively straightforward for years — the companies could either go public or be acquired. Now the menu of possible options has significantly expanded, as Direct Listings and SPACs have also become tested-and-proven pathways to the public markets. All these choices add complexity for founders and investors, and... Read More
The post IPOs and Beyond: A Guide to Exit Options for Companies appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Blake Kim and Quinten Burgunder</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Computer Architecture Through a Game]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=16911</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/11/29/learning-computer-architecture-through-a-game/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[29 November 2021 by Phillip JohnstonLearning and meta-learning have been lifelong passions of mine. I find it endlessly fascinating to think about how we learn, to improve my own ability to learn, and to rethink the ways that we try to teach in our society. One nagging thread I’ve been thinking about is what’s next for learning, … 
Continue reading "Learning Computer Architecture Through a Game"
The post Learning Computer Architecture Through a Game appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Fest in Spain: Exploring the Potential of Artificial Intelligence in Careers, Communities, and Commerce]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdg-ai-fest-spain.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdg-ai-fest-spain.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T17:59:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Alessandro Palmieri, Regional Lead for Spain Developer Communities
 Google Developer Groups (GDGs) around the world are in a unique position to organize events on technology topics that community members are passionate about.  That’s what happened in Spain in July 2021, where two GDG chapters decided to put on an event called AI Fest after noticing a lack of conferences dedicated exclusively to artificial intelligence. “Artificial intelligence is everywhere, although many people do not know it,” says Irene Ruiz Pozo, the organizer of GDG Murcia and GDG Cartagena. While AI has the potential to transform industries from retail to real estate with products like Dialogflow and Lending DocAI, “there are still companies falling behind,” she notes. 
   
  
Irene and her GDG team members…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877105/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877105/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T16:06:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bluez, icu, libntlm, libvorbis, libvpx, opensc, roundcube, and tar), Fedora (kernel, kernel-headers, kernel-tools, puppet, slurm, stargz-snapshotter, and suricata), openSUSE (netcdf), Oracle (bluez, kernel, kernel-container, krb5, mailman:2.1, openssh, python3, and rpm), Red Hat (samba), and SUSE (xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve and track your home’s air quality]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9393</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-improve-and-track-your-homes-air-quality/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T14:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If the pandemic was the big story of 2020, then climate change was the big story of 2021, with prolonged freezes in Texas, raging wildfires in California, and devastating floods in Europe. Yet even as more and more people wake up to the reality of a hotter world, we’re apparently still not ready to pull […]
The post How to improve and track your home’s air quality appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[단지 그대가 ‘용역’이라는 이유만으로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82775</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82775"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T08:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2020년 7월 서울청년유니온 조합원이 직장 내 괴롭힘 문제로 상담을 요청했습니다. 해당 조합원은 서울시 사업을 수행하는 서울바이오허브와 용역계약을 맺은 시설관리업체 소속 근로자로, 시설관리 용역업체가 변경됨에 따라 고용승계 후 3개월 단기 계약을 맺었으며, 직장 내 괴롭힘 신고 후 계약만료로 이어진 상황이었습니다. 서울청년유니온은 해당 사건을 계약· 만료가 아닌 직장 내 괴롭힘 신고로 인한 부당해고 건으로 파악하고 이에 대응했습니다.  입사에서 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>청년유니온</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877031/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877031/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-29T04:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc3 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "So rc3 is usually a bit larger than rc2 just because people had some
time to start finding things.

So too this time, although it's not like this is a particularly big
rc3."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP 8.1.0 and a new foundation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/877024/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/877024/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T22:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
8.1.0 of the PHP language has been released.  This release includes a
number of new features, including enumerations,
read-only
properties,
fibers, and more.

Meanwhile, a
new foundation has been created to support development of PHP:


	The initial purpose of the PHP Foundation is to support the
	development of PHP by contracting developers to work on php-src
	either part-time or full-time. If that sounds interesting to you,
	be sure to apply!

	The foundation does not have any decision-making power on language
	changes: these remain within the sole purview of the internals
	mailing list and the RFC process. The fact that some work has been
	funded by the foundation does not imply that it will be accepted
	into PHP.


More information can be found in this
blog entry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An article for those who, like me, do not understand the purpose of std::common_type]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0892/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0892/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article investigates why the standard library needs a way to deduce a common type, how it is implemented and how it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Far-field wireless power transfer takes big step forward]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471795</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/far-field-wireless-power-transfer-takes-big-step-forward/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following approval in Europe, the US certification will enable the expansion of Energous wireless power transfer solutions at any distance, especially for IoT devices. Energous...
The post Far-field wireless power transfer takes big step forward appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maurizio Di Paolo Emilio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quick tip: Change URL query params in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/change-url-query-params-in-go</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/change-url-query-params-in-go"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this short post we're going to discuss how to add, modify or delete URL query string parameters in Go. To illustrate, we'll look at how to change this URL:



To this:



If you want to change the URL query string in place:

  

Running this will print out:



If you want to create a clone of the URL but with a different query string, while leaving the original URL unchanged, you need to create a copy of the original url.URL struct first. 
There are a couple of ways to do this. You can either re-parse the URL, or you can dereference the original url.URL and make a copy, like so:



When you do this, you create a new newURL variable of type url.URL which is initialized to the (dereferenced) value of *originalURL. This means that newURL has a different address in memory to originalURL.
Putting this together, the pattern for creating a new URL with different parameters is:



Running this will print out:



As a side note, you can use this technique any time you want to 'clone' a URL and make changes to it. For example to create a clone of a URL with a different path, you can do this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Space War]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/11/28/Spacewar.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/11/28/Spacewar.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the last month I've been spending a lot of time working on Space War.  I know, I know, I should have been working on Clean Code Episode 67: Legacy Code, and Euler 5, and Countest and Curmugeon 3.  I should have been working on a blog, or a new book, or...  But I couldn't let go of Space War.  It kept calling me.
The first time I wrote Space War was in 1978.  I wrote it in Alcom, which was a simple derivative of Focal, which was an analog of Basic for the PDP-8.  The computer was an M365 which was an augmented version of a PDP-8 and was proprietery to Teradyne, my employer at the time.
The UI was screen based, using character graphics, similar to curses.  Screen updates took on the order of a second.  All input was through the keyboard.
We used to play it on one machine while waiting fo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Clean Code Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주관적 의미와 의미 회의주의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222580676689</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222580676689"/>
        <updated>2021-11-27T21:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인은 <철학적 탐구> §201에서 하나의 역설을 말한다. 우리의 역설은 이것이었다. 모든 행위 방식을 하나의 규칙과 일치하게 만들 수 있기 때문에, 규칙은 어떠한 행위 방식도 규정할 수 있다. 규칙은 하나의, 특정한 행위 방식을 규정한다. 그런데 모든 행위 방식을 그 규칙에 일치하게 만들 수 있다. 따라서 규칙은 결국 하나의 특정한 행위 방식을 규정할 수 없다. 즉 규칙은 규칙으로서 기능할 수 없다. 이것이 규칙 회의주의이다. 규칙은 규칙으로서 그 역할을 하지만, 우리는 그것을 정당화할 수 없다. 규칙이 의미를 규정한다. 의미는 사용 규칙에 의해 규정된다. 그런데 사용 규칙이 정당화되지 않기 때문에 결국 의미도.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news: HPC, BMS, & network sharing podcast, plus CAD tool goes from cloud to desktop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471718</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-hpc-bms-network-sharing-podcast-plus-cad-tool-goes-from-cloud-to-desktop/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T19:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes a new embedded edge with Nitin podcast, a look at hardware for the metaverse, new desktop app integration for a popular online component design library plus news of products, people and events.
The post embedded news: HPC, BMS, & network sharing podcast, plus CAD tool goes from cloud to desktop appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SnapEDA launches on desktop as users seek bridge with existing CAD tools]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471709</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/snapeda-launches-on-desktop-as-users-seek-bridge-with-existing-cad-tools/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T18:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many designers wanted a better integration with their existing desktop CAD tools, so SnapEDA, an online design library for CAD models of electronic parts, launched a desktop app.
The post SnapEDA launches on desktop as users seek bridge with existing CAD tools appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 26, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9385</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-26-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GM is simplifying its chip supply chain: I think this is a smart move on GM’s part and also an indication that as we put computers into more places, we need to consolidate platforms and simplify the underlying hardware and software. GM will co-develop chips with its suppliers as well as shrink the number of chip families […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 26, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codasip adopts Imperas for RISC-V processor verification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471703</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/codasip-adopts-imperas-for-risc-v-processor-verification/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T16:17:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Codasip has included Imperas golden reference models in its DV testbenches to ensure an efficient verification flow that accommodates a wide range of flexible features and options while scaling across the entire roadmap of future cores.
The post Codasip adopts Imperas for RISC-V processor verification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrossSync PHY interposer supports PCIe 5.0 in CEM form factor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471696</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/crosssync-phy-interposer-supports-pcie-5-0-in-cem-form-factor/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T15:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New interposer brings CrossSync PHY capability to the CEM specification form factor at the full PCIe 5.0 rate of 32 GT/s. It includes probing points for reference clock, sideband signal, and power rail voltage and current monitoring, in addition to data signals for the protocol analyzer.
The post CrossSync PHY interposer supports PCIe 5.0 in CEM form factor appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ShieldIoT raises $7.4m to deploy coreset-AI for IoT cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471691</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/shieldiot-raises-7-4m-to-deploy-coreset-ai-for-iot-cybersecurity/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As IoT networks become larger using conventional anomaly detection algorithms on large datasets can take hours or days, which increases vulnerability to IoT cyber-attacks. ShieldIoT’s coreset-AI helps cut that time down to minutes.
The post ShieldIoT raises $7.4m to deploy coreset-AI for IoT cybersecurity appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six more stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876923/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876923/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of six new stable kernels: 5.10.82, 5.4.162, 4.19.218, 4.14.256, 4.9.291, and 4.4.293.  These kernels contain lots of
important fixes throughout the tree; users of those series should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876922/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876922/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T14:14:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (freerdp, gnome-boxes, gnome-connections, gnome-remote-desktop, guacamole-server, hydra, java-1.8.0-openjdk-aarch32, medusa, mingw-gstreamer1, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-base, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-good, php, pidgin-sipe, remmina, vinagre, and weston), openSUSE (kernel and netcdf), and SUSE (kernel and netcdf).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microchip adds edge compute dev tool for smart vision in IIoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471687</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/microchip-adds-edge-compute-dev-tool-for-smart-vision-in-iiot/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T13:11:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Second development tool in its smart embedded vision initiative for designers using its PolarFire RISC-V SoC FPGA simplifies edge-compute design in thermally challenging IIoT and factory automation environments.
The post Microchip adds edge compute dev tool for smart vision in IIoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling the hardware for the metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471678</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/enabling-the-hardware-for-the-metaverse/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T12:09:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How far are we in creating the hardware and software for enabling the metaverse that leading tech firms seem to want us to live in? Analyst firm IDTechEx provides a view of the key technologies and companies involved.
The post Enabling the hardware for the metaverse appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sensor fusion algorithm uses raw data for automotive models]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471672</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/sensor-fusion-algorithm-uses-raw-data-for-automotive-models/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T10:41:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BASELABS’ new Dynamic Grid algorithm takes high-resolution raw sensor data to provide a consistent, detailed environment model, and includes dynamic and static objects as well as free space estimation.
The post Sensor fusion algorithm uses raw data for automotive models appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논증이냐 아니냐: 고등학교와 대학 글쓰기의 차이]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82794</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82794"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T08:48:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대학에 입학하고 첫 작문 과제를 제출했을 때 받은 피드백을 기억하는가? 상당히 많은 이들이 당황스러운 경험을 한다. 공 들인 과제에 낮은 점수를 받은 것은 차치하고라도, 과제물에 적힌 교수의 코멘트는 대개 충격적이다. 대학에서 요구하는 글쓰기는 고등학교에서 요구하는 글쓰기와 완전히 다르기 때문이다. 그 차이의 핵심은 바로 ‘논증’에 있다. 고등학교 글쓰기: 요약과 의견  고등학교에서 요구하는 글쓰기란 대개 어떤 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사적 언어와 주관적 정당화]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222579383082</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222579383082"/>
        <updated>2021-11-26T06:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<비트겐슈타인은 “내가 어떤 것을 ‘S’라고 부른 다음에 내가 그것이 진짜 S인지 어떻게 아는가?”하는 것을 논의하고 있는 것이 아니다. 오히려 “내가 무엇을 ‘S’라고 부른 다음에 ‘S’에 의해서 의미하는 것을 내가 어떻게 아는가?” 하는 것을 논의하고 있다. 어떤 것을 S라고 잘못 생각하는 경우조차 나는 ‘S’의 의미를 알고 있어야만 한다. 이것이 비트겐슈타인이 사적 언어에서 불가능하다고 주장하는 것이다. 비트겐슈타인은 다음처럼 말한다. <오로지 우리 상상 속에 존재하는 어떤 일람표, 사전과 같은 것을 생각해 보자. 가령, 우리들은 사전에 의해서 낱말 X를 낱말 Y로 번역하는 것을 정당화할 수 있다. 그러나 이 일.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전두환 사망, "어두웠던 역사의 기억도 함께 떠나보내"자는 어느 언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82780</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82780"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T23:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[11월 23일 오전 제12대·13대 대통령을 지낸 전두환 씨가 사망했습니다. 전 씨는 12·12군사쿠데타를 일으켜 권력을 탈취한 뒤, 5.18민주화운동을 무자비하게 진압해 수많은 이들을 희생시켰으며 집권기간 내내 독재로 일관하며 시민들의 민주화 열망을 짓밟았습니다. 하지만 권력에서 물러나 죽음에 이르기까지 단 한 번도 과오를 사죄하지 않았습니다. 이처럼 역사 속에서 학살자이자 독재자로 평가받는 전 씨가 사망하자 언론은 관련 보도를 쏟아냈는데요. 민주언론시민연합은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Tips for Optimizing GUIs in Industrial Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=13734</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/5-tips-for-optimizing-guis-in-industrial-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T22:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial applications have traditionally involved analog buttons, switches, and dials to interact with a user. As you are aware, times are changing, and industrial application users now need rich graphical user interfaces. Many interfaces are built on top of embedded systems, which are quite powerful, but they are still resource-constrained systems. They may be resource-constrained … Continue reading 5 Tips for Optimizing GUIs in Industrial Applications
5 Tips for Optimizing GUIs in Industrial Applications first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 5.15.5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876861/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876861/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T21:52:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.15.5 stable kernel has been
released.  As usual, it contains lots of important fixes throughout the
kernel tree.  Users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual function calls in constructors and destructors (C++)]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0891/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0891/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In different programming languages, the behavior of virtual functions differs when it comes to constructors and destructors. Incorrect use of virtual functions is a classic mistake. Developers often use virtual functions incorrectly. In this article, we discuss this classic mistake. I suppose the reader is familiar with virtual functions in C++. Let's get straight to the point. When we call a virtual function in a constructor, the function is overridden only within a base class or a currently created class. Constructors in the derived classes have not yet been called. Therefore, the virtual functions implemented in them will not be called. Let me illustrate this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEC- Embedded Software Development Tools and Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=13741</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/cec-embedded-software-development-tools-and-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T17:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The tools and techniques developers use to design and build their systems can make the difference between success and failure. Tools and techniques are constantly evolving and to stay relevant and beat out the competition, it’s critical to be up to date on the latest and greatest. In this course, we will explore a wide … Continue reading CEC- Embedded Software Development Tools and Techniques
CEC- Embedded Software Development Tools and Techniques first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876852/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876852/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T14:29:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (busybox, getdata, and php), Mageia (couchdb, freerdp, openexr, postgresql, python-reportlab, and rsh), openSUSE (bind, java-1_8_0-openjdk, and kernel), SUSE (java-1_7_0-openjdk), and Ubuntu (icu).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: We’re thankful for smart cows]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9386</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-were-thankful-for-smart-cows/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T14:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Heading into the holiday weekend, Kevin and I share what we’re thankful for (mostly y’all, our sponsors, each other, and Thread), while also talking about the sad sale of Tile to Life360. We also discuss Clevr, Qeexo, and efforts to make AI accessible to people who can’t or don’t want to code. After that, I discuss my desire […]
The post Podcast: We’re thankful for smart cows appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[로티 - 실용주의와 직관적 실재론]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222578622391</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222578622391"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T10:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[진리는 언명 가능한 것, 그 이상이다. 고통은 두뇌 상태, 그 이상의 것이다. 물리학과 도덕적 책임 사이에 중대한 차이가 있다. 이런 주장을 해명하는 철학적 견해를 찾아야 한다. 이것이 <직관적 실재론자>의 주장이다. 그러나 실용주의자는 그러한 주장에 대한 직관을 갖는 것을 그만하자고 역설한다. 사람들은 서로 공통된 요소가 있으며, 대문자 철학은 그것을 추출해서 모두가 합리적으로 수용할 수 있는 논제나 중요한 문제를 구성할 수 있다고 직관적 실재론은 주장한다. 즉 진짜 해결해야 할 철학적 문제가 있다. 실용주의는 모든 인간의 공통된 본성 같은 것을 거부한다. 그런 것을 추구할 유용성도 없다. 다양한 담론들을 통약 가.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AP, 미국이 세계를 바라보는 시각을 결정한다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82763</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82763"/>
        <updated>2021-11-25T05:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한 국가 전체를 거의 혼자 취재해야 하는 상황에서 특파원들이 가장 먼저 해결해야 하는 기본적인 문제는 바로 무엇을 뉴스로 다룰 것인지 결정하는 것이다. AP에서 작성한 기사가 전 세계 주요 언론사들을 통해 나가기 때문에 AP 뉴스는 곧 국제 사회에서 의제를 설정하는 역할을 한다. AP 뉴스는 미국인은 물론 세계인이 세상을 바라보는 인식과 이해에 중대한 영향을 미친다. AP는 실제로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A gentle approach to AI and ML for all interested in the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9367</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/a-gentle-approach-to-ai-and-ml-for-all-interested-in-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T22:46:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often discuss Artificial Intelligence (AI) and Machine Learning (ML) here on the site and in our weekly IoT Podcast. And we should: These technologies take data from sensors and other inputs, turning that data into actionable “smarts”. But for many, ML and AI are nebulous terms, akin to some dark magic taught at Hogwarts […]
The post A gentle approach to AI and ML for all interested in the IoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876799/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876799/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T16:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (openjdk-17), Fedora (libxls, roundcubemail, and vim), openSUSE (bind, java-1_8_0-openjdk, and redis), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, krb5, mailman:2.1, openssh, and rpm), Scientific Linux (kernel, krb5, openssh, and rpm), SUSE (bind, java-1_8_0-openjdk, redis, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (bluez).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Need a HomeKit sensor and light strip for a closet? Here are some suggestions.]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9359</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/need-a-homekit-sensor-and-light-strip-for-a-closet-here-are-some-suggestions/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T13:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Michael called in to our voicemail hotline with a closet question. More specifically, he’s looking for a HomeKit solution to enable light strips in his closets. The idea is to have the light strips turn on when he opens the door, and Michael is looking for some sensor […]
The post Need a HomeKit sensor and light strip for a closet? Here are some suggestions. appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What does Matter mean to you?]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/fa3bb53a7793</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/what-does-matter-mean-to-you-fa3bb53a7793?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T09:04:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Matter Series #1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Sovani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시신 투척 사건이 아니라 ‘교제 살인’, ‘스토킹 살인’이다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82752</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82752"/>
        <updated>2021-11-24T06:29:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여성 두 명이 교제했던 남성에 의해 살해당했다. 11월 17일 30대 남성이 전 연인인 여성을 흉기로 찌른 뒤 베란다에서 내던져 살해한 혐의로 체포됐다. 여성이 이별을 요구하자 죽인 것으로 알려졌다. 이틀 뒤인 11월 19일엔 옛 연인이 휘두른 흉기에 찔려 여성 한 명이 사망했다. 이 여성은 스토킹 피해를 호소해 신변보호를 받던 중이다. 108명. 2016년부터 3년간 ‘법적으로 결혼하지 않은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이클 데빗]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222577024933</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222577024933"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T22:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[왜 데빗(M. Devitt)이 계속 책을 쓰지 않는가 생각하다가 그의 나이를 살펴보니 벌써 83세이다. 나는 그가 이렇게 늙었다고 전혀 생각하지 못했다. 내가 데빗의 책을 열심히 수집한 것이 2000년 초 같은데, 내 시간 관념이 여전히 거기에 머무르고 있다. 게다가 이 당시에 전개되었던 분석철학이 오늘날 전개되는 양상보다 더 흥미롭다고 느낀다. 아마 이것이 바로 과거를 살고 있는 인간이 보여주는 전형적 모습일 것이다. 자기에게 친숙한 것을 좋아하는 그러한 경향 말이다. 그러나 어떤 공통적 주제 없이 산만하게 전개되는 철학적 활동보다는 그 당시에 여러 철학자들의 공통적 논의 주제가 되었던 실재론, 진리, 의미에 대한 논의가 더 철.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A variety of errors in C# code by the example of CMS DotNetNuke: 40 questions about the quality]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0890/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0890/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, we discuss C# code quality and a variety of errors by the example of CMS DotNetNuke. We're going to dig into its source code. You're going to need a cup of coffee... DotNetNuke is an open-source content management system (CMS) written mainly in C#. The source code is available on GitHub. The project is part of the .NET Foundation. The project has its website, Twitter, YouTube channel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improve your development workflow with Interactive Canvas DevTools]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/improve-your-development-workflow-with-interactive-canvas-devtools.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/improve-your-development-workflow-with-interactive-canvas-devtools.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nick Felker, Developer Relations Engineer
    Interactive Canvas helps developers build multimodal apps for games, storytelling, and educational experiences on smart displays like the Nest Hub and Nest Hub Max. Setting up an Interactive Canvas app involves building a web app, a conversational model, and a server-based fulfillment to respond to voice commands. All three of these components need to be built out to test your apps using the simulator in the Actions Console. This works for teams who are able to build all three at once… but it means that everything has to be hooked up, even if you just want to test out the web portion of your app. In many cases, the web app provides the bulk of the functionality of an Interactive Canvas app. We recently published Interactive Canvas Dev…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using blockchain to share and monetize telecoms assets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471647</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/using-blockchain-to-share-and-monetize-telecoms-assets/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T17:08:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weaver Labs has created a software solution to enable sharing and monetization of telecom network infrastructure assets in a secure, open and interconnected network using blockchain technology in an internal cryptocurrency system.
The post Using blockchain to share and monetize telecoms assets appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876723/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876723/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T16:55:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (mbedtls), Red Hat (kernel and rpm), and Ubuntu (freerdp2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless BMS eliminates wires, adds intelligence to each battery cell]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471641</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/wireless-bms-eliminates-wires-adds-intelligence-to-each-battery-cell/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T15:29:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wireless battery management system (BMS) from Dukosi puts chip and embedded software on each battery cell to enable ‘edge intelligence’ for safer and better performance batteries.
The post Wireless BMS eliminates wires, adds intelligence to each battery cell appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Presenting the Advantages of ESP32-S3-BOX, Espressif’s AI Voice Development Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/56852737e229</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/presenting-the-advantages-of-esp32-s3-box-espressifs-ai-voice-development-kit-56852737e229?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:01:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Espressif Systems has recently released an AI voice development kit dubbed ESP32-S3-BOX, based on ESP32-S3 Wi-Fi + Bluetooth 5 (LE) SoC. It…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amey Inamdar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The unbearable fussiness of the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9356</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/the-unbearable-fussiness-of-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we head into another gifting season and more and more connected devices make their way onto gift guides, I want to offer a cautionary note. The smart home is like a cat — mostly self-sufficient and nice to have, but also possessing a mind of its own that can lead to frustration and confusion […]
The post The unbearable fussiness of the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A preview of Amazon's AL2022 distribution]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876696/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876696/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T13:51:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazon has announced
a preview release of its upcoming AL2022 distribution.  The company plans
to support AL2022 for five years after its release.


	AL2022 uses the Fedora project as its upstream to provide customers
	with a wide variety of the latest software, such as updated
	language runtimes, as part of quarterly releases. In addition,
	AL2022 has SELinux enabled and enforced by default.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[종부세 폭탄론이 새빨간 거짓말인 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82744</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82744"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T10:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[종합부동산세(종부세) 고지서가 발부되자 올해도 어김없이 대다수 언론이 ‘세금폭탄’ 프레임을 쏟아내고 있다. 종부세가 생긴 지 15년이 지났건만 언론의 ‘세금폭탄’ 타령은 그칠 줄을 모른다. 하지만 과거에도, 지금도 종부세는 ‘세금폭탄’이 아니다.  언론은 15년째 ‘폭탄타령’ 정부 발표에 따르면 2021년 주택분 종부세 고지 인원은 94.7만 명이고, 세액은 5.7조 원이다. 국민의 98%는 종부세 과세대상이 아닌 것이다. 2%에 해당하는 종부세 과세대상 중에서도 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[헌재의 안으로 굽은 팔: 법관 임성근 탄핵심판 사건 (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82735</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82735"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T09:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[판사 출신이 8명, 그 중에서도 고법부장이나 법원장급의 경력자가 6명이나 자리하고 있는 헌법재판소가 마찬가지로 그 경력 사다리를 따라가고 있는 엘리트 법관을 파면시킬 수 있을까? 법원은 유달리 선례와 관행에 집착한다. 법원의 현재는 법원의 과거이자 동시에 법원의 미래다. 고법부장 승진을 목전에 둔 수석부장판사가 ‘휘하의’ 법관이 작성한 판결문에 ‘빨간펜’ 첨삭지도를 하였다면 그것은 선배 수석부장판사로부터 배운 것이자 후임의 수석부장판사가 따라 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocket article: How to implement and use `.noinit` RAM]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/noinit-memory</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/noinit-memory"/>
        <updated>2021-11-23T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This pocket article will describe how a non-initialized region of memory works,
how to implement it, and how it can be used in a typical embedded system.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Metcalfe’s Law for Network Effects, and Towards a Better Model]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2573</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/metcalfes-law-network-effects-better-model-cold-start-problem/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T21:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The following is an excerpt from the book The Cold Start Problem: How to Start and Scale Network Effects by Andrew Chen. Copyright © 2021 by Andrew Chen. Published on Future/ a16z, with permission from Harper Collins, an imprint of HarperCollins Publishers. A core pillar in the study of network effects is Metcalfe’s Law, where... Read More
The post Beyond Metcalfe’s Law for Network Effects, and Towards a Better Model appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876661/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876661/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second 5.16 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Nothing especially noteworthy stands out for the last
week, it all felt pretty normal for a rc2 week".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Student Leader Promotes Neurodiversity Awareness in Brazil and Beyond]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdsc-lead-joao-in-brazil.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/gdsc-lead-joao-in-brazil.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T18:17:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rodrigo Hirooka, Regional Lead for Brazil Developer Communities
           
Perceiving that one is not like everyone else can be painful. Yet, the experience can also be illuminating. As a child in Brazil, João Victor Ipirajá, lead of the Google Student Developer Club (GDSC) at the Federal Institute of Science and Technology of Ceará (IFCE), knew he was different. He often felt overwhelmed by physical sensations and missed social cues. When he was eventually diagnosed as being on the autistic spectrum, he was actually relieved. Far from being a limitation, the realization gave him a new perspective on his intellectual strengths—such as his ability to perceive mathematical concepts in a highly visual way and his capacity for logical thinking and computer programming. “I was reborn…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876655/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876655/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firebird3.0, libmodbus, and salt), Fedora (js-jquery-ui and wordpress), Mageia (arpwatch, chromium-browser-stable, php, rust, and wireshark), openSUSE (barrier, firefox, hylafax+, opera, postgresql12, postgresql13, postgresql14, and tomcat), SUSE (ardana-ansible, ardana-monasca, crowbar-openstack, influxdb, kibana, openstack-cinder, openstack-ec2-api, openstack-heat-gbp, openstack-heat-templates, openstack-horizon-plugin-gbp-ui, openstack-keystone, openstack-neutron-gbp, openstack-nova, python-eventlet, rubygem-redcarpet, rubygem-puma, ardana-ansible, ardana-monasca, documentation-suse-openstack-cloud, openstack-ec2-api, openstack-heat-templates, python-Django, python-monasca-common, rubygem-redcarpet, rubygem-puma, firefox, kernel, postgresql, postgresql13, postgresql14, postgresql10, postgresql12, postgresql13, postgresql14, postgresql96, and samba), and Ubuntu (libreoffice).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876610/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876610/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T16:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.15.4,
5.14.21,
5.10.81, and
5.4.161 stable kernels have been released.
Each contains another set of important updates, but it's worth
noting that 5.4.161
hasn't been through the usual review process due to an amusing bit of
scripting confusion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kinetic offers IoT-enabled workers’ comp insurance]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9352</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/kinetic-offers-iot-enabled-workers-comp-insurance/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T14:00:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I saw the first instance of IoT being used in insurance outside of the auto industry. Nationwide Insurance and Kinetic, a seven-year-old maker of a wearable device that tracks worker movements, have launched a policy for workers’ compensation. Companies will buy the policy from Kinetic and deploy its wearable among their workforces. The goal […]
The post Kinetic offers IoT-enabled workers’ comp insurance appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노동감시 대응 가이드: 일하면서 감시받고 있다고 느낄 때]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82728</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82728"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T08:54:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘노동감시 대응 가이드’ 홈페이지에서 보기 (클릭!) PDF 다운하기 (클릭!) 노동감시 대응 사업단은 일터에서 진행되는 노동감시를 유형별로 분류하고 이에 대한 대응 방법을 소개하는 [노동감시 대응 가이드]를 발간 했습니다. 이번 가이드는 지난 2021년 8월 2일 발간한 [디지털 노동감시 실태조사 및 법제도 개선방안] 보고서를 바탕으로 노동감시와 관련된 여러 법제를 살펴보고 개별 노동자들이 각자의 현장에서 어떻게 대응할 수 있을지에 관한 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NoHat 21]]></title>
        <id>https://limitedresults.com/?p=1364</id>
        <link href="https://limitedresults.com/2021/11/nohat-21/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T08:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[20 November 2021, Bergamo The event Webpage here. My talk Conclusion Solid and high technical program, perfect organisation, fun people all around. Premium. Grazie a tutti!
The post NoHat 21 appeared first on LimitedResults.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LimitedResults</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[명예훼손, 네 가지 구제 방법과 그 한계]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82720</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82720"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T07:15:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[민법은 ‘명예훼손의 경우의 특칙'(제764조)으로 ‘타인의 명예를 훼손한 자에 대하여는 법원은 피해자의 청구에 의하여 손해배상에 갈음하거나 손해배상과 함께 명예회복에 적당한 처분을 명할 수 있다’고 규정한다. 언론중재 및 피해구제 등에 관한 법률은 정정보도, 반론보도, 사후보도 청구의 근거를 둔다. 또한, 판례는 인격권 침해를 이유로 한 방해배제청구권으로서 기사삭제청구권을 인정하고 있다. 즉, 피해자의 명예 회복을 위해 가해자(언론)가 할 수 있는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designated Initializers in C++20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/designated-init-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/designated-init-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Standard, new ways to initialize objects!
With C++20, we get a handy way of initializing data members. The new feature is called designated initializers and might be familiar to C programmers.
Let’s have a look at this small feature:
The basics
Designated Initialization is a form of Aggregate Initialization.
As of C++20, an Aggregate type::
is an array type or,
is a class type that:

has no private or protected direct non-static data members
has no user-declared or inherited constructors
has no virtual, private, or protected base classes
has no virtual member functions
In a basic form in C++20, you can write:
Type obj = { .designator = val, .designator = val2, ... };
// or
Type obj = { .designator { val }, .designator { val2 }, ... };


For example:
struct Point { 
    double x { 0.0 }…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major errors on this blog (and their corrections)]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/corrections/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/corrections/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here's a list of errors on this blog that I think were fairly serious. While what I think of as serious is, of course, subjective, I don't think there's any reasonable way to avoid that because, e.g., I make a huge number of typos, so many that the majority of acknowledgements on many posts are for people who e-mailed or DM'ed me typo fixes.
A list that included everything, including typos would both be uninteresting for other people to read as well as high overhead for me, which is why I've drawn the line somewhere. An example of an error I don't think of as serious is, in this post on how I learned to program, I originally had the dates wrong on when the competition programmers from my high school made money (it was a couple years after I thought it was). In that case, and many others, I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/live-immediately/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/live-immediately/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T23:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[THE WHOLE FUTURE LIES IN UNCERTAINTY: LIVE IMMEDIATELY. @subliming.jpg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks, Mario, but the code needs fixing — checking TheXTech]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0889/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0889/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's cool when enthusiastic developers create a working clone of a famous game. It's even cooler when people are ready to continue the development of such projects! In this article, we check TheXTech with PVS-Studio. TheXTech is an open implementation of the game from the Super Mario universe. TheXTech is the SMBX 1.3. game engine rewritten on C++. The original SMBX (Super Mario Bros. X) was written on Visual Basic 6 by Andrew Spinks in 2009. It allows to create levels from the elements of the Nintendo's Super Mario Bros games. TheXTech accurately reproduces the original game's behavior. It also includes optional bug fixes. It runs not only on Windows, but also on macOS, and Linux systems with x86, ARM or PowerPC processors. Some developers also ported it on 3DS and PS Vista The TheXTech developer — Vitaliy Novichkov (Wohlstand) — described the development process in detail on Habr. He also described the techniques he used to smooth out the differences when porting the project from VB6 to C++. There's a disclaimer on the GitHub page that explains why the source code is not in the best condition. It's because the original code is unstructured something fierce. Its fragments you'll see below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한류 – 한국의 문화경제와 대중문화의 파도 (번역)]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2811</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2021/11/21/korean-wave-hallyu/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-21T08:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국의 비즈니스, 문화, 국가 이미지에 한류는 그야말로 축복입니다. 1999년대부터 한류는 아시아 전역에서 가장 큰 문화적 현상으로 자리를 잡았습니다. 한류의 영향은 점점 엄청나게 커져 2004년 한국 GDP의 0.2%, 약 18억 7천만 불을 차지하였으며 2019년에는 약 123억 불로 한국 경제를 부양하고 있습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 범주의 초월적 연역으로 이행]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222574305908</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222574305908"/>
        <updated>2021-11-20T22:28:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<종합적 표상과 그 대상이 함께 만나는, 서로 필연적으로 관계 맺는, 그러니까 이를테면 서로 마주칠 수 있는 경우는 오로지 두 경우가 있을 수 있다. 대상이 표상을 가능하게 한 경우이거나 표상이 대상을 가능하게 한 경우이다. 앞의 경우라면, 그 양자의 관계맺음은 단지 경험적인 것이고, 그 표상은 결코 선험적으로 가능한 것일 수 없다. 현상에서 감각에 속하는 것을 살피는 경우가 바로 이에 해당한다. 그러나 뒤의 경우에는 표상 자신이 - 여기서는 의지에 의한 인과성은 문제삼지 않으므로 - 그것의 대상을 현존의 면에서 산출하지는 않는다. 그럼에도 표상은 그것에 의해서만 어떤 것을 하나의 대상으로 인식하는 것이 가능할 대상.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>