<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2021-07-13T20:07:24.953Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 90 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862781/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862781/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T18:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
90 of the Firefox browser is out.  The headline feature this time
around, beyond working links in PDF output, is a new
version of the SmartBlock feature which appears to have been designed
with a specific goal in mind: "Third-party Facebook scripts are
blocked to prevent you from being tracked, but are now automatically loaded
'just in time' if you decide to 'Log in with Facebook' on any
website."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tails 4.20 is out]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862771/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862771/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T16:22:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tails is a privacy focused distribution and Tails 4.20
"completely changes how to connect to the Tor network from
Tails" with the new Tor Connection assistant.

This new assistant is most useful for users who are at high risk of
physical surveillance, under heavy network censorship, or on a poor
Internet connection:


 It protects better the users who need to go unnoticed if using Tor
could look suspicious to someone who monitors their Internet connection
(parental control, abusive partner, school or work network, etc.).

 It allows people who need to connect to Tor using bridges to configure
them without having to change the default configuration in the Welcome
Screen.

 It helps first-time users understand how to connect to a local Wi-Fi
network.

 It provides feedback while connecting to Tor and helps troubleshoot
network problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862767/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862767/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T14:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (sogo), Fedora (libvirt), Gentoo (polkit), Mageia (binutils, freeradius, guile1.8, kernel, kernel-linus, libgrss, mediawiki, mosquitto, php-phpmailer, and webmin), openSUSE (bluez and jdom2), Oracle (kernel and xstream), Scientific Linux (xstream), and SUSE (kernel and python-pip).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s in my smart home in July 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8632</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/whats-in-my-smart-home-in-july-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T14:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been two years since I moved from my home in Austin to a rental home on Bainbridge Island outside of Seattle, and one year since I moved into my permanent home here. Which means I’ve had ample time to set up a new smart home infrastructure that will wow you with its awesomeness and […]
The post What’s in my smart home in July 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interfacing Modbus industrial sensors with an open source IIoT gateway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470329</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/interfacing-modbus-industrial-sensors-with-an-open-source-iiot-gateway/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T12:59:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial internet of things (IIoT) applications typically require an edge gateway to integrate Modbus peripherals and other devices, but implementing a gateway can be costly...
The post Interfacing Modbus industrial sensors with an open source IIoT gateway appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vediyappan Villali, Vijay Annamalaisamy and Sathya Durai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[표준시장단가: 이재명의 도전 vs. 건설업계의 저항]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81337</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/XssxEoKLWsw/81337"/>
        <updated>2021-07-13T04:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[경기도(도지사 이재명)는 2018년부터 모든 공공공사에 대하여 표준시장단가 적용을 시도하였다. 예산의 효율적 사용이 목적이었다. 공직기관으로서 지극히 당연한 처사다. 그러나 중앙정부(행정안전부, 국토교통부)와 도의회의 반대로 좌절되었다. 이들은 건설업계의 이해를 대변한다고 비판받기도 했다. 안타까운 일이다. 그럼에도 광역자치단체 최초로 시도된 경기도의 예산 낭비 방지 노력은, 정책관료와 지방의회가 어떻게 이익단체에 봉사하고 있는지를 일깨워 준 사례이기에 씁쓸하면서도 의미는 크다. 7월 6일 경기도는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standalone SWO]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33099</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/07/12/standalone-swo/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SWO (Single Wire Output) in ARM cores is probably one of the most under-used features. Which is surprising, because SWO can be very useful. In a nut shell: SWO is a single wire output pin/signal channel which can provide lots … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The conclusion of the 5.14 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861695/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861695/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.14 merge window closed with the 5.14-rc1
release on July 11.  By that time, some 12,981 non-merge changesets had
been pulled into the mainline repository; nearly 8,000 of those arrived
after the first LWN 5.14 merge-window summary
was written.  This merge window has thus seen fewer commits than its
predecessor, which saw 14,231 changesets before the 5.13-rc1 release.  That
said, there is still a lot of interesting work that has found its way into
the kernel this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논증적으로 생각하기 2]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222429584212</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222429584212"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T21:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* <우리는 도에 대해서 이야기할 수 없다. 왜냐하면, 도는 우리의 인식, 표상, 언어를 초월한 존재이기 때문이다.> 도에 대해서 이야기할 수 없다는 것은 도는 우리 언어를 초월한 존재라는 소리이다. 결국 이 논증은 <p이다. 왜냐하면 p이기 때문이다>의 형태를 보여주고 있다. 이러한 형태의 논증은 비형식적 차원에서 <선결 문제 요구의 오류>를 범하고 있다. https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222193341646 https://blog.naver.com/sellars/100120413120 그러나 형식적 차원에서 타당한 논증이다. 즉 전제가 참이라면, 결론은 반드시 참이며, 전제가 참인데 결론이 거짓인 경우가 불가능하다. 교과서적 논리학 책은 형식 논.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Private networks are coming. Businesses are not ready.]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8629</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/private-networks-are-coming-businesses-are-not-ready/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T19:15:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yes, it was just two weeks ago that I wrote about factories not yet deploying 5G networks. And that’s still true. But in the meantime, as companies investigate 5G, they are also assessing the validity of private networks — networks that don’t share traffic with the traditional cellular networks in the area. Such private networks would […]
The post Private networks are coming. Businesses are not ready. appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862673/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862673/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T15:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (djvulibre), Gentoo (connman, gnuchess, openexr, and xen), openSUSE (arpwatch, avahi, dbus-1, dhcp, djvulibre, freeradius-server, fribidi, gstreamer, gstreamer-plugins-bad, gstreamer-plugins-base, gstreamer-plugins-good, gstreamer-plugins-ugly, gupnp, hivex, icinga2, jdom2, jetty-minimal, kernel, kubevirt, libgcrypt, libnettle, libxml2, openexr, openscad, pam_radius, polkit, postgresql13, python-httplib2, python-py, python-rsa, qemu, redis, rubygem-actionpack-5_1, salt, snakeyaml, squid, tpm2.0-tools, and xstream), Red Hat (xstream), and SUSE (bluez, csync2, dbus-1, jdom2, postgresql13, redis, slurm_20_11, and xstream).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating the Go Memory Model]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/gomm</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/gomm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What changes should we make to Go's memory model? (Memory Models, Part 3)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solus 4.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862604/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862604/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T13:35:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.3
of the Solus "home computing" distribution has been released.  "This
release delivers new desktop environment updates, software stacks, and
hardware enablement."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공적인 것과 사적인 것]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222429105033</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222429105033"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T11:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[로티의 <우연성, 아이러니, 연대성>의 <서론>은 매우 매력적이다. (절판되었던 이 책이 <사월의 책>이라는 출판사에 의해 다시 출판되었다.) 로티에 의하면, 공적 영역과 사적 영역을 융합하거나 통합시키려는 시도는 이론적으로, 혹은 철학적으로 불가능하다. 왜냐하면 그러한 시도는 공통적 인간 본성을 주장하는데, 그런 것이 없기 때문이다. 오히려 그것은 역사적으로 문화적으로 구성된 것이다. 인간의 본성이나 본질에 대해서 로티는 역사주의 또는 유명론적 입장, 즉 비본질주의를 주장한다. 로티에 의하면, 역사주의에도 두 가지 경향이 있다. 하이데거나 푸코에서 볼 수 있듯이, 사적인 것, 즉 자아의 창조나 사적인.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEGGER and Analog Devices Collaboration Delivers Communication Solution for Industrial Ethernet-APL]]></title>
        <id>https://www.segger.com/news/segger-and-analog-devices-collaboration-delivers-communication-solution-for-industrial-ethernet-apl/</id>
        <link href="https://www.segger.com/news/segger-and-analog-devices-collaboration-delivers-communication-solution-for-industrial-ethernet-apl/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEGGER Microcontroller GmbH, a leading provider of development tools and software for embedded systems, today announced a collaboration with Analog Devices, Inc., a leading global high-performance semiconductor company that provides embedded engineers with a new solution for the development of industrial Ethernet applications including the new Ethernet-APL standard.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEGGER Microcontroller RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.14-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862566/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862566/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-12T02:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 5.14-rc1 and closed the
merge window for this development cycle:


	On the whole, I don't think there are any huge surprises in here,
	and size-wise this seems to be a pretty regular release too. Let's
	hope that that translates to a nice and calm release cycle, but you
	never know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Unexpected Article About Our Unicorn: Who Is the PVS-Studio Mascot?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0843/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/b6FkjZzcS5U/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio has a mascot that became inseparable from the brand - a unicorn. Lately we've been getting many questions about our magic steed: why the unicorn, why has he changed so much, does he have hooves, how come he doesn't wear pants, and how do we draw him. The answers are finally here, in this very article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some weekend stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862543/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862543/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T20:53:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.12.16,
5.10.49,
5.4.131,
4.19.197,
4.14.239,
4.9.275, and
4.4.275
stable kernels have been released.  Each contains a relatively small set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가비아의 도전: 호스팅 업체에서 클라우드 사업자로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81327</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/bDd-z-dm0ns/81327"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T19:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[가비아는 1999년 도메인과 호스팅 사업으로 사업에 첫발을 내디뎠다. 이후 호스팅 사업 확장과 홈페이지 제작, vIDC 사업 등 온라인 비즈니스를 하는 기업에게 필수적인 서비스를 주력으로 사업을 확장해 왔다. 중립적인 인터넷 회선 연동(IX: Internet eXchange)을 주력으로 하는 케이아이앤엑스(KINX), 보안 기업 엑스게이트 등의 인수를 통해 기존 사업 강화와 새로운 영역 진출이라는 두 마리 토끼를 잡으면서 사업을 전개하고 있다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Round MetaClockClock]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33065</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/07/11/round-metaclockclock/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T18:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been a while since my last MetaClockClock, and with the continued shortage of electronics on the market I had no chance to order new parts. But I still had some remaining parts, and with the modular design of … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국이 디디추싱 미국 상장 후 디디추싱 탄압과 규제 강화 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581842</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581842/%eb%94%94%eb%94%94%ec%b6%94%ec%8b%b1-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%83%81%ec%9e%a5-%ed%9b%84-%eb%94%94%eb%94%94%ec%b6%94%ec%8b%b1-%ed%83%84%ec%95%95%ea%b3%bc-%ea%b7%9c%ec%a0%9c%eb%a5%bc-%ea%b0%95%ed%99%94"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T14:48:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오피스 365 아웃룩 메일 저장위치 변경, PST 위치 및 OST 위치 변경 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581817</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581817/%ec%95%84%ec%9b%83%eb%a3%a9-%eb%a9%94%ec%9d%bc-%ec%a0%80%ec%9e%a5%ec%9c%84%ec%b9%98-%eb%b3%80%ea%b2%bd"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T11:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[지적 사기] 서문]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222427652627</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222427652627"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T06:43:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[소칼과 브리크몽이 말한다. <라캉, 크리스테바, 보드리야르, 들뢰즈와 같은 이름난 지식인들이 납득할 만한 설명도 없이 원래의 맥락에서 완전히 벗어난 과학적 개념을 써먹거나 (즉 한 영역에서 다른 영역으로 아무런 논증 없이 개념을 이식하거나) 과학에 문외한인 독자에게 이 개념을 끌어들이는 것이 타당하지에 대한 성찰은 고사하고, 개념의 정확한 뜻조차 밝히지 않고 과학적 개념과 어휘를 남용하기 일쑤였다는 사실을 보여주고 싶다.> 소칼과 브리크몽은 이들 지식인들의 책 전체가 엉터리라고 주장하는 것이 아니라고 분명하게 밝힌다. 그런데 나는 이들이 문제 삼고 있는 과학적 개념들뿐만 아니라, 저들 지식인들이 사용하는 핵.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윈도우 10 메이저 업데이트와 윈도우 10 수동 업데이트 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581793</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581793/%ec%9c%88%eb%8f%84%ec%9a%b0-10-%ec%88%98%eb%8f%99-%ec%97%85%eb%8d%b0%ec%9d%b4%ed%8a%b8-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T04:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[앱스토어 정책, 과연 중요할까? 누구에게, 얼마나? (번역)]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2614</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2021/07/11/app-store/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T03:24:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 10년 동안 논쟁이 아니었던 적이 없었습니다. 애플이 만든 앱스토어 정책은 말이죠. 그런데 요즘들어 그 논의가 급물살을 타는 듯 합니다. 미국에서는 일단 두 가지 법안(하나는 일견 합리적이지만 다른 하나는 그닥..) 이 상정되었습니다. 영국에서도 한참 논쟁 중이고, EU는 현재 상황이 용납되지 않음을 천명했습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10.0b4 is available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/4EX53HOlNa4/python-3100b4-is-available.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/4EX53HOlNa4/python-3100b4-is-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-11T01:48:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wow! A release on a Saturday? Do the release management team even rest? You better believe it, because this is the last of the planned beta releases. This means that the next pre-release will be the first release candidate of Python 3.10.0. Remember that our goal is to have no ABI changes after this beta and a few code changes as possible after 3.10.0rc1. 
The final release is closer and closer.... just a few more months!
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3100b4/
This is a beta preview of Python 3.10
Python 3.10 is still in development. 3.10.0b4 is the fourth and last of the beta release previews. Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their projects to support the new feature release.
W…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862487/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862487/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T23:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (gitlab, nodejs, openexr, php, php7, rabbitmq, ruby-addressable, and spice), Fedora (suricata), Gentoo (binutils, docker, runc, and tor), Mageia (avahi, botan2, connman, gstreamer1.0-plugins, htmldoc, jhead, libcroco, libebml, libosinfo, openexr, php, php-smarty, pjproject, and python), openSUSE (apache2, bind, bouncycastle, ceph, containerd, docker, runc, cryptctl, curl, dovecot23, firefox, graphviz, gstreamer-plugins-bad, java-1_8_0-openj9, java-1_8_0-openjdk, libass, libjpeg-turbo, libopenmpt, libqt5-qtwebengine, libu2f-host, libwebp, libX11, lua53, lz4, nginx, ovmf, postgresql10, postgresql12, python-urllib3, qemu, roundcubemail, solo, thunderbird, ucode-intel, wireshark, and xterm), and SUSE (permissions).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can you make your own devices that work with Amazon Sidewalk?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8621</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/can-you-make-your-own-devices-that-work-with-amazon-sidewalk/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T17:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast episode, Chris called in asking about Amazon’s Sidewalk network. He wants to know if he can make his own devices that work with Sidewalk now. Since this low-range, wide-area network only went live last month, it’s a little early for that. But soon, anyone with the right DIY skills […]
The post Can you make your own devices that work with Amazon Sidewalk? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윈도우 10 랜섬웨어 보호 폴더 접속 허용 앱 추가 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581780</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581780/%ec%9c%88%eb%8f%84%ec%9a%b0-10-%eb%9e%9c%ec%84%ac%ec%9b%a8%ec%96%b4-%eb%b3%b4%ed%98%b8-%ed%8f%b4%eb%8d%94-%ec%a0%91%ec%86%8d-%ed%97%88%ec%9a%a9-%ec%95%b1-%ec%b6%94%ea%b0%80-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T12:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[논증적으로 사유하기 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222426852633</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222426852633"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T10:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 논증이란 무엇인가? 논증은 전제와 결론, 혹은 주장과 그것에 대한 근거로 되어 있다. * 전제와 결론으로 된 논증을 구성해 보라. https://blog.naver.com/sellars/100055925694 * 모든 것을 설명하는 이론은 약점이 있다. 왜 그런가? <모든 것을 설명하는 이론은 약점이 있다. 왜냐하면 그 이론은 결코 반증 혹은 반박되지 않기 때문이다. 즉 그 이론을 정당하게 과학이론이라고 이야기할 수 없다.> * 포퍼는 마르크스 이론과 정신분석학의 이론을 사이비 과학이라고 주장한다. * 다음 글을 논증으로 요약해 보라. 비록 동물은 우리로 하여금 그들이 사고한다고 확신할 수 있게 해주는 어떤 일도 하지 않지만, 그럼에도 불구하고 그들의.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21년 연령별 인구통계에서 읽는 시대 변화 트렌드 3가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581756</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581756/21%eb%85%84-%ec%97%b0%eb%a0%b9%eb%b3%84-%ec%9d%b8%ea%b5%ac%ed%86%b5%ea%b3%84"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T10:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[불필요한 윈도우 10 기본앱 삭제 방법, 가벼운 윈도우 10 만들기 프로젝트]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581757</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581757/%ec%9c%88%eb%8f%84%ec%9a%b0-10-%ea%b8%b0%eb%b3%b8%ec%95%b1-%ec%82%ad%ec%a0%9c-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-07-10T06:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT News of the Week for July 9, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8618</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-july-9-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:17:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Solid-state lighting moves a bit further: Amber, a startup building solid-state silicon to control lighting, has signed a deal with Infineon to commercialize its next-generation lighting controller, Amber (which I profiled last year). Amber’s technology results in a smaller form factor for electrical infrastructure such as circuit breakers or switch boxes. But it’s pretty novel, which […]
The post IoT News of the Week for July 9, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Arti, a pure-Rust Tor implementation (Tor blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862329/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862329/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T18:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Tor project, which provides tools for  internet privacy and anonymity, has announced a rewrite of the Tor protocols in Rust, called Arti.  It is not ready for prime time, yet, but based on a grant from Zcash Open Major Grants (ZOMG), significant work is ongoing; the plan is "to try bring Arti to a production-quality client implementation over the next year and a half".  The C implementation is not going away anytime soon, but the idea is that Arti will eventually supplant it.  The project sees a number of benefits from using Rust, including:


For years now, we've wanted to split Tor's relay cryptography across multiple CPU cores, but we've run into trouble. C's support for thread-safety is quite fragile, and it is very easy to write a program that looks safe to run across multiple threads, but which introduces subtle bugs or security holes. If one thread accesses a piece of state at the same time that another thread is changing it, then your whole program can exhibit some truly confusing and bizarre bugs.

But in Rust, this kind of bug is easy to avoid: the same type system that keeps us from writing memory unsafety prevents us from writing dangerous concurrent access patterns. Because of that, Arti's circuit cryptography has been multicore from day 1, at very little additional programming effort.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Calendar API has changed how we manage API usage]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/fuV_ral0RcY/the-google-calendar-api-has-changed-how-we-manage-API-usage.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/fuV_ral0RcY/the-google-calendar-api-has-changed-how-we-manage-API-usage.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Charles Maxson, Developer Advocate 
 The Google Calendar API has changed how it manages API usage. Previously, queries were monitored and limited on a daily basis. As of May 2021, queries started to be monitored and limited on a per-minute basis. This introduces better behavior when your quota is exceeded, as requests are rate-limited until quota is available rather than failing all requests for the rest of the day. This also helps developers recognize issues around quota enforcements faster and shouldn't affect the performance of existing projects.  
To view your usage and quota limits, have a look in the Google API console. 
 
 To help you manage your quotas, we’ve put together a few helpful tips: 
 
Use push notifications instead of polling.  
If you cannot avoid polling, make sure you only poll when necessary (for example poll very seldomly at night).   
Make sure to use randomized timing so that requests from your users spread out evenly instead of creating bursts.  
Use incremental synchronization with sync tokens for all collections instead of repeatedly retrieving all the entries.  
Increase page size to retrieve more data at once by using the maxResults parameter.  
Update events when they change, avoid recreating all the events on every sync.  
Use exponential backoff for error retries to make rate-limiting work properly. 

For further details into managing quotas please review the manage quotas documentation. You can also find more details on error handling on the resolve errors documentation.  
To stay on top of news and updates around Google Workspace APIs and developer platform please sign up to our developer newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Syncing all the things]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861978/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861978/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T13:53:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Computing devices are wonderful; they surely must be, since so many
of us have so many of them.  The proliferation of computers leads directly
to a familiar problem, though: the files we want are always on the wrong
machine.  One solution is synchronization services that keep a set of files
up to date across a multitude of machines; a number of companies have
created successful commercial offerings based on such services.  Some of
us, though, are stubbornly resistant to the idea of placing our data in the
hands of corporations and their proprietary systems.  For those of us who
would rather stay in control of our data, systems like Syncthing offer a possible solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862299/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862299/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T13:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache2 and scilab), Fedora (chromium and perl-Mojolicious), Gentoo (inspircd, redis, and wireshark), and Mageia (fluidsynth, glib2.0, gnome-shell, grub2, gupnp, hivex, libupnp, redis, and zstd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘데이터 클라우드’란 무엇인가 (ft. 스노우플레이크, 구글)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81312</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/o57PlI8P7vo/81312"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T05:20:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[데이터 클라우드는 데이터셋이 전 세계에 사일로(Silo) 방식으로 쌓여 있고 클라우드 데이터 스토리지나 온프레미스 데이터 센터에 고립되어 있는 상황을 벗어나도록 사일로를 제거하고 이를 통합, 분석, 공유, 그리고 수익 창출을 하게 만들기 위한 것이다. ‘데이터 클라우드’란 무엇인가  데이터가 아무리 중요한 자산이라고 해도 실제 기업에서 겪는 문제는, 데이터가 대부분 조각나서 저장되어 있다는 조각화 문제인데 대부분 데이터가 제대로 목록으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반(反)신뢰 언론 시스템]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81305</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/99NXM5WooJ8/81305"/>
        <updated>2021-07-09T03:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국언론진흥재단, 로이터저널리즘연구소 등에서 매년 발표하는 언론신뢰 지표는 대다수 시민이 ‘국내 언론을 신뢰하지 않는다’고 명백히 표명하고 있음을 보여준다. 신문 산업의 경우 구독률과 언론사 홈페이지 방문율은 이미 유의미하지 않은 수준이다. 여러 지표에서도 드러나듯 신뢰의 가치 차원과 물적 차원에서 모두, 언론은 시민으로부터 외면받는 상황이다. 하지만 신문사 매출액은 2017년 3조 7천억, 2018년 3조 8천억, 2019년 3조 9천억 원으로 상대적으로 안정적이다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from App Engine webapp2 to Flask]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/r26LVyJohVo/migrating-from-app-engine-webapp2-to-flask.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/r26LVyJohVo/migrating-from-app-engine-webapp2-to-flask.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Wesley Chun (@wescpy), Developer Advocate, Google Cloud 

 Migrating web framework
  
The Google Cloud team recently introduced a series of codelabs (free, self-paced, hands-on tutorials) and corresponding videos designed to help users on one of our serverless compute platforms modernize their apps, with an initial focus on our earliest users running their apps on Google App Engine. We kick off this content by showing users how to migrate from App Engine's webapp2 web framework to Flask, a popular framework in the Python community.  
While users have always been able to use other frameworks with App Engine, webapp2 comes bundled with App Engine, making it the default choice for many developers. One new requirement in App Engine's next generation platform (which launched in 2018) …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[폴 그레이엄 – 최선을 다한다는 것(2/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72956</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/07/08/workhard2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=workhard2"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Paul Graham) 원문 보기 한계를 알기 위해서는 그 한계를 넘어서보는 수 밖에 없습니다. 지금 당신이 하는 일의 결과에 대한 감을 길러야 하며, 그 감은 언제 당신의 노력이 더 이상 효과가 없는지를 알게 해 줍니다. 여기서도 정직은 가장 중요한 가치입니다. 당신이 지금 게으름을 피고 있는지, 혹은 불필요하게 과한 노력을 하고 있는지를 판단해야 합니다. 혹시 당신이 과도한 노력에 대한 어떤 로망을 가지고 있다면, 그 로망은 버려야 합니다. 그 로망은 당신의 결과를 해칠 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[폴 그레이엄 – 최선을 다한다는 것(1/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72955</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/07/08/workhard1/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=workhard1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T22:54:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Paul Graham) 원문 보기 최선을 다한다는 것이 무슨 뜻인지는 누구나 아는 것처럼 보입니다. 학교를 다녀본 이들은 비록 자신들은 그렇게 열심히 하지 않았다 하더라도 그게 어떤 것인지를 대략은 알고 있습니다. 하지만, 내게 학생 때보다 그 의미를 이제 더 잘 알고 있냐고 묻는다면 당연히 그렇다고 답할겁니다. 일단, 당신이 무언가 위대한 일을 하고 싶다면, 당신은 최선을 다 해야 합니다. 어릴때는 나도 그 점을 확신하지 못했습니다. 학교에서 주어지는 일은 매우 다양하며, 어떤 일들은 최선을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[뒤쳐진 유럽에서 부는 퀵커머스 열풍, 10분 배송을 향한한 유럽 퀵커머스 스타트업들]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581718</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581718/%ec%9c%a0%eb%9f%bd-%ed%80%b5%ec%bb%a4%eb%a8%b8%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%80%ed%8a%b8%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T20:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Another misstep for Audacity]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862073/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862073/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T18:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it has often been said that there is no such thing as bad publicity,
the new owners of the Audacity
audio-editor project may beg to differ.  The project has only recently
weathered the controversies around its acquisition by the Muse Group,
proposed telemetry features, and imposition of
a new license agreement on its contributors.  Now, the posting of a new
privacy policy has set off a new round of criticism, with some accusing the
project of planning to ship spyware.    The
situation with Audacity is not remotely as bad as it has been portrayed,
but it is a lesson on what can happen when a project loses the trust of its
user community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PC는 작동하는데 PC 모니터 화면이 안나올 때 대처 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581733</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581733/pc-%eb%aa%a8%eb%8b%88%ed%84%b0-%ed%99%94%eb%a9%b4%ec%9d%b4-%ec%95%88%eb%82%98%ec%98%ac-%eb%95%8c-%ed%95%b4%ea%b2%b0-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T17:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CMake Part 1 &#8211; The Dark Arts]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/07/cmake-part-1-the-dark-arts/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/07/cmake-part-1-the-dark-arts/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T15:18:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In our previous post Why We Need Build Systems we examined the need for Build Systems in modern software development. In this post we will examine how to use CMake to mange the build process for a cross compilation project.</p>
<p>CMake can be described as a marmite application: you either love it or hate it. Here at Feabhas, we find ourselves falling in the latter category, despite the fact the CMake is widely used within the embedded and deeply embedded development [...] </p>
<div class="clearfix"></div>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2021/07/cmake-part-1-the-dark-arts/">CMake Part 1 &#8211; The Dark Arts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://blog.feabhas.com">Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas</a>.</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sticky Bits – Powered by Feabhas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862163/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862163/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T13:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (linuxptp), Fedora (kernel and php), Gentoo (bladeenc, blktrace, jinja, mechanize, privoxy, and rclone), Oracle (linuxptp, ruby:2.6, and ruby:2.7), Red Hat (kernel and kpatch-patch), SUSE (kubevirt), and Ubuntu (avahi).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: The IoT is a privacy nightmare and more 5G]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8615</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-the-iot-is-a-privacy-nightmare-and-more-5g/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine all of the potential problems associated with the internet of things, and then settle in, because I think we talk about all of them in this episode. We start by detailing research out of Northeastern University that shows old data isn’t deleted from hardware-reset Amazon Echo devices and then discuss a class action lawsuit […]
The post Podcast: The IoT is a privacy nightmare and more 5G appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving full MCU partition isolation: MPU management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470317</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/achieving-full-mcu-partition-isolation-mpu-management/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T12:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving full microcontroller (MCU) partition isolation is essential for achieving high security for MCU-based systems. Continuing a series on this complex topic, this article gets...
The post Achieving full MCU partition isolation: MPU management appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TPM 과 HSM]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222424607952</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222424607952"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T07:09:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft사가 차세대 Windows OS로 발표한 Windows 11에서, TPM(Trusted Platform Module) 기능이 기본 보안 기능으로 들어감에 따라, TPM에 대한 대중적인 관심이 높아 졌기에, 유사한 보안 기능을 제공하는 HSM(Hardware Security Module)과의 차이에 대하여 간략하게 설명하고자 합니다. 암호키와 같은 민감한 정보를 Hardware적으로 안전하게 보호하기 위한 Hardware Solution을HSM(Hardware Security Module) 이라고 부릅니다. HSM은 단어가 의미하듯이 Hardware 적인 장치를 사용하여 민감한 정보를 특별하고 안전한 장소에 보관하는 기능을 가진 Module 입니다. HSM의 모양은 구현 기능과 방식에 따라 다양할 수 있습니다. 예를 들면, “.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aepkoreanet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 8, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861535/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861535/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-08T01:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 8, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국가 간 빈부 양극화를 부추기는 코로나바이러스]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72951</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/07/07/how-covid-19-could-impede-the-catch-up-of-poor-countries-with-rich-ones/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=how-covid-19-could-impede-the-catch-up-of-poor-countries-with-rich-ones"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T22:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한때 코로나19가 가난한 나라보다 북미, 유럽의 부유한 나라에 더 큰 피해를 입히는 것처럼 보였습니다. 그러나 최근 코로나바이러스는 선진국을 추격하는 신흥국의 발목을 잡고 있습니다. 백신 공급의 글로벌 양극화와 2차, 3차 대유행으로 신흥국 경제는 회생의 기회를 찾지 못하고 있습니다. 과연 코로나 팬데믹은 글로벌 부의 양극화에 어떤 영향을 미칠까요? 이코노미스트지의 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rust for Linux redux]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862018/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862018/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T22:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 4, the Rust for Linux project
posted
another version of its patch set adding support for the language to the
kernel.  It would seem that the project feels that it is ready to be considered for
merging into the mainline.  Perhaps a bigger question lingers, though: is the kernel
development community ready for Rust?  That part still seems to be up in the air.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to easily migrate IoT devices on four networks to a mesh Wi-Fi router]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8581</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-easily-migrate-iot-devices-on-four-networks-to-a-mesh-wi-fi-router/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, John called in with a Wi-Fi upgrade question. He currently has four wireless networks (regular and guests) on both 2.4 GHzand 5 GHz frequencies using a single router. He’s thinking about upgrading to a Wi-Fi mesh network. John wants to know if he’ll have to reconfigure his IoT devices […]
The post How to easily migrate IoT devices on four networks to a mesh Wi-Fi router appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[깜짝 실적의 2분기 삼성전자 실적에도 삼성전자 주가가 떨어진 이유를 생각해 본다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581722</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581722/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%82%bc%ec%84%b1%ec%a0%84%ec%9e%90-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%ec%82%bc%ec%84%b1%ec%a0%84%ec%9e%90-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a path through the IoT security maze]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470352</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/building-a-path-through-the-iot-security-maze/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We caught up with CEO and a founder of Intrinsic ID, Pim Tuyls, to understand more about the world of PUF security, the challenges for...
The post Building a path through the IoT security maze appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four 5.x stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862045/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862045/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T15:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sasha Levin has released stable kernels 5.13.1, 5.12.15, 5.10.48, and 5.4.130.  They all contain a small set of
important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/862044/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/862044/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T15:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (glibc), Gentoo (doas, firefox, glib, schismtracker, and tpm2-tss), Mageia (httpcomponents-client), openSUSE (virtualbox), Red Hat (linuxptp), Scientific Linux (linuxptp), and Ubuntu (libuv1 and php7.2, php7.4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wyze Lock and Keypad review: Good value for the money but some quirks]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8591</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/wyze-lock-and-keypad-review-good-value-for-the-money-but-some-quirks/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T14:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s no lack of smart locks available on the market these days. Some will cost you $300 or more. So when Wyze introduced its Wyze Lock for a fraction of that price, I initially wrote it off. How good could a $107.98 smart lock be? After using one that Wyze loaned me, I found an […]
The post Wyze Lock and Keypad review: Good value for the money but some quirks appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoTSF Champion Award is Back in 2021 and Open for Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21206</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/iotsf-champion-award-is-back-in-2021-and-open-for-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T12:30:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're delighted to announce that applications for the prestigious IoT Security Foundation's Champion Award are now open and we're inviting you to apply. What's the award for? The IoT Security Foundation Champion Award celebrates exemplars of the security-minded organisations as part of its mission to ‘make it safe to connect’. Who can apply? OPEN]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡의 두 얼굴: 혁신인가, 착취인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81286</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/g3TxjUEHNJQ/81286"/>
        <updated>2021-07-07T08:05:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡은 올해(2021) 1분기 매출이 작년 국내 전자상거래 분야 시장점유율 1위인 네이버(약 1조 5억 원)의 3배가 넘는 수준인 42억 달러(약 4조 7천억 원)를 달성하는 등 급격한 성장세에 있습니다. 쿠팡에서 운영하는 배달앱인 쿠팡이츠 역시 시장진출 1년만에 배달앱 시장에서 비약적인 성장을 달성 중입니다. 하지만 이러한 외적 성장에 비해 마땅히 짊어져야 할 노동권 보장 등 사회적 책임에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 가짜뉴스는 실제로 사람들의 행동에 영향을 미쳤을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72942</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/07/06/covid19fakenews/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=covid19fakenews"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유니버시티 칼리지 더블린 심리학과의 클라라 그린 교수가 코로나19와 관련한 가짜뉴스의 영향을 실험한 결과를 정리한 글입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python attributes, __slots__, and API design]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861910/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861910/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T22:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion on the python-ideas mailing list touched on a number of
interesting topics, from the problems with misspelled attribute names
through the  design of security-sensitive interfaces and to the use of the
__slots__ attribute of objects.  The latter may not be all that
well-known (or well-documented), but could potentially fix the problem at
hand, though not in a backward-compatible way.  The conversation revolves
around the ssl module
in the standard library, which has  been targeted for
upgrades, more than once, 
over the years—with luck, the maintainers may find time for some upgrades relatively soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimized Vinyl Cutting G-Code Tool Path with DXF2GCODE]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32994</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/07/06/optimized-g-code-tool-path-for-vinyl-cutting-with-dxf2gcode/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T21:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[G-Code (or RS-274) is a widely used protocol for CNC machines. I have added vinyl cutting capabilities to the Shapeoko desktop CNC recently (see DIY Vinyl Cutting Drag Knife for Desktop CNC), however cutting vinyl with a drag knife is whole … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identifying AI security threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470299</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/identifying-ai-security-threats/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:45:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As artificial intelligence (AI) deployments continue to expand, securing AI is vital, but AI applications face multiple sophisticated threats. Artificial Intelligence (AI) advances foster various...
The post Identifying AI security threats appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Miller and Hsiao-Ying Lin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build and Heat Treatment of a Carbohydrate Source]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=10810</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2021/07/06/build-and-heat-treatment-of-a-carbohydrate-source/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T20:39:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this short tutorial, I will explain step by step, how you can build a solid carbohydrate source. You will find the bill of materials and all required tools. I will use SI units to simplify all measurements. This is no quick build, the substances require long reaction and activation times. For this reason, the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RF sensing is big news, so here are the other options]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8587</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/rf-sensing-is-big-news-so-here-are-the-other-options/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T19:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just spent a few hundred words explaining how Wi-Fi sensing would become the next big thing, but it’s not the only sensing technology coming out that will take advantage of radio waves to determine where people and things are in space. Two other technologies deserve a mention as well: radar and ultra-wideband. Ultra-wideband, or UWB, […]
The post RF sensing is big news, so here are the other options appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtuozzo VzLinux 8.4 Now Available]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861975/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861975/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T16:25:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Virtuozzo team has announced
the release of VzLinux 8.4; its fork of RHEL. "Thanks for noticing that we are fixing bugs so quickly (24 hours) and that you think VzLinux is stable and enterprise ready. To those who have asked if we will be following a similar path as CentOS, shifting its focus to Stream, the answer is: there are no plans for us to go this route, VzLinux will remain free to download, use and distribute.
See the release
notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The next big Wi-Fi standard is for sensing, not communication]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8579</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/the-next-big-wi-fi-standard-is-for-sensing-not-communication/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T15:51:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometime in 2024, the IEEE will unveil a new 802.11 standard that will bring new capabilities to everyone’s favorite wireless communication standard. But the upcoming 802.11bf standard isn’t for communication — it’s for sensing. The newest version of Wi-Fi layers on the ability to sense people or objects by using math to calculate how they disturb the […]
The post The next big Wi-Fi standard is for sensing, not communication appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is the vehicle automation numbering system useful?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470339</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/is-the-vehicle-automation-numbering-system-useful/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of a sequential numbering system (from 0 to 5) for vehicle automation has been widely misinterpreted to mean one level leads on to...
The post Is the vehicle automation numbering system useful? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colin Barnden</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming Language Memory Models]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/plmm</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/plmm"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to programming language memory models. (Memory Models, Part 2)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861972/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861972/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T14:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (python-django), Debian (libuv1, libxstream-java, and php7.3), Fedora (rabbitmq-server), Gentoo (glibc, google-chrome, libxml2, and postsrsd), openSUSE (libqt5-qtwebengine and roundcubemail), SUSE (python-rsa), and Ubuntu (djvulibre).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡이츠 마트 출시로 격화되는 한국 퀵커머스 현황을 정리해 보자]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581692</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581692/%ec%bf%a0%ed%8c%a1%ec%9d%b4%ec%b8%a0-%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8%ec%99%80-%ed%95%9c%ea%b5%ad-%ed%80%b5%ec%bb%a4%eb%a8%b8%ec%8a%a4-%ed%98%84%ed%99%a9"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T07:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[수술실 ‘내’ CCTV 설치, 찬성하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81273</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/ePP6zDWqyYk/81273"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T05:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[불법 의료, 중대 범죄가 끊이지 않는 수술실은 여전히 성역이다. 수술실은 내부 제보가 아니면 범죄와 사고를 알 수 없기 때문에 환자의 안전과 인권 보호에 있어 사각지대다. 수술실에 CCTV 설치를 의무화하자는 법안이 19대 국회부터 발의됐지만 21대 국회까지도 정치권의 의사 눈치 보기로 제자리에 있다. 만연한 무자격자 대리수술과 성범죄 실상은 어제오늘의 얘기가 아님에도 의료계는 자정 노력하겠다는 말로 국민의 분노를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing ESP Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/7d85a1383d21</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/the-esp-journal/introducing-esp-insights-7d85a1383d21?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T03:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are announcing ESP Insights.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kedar Sovani</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연도별 클라우드 시장 규모 및 클라우드 시장 점유율 추이(20년 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581688</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581688/%ed%81%b4%eb%9d%bc%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5-%ea%b7%9c%eb%aa%a8-%eb%b0%8f-%ed%81%b4%eb%9d%bc%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T00:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in June]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/june-2021-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/june-2021-roundup"/>
        <updated>2021-07-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
June.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제프 베조스가 세운 아마존 제국을 설명하는 7개 차트]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581677</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581677/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%a0%9c%ea%b5%ad%ec%9d%84-%ec%84%a4%eb%aa%85%ed%95%98%eb%8a%94-7%ea%b0%9c-%ec%b0%a8%ed%8a%b8"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T18:33:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Strategies for balancing series connected supercapacitors]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470342</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/strategies-for-balancing-series-connected-supercapacitors/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T15:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Supercapacitors generally operate at low voltages of about 2.7 V. To achieve higher operating voltages, it is necessary to build up a cascade of SC...
The post Strategies for balancing series connected supercapacitors appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>René Kalbitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Bye-bye bdflush()]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861431/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861431/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T15:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The addition of system calls to the Linux kernel is a routine affair; it
happens during almost every merge window.  The removal of system calls,
instead, is much more uncommon.  That appears likely to happen
soon, though, as discussions proceed on the removal of bdflush().
Read on for a look at the purpose and history of this obscure system call and to
learn whether you will miss it (you won't).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861906/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861906/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T15:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (electron11, electron12, istio, jenkins, libtpms, mediawiki, mruby, opera, puppet, and python-fastapi), Debian (djvulibre and openexr), Fedora (dovecot, libtpms, nginx, and php-league-flysystem), Gentoo (corosync, freeimage, graphviz, and libqb), Mageia (busybox, file-roller, live, networkmanager, and php), openSUSE (clamav-database, lua53, and roundcubemail), Oracle (389-ds:1.4, kernel, libxml2, python38:3.8 and python38-devel:3.8, and ruby:2.5), and SUSE (crmsh, djvulibre, python-py, and python-rsa).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wearable demonstrates contactless payment design approach]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470336</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/wearable-demonstrates-contactless-payment-design-approach/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T14:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chipmakers are providing major IoT building blocks to wearable design developers to support contactless payments using biometrics data. A screenless wearable device interprets human gestures...
The post Wearable demonstrates contactless payment design approach appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Majeed Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darktable 3.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861844/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861844/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T13:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 3.6
of the Darktable raw photo editor has been released.  "The darktable
team is proud to announce our second summer feature release, darktable
3.6. Merry (summer) Christmas!  This is the first of two releases this year
and, from here on, we intend to issue two new feature releases each year,
around the summer and winter solstices."  The list of new features
is long, including a new color-balance module, a "censorize" module for
partial pixelization of images, a new demosaic algorithm, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21년 미국 스트리밍 점유율,  넷플릭스가 지고 HBO가 뜨다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581667</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581667/21%eb%85%84-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%a6%ac%eb%b0%8d-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T11:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[구글 머신러닝 클라우드, ‘버텍스 AI’로 무장하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81261</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/bh3qzBUB5qY/81261"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T05:38:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[올해 구글IO에서는 ‘버텍스 AI(Vertex AI)’라는 새 이름으로 그동안 키워왔던 구글 클라우드 기반의 머신러닝 개발 및 배포, 운영 플랫폼을 내놓았다. 일반적으로 이러한 플랫폼을 서비스로서의 머신러닝(MLaaS, Machine Learning As A Service)로 클라우드컴퓨팅서비스의 일부로서 머신러닝 도구를 제공하는 서비스이다. 구글 클라우드 외에 AWS사의 세이지메이커(SageMaker)나 MS 애저의 애저 ML 스튜디오가 현재 경쟁을 펼치고 있다. ‘서비스로서의 머신러닝’은 고객이 내부 조직에서 머신러닝 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존 창업자 제프 베조스의 신뢰 구축 방법 4가지, 간단하지만 수많은 연구에서 입증된 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581665</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581665/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%b0%bd%ec%97%85%ec%9e%90-%ec%a0%9c%ed%94%84-%eb%b2%a0%ec%a1%b0%ec%8a%a4%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%a0%eb%a2%b0-%ea%b5%ac%ec%b6%95-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95-4%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80-%ea%b0%84"/>
        <updated>2021-07-05T03:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Day in the Life of PVS-Studio Developer, or How I Debugged Diagnostic That Surpassed Three Programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0842/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/b04mjxg6RWk/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static analyzers' primary aim is to search for errors missed by developers. Recently, the PVS-Studio team again found an interesting example proving the power of static analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유통별 수수료 및 유통업체별 판매 수수료 정리, 가장 판매 수수료가 높은 유통은?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581644</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581644/%ec%9c%a0%ed%86%b5%eb%b3%84-%ec%88%98%ec%88%98%eb%a3%8c-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%9c%a0%ed%86%b5%ec%97%85%ec%b2%b4%eb%b3%84-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4-%ec%88%98%ec%88%98%eb%a3%8c"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T13:43:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빅토리아 시크릿 전략, 섹시를 버리고 다양성을 수용한 빅토리아 시크릿 변신은 성공할까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581613</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581613/%eb%b9%85%ed%86%a0%eb%a6%ac%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%9c%ed%81%ac%eb%a6%bf-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5-%ec%84%b9%ec%8b%9c%eb%b3%b4%eb%8b%a4-%eb%8b%a4%ec%96%91%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T05:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“초당 6개 이상의 택배”를 토해내는 컨베이어벨트]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=81956</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Economic_View/~3/HAStrybrfMA/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-04T04:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By Item is held by John Oxley Library, State Library of Queensland., Public Domain, Link 노동강도의 증대는 같은 시간 내의 노동력 지출의 증가를 의미힌다. 그러므로 노동강도가 보다 높은 노동일은 노동강도가 보다 낮은 노동일에 비해서, 비록 각각의 노동일은 같다고 하더라고, 더욱 많은 양의 생산물로 체화된다. [중략] 그리하여 노동일의 길이가 불변인 경우, 강도가 높아진 하루의 노동은 증대된 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Text Broadcast of CppCast 298: SonarSource Analysis Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0841/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/Ngcla5fQTpE/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Episode 298 of CppCast was recorded on May 5th, 2021. On this episode, Rob Irving and Jason Turner are joined by Loïc Joly, who talks about SonarSource static analysis tools. Also, they discuss Visual Studio 2019 STL, GCC 11.1 updates and Meeting C++ survey results.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[분기별 미국 자동차 판매량과 점유율, 현대기아차 미국 점유율이 처음으로 10%를 넘다(21년 2분기 업데이트)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581595</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581595/%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0%eb%b3%84-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%9e%90%eb%8f%99%ec%b0%a8-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89-%eb%b0%8f-%ed%98%84%eb%8c%80%ea%b8%b0%ec%95%84%ec%b0%a8-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2021-07-03T04:35:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[분기 20만대 시대를 연 2분기 테슬라 판매량 , 하지만 기장 기대에는 미치지 못하다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581580</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581580/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89"/>
        <updated>2021-07-03T00:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for July 2, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8577</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-july-2-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T23:50:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New gesture sensor sees a bit farther: Maxim Integrated has announced a new infrared-based gesture detection sensor that can see from about 8 inches to 16 inches away. Maxim imagines the sensor, which comes encased in glass, being used for gesture detection on screens in automotive or home environments. It could become especially helpful in cars, […]
The post IoT news of the week for July 2, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[photostream 126]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/photos/126.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/photos/126.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T21:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bacharach, Rhineland-Palatinate, Germany (2016)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Assistant Recap Google I/O 2021]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/OEBr3GBWud0/assistant-recap-google-io-2021.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/OEBr3GBWud0/assistant-recap-google-io-2021.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T17:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Written by: Jessica Dene Earley-Cha, Mike Bifulco and Toni Klopfenstein, Developer Relations Engineers for Google Assistant
     
Now that we’ve packed up all of the virtual stages from Google I/O 2021, let's take a look at some of the highlights and new product announcements for App Actions, Conversational Actions, and Smart Home Actions. We also held a number of amazing live events and meetups that happened during I/O - which we’ll summarize as well. 
  
App Actions
  
App Actions allows developers to extend their Android App to Google Assistant. For our Android Developers, we are happy to announce that App Actions is now part of the Android framework. With the introduction of the beta shortcuts.xml configuration resource and our latest Google Assistant Plug App Actions is moving closer …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비비고 만두는 어떻게 미국인 입맛을 사로 잡았을까? CJ제일제당 비비고 만두 사례]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581543</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581543/cj%ec%a0%9c%ec%9d%bc%ec%a0%9c%eb%8b%b9-%eb%b9%84%eb%b9%84%ea%b3%a0-%eb%a7%8c%eb%91%90-%ec%82%ac%eb%a1%80"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T15:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarking OpenCV on STM32 MCUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470282</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/benchmarking-opencv-on-stm32-mcus/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T14:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenCV is focused primarily on high-performance computing platforms/microprocessors, but it can execute several types of image processing applications on MCUs.
The post Benchmarking OpenCV on STM32 MCUs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Bondarev and Alexander Kalmuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The first half of the 5.14 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861248/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861248/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T13:58:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of this writing, just under 5,000 non-merge changesets have been pulled
into the mainline repository for the 5.14 development cycle.  That is less
than half of the patches that have been queued up in linux-next, so it is
fair to say that this merge window is getting off to a bit of a slow
start.  Nonetheless, a fair number of significant changes have been merged.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861679/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861679/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T13:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (ansible and seamonkey), openSUSE (go1.15 and opera), Oracle (kernel and microcode_ctl), and Red Hat (go-toolset-1.15 and go-toolset-1.15-golang).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Test solutions bolster security in IoT designs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470308</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/test-solutions-bolster-security-in-iot-designs/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T11:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The growing threat of cyberinfrastructure intrusions from hostile actors is leading to the creation of new security testing mechanisms for IoT software and hardware. The...
The post Test solutions bolster security in IoT designs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Majeed Ahmad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알림]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222417720302</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222417720302"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T07:29:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<비트겐슈타인과 선>에 링크를 달았던 댓글이 삭제되어 그 곳을 찾아갈 수 없으니, 이 글에 다시 비밀댓글로 그 곳을 가르쳐 주면 될 것입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이동훈·엄성섭 금품수수 의혹, 조선일보·TV은 왜 침묵하는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81250</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/DJV1LXvjOMc/81250"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T05:52:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[현직 부장검사의 청탁금지법 위반 혐의를 수사하던 경찰이 언론인 2명을 입건했다는 보도가 6월 29일 나왔습니다. 윤석열 전 검찰총장 대변인을 맡았던 이동훈 전 조선일보 논설위원과 TV조선 엄성섭 앵커입니다. 혐의 내용이 사실이라면 현직 언론인 신분으로 금품을 수수한 중대한 사건입니다. 민주언론시민연합은 두 언론인의 청탁금지법 위반 혐의 의혹을 정리하고, 언론이 이번 사건을 어떻게 보도하고 있는지 확인했습니다. 이동훈·엄성섭 금품수수 의혹 먼저 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사면과 여론조작: 언론이 사랑한 어느 피고인]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81245</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/O7RTUNStL38/81245"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T04:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어느 피고인이 있다. 뇌물공여 등으로 형이 확정되었고, 확정되기 전과 후로 회계부정, 마약관련법률위반 등 또다른 사건으로 기소되어 재판을 받고 있는 사람이다. 죄와 벌 그리고 사면   그 피고인은 2017. 2. 28. 구속기소되어 2017. 8. 25. 징역 5년 및 추징을 선고받았고, 이후 2018. 2. 5. 징역 2년6월, 집행유예 4년, 일부 무죄를 선고받고 풀려났으나, 2019. 8. 29. 대법원에서 파기환송되었고, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크론 주가 하락 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581551</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581551/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ed%95%98%eb%9d%bd-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2021-07-02T00:19:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[꿈을 꾸는 동안 그 꿈을 묘사할 수 있다면]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72934</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/07/01/m-lucid/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-lucid"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T22:54:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(노틸러스, Jim Davis) 원문 보기 꿈은 매력적이지만 그만큼 쉽지 않은 연구 대상입니다. 지그문트 프로이트와 칼 융은 일찍이 꿈의 의미와 중요성을 밝혀 이름을 날렸지만, 뇌를 관찰하는 기술이 훨씬 발달한 오늘날에도 실제로 꿈을 꿀 때 뇌에서 어떤 일이 벌어지는지 파악하기는 쉽지 않은 일입니다. 실험 대상이 아침에 잠에서 깨기를 기다리는 연구자들은 “급속 망각”과 싸워야 합니다. 꿈을 꾸는 대상을 바로 깨우는 방법도 있지만, 이 경우 수면 연구실을 따로 만들어야 하며 이는 큰 비용이 듭니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kuhn: It Matters Who Owns Your Copylefted Copyrights]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861566/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861566/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T17:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bradley Kuhn has posted a
lengthy missive on the Software Freedom Conservancy blog about the
hazards of distributed copyright ownership.


	As a result, in debates about copyright ownership, discussions of
	what policy contributors want regarding the fruits of their labor
	is sadly moot. Without a clear, organized mitigation strategy to
	assure that FOSS contributors keep their own copyrights, a project
	(such as GCC or glibc) that switches from a standing “(nearly) all
	copyrights assigned to a charity” model to a plain Developer
	Certificate of Origin (DCO) or naked inbound=outbound contributor
	arrangement will, after a period of years, mostly likely to have
	copyrights that are primarily held by the employers of the most
	prolific contributors, rather than by the contributors themselves.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing artworks to life with AR]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/CHDtlghiMNg/bringing-artworks-to-life-with-ar.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/CHDtlghiMNg/bringing-artworks-to-life-with-ar.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Richard Adem, UX Engineer at Google Arts & Culture 
   
What is Art Filter?
  
One of the best ways to learn about global culture is by trying on famous art pieces using Google’s Augmented Reality technology on your mobile device. What does it feel like to wear a three thousand year old necklace, put on a sixteenth century Japanese helmet or don pearl earrings and pose in a Vermeer? 
Google Arts & Culture have created a new feature called Art Filter allowing everyone to learn about culturally significant art pieces from around the world and put themselves inside famous paintings, normally safely displayed in a museum. 
We teamed up with the  MediaPipe team, which offers cross-platform, customizable ML solutions to combine ML with rendering to generate stunning visuals. 
Working c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Core scheduling lands in 5.14]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861251/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861251/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T15:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The core scheduling feature has been under
discussion for over three years.  For those who need it, the wait
is over at last; core scheduling was merged for the 5.14 kernel release.
Now that 
this work has reached a (presumably) final form, a look at why this feature
makes sense and how it works is warranted.  Core scheduling is not for
everybody, but it may prove to be quite useful for some user communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Follower Reads]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/follower-reads.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/follower-reads.html"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T14:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you are using Leaders and Followers, you can use Follower Reads to
      achieve better throughput and lower latency. However there is always a
      replication lag between the leader and the followers, so you may need to
      take action to preserve consistency.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Amazon’s Halo health push and more Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8572</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-amazons-halo-health-push-and-more-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T13:00:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Any Amazon Halo subscriber can try Amazon’s Movement Health service now, so Kevin and I explain what it is and what Amazon’s decisions around the Halo fitness tracker signal about the company’s interest in healthcare. We then cover the good news that Google will support connected Nest devices with security updates for up to five […]
The post Podcast: Amazon’s Halo health push and more Matter appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861521/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861521/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T12:16:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (htmldoc, ipmitool, and node-bl), Fedora (libgcrypt and libtpms), Mageia (dhcp, glibc, p7zip, sqlite3, systemd, and thunar), openSUSE (arpwatch, go1.15, and kernel), SUSE (curl, dbus-1, go1.15, and qemu), and Ubuntu (xorg-server).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[하지 않은 질문, 받아야 할 질문: 윤석열 출마 선언 관련 보도 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81224</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/7bXwBPZ9fXA/81224"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T08:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 전 검찰총장은 6월 29일 기자회견을 열고 제20대 대통령 선거 출마를 선언했습니다. 문재인 정부에 대한 비판과 함께 정권교체라는 목표를 제시한 윤 전 총장은 회견문 발표 후 20개 남짓 질문을 받아 답변도 했습니다. 이날 기자회견은 많은 언론의 관심 속에 관련 보도도 쏟아졌습니다. 민주언론시민연합은 윤 전 총장이 대선출마 기자회견에서 받은 질문과 6월 29일 지상파 3사와 종합편성채널 4사 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미래의 예능 PD에게: 고찬수 PD 인터뷰]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81207</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/Oe4c-8zUJS8/81207"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T06:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“안녕하세요, 저는 KBS 예능PD 고찬수입니다. 1995년 KBS에 입사를 했으니 벌써 20년이 넘게 예능 콘텐츠 제작 일을 하고 있네요.” 27년차 예능 베테랑 고찬수 PD는 KBS에서 웹드라마와 MCN 사업을  진행하기도 했다. IT 분야에도 관심이 많아[인공지능 콘텐츠혁명], [스마트TV혁명] 등의 책을 출간했다. 최근에는 콘텐츠 분야에서의 메타버스 사례에 관심을 두고서 관련 글을 브런치에 올린다. 하지만 그의 본업이라고 할 수 있는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>좋은습관연구소</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 1, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860820/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860820/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T01:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 1, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of reading: April - June 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/summary-of-reading-april-june-2021/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/summary-of-reading-april-june-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T00:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<ul class="simple">
<li>&quot;Gandhi before India&quot; by Ramachandra Guha - part 1 of MK Gandhi's biography,
focusing on his early life and his time as the leader of South African Indians
in their struggle for better rights and treatment from the government.
Very detailed book, providing a strong foundation for Gandhi's later (and
more …</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 마이크론 실적, 매출 37% 및 순이익 171% 증가와 더불어 강한 메모리 수요 예측]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581518</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581518/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c-37-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%88%9c%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5-171-%ec%a6%9d%ea%b0%80%ec%99%80-%eb%8d%94%eb%b6%88%ec%96%b4"/>
        <updated>2021-07-01T00:28:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모험적 시도 – 뉴스페퍼민트/슬랙]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72927</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/30/m-slack/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-slack"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T22:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[안녕하세요, 3년 만에 올리는 공지글입니다. 지난 번 글은 4년 만에 올렸었네요. 모든 것이 빠른 이 시대에, 그래도 이렇게 드물게 올라오는 뉴스페퍼민트의 소리가 어딘가의 누군가에게는 가닿지 않을까 하는 생각으로 글을 올립니다. 뉴스페퍼민트를 오래 보신 분들은 저희가 예전 같지 않다는 것을 아시겠지요. 올라오는 글의 수가, 그리고 글을 올리는 사람이 예전에 비해 많이 줄었습니다. 물론 전에도 글을 올리시는 분들이 주기적으로 바뀌긴 했지요. 그래도 새로 지원하시는 분들과 잠시 쉬시는 – 그러다 잠시가 좀 길어지시는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Mozilla Rally: trading privacy for the "public good"]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861379/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861379/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T22:35:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new project from Mozilla, which is meant to help researchers collect
browsing data, but only with the informed consent of the browser-user, is taking a lot of
heat, perhaps in part because the company can never seem to do anything
right, at least in the
eyes of some.  Mozilla Rally was
announced
on June 25 as joint venture between the company and researchers at
Princeton University "to enable crowdsourced science for public
good".   The idea is that users can volunteer to give academic studies access to
the same kinds of browser data that is being tracked in some browsers
today.  Whether the privacy safeguards are strong 
enough—and if there is sufficient reason for users to sign up—remains to be seen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[밀레니얼은 운전하기를 싫어한다? 밀레니얼 중고차 수요가 증가한 이유는?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581515</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581515/%eb%b0%80%eb%a0%88%eb%8b%88%ec%96%bc-%ec%a4%91%ea%b3%a0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%88%98%ec%9a%94"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T17:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google updates Passes API to store COVID vaccination and testing information on Android devices]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/LYWD6lKZoWE/google-updates-passes-api-to-save-covid-testing-and-vaccination-information-on-Android-devices.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/LYWD6lKZoWE/google-updates-passes-api-to-save-covid-testing-and-vaccination-information-on-Android-devices.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Irfan Faizullabhoy 
   
Google has updated its Passes API to enable a simple and secure way to store and access COVID vaccination and test cards on Android devices. Starting today, developers from  healthcare organizations, government agencies and organizations authorized by public health authorities to distribute COVID vaccines and/or tests will have access to these APIs to create a digital version of COVID vaccination or test information. This will roll out initially in the United States followed by other countries.  
  

   
 Example COVID Cards from Healthvana, a company serving Los Angeles County  
      
Once a user stores the digital version of the COVID Card to their device, they will be able to access it via a shortcut on their device home screen, even when they are offl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-capable cameras drive smart city trial]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470349</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ai-capable-cameras-drive-smart-city-trial/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An AI-powered smart city trial in Rome, using Sony image sensors with AI capability as part of a “Smart Tip” system, is intended to help...
The post AI-capable cameras drive smart city trial appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Ward-Foxton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A set of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861421/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861421/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:40:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.12.14, 5.10.47, 5.4.129, 4.19.196, 4.14.238, 4.9.274, and 4.4.274 have been released.  They all contain
important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861420/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861420/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:30:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (fluidsynth), Fedora (libgcrypt and tpm2-tools), Mageia (nettle, nginx, openvpn, and re2c), openSUSE (kernel, roundcubemail, and tor), Oracle (edk2, lz4, and rpm), Red Hat (389-ds:1.4, edk2, fwupd, kernel, kernel-rt, libxml2, lz4, python38:3.8 and python38-devel:3.8, rpm, ruby:2.5, ruby:2.6, and ruby:2.7), and SUSE (kernel and lua53).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why is Verizon readying a smart display with LTE Cat M1?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8562</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/why-is-verizon-readying-a-smart-display-with-lte-cat-m1/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T15:13:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After earlier attempts to crack the smart home market failed, it appears that Verizon is ready for another go with its own smart display. Protocol reported the news late last week based on FCC filings showing the radio internals and user manual of the display.  I spent some time reviewing the filing documents and came […]
The post Why is Verizon readying a smart display with LTE Cat M1? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이마트 이베이코리아  인수는  온라인쇼핑 시장의 왝더독이 될까 , 찻잔속의 태풍이 될까]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581497</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581497/%ec%9d%b4%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8-%ec%9d%b4%eb%b2%a0%ec%9d%b4%ec%bd%94%eb%a6%ac%ec%95%84-%ec%9d%b8%ec%88%98"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T11:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t trust reported TOPS metrics for deep learning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470302</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/dont-trust-reported-tops-metrics-for-deep-learning/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T11:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reported tera operations per second (TOPS) is an exaggerated performance number that most neural networks will never see under real-world conditions. Instead, evaluate real-world TOPS...
The post Don’t trust reported TOPS metrics for deep learning appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ludovic Larzul</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘선한 의도’로 만든 ‘패륜 퀴즈’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81197</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/lfaSkIn4lFg/81197"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T07:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 배달앱으로 ‘새우튀김’을 주문한 소비자의 과도한 불만 접수 과정에서 세상을 떠난 한 음식점 점주의 사연이 세상에 전해졌습니다. 지난 22일 KBS라디오 쿨FM의 [황정민의 뮤직쇼]는 이 사연을 퀴즈로 만들었습니다: “이것 한 개의 환불 다툼에서 시작된 싸움이 분식집 주인을 숨지게 해 공분을 사고 있습니다. 다움 중 이것은?” 1번 삶은 달걀, 2번 새우튀김, 3번 순대염통. (정답 상품은 ‘화장품’이었습니다.)  많은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An EPYC escape: Case-study of a KVM breakout (Project Zero blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861330/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861330/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-30T00:54:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over at the Project Zero blog, Felix Wilhelm posted a lengthy account of a vulnerability he found in the Linux kernel's KVM (Kernel-based virtual machine) subsystem:

In this blog post I describe a vulnerability in KVM’s AMD-specific code and discuss how this bug can be turned into a full virtual machine escape. To the best of my knowledge, this is the first public writeup of a KVM guest-to-host breakout that does not rely on bugs in user space components such as QEMU. The discussed bug was assigned CVE-2021-29657, affects kernel versions v5.10-rc1 to v5.12-rc6 and was patched at the end of March 2021. As the bug only became exploitable in v5.10 and was discovered roughly 5 months later, most real world deployments of KVM should not be affected. I still think the issue is an interesting case study in the work required to build a stable guest-to-host escape against KVM and hope that this writeup can strengthen the case that hypervisor compromises are not only theoretical issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] An unpleasant surprise for My Book Live owners]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861235/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861235/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T23:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded devices need regular software updates in order to even be
minimally safe on today's internet.  Products that have reached their "end
of life", thus are no longer being updated, are essentially ticking time
bombs—it is only a matter of time before they are vulnerable to
attack.  That situation played out in June for owners of  Western
Digital (WD) My Book Live network-attached storage (NAS) devices; what was
meant to be a disk for home users 
accessible via the internet turned into a black hole when a remote
command-execution flaw was used to delete all of the data stored there.  Or
so it seemed at first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More DLL fun with w64devkit: Go, assembly, and Python]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/06/29/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2021/06/29/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T21:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[My previous article explained how to work with dynamic-link libraries
(DLLs) using w64devkit. These techniques also apply to other
circumstances, including with languages and ecosystems outside of C and
C++. In particular, w64devkit is a great complement to Go and reliably
fullfills all the needs of cgo — Go’s C interop — and can even
bootstrap Go itself. As before, this article is in large part an exercise
in capturing practical information I’ve picked up over time.
Go: bootstrap and cgo
The primary Go implementation, confusingly named “gc”, is an
incredible piece of software engineering. This is apparent when
building the Go toolchain itself, a process that is fast, reliable, easy,
and simple. It was originally written in C, but was re-written in Go
starting with Go 1.5. The C compiler i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch: Drop Test of the Ryujinx Emulator's Source Code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0840/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/_6NafdNAfPg/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each generation, companies like Sony, Microsoft and Nintendo delight their consumers with new consoles and different games for them. Yet there is a caveat - some games exclusively run on their platforms. Whereas a console may be worth an expensive PC component or a full-fledged computer. So what can you do? Emulators come to the rescue here. The market is full of similar projects, some are released as open source. Let us turn our attention to Nintendo Switch emulators. On the network, Ryujinx and Yuzu projects are among most popular responses. Let's check the code of the Ryujinx emulator and find out how many interesting bugs can be found using static analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming security changes to Google's OAuth 2.0 authorization endpoint in embedded webviews]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/6dtiO6wgGLU/upcoming-security-changes-to-googles-oauth-2.0-authorization-endpoint.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/6dtiO6wgGLU/upcoming-security-changes-to-googles-oauth-2.0-authorization-endpoint.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T18:30:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Badi Azad, Group Product Manager (@badiazad) 
 The Google Identity team is continually working to improve Google Account security and create a safer and more secure experience for our users. As part of that work, we recently introduced a new secure browser policy prohibiting Google OAuth requests in embedded browser libraries commonly referred to as embedded webviews. All embedded webviews will be blocked starting on September 30, 2021. 
Embedded webview libraries are problematic because they allow a nefarious developer to intercept and alter communications between Google and its users by acting as a "man in the middle." An application embedding a webview can modify or intercept network requests, insert custom scripts that can potentially record every keystroke entered in a login…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware Memory Models]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/hwmm</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/hwmm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T16:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to hardware memory models.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory Models]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/mm</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/mm"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Topic Index]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the IoT is shaping asset management solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470250</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-the-iot-is-shaping-asset-management-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T16:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IoT solutions for asset management can be expensive or impractical to implement because of the vast area the asset needs to travel, but a reliable asset tracking solution can be built by combining cost efficient, low power and secure wireless connectivity with a standardized infrastructure. 
The post How the IoT is shaping asset management solutions appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marc Pégulu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stepping Back from Speaking]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/202106-reducing-speaking.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/202106-reducing-speaking.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A personal note on why I wish to give up doing talks
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861310/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861310/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T15:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (klibc and libjdom2-java), Mageia (bash, glibc, gnutls, java-openjdk, kernel, kernel-linus, leptonica, libgcrypt, openjpeg2, tor, and trousers), openSUSE (bouncycastle, chromium, go1.16, and kernel), Oracle (docker-engine docker-cli and qemu), Red Hat (kpatch-patch), and SUSE (arpwatch, go1.16, kernel, libsolv, microcode_ctl, and python-urllib3, python-requests).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Version Vector]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/version-vector.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/version-vector.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T14:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Lamport Clock is effective to order events on a single server, but
      with multiple servers we need a vector of version numbers to detect
      concurrent updates.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With 1,600 students by his side, Jack Lee grew the largest Google Developer Student Club in the world]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/B0di_q-NQIo/with-1600-students-by-his-side-jack-lee.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/B0di_q-NQIo/with-1600-students-by-his-side-jack-lee.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T13:33:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Noa Havazelet, Program Manager, Google Developer Student Clubs, UK & Ireland 
  
With 1,600 students by his side, Jack Lee grew the largest Google Developer Student Club in the world in just 6 months at the London School of Economics (LSE). A life-long athlete, who loves leading teams, Jack saw that reigniting his university’s GDSC would be a great opportunity to have a large impact on the local tech scene. With a heavy focus on partnerships, Jack connected members of his club with leaders at top companies and other student groups across Scotland, France, Norway, Canada, and Nigeria. These collaborations enabled students to practice networking, while gaining access to key internships.  
Learn more about Jack and his club below.  
       
 Image of Jack Lee speaking at a GDSC even…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t wait up for 5G factory deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8560</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/dont-wait-up-for-5g-factory-deployments/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T13:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every week, I get a new press release discussing a pilot project that’s bringing 5G connectivity to manufacturing plants. Maybe it’s Ericsson making its own gear, or Intel and several partners, or even Qualcomm and ASE. This cavalcade of announcements does not jibe with my experience, however. In my discussions with actual plant operators, I haven’t heard any of […]
The post Don’t wait up for 5G factory deployments appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개발자 부족 문제, 어떻게 해결할까? (ft. 빌드 2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81172</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/HJnXXi-W9R8/81172"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T08:07:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아마존 마켓 플레이스에는 약 620만 명의 소매업자가 있다. 그들은 매월 사용료에 덧붙여 8%~15%에 해당하는 판매 수수료를 지불한다. 10%의 배달 수수료를 추가 지불하기도 한다(관련 링크). 수많은 소상공인의 판매 마진중 적지 않은 돈이 플랫폼 소유 기업으로 흘러 들어간다. 2019년 모바일 월드 컨퍼런스(MWC)에서 마이크로소프트 CEO 사티야 나델라는 모든 분야에서 새로운 애플리케이션과 그 애플리케이션을 만들어 줄 개발자의 중요성을 강조하면서 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11에서 요구하는 TPM 과 Secure Boot 기능]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222414201072</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/aepkoreanet/222414201072"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T07:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft사는 Windows 11이 동작되는 PC의 기본 요구 사양에 TPM(Ver 2.0) 지원과 Secure Boot 기능을 포함시켰습니다. Windows 10사용자는 Windows 11로 무료로 Upgrade 할 수 있지만, 사용하고 있는 PC에서 TPM 기능과 Secure Boot 기능을 지원하지 않으면 Upgrade 되지 않는 다고 합니다. TPM(Trusted Platform Module) 기업용 PC 특히 Notebook PC에서 암호키를 포함한 민감한 data를 Hardware적으로 안전하게 보관하기 위한 장치로 사용되고 있는 것이 TPM(Trusted Platform Module) 입니다. Hardware로 된 Module을 PC에 장착하여 사용합니다. Option 방식으로 Plug-In 하기도 하고, PC의 Mother board에 바로 soldering 되어서 공급되기.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>aepkoreanet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비즈니스 관점에서 본 윈도우 11 출시와  애플 대항 마이크로소프트 전략 변화]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581491</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581491/%eb%b9%84%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88%ec%8a%a4-%ea%b4%80%ec%a0%90%ec%97%90%ec%84%9c-%eb%b3%b8-%ec%9c%88%eb%8f%84%ec%9a%b0-11-%ec%b6%9c%ec%8b%9c%ec%99%80-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%eb%8c%80%ed%95%ad-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T06:28:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연도별 이베이코리아 실적, 이베이코리아 매출 및 영업이익 등]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581482</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581482/%ec%97%b0%eb%8f%84%eb%b3%84-%ec%9d%b4%eb%b2%a0%ec%9d%b4%ec%bd%94%eb%a6%ac%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T00:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More On Types]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/06/29/MoreOnTypes.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/06/29/MoreOnTypes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently I wrote a cute little program for doing Turtle Graphics.  For those of you who don't know, turtle graphics were originally added to the LOGO language by Seymour Papert in the late 1960s.  He built a robot that he called a "turtle" that could hold a pen.  The robot had wheels and could move forwards and backwards, and could rotate left and right.  It could also raise and lower the pen.  When placed on a sheet of paper, the turtle could be commanded to draw interesting designs.
Papert's goal was to teach children about programming.  As the years went by the robot got replaced with screens, and the turtle became an icon that could draw lines.  Children from the 70s until now have been enthralled by the simple commands for directing the turtle, and the elegant drawings they can make.
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Clean Code Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The first ever KernelCI hackfest]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861249/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861249/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T22:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The KernelCI continuous-integration project held
its first hackfest recently.  Developers from the KernelCI team,
Google, and Collabora worked to improve many different aspects of KernelCI
testing capabilities.  There are plans for more hackfests.

The first-ever KernelCI hackfest was a success. It kicked off the work to enable kernel testing through Chromium OS, a product-specific userspace. Enabling full userspace images and real-world tests like video call simulations adds a lot of complexity to the testing process. However, the benefits are a clear win for the community. They allow a more thorough kernel testing and validation through real application use cases, which can exercise several different kernel areas at the same time in an organized manner. Generally, it is not simple for lower-level kernel test suites like kselftests or LTP to orchestrate a similar use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pride Week with Google Developer Groups from Floripa and Belo Horizonte, Brazil]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/_IYQa6ZOWy0/pride-week-with-google-developer-group.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/_IYQa6ZOWy0/pride-week-with-google-developer-group.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T22:21:00.012Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rodrigo Akira Hirooka, Program Manager, Google Developer Groups Latin America 
 Lorena Locks is on a mission to grow the LGBTQIA+ tech community in Brazil. Her inspiration came from hosting Google Developer Group (GDG) Floripa meetups with her friend Catarina, where they were able to identify a need in their community.  
     
“We felt there wasn't a forum to meet people in the tech industry that reflected ourselves. So we decided to think bigger.”
      

    
 Image from GDG Floripa event  
  
Pride Week at GDG Floripa and Belo Horizonte, Brazil 
  
As a Women Techmakers Ambassador and Google Developer Group lead in Floripa, Brazil,  Lorena worked with the local community to create a week of special events, including over 12 talks and sessions centered on empowering the LGBTQIA+ experience in tech.  
The events took place every night at 7pm from June 21st - 25th and focused on creating inclusive representation and building trust among developer communities.  
     
Lorena’s commitment to this underrepresented group gained the attention of many local leaders in tech who identify as LGBTQIA+ and volunteered as speakers during Pride Week.
     
By creating spaces to talk about important LGBTQIA+ topics in tech, Pride Week events included sessions on: 
 
Spotting binary designs in products  
How to build inclusive tech teams  
Being an LGBTQIA+ manager   
Developing 'Nohs Somos' an app for the LGBTQIA+ community  
The best practices for D&I   
General Personal Data Protection Law and inclusive gender questions on forms 
  

 
  Speakers in photo: Lorena Locks and Catarina Schein  
  
With one-hundred percent of the speakers at these events coming from the LGTBQIA+ community, Pride Week at GDG Floripa and Belo Horizonte was a high impact program that has gone on to inspire GDGs around the world.  
If you want to learn more about how to get involved in Google Developer Group communities like this one, visit the site here.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.6, 3.8.11, 3.7.11, and 3.6.14 are now available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/mjnsTchkg4Q/python-396-3811-3711-and-3614-are-now.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/mjnsTchkg4Q/python-396-3811-3711-and-3614-are-now.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T19:10:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.6
Get it here: https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-396/

Python 3.9.6 is the newest major stable release of 
the Python programming language, and it contains many new features and 
optimizations. There’s been 146 commits since 3.9.5 which is a similar 
amount compared to 3.8 at the same stage of the release cycle. See the change log for details.

On macOS, we encourage you to use the universal2 binary installer variant whenever possible. The legacy 10.9+ Intel-only variant will not be provided for Python 3.10 and the universal2 variant will become the default download for future 3.9.x releases. You may need to upgrade third-party components, like pip,
 to later versions once they are released. You may experience 
differences in behavior in IDLE and other Tk-bas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some 5.13 development statistics]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860989/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860989/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T18:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As expected, the 5.13 development cycle turned out to be a busy one, with
16,030 non-merge changesets being pulled into the mainline over a
period of nine weeks.  The 5.13
release happened on June 27, meaning 
that it must be time for our traditional look at the provenance of the code
that was merged for this kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 근무형태 모델 5가지, 어떻게 최적 근무형태를 선택할 것인가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581476</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581476/%ed%8c%ac%eb%8d%b0%eb%af%b9-%ec%9d%b4%ed%9b%84-%ea%b7%bc%eb%ac%b4%ed%98%95%ed%83%9c-%eb%aa%a8%eb%8d%b8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T16:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861221/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861221/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T15:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bluez, intel-microcode, tiff, and xmlbeans), Fedora (openssh and php-phpmailer6), openSUSE (freeradius-server, java-1_8_0-openjdk, live555, openexr, roundcubemail, tor, and tpm2.0-tools), SUSE (bouncycastle and zziplib), and Ubuntu (linux-kvm and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discard an Axiom]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=14999</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/06/28/discard-an-axiom/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T14:38:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[28 June 2021 by Phillip JohnstonI’ve previously written about strategies that I use whenever I feel stuck in a rut. One of those strategies, especially useful when I’m feeling stuck creatively, is to inject novel ideas into the situation. One of my favorite tools for doing that with creative work is Brian Eno’s Oblique Strategies. … 
Continue reading "Discard an Axiom"
The post Discard an Axiom appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI is driving computing to the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8557</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/ai-is-driving-computing-to-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T13:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to the buzzwords from the past few years, edge computing is right up there with 5G and AI. But the results of a survey by the Eclipse Foundation show that edge computing is actually gaining ground in the enterprise and is much faster to deploy than either of them. The Eclipse Foundation surveyed 301 […]
The post AI is driving computing to the edge appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using an open source IIoT gateway to speed Modbus device integration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470242</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/using-an-open-source-iiot-gateway-to-speed-modbus-device-integration/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial internet of things (IIoT) applications typically require an edge gateway to integrate Modbus peripherals and other devices, but implementing a gateway can be costly...
The post Using an open source IIoT gateway to speed Modbus device integration appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vediyappan Villali, Vijay Annamalaisamy and Sathya Durai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-enabled SoCs handle multiple video streams]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470305</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ai-enabled-socs-handle-multiple-video-streams/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T11:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ambarella launches two devices for computer vision and AI processing from multiple or single inputs in security cameras and smart city systems. Image processing specialist...
The post AI-enabled SoCs handle multiple video streams appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Ward-Foxton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[집게손가락 논란 정리: 언론이 부추긴 허구의 혐오]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81147</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/DWCLiA4I1rg/81147"/>
        <updated>2021-06-28T06:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2018년 서지현 검사의 검찰 성추행 은폐 사건 고발로 촉발된 미투운동은 우리 사회에 여전히 성폭력, 차별이 만연하다는 현실을 보여줬습니다. 미투운동은 페미니즘을 한국 사회 담론으로 확장했고, 온·오프라인에서 페미니즘 운동이 본격화됐습니다. 그러자 성평등을 향한 페미니즘에 대한 반발성 공격으로서 ‘백래시’가 등장했습니다. 성평등 운동이 일으키는 변화로 자신의 사회적 영향력이 줄어든다고 느끼는 이들의 반발 현상을 말합니다. 백래시는 성폭력 피해자를 공격하거나 피해자에게 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대통령 연줄로 임명된 대사가 잔뼈 굵은 외교관 출신보다 나을 수 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72920</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/27/politicalapointedambassabor/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=politicalapointedambassabor"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T22:59:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국의 대사 임명 사례를 분석한 논문을 바탕으로 폴 맥도널드 교수가 워싱턴포스트에 쓴 글입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.13 kernel has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861131/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861131/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T22:52:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released the 5.13 kernel.


Of course, if the last week was small and calm, 5.13 overall is
actually fairly large. In fact, it's one of the bigger 5.x releases,
with over 16k commits (over 17k if you count merges), from over 2k
developers. But it's a 'big all over' kind of thing, not something
particular that stands out as particularly unusual.




Headline features in this release include
the "misc" group controller,
multiple
sources for trusted keys,
kernel
stack randomization on every system call,
support for Clang control-flow integrity
enforcement,
the ability to call kernel functions
directly from BPF programs,
minor-fault
handling for userfaultfd(),
the removal of /dev/kmem,
the Landlock security module,
and, of course, thousands of cleanups and fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shiny Green Damselfly]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32983</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/06/28/shiny-green-damselfly/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among the many wonderful things that nature can provide, I love to watch damselflies flying above the water. It is pretty hard to catch one of these insects, but today I was lucky to capture one of these shiny predators: … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beta-Testing of PVS-Studio Plugin for JetBrains CLion]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0839/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/aV8M5kaaphw/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio from Microsoft has long been the main development environment to work with the PVS-Studio analyzer. Our analyzer started off on Windows, so Visual Studio was an obvious and reasonable choice. In more than 10 years of PVS-Studio development, the analyzer has become available for several other languages and platforms. No wonder people ask us if we can integrate PVS-Studio into their favorite IDEs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid architecture speeds AI, vision workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470296</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/hybrid-architecture-speeds-ai-vision-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T19:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A novel hybrid data-flow and Von Neumann architecture can accelerate workloads including neural networks, machine learning, computer vision, DSP and basic linear algebra subprograms. Quadric,...
The post Hybrid architecture speeds AI, vision workloads appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Ward-Foxton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DIY Vinyl Cutting Drag Knife for Desktop CNC]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32890</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/06/27/diy-vinyl-cutting-drag-knife-for-desktop-cnc/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T18:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A desktop CNC is a great addition to any 3D printer or laser cutter. I consider them ‘the trinity’ for any maker garage. While a desktop CNC is great for wood and some metals like aluminum or brass, it would … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 스포츠 시장을 지배할 나이키 전략 핵심은 나이키 멤버쉽과 결합한 사용자 데이타]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581461</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581461/%eb%82%98%ec%9d%b4%ed%82%a4-%eb%a9%a4%eb%b2%84%ec%89%bd%ea%b3%bc-%ea%b2%b0%ed%95%a9%ed%95%9c-%ec%82%ac%ec%9a%a9%ec%9e%90-%eb%8d%b0%ec%9d%b4%ed%83%80"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T12:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연도별 나이키 실적, 매출 및 이익에서 읽는 나이키 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581438</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581438/%ec%97%b0%eb%8f%84%eb%b3%84-%eb%82%98%ec%9d%b4%ed%82%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T03:58:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사상 최대 매출과 이익의 2분기 나이키 실적,  향후 전망은 어떻까? 25년 전망 제시로 자신감 과시]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581427</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581427/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%82%98%ec%9d%b4%ed%82%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-06-27T00:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aglais Urticae]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=32907</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/06/26/aglais-urticae/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T19:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kleiner Fuchs (German), Small Tortoiseshell (English) or Algais Urticae is a colorful mid-size butterfly, found in most parts of Europe and across Asia. The caterpillars feed on nettles. With intensive farming and agriculture, nettles have been reduced and butterflies like … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adaptive ANC solutions bring enhanced audio capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470292</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/adaptive-anc-solutions-bring-enhanced-audio-capabilities/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While active noise cancellation (ANC) is nothing new to audiophiles, the technology has grown in popularity since a well-known Californian company released its first earbuds....
The post Adaptive ANC solutions bring enhanced audio capabilities appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Horst Gether</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are smart home devices from your insurance company a Trojan horse?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8542</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/are-smart-home-devices-from-your-insurance-company-a-trojan-horse/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T13:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Neil called in to our voicemail hotline with a question about a free smart home device and service offered by his home insurance company. The device is called Ting and it monitors your home’s electricity to warn you of any wiring problems to prevent fires. Should Neil be concerned […]
The post Are smart home devices from your insurance company a Trojan horse? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[택배 박스, 택배 트럭 그리고 바이크 (번역)]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2594</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2021/06/26/boxes-trucks-and-bikes/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T08:35:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[그런데 상품 카테고리나 소비자의 구매 경험으로 분석하는 것 이상으로 점점 더 중요성을 갖고 있는 모델이 있습니다. 유통 모델을 기준으로 쪼개 보는 방법입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>에디</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[커넥티드 TV 플랫폼 리더, 로쿠(Roku) 비즈니스 모델 분석]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581400</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581400/%eb%a1%9c%ec%bf%a0roku-%eb%b9%84%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88%ec%8a%a4-%eb%aa%a8%eb%8d%b8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-26T08:20:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take control over your data with Rally, a novel privacy-first data sharing platform (Mozilla blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/861004/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/861004/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T18:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Mozilla blog, the company has announced a new platform, Mozilla Rally, that "puts users in control of their data and empowers them to contribute their browsing data to crowdfund projects for a better Internet and a better society".  Rally comes out of work that Mozilla did with Professor Jonathan Mayer's research group at Princeton University .

Your data is valuable. But for too long, online services have pilfered, swapped, and exploited your data without your awareness. Privacy violations and filter bubbles are all consequences of a surveillance data economy. But what if, instead of companies taking your data without giving you a say, you could select who gets access to your data and put it to work for public good?

[...] By leveraging the scale of web browsers – a piece of software used by billions of people around the world – Rally has the potential to help address societal problems we could not solve before. Our goal is to demonstrate that there is a case for an equitable market for data, one where every party is treated fairly, and we welcome mission-aligned organizations that want to join us on this journey.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for June 25, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8507</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-june-25-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T17:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Honeywell’s latest report finds USB drives are an IIoT security weak spot: Threats capable of propagating over USB, or exploiting USB media for initial infection, rose from 19% in 2019 to just over 37% in 2020, according to a report from Honeywell. The company, which sells a product to secure USB drives that are brought into a […]
The post IoT news of the week for June 25, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developer updates from Coral]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/1eVnUH0ezwA/developer-updates-from-coral.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/1eVnUH0ezwA/developer-updates-from-coral.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by The Coral Team 
  
We're always excited to share updates to our Coral platform for building edge ML applications. In this post, we have some interesting demos, interfaces, and tutorials to share, and we'll start by pointing you to an important software update for the Coral Dev Board.  
 Important update for the Dev Board / SoM
 If you have a Coral Dev Board or Coral SoM, please install our latest Mendel update as soon as possible to receive a critical fix to part of the SoC power configuration. To get it, just log onto your board and install the update as follows: 
  

     
This will install a patch from NXP for the Dev Board / SoM's SoC, without which it's possible the SoC will overstress and the lifetime of the device could be reduced. If you recently flashed your board with t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Future.com – What’s Next?]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1180</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/future-com-welcome-what-now-next/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T16:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, world… welcome to Future, a place to make sense of, well, the future as technology changes the way we work, live, and play.  We just launched with a big “drop” — our very first, June edition of Future — of 30+ pieces, and our next monthly drop is coming in July. Sign up for... Read More
The post Future.com – What’s Next? appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sonal Chokshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Suppressing SIGBUS signals]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860419/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860419/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T15:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mmap()
system call creates a mapping for a range of virtual addresses; it
has a long list of options controlling just how that mapping should work.
Ming Lin is proposing
the addition of yet another option, called MAP_NOSIGBUS, which
changes the kernel's response when a process accesses an unmapped address.
What this option does is relatively easy to understand; why it is 
useful takes a bit more explanation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860981/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860981/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T15:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (chromium, dovecot, exiv2, helm, keycloak, libslirp, matrix-appservice-irc, nginx-mainline, opera, pigeonhole, tor, tpm2-tools, and vivaldi), Debian (libgcrypt20), Fedora (pdfbox), Mageia (graphicsmagick, matio, and samba and ldb), openSUSE (dovecot23, gupnp, libgcrypt, live555, and ovmf), SUSE (gupnp, libgcrypt, openexr, and ovmf), and Ubuntu (ceph and rabbitmq-server).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트리플모니터 사용법, 트리플모니터 절전 후 화면 재배치 현상 방지하기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581401</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581401/%ed%8a%b8%eb%a6%ac%ed%94%8c%eb%aa%a8%eb%8b%88%ed%84%b0-%ec%82%ac%ec%9a%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T14:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's open-source vulnerability schema]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860943/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860943/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T14:39:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Security Blog announces
the release of a schema intended to describe vulnerabilities in a
project-independent manner:


	With this schema we hope to define a format that all vulnerability
	databases can export. A unified format means that vulnerability
	databases, open source users, and security researchers can easily
	share tooling and consume vulnerabilities across all of open
	source. This means a more complete view of vulnerabilities in open
	source for everyone, as well as faster detection and remediation
	times resulting from easier automation.


This schema is already being provided by a number projects, including Go,
Rust, Python, DWF, and OSS-Fuzz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MyGNUHealth Personal Health Record 1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860937/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860937/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T13:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first stable release of MyGNUHealth is out.


I am proud to announce the first stable release of MyGNUHealth, the GNU
Health Personal Health Record for desktop and mobile devices.

From now on, anyone can benefit from a Libre Personal Health
application that respects our privacy, both from our desktops and from
our libre phones (such as the PinePhone). MyGNUHealth is more than a
health and activity tracker, since it incorporates state-of-the-art
technology and resources from medicine, genomics and
bioinformatics. Thanks to the integration with the GNU Federation, we
can communicate and share the information we wish with our health
professionals in real-time.


See this
announcement for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding wavelength choice in LiDAR systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470259</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/understanding-wavelength-choice-in-lidar-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are different types of LiDAR. Those involved in the auto industry ought to be aware of the relative strengths and weaknesses of each. It...
The post Understanding wavelength choice in LiDAR systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bahman Hadji</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Features in ESP RainMaker]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cdb4a2f3fdc3</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/the-esp-journal/new-features-in-esp-rainmaker-cdb4a2f3fdc3?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T10:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ESP RainMaker has been around for more than a year now and we have been adding quite some features to it every few months. Here we are now…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 IT ‘빅5’ 동향: 클라우드를 중심으로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=80988</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/BGoSv5z3vYY/80988"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T05:12:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주요 빅테크 기업이 월스트리트에 제출한 2021년 1분기별 실적을 보면, 애플, 마이크로소프트, 아마존, 페이스북 및 구글은 코로나 유행 기간과 상관없이 오히려 시장 지배력과 영향력이 계속해서 상승했다. 아래 그림에서 보듯이, 각 회사는 2019년 코로나 유행 전부터 지금까지 수년 만에 가장 빠른 속도로 판매 및 이익에 대해 최고의 기록했다. 그뿐만 아니다. 주식 가치는 5년 전보다 거의 두 배로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조선일보의 실수인가, ‘악의적’ 고의인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81134</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/L3CeZWD6CVY/81134"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T04:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 23일 조선일보는 3인 혼성 절도단이 성매매를 원하는 50대 남성을 유인한 후 협박해 돈을 뜯어낸 사건을 보도하면서 조국 전 법무부 장관과 그의 딸 등의 모습이 묘사된 삽화를 사용했다. 언론인권센터는 조선일보의 조국 부녀 삽화 사용을 강력히 규탄하며, 한국 언론사의 기사 삽화 사용에 있어서 윤리적 고려가 시급하다. 조선일보가 송고한 ‘”먼저 씻으세요” 성매매 유인해 지갑 털어’라는 기사에서 조국 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Types]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/06/25/OnTypes.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/06/25/OnTypes.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I wrote my first program in 1964.  The name of the program was: Mr Patternson's Computerized Gate, and it was implemented on a little plastic computer named DIGICOMP-I, which was a cute little three bit finite state machine with 6 AND gates.
The first electronic computer I ever wrote a program for was an ECP-18 in 1966.  This was a 15 bit wide machine with 1024 words of drum memory.  The programs I wrote were all in binary machine language and were entered through the front-panel switches.
In the years between 1967 and 1969 my father would drive my friend, Tim Conrad, and I 25 miles to the Digital Equipment Corp sales office, where we would spend our Saturdays entering programs into the PDP-8 that they had on the floor.  They were very gracious to allow us such access and freedom.  The cod…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Clean Code Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yo, Ho, Ho, And a Bottle of Rum - Or How We Analyzed Storm Engine's Bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0838/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/d0CKRk0vjoU/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio is a static analysis tool that helps find errors in software source code. This time PVS-Studio looked for bugs in Storm Engine's source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Spectre revisits BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860597/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860597/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:43:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been well over three years now since the
Spectre hardware 
vulnerabilities were disclosed, but Spectre is truly a gift that keeps on
giving.  Writing correct and secure code is hard enough when the hardware
behaves in predictable ways; the problem gets far worse when processors can
do random and crazy things.  For an illustration of the challenges
involved, one need look no further than the BPF vulnerability described in
this
advisory, which was fixed in the 5.13-rc7 release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apply now for Google for Startups Accelerator: Women Founders]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/foIG5av9fPY/apply-now-for-google-for-startups-accelerator-women-founders.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/foIG5av9fPY/apply-now-for-google-for-startups-accelerator-women-founders.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T16:00:00.005Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ashley Francisco
 
 The Google for Startups Accelerator: Women Founders program is now open for applications until July 19.
Last year, we launched the inaugural Google for Startups Accelerator: Women Founders program in North America to help women-led startups identify and solve technical challenges while scaling their companies. The inaugural cohort also received tailored programming to address some of the longstanding barriers that women founders face.  
Women founders remain underrepresented in the tech startup ecosystem because they often lack access to the resources needed to start, build, and grow their businesses. The COVID-19 pandemic exacerbated these structural barriers by disproportionately impacting women in the workforce—and research shows women were more vulnerable to the economic effects of COVID-19 because of existing gender disparities.    
For women founders, access to capital is one of the major challenges to launching their business.  A recent report showed women-led startups received a mere 2.3% of global venture capitalist funding in 2020, falling from 2.8% the year before.  
The Google for Startups Accelerator: Women Founders program aims to help bridge the gap and create opportunities for women founders to succeed.  Beyond mentorship and technical project support, the accelerator also includes deep dives and workshops focused on product design, customer acquisition, and leadership development for founders. Participants will also hear from a roster of speakers and facilitators who deliver both technical and nontechnical programming for women-led startups.  
Applications for the second Google for Startups Accelerator: Women Founders program are now open until July 19, for North American applicants. Approximately 10-12 startups with at least one woman founder will be selected from across North America. The accelerator runs from September through to December 2021.  
To learn more about the program and to apply, visit the website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860809/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860809/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:48:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (apache-mod_auth_openidc, bind, bluez, cifs-utils, ffmpeg, gnome-autoar, guacd, kernel, kernel-linus, qtwebsockets5, slic3r, tunnel, wavpack, wireshark, and xscreensaver), openSUSE (apache2, cryptctl, go1.15, libnettle, python-rsa, salt, thunderbird, wireshark, libvirt, sbc, libqt5-qtmultimedia, xstream, and xterm), and SUSE (cryptctl, freeradius-server, libnettle, and libsolv).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: It’s about ethics in smart devices]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8533</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-its-about-ethics-in-smart-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T13:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kevin and I start this week’s show with a discussion of his Amazon Prime Day purchases and then talk about the kerfuffle over smart thermostats and demand-response energy programs in Texas. I happened to be there at the time, and there is a definite right and wrong way to enroll people in the program. We […]
The post Podcast: It’s about ethics in smart devices appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30평 아파트 사려면? 25년, 50년, 118년]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81117</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/rFx7NvIb2bo/81117"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T03:42:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[문재인 정부가 출범한 2017년 5월경 서울아파트값은 평당 2,061만 원이었다. 그로부터 4년이 지난 2021년 5월 현재 서울아파트값은 1,910만 원(93%)이 올라 3,971만 원이 됐다. 30평형 아파트로 환산하면 6.2억짜리 아파트가 5.7억이 올라 11.9억이 된 것이다. 문재인 대통령은 2020년 1월 신년 기자회견 중 이렇게 말했다: “일부 지역은 서민들이 납득하기 어려울 만큼 급격한 가격상승이 있었는데  (2017년 5월 취임 이전 수준으로)원상회복돼야 한다고 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 24, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860161/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860161/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T01:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 24, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond the Meme: Ever Given, Supply Chains, and the Physical World]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=975</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/beyond-the-meme-ever-given-supply-chains-and-the-physical-world/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-24T00:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world watched when the container ship Ever Given blocked the Suez Canal this March. Some people made sites, many people made memes; I made a children’s book. It seemed almost comical: A patch of bad weather drove the 1312-foot long, 200000 tonnes-heavy container ship Ever Given askew, wedging her into the narrow canal at... Read More
The post Beyond the Meme: Ever Given, Supply Chains, and the Physical World appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Besart Copa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[웹, 브라우저, 서버에서 SSL 인증서 정보 확인 방법, SSL 인증서 만료일 확인 등]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581380</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581380/ssl-%ec%9d%b8%ec%a6%9d%ec%84%9c-%ec%a0%95%eb%b3%b4-%ed%99%95%ec%9d%b8-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T23:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고객들도 감당하기 어려운 디지털 헬스케어 스타트업 붐]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72911</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/23/%ea%b3%a0%ea%b0%9d%eb%93%a4%eb%8f%84-%ea%b0%90%eb%8b%b9%ed%95%98%ea%b8%b0-%ec%96%b4%eb%a0%a4%ec%9a%b4-%eb%94%94%ec%a7%80%ed%84%b8-%ed%97%ac%ec%8a%a4%ec%bc%80%ec%96%b4-%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%80%ed%8a%b8/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=%25ea%25b3%25a0%25ea%25b0%259d%25eb%2593%25a4%25eb%258f%2584-%25ea%25b0%2590%25eb%258b%25b9%25ed%2595%2598%25ea%25b8%25b0-%25ec%2596%25b4%25eb%25a0%25a4%25ec%259a%25b4-%25eb%2594%2594%25ec%25a7%2580%25ed%2584%25b8-%25ed%2597%25ac%25ec%258a%25a4%25ec%25bc%2580%25ec%2596%25b4-%25ec%258a%25a4%25ed%2583%2580%25ed%258a%25b8"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T22:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 기간 동안 디지털 헬스케어 스타트업의 붐이 일어났습니다. 원격의료와 건강관리에 대한 관심이 높아지고 해당 분야 기업의 실적이 개선되면서 전례 없는 막대한 투자가 쏟아졌습니다. 이를 바탕으로 다양한 서비스를 제공하는 기업들이 우후죽순으로 나타났습니다. 기존 기업들과의 경쟁이 심해지면서 이합집산이 일어나기도 합니다. 일부 소비자들은 서비스가 이미 충분하다고 손사래 칠 정도입니다. 디지털 헬스케어 산업의 변화에 대해  소개하는 월스트리트저널의 기사입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Pulling GitHub into the kernel process]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860607/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860607/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T22:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is an ongoing effort to "modernize" the kernel-development process;
so far, the focus has been on providing better
tools that can streamline the usual email-based workflow.  But that
"email-based" part has proven to be problematic for some potential
contributors, especially those who might want to simply submit a small bug
fix and are not interested in getting set up with that workflow.  The
project-hosting "forge" sites, like GitHub and GitLab, provide a nearly
frictionless path for these kinds of one-off contributions, but they do
not mesh well—at all, really—with most of mainline kernel development.
There is some ongoing work that may change all of that, however.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A review of the kernel's release-signing practices]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860681/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860681/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:33:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the behest of the Linux Foundation, a security-oriented review of the
kernel project's release-signing and key-management practices was done; the
report from this work has now been published.  "This review
resulted in seven recommendations that can help improve the robustness of
the security and use of the signing keys for the Linux
Kernel. Additionally, Trail of Bits suggested that more comprehensive and
up to date documentation on the current procedures and policies are needed
to help organizations around the world to best understand the current
stratagem."  See the
full report for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Louis: PipeWire under the hood]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860680/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860680/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T19:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those wanting lots of grungy details about how the PipeWire system
works, this
blog entry from Patrick Louis should be of interest.
"The session manager is the piece of software that is responsible for the policy: to find and configure devices, attach them appropriately to the graph, set and restore their properties if needed, route streams to the right device, set their volume, and more.
It can create it’s own objects in the PipeWire graph related to session management such as endpoints and links between them, a sort of abstraction on top of PipeWire nodes.

There are currently two implementations of the session manager:
pipewire-media session and WirePlumber."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE Linux Enterprise 15 SP3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860672/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860672/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T18:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE Linux Enterprise (SLE) 15 SP3 has
been released. "With the release of SLES 15 SP3 we now have 100%
binary compatibility with openSUSE Leap 15.3 (our developer platform).
That means that you can smoothly move workloads from development to
production environments that run SLE 15 SP3 – and back again – with assured
application compatibility."  See the release
notes for additional information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing "Serverless Migration Station" Learning Modules]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/NPnfH2nxidk/introducing-serverless-migration.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/NPnfH2nxidk/introducing-serverless-migration.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T17:12:00.013Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Wesley Chun (@wescpy), Developer Advocate, Google Cloud 

 Helping users modernize their serverless apps
  
Earlier this year, the Google Cloud team introduced a series of codelabs (free, online, self-paced, hands-on tutorials) designed for technical practitioners modernizing their serverless applications. Today, we're excited to announce companion videos, forming a set of "learning modules" made up of these videos and their corresponding codelab tutorials. Modernizing your applications allows you to access continuing product innovation and experience a more open Google Cloud. The initial content is designed with App Engine developers in mind, our earliest users, to help you take advantage of the latest features in Google Cloud. Here are some of the key migrations and why they be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/hybrid-clock.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/hybrid-clock.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T15:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While a Lamport Clock is often necessary to order events in a
      distributed system, clients often need to know the actual times too.
     The Hybrid Clock,  Unmesh's next pattern, combines these two demands.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lamport Clock]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/lamport-clock.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/lamport-clock.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T15:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next distributed system pattern from Unmesh is the Lamport Clock.
      Distributed systems can't assume that time is consistent between servers,
      and sometimes time goes backwards. Yet it's important to have some way to order events.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860653/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860653/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T15:02:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.12.13, 5.10.46, and 5.4.128 have been released with the usual set
of important fixes.  Users should upgrade.

Note that 5.12.13 and 5.10.46 contain a fix for a
significant Spectre vulnerability; stay tuned to LWN for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860652/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860652/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T14:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel and linux-4.19), Fedora (tor), Oracle (rh-postgresql10-postgresql), Red Hat (kernel), SUSE (ansible, apache2, dovecot23, OpenEXR, ovmf, and wireshark), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.8, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.8, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.8, linux-hwe-5.8, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.8, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux-hwe, linux-gke-5.3, linux-raspi2-5.3, linux-oem-5.10, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm’s confidential compute will boost security starting around 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8519</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/arms-confidential-compute-will-boost-security-starting-around-2024/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T13:00:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If Arm has its way, some time in 2024 or 2025 you might be able to buy a phone that can process your health data securely on the device, or an industrial client might be able to run a proprietary algorithm on a gateway device that’s shared by others without disclosing its intellectual property. Thanks […]
The post Arm’s confidential compute will boost security starting around 2024 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smoothing EV powertrain performance with a field-oriented control algorithm]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470266</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/smoothing-ev-powertrain-performance-with-a-field-oriented-control-algorithm/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Field-oriented control as a motor control scheme is indispensable for EV powertrains because of their noiseless and smooth motor operations.
The post Smoothing EV powertrain performance with a field-oriented control algorithm appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vaibhav Anand and Saurabh S. Khobe</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEGGER emPower OS Enables On-Going Production During Chip Shortages]]></title>
        <id>https://www.segger.com/news/segger-empower-os-enables-on-going-production-during-chip-shortages/</id>
        <link href="https://www.segger.com/news/segger-empower-os-enables-on-going-production-during-chip-shortages/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T09:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEGGER introduces its all-in-one embedded operating system emPower OS. It uses proven components from the software toolbox that already lays the groundwork for many customer products and for SEGGER’s successful J-Link debugger. emPower OS provides an out-of- the-box experience for complex embedded software applications on close to one thousand hardware platforms while supporting many more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEGGER Microcontroller RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘관계자 저널리즘’이 만든 오보: 경향 ‘포털뉴스 편집권 폐지’ 오보 사례]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81109</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/F0O7FnD2dTw/81109"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T04:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[경향신문은 6월 17일 1면 머릿기사로 [네이버·다음 ‘뉴스 편집’ 완전히 손 뗀다] (곽희양·박광연 기자)를 보도했습니다. 더불어민주당이 ‘인공지능(AI) 알고리즘 뉴스 추천’ 등 포털사이트 내 뉴스편집권을 완전히 없애기로 포털사업자와 사실상 합의했다는 내용입니다. 경향신문은 3면에 포털 알고리즘이 불공정성 논란으로 직접 편집권을 줄이는 방향으로 발전돼 왔고 이제는 논란 소지를 원천 차단하기로 판단한 것이라며 ‘포털 뉴스편집권 폐지’를 강조했습니다. 그러나 경향신문은 이날 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] New features and other changes in Python 3.10]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860389/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860389/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-23T02:01:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10 is proceeding apace; everything looks to be on
track for the final release, which is expected on
October 4. The beta releases started 
in early May, with the first of those marking the feature-freeze for this version of
the language.  There are a number of interesting changes that are coming with
Python 3.10, including what is perhaps the "headline feature":
structural pattern matching.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[북유럽 국가가 행복한 진짜 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=72908</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/06/22/m-lagom/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-lagom"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T22:54:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Jukka Savolainen, 슬레이트) 원문 보기 ‘휘게’라는 단어를 들어보셨나요? 덴마크 인들이 편안하고 아늑한 느낌을 설명할때 사용하는 이 단어는 덴마크 인들의 행복의 비결로 오랫동안 여겨져 왔습니다. 몇년 전에는 휘게에 관한 책과 기사, 가정용품들이 나오기도 했지요. 전세계의 언론인들이 덴마크를 방문하고 이들의 독특한 생활양식을 전하기도 했습니다. 여기에는 덴마크가 전세계에서 가장 행복한 국가로 뽑혔다는 사실 또한 일조했습니다. 하지만 최근에 나는 이 곳 미시간 앤 아버의 인테리어 가게에 휘게 스타일의 양초들이 모두 할인코너로 옮겨진 것을 보았습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아마존고 대형 매장 적용, 첫 대형 아마존고 매장을 오픈한 아마존]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581352</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581352/%ec%b2%ab-%eb%8c%80%ed%98%95-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4%ea%b3%a0-%eb%a7%a4%ec%9e%a5-%ec%98%a4%ed%94%88"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T17:12:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pay plugin for Magento 2]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/Fyi8O7iMfE4/google-pay-plugin-for-magento-2.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/Fyi8O7iMfE4/google-pay-plugin-for-magento-2.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Soc Sieng, Developer Advocate

Google Pay plugin for Magento 2
Update June 15, 2021:  The Google Pay extension v1.1.1 for Magento now supports the Cybersource payment gateway allowing merchants who prefer Cybersource to easily integrate Google Pay into their checkout flow.
 Other key updates include support for Magento 2.4 as well as Magento 2.3. Easy to download and install without any coding, Google Pay for Magento provides fast, frictionless checkout and allows consumers to use already-stored payment credentials. This reduces data entry errors and translates to higher conversion rates and larger average order size for merchants.
 We are pleased to announce the launch of the official Google Pay plugin for Magento 2. The Google Pay plugin can help increase conversions by enablin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860559/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860559/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T15:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (audacity), openSUSE (chromium), Oracle (glib2), SUSE (Salt and salt), and Ubuntu (apache2 and openexr).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Will your current smart home devices work with Matter?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8501</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/will-your-current-smart-home-devices-work-with-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T15:03:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the most recent IoT Podcast, David called in with a question about the new Matter standard. He has multiple connected devices in his smart home now and is wondering if they will work with Matter once device makers start bringing new Matter-compliant devices to market. It’s a great question but unfortunately, Amazon, Apple, Google, […]
The post Will your current smart home devices work with Matter? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2021년 세계 100대 브랜드, 가장 가치있는 브랜드 아마존으로 3년 연속 선정, 2위는 애플]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581347</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581347/2021%eb%85%84-%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84-100%eb%8c%80-%eb%b8%8c%eb%9e%9c%eb%93%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T13:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Versioned Value]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/versioned-value.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/versioned-value.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T13:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When a distributed system has mutable data, nodes need to know which is
      the most recent value, so a versioned value stores a version
      number with every value.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5G is for things, so EdgeQ built a chip to optimize for the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8513</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/5g-is-for-things-so-edgeq-built-a-chip-to-optimize-for-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EdgeQ is a chip design firm that covers a trifecta of my nerdiest interests. It’s using the open source RISC-V architecture to build a 5G chip that can also handle edge AI tasks, and it’s doing so in a way that will disrupt the business model of proprietary network equipment vendors. As an added bonus, […]
The post 5G is for things, so EdgeQ built a chip to optimize for the IoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enter the EFM32 Gecko]]></title>
        <id>https://limitedresults.com/?p=1267</id>
        <link href="https://limitedresults.com/2021/06/enter-the-efm32-gecko/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T12:42:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new post presents an hardware exploit to unlock the debug port on the EFM32 Gecko MCUs Series 1 designed by Silicon Labs. Once again, after the previous nRF52 episode, this security research reveals an entire range of products vulnerable to a silicon design vulnerability. The way to unlock these chips was quite challenging and...
The post Enter the EFM32 Gecko appeared first on LimitedResults.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LimitedResults</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[패데믹 이후 근무형태, 하이브리드 근무 성과를 올릴 17가지 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581345</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581345/%ed%95%98%ec%9d%b4%eb%b8%8c%eb%a6%ac%eb%93%9c-%ea%b7%bc%eb%ac%b4-%ec%84%b1%ea%b3%bc%eb%a5%bc-%ec%98%ac%eb%a6%b4-17%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80-%eb%b0%a9%eb%b2%95"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T11:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[죽음의 소형 타워크레인, 그들이 총파업한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81092</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/_uFaPtCKCsU/81092"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T05:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[타워크레인 노동조합은 6월 8일, 국토교통부의 소형 타워크레인 안전대책 수립과 등록말소·시정조치 명령이 부과된 타워크레인 운행중단을 촉구하며 총파업에 들어갔습니다. 6월 11일 노동조합과 국토교통부 합의로 파업은 종료됐지만 언론이 이번 파업을 어떻게 보도했는지는 돌아볼 필요가 있습니다. 민주언론시민연합은 타워크레인 노동조합이 파업한 과정과 원인, 언론보도 양상을 정리했습니다. 타워크레인 노동자들은 왜 다시 총파업에 나섰나 ‘파업 보도’ 기본은 왜 파업을 하는지 전달하는 것입니다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pocket article: Undefined Behavior Sanitizer Trap on Error]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/ubsan-trap</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/ubsan-trap"/>
        <updated>2021-06-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is a brief overview on how the Undefined Behavior Sanitizer can be
used to trap unintentional or error prone parts of a C program. We’re going to
look at how it’s used on a desktop program, as well as a way to use it in small
embedded programs!
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[넷플릭스 온라인쇼핑 진출에서 읽는 넷플릭스 전략 시사점]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581341</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581341/%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%98%a8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8%ec%87%bc%ed%95%91-%ec%a7%84%ec%b6%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T23:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocky Linux 8.4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860420/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860420/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T17:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rocky Linux is a community enterprise
operating system, created by Gregory Kurtzer, founder of the CentOS
project. Rocky Linux 8.4 has been
released for x86-64 and aarch64. "Sufficient testing has been performed such that we have confidence in its stability for production systems."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying complex designs with task-specific microcontrollers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470253</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/simplifying-complex-designs-with-task-specific-microcontrollers/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Task-specific 8- and 16-bit microcontrollers can be used to offload actions from large 32-bit MCUs and MPUs and thus simplify the design process.
The post Simplifying complex designs with task-specific microcontrollers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Perkel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A stable bug fix bites proprietary modules]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860262/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860262/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:24:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel-development community has long had a tense relationship with
companies that create and ship proprietary loadable kernel modules.  In the
view of many developers, such modules are a violation of the GPL and should
simply be disallowed.  That has never happened, though; instead, the
community has pursued a policy of legal ambiguity and technical
inconvenience to discourage proprietary modules.  A
"technical-inconvenience" patch that was merged nearly one year ago has
begun to show up in stable kernel releases, leading at least one
developer to complain that things have gone a little too far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to correctly use Basic Authentication in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/basic-authentication-in-go</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/basic-authentication-in-go"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When searching for examples of HTTP basic authentication with Go, every result I could find unfortunately contained code which is either out-of-date (i.e. doesn't use the r.BasicAuth() functionality that was introduced in Go 1.4) or is vulnerable to timing attacks.
So in this post I'd like to quickly discuss how to implement basic authentication correctly in your Go applications.
We'll start with a bit of background information, but if you're not interested in that you can skip straight to the code.
What is basic authentication? When should I use it?
As a developer, you're probably already familiar with the prompt that web browsers show when you visit a URL that's protected by basic authentication.

When you input a username and password into this prompt, the web browser will send a HTTP r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Custom command-line flags with flag.Func]]></title>
        <id>https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/custom-command-line-flags</id>
        <link href="https://www.alexedwards.net/blog/custom-command-line-flags"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my favorite things about the recent Go 1.16 release is a small — but very welcome — addition to the flag package: the flag.Func() function. This makes it much easier to define and use custom command-line flags in your application.
For example, if you want to parse a flag like --pause=10s directly into a time.Duration type,  or parse --urls="http://example.com http://example.org" directly into a []string slice, then previously you had two options. You could either create a custom type to implement the flag.Value interface, or use a third-party package like pflag.
But now the flag.Func() function gives you a simple and lightweight alternative. In this short post we're going to take a look at a few examples of how you can use it in your own code.
Parsing custom flag types
To demonstrat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Edwards</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860418/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860418/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T15:10:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (connman, go, and grub), Debian (nettle, prosody, and tor), Fedora (iaito, mingw-ilmbase, mingw-openexr, mingw-python-urllib3, mosquitto, nettle, polkit, and radare2), Mageia (puddletag, python-babel, python-eventlet, and python-pikepdf), openSUSE (htmldoc), SUSE (go1.15, go1.16, gupnp, and libgcrypt), and Ubuntu (apache2 and dovecot).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Barnacle found the right network for its tracking biz]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8508</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-barnacle-found-the-right-network-for-its-tracking-biz/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T13:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, two entrepreneurs in Atlanta launched Barnacle, a package-tracking business built on the Helium Low-Power Wide-Area Network (LPWAN). I was excited to hear this because I’m always on the lookout for use cases for LPWANs and because I host a Helium hotspot and want to provide an essential (or at least useful) service. The […]
The post How Barnacle found the right network for its tracking biz appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SEGGER and Codasip Announce Cooperation on RISC-V]]></title>
        <id>https://www.segger.com/news/segger-and-codasip-announce-cooperation-on-risc-v/</id>
        <link href="https://www.segger.com/news/segger-and-codasip-announce-cooperation-on-risc-v/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T07:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SEGGER and Codasip announce that SEGGER’s J-Link debug probes and its Embedded Studio IDE fully support Codasip’s RISC-V processors, right out-of-the-box.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEGGER Microcontroller RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[좋은 이미지, 나쁜 일터: 이케아코리아 ‘단시간 노동’ 사례]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81083</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/DtM09e1jcMM/81083"/>
        <updated>2021-06-21T05:29:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“초단기 근로계약은 법의 허점을 교묘히 악용하는 행위다. 현행 기간제보호법에 따른 정규직 전환 의무 조항이 주당 15시간 이상 근로에만 적용된다는 점을 역으로 이용해 서류상 15시간 미만의 고용계약을 유지하고 있는 것이다. 이런 계약을 받아들인 노동자는 급여가 형편없이 적은 것은 물론이고, 고용보험과 직장 국민연금 가입 자격이 없어 해고되면 생계조차 막막해진다.” – 한겨레, 사설: 교육현자의 참담한 ‘초단기 노동자’ (2015. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>청년유니온</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.13-rc7]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860358/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860358/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T23:16:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.13-rc7 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "So there's not a huge number of patches in here, and most of the
patches are pretty small too. A fair number of one-liners and
'few-liners'.

Which is just how I like it."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How WCF Shoots Itself in the Foot With TraceSource]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0837/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/2k0dfxs4dRU/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We don't often get the chance to write something on parallel programming issues. This time we "got lucky". The TraceEvent standard method has some implementation peculiarities. They resulted in an error with multiple threads blocking. So we'd like to warn users about this nuance and cover this interesting case from our users support practice. Why was our support involved? Keep reading to find out. Enjoy the reading!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연도별 미국 자동차 판매량 및 미국  중고차 판매량 추이(20년 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581293</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581293/%ec%97%b0%eb%8f%84%eb%b3%84-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%9e%90%eb%8f%99%ec%b0%a8-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T12:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmarks show AI performance on tiny systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470263</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/benchmarks-show-ai-performance-on-tiny-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New TinyML benchmark has metrics for latency and energy consumption – and the first round of results are out. MLCommons, the industry consortium behind the...
The post Benchmarks show AI performance on tiny systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sally Ward-Foxton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 온라인 중고차 플랫폼 카바나 성공요인 7가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581291</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581291/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%98%a8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b8-%ec%a4%91%ea%b3%a0%ec%b0%a8-%ed%94%8c%eb%9e%ab%ed%8f%bc-%ec%b9%b4%eb%b0%94%eb%82%98-%ec%84%b1%ea%b3%b5%ec%9a%94%ec%9d%b8-7%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T10:16:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡 사태 관련 트윗 모음]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=81935</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Economic_View/~3/ifuuJrMXSMc/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-20T00:15:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[# 사실 미국에서 자라 교육받으며 미국식 경영마인드를 골수까지 장착한 Bom Kim(a.k.a 김범석) 씨는 지금 상황이 매우 기이하게 느껴질지도 모르겠다는 생각이 든다. 그의 비즈니스는 정확히 아마존이나 우버의 그것과 같은데 왜 한국인은 미국인과 달리 불매를 외치고 있을까 하고 말이다. # 그만큼 사실 우리나라를 포함한 전 세계는 기술, 유통, 금융이 결합한 새로운 형태의 자본주의의 – 야니스 바루파키스라는 학자는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 모델 S Plaid 출시, 프리미엄 전기차 시장을 회복할 수 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581257</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581257/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%eb%aa%a8%eb%8d%b8-s-plaid-%ec%b6%9c%ec%8b%9c%ec%99%80-%ed%94%84%eb%a6%ac%eb%af%b8%ec%97%84-%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-19T05:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“時間의 主人”은 누구인가?]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=81919</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Economic_View/~3/o3mGwGQ3wwQ/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-19T02:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[그보다도 더 큰 이익은 노동자 자신의 시간과 고용주의 시간 사이에 드디어 명백한 구별이 생겼다는 점이다. 노동자는 이제 자기가 판매하는 시간이 언제 끝나고 언제부터 자기 자신의 시간이 시작되는가를 알고 있으며, 그리고 이것을 미리부터 정확히 알고 있음으로써 자기 자신의 시간을 자기 자신의 목적을 위해 미리 배정할 수 있게 된다.(공장감독관 보고서, 1859년 10월 31일, p52) 그것(공장법)은 노동자들을 자기 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for June 18, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8498</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-june-18-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T16:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Home works with multiple voice assistants? Google claims that its Home products only work with Google Assistant. Sonos, however, disagrees, and to prove it has even offered to demonstrate how its own technology supports both Alexa and Google Assistant on the same device. This back-and-forth all came to light earlier this week as part of a U.S. Senate […]
The post IoT news of the week for June 18, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.12.12, 5.10.45, and 5.4.127]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860264/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860264/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:44:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.12.12, 5.10.45, and 5.4.127 stable kernels have been released.
They contain important fixes, as usual, so users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Protecting control dependencies with volatile_if()]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860037/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860037/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T15:36:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Memory ordering issues are, as Linus Torvalds recently
observed, "the rocket science of CS".  Understanding
memory ordering is increasingly necessary to write scalable code, so kernel
developers often find themselves having to become rocket scientists.  The
subtleties associated with control dependencies turn out to be an
especially tricky sort of rocket.  A recent discussion about how to force
control dependencies to be observed shows the sorts of difficulties that
arise in this area.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860260/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860260/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T14:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (aspnet-runtime, aspnet-runtime-3.1, chromium, drupal, intel-ucode, nginx, opera, python-django, radare2, thefuck, and vivaldi), Debian (jetty9), Fedora (dogtag-pki and pki-core), openSUSE (htmldoc and postgresql10), Oracle (dhcp), SUSE (apache2, caribou, jetty-minimal, libxml2, postgresql12, python-PyJWT, python-rsa, python-urllib3, thunderbird, tpm2.0-tools, xstream, and xterm), and Ubuntu (grub2-signed, grub2-unsigned and libxml2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Carbon 6세대 디스플레이 교체기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-6gen-display-replacement/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-6gen-display-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2018년 중순에 구입한 싱크패드를 계속 사용하고 있었다. 구입할 당시에 가장 고민했던 부분이 바로 디스플레이였는데 Costco에서 판매하는 모델은 밝기가 상당히 낮은 디스플레이를 탑재하고 있었다. 들고 다니는 용도라서 FHD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Carbon 6세대 디스플레이 교체기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/post/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-6gen-display-replacement/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/post/lenovo-thinkpad-x1-6gen-display-replacement/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T13:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2018년 중순에 구입한 싱크패드를 계속 사용하고 있었다. 구입할 당시에 가장 고민했던 부분이 바로 디스플레이였는데 Costco에서 판매하는 모델은 밝기가 상당히 낮은 디스플레이를 탑재하고 있었다. 들고 다니는 용도라서 FHD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[南國의 여름]]></title>
        <id>http://wallflower.egloos.com/4198236</id>
        <link href="http://wallflower.egloos.com/4198236"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T08:49:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어린 시절부터 내 마음을 사로잡는 표현이 바로 남국(南國)이었다. 남국과 어우러져서 남양(南洋)이라는 표현 역시 내 정서를 압도하곤 했다. 부산에서 어린 시절을 보낼 때, 용두산 공원에 가면 먼 부도에 정박한 상선들이나 크루즈 여객선들을 볼 수 있었다. 당시에 우.... 글 전체보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이택광</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[손정민 사건 리포트(하): 유튜브 음모론 받아쓰기 언론들]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81062</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/PMmmuxXWdlw/81062"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T05:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[서울 반포한강공원에서 실종된 뒤 숨진 채 발견된 고 손정민 씨 사망사건은 언론의 큰 관심 사안이었습니다. 현장상황을 기록한 폐쇄회로영상 등 객관적 증거가 나오지 않았고, 사건 당일 손 씨와 술을 마신 친구 A씨도 정확한 기억이 없어 실체적 진실이 쉽게 드러나지 않았기 때문입니다. 경찰 수사에 이목이 집중됐고, 일부 언론과 유튜브 채널은 확인되지 않은 정보를 여과 없이 중계하며 논란을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieving full MCU partition isolation: Fundamentals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470190</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/achieving-full-mcu-partition-isolation-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-18T01:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is very little a hacker can do from inside of a partition that is fully isolated from the rest of the system. Achieving full...
The post Achieving full MCU partition isolation: Fundamentals appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ralph Moore</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10.0b3 is available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/bwg2ghZoNfI/python-3100b3-is-available.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/bwg2ghZoNfI/python-3100b3-is-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T21:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Summer is almost here (at least in half of the planet) and Python 3.10 is finishing baking in the oven. For those of you that want to taste it before is finally ready (and if you are a library developer, you certainly do!) you can have the second-to-last beta now, but be careful as is very hot 
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3100b3/
This is a beta preview of Python 3.10
Python 3.10 is still in development. 3.10.0b3 is the third of four planned beta release previews. Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their projects to support the new feature release.
We **strongly encourage** maintainers of third-party Python projects to **test with 3.10** during the beta phase and report issues f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reference design simplifies industrial robotic motor control]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470219</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/reference-design-simplifies-industrial-robotic-motor-control/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T20:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new reference design speeds development of end-of-arm tooling for industrial robotics using single-axis servo controller/driver module with integrated motion control. Trinamic, now part of...
The post Reference design simplifies industrial robotic motor control appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maurizio Di Paolo Emilio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Landlock (finally) sets sail]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859908/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859908/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T18:47:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel development is not for people who lack persistence; changes can take
a number of revisions and a lot of time to make it into a mainline
release.  Even so, the story of the Landlock security module, developed by
Mickaël Salaün, seems like an extreme case; this code was merged for 5.13 after
more than five years of development and 34 versions of the patch set.
This sandboxing mechanism has evolved considerably since LWN covered version 3 of the patch set in
2016, so a look at what Landlock has become is warranted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supporting Miguel Ojeda’s Work on Rust in the Linux Kernel (Prossimo blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860160/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860160/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T18:17:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Prossimo project has announced
that it has contracted with Miguel Ojeda to work on Rust in the Linux kernel
for the next year.  Prossimo is a new name for the memory-safety
projects being run by the Internet Security Research
Group (ISRG), which is the organization behind the Let's Encrypt certificate authority
(CA) project.  Google provided the funds to enable Ojeda to work full-time
on the project starting back in April.


The Linux kernel is at the heart of the modern Internet, from
servers to client devices. It’s on the front line for processing network
data and other forms of input. As such, vulnerabilities in the Linux kernel
can have a wide-ranging impact, putting security and privacy for people,
organizations, and devices at risk. Since it’s written largely in the C
language, which is not memory-safe, memory safety vulnerabilities such as
buffer overflows and use-after-frees are a constant concern. By making it
possible to write parts of the Linux kernel in Rust, which is memory-safe,
we can entirely eliminate memory safety vulnerabilities from certain
components, such as drivers.


We have previously covered another
Prossimo project, which provides funding for
Rustls development, as well as Ojeda's work
on Rust in the kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add dialogs and slash commands to your Google Workspace Chat bots]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/WEp4WfKnRQI/add-dialogs-and-slash-commands-to-your-google-workspace-chat-bots.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/WEp4WfKnRQI/add-dialogs-and-slash-commands-to-your-google-workspace-chat-bots.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T17:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Charles Maxson, Developer Advocate
 
Developing your own custom Google Chat bot is a great way for users and teams to interact with your solutions and services both directly and within context as they collaborate in Chat. More specifically, Chat bots can be used in group conversations to streamline workflows, assist with activities in the context of discussions, and provide information and notifications in real time. Chat bots can also be used in direct messages, offering a new way to optimize workflows and personal productivity, such as managing project tasks or reporting time activity. Because use cases for bots are varied,  you can consistently reach a growing audience of Chat users over time, directly where they work and uh-hum, chat. 
Once you’ve identified your specific use…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gossip Dissemination]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/gossip-dissemination.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-of-distributed-systems/gossip-dissemination.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unmesh Joshi is completing another batch of his series on Patterns of
      Distributed Systems. First of these is Gossip Dissemination, which uses a
      random selection of nodes to pass on information to ensure it reaches all
      the nodes in the cluster without flooding the network
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEC – Best Practices for Designing Real-Time Embedded Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=13348</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/cec-best-practices-for-designing-real-time-embedded-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T14:05:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Development teams today are faced with the need to develop systems within smaller budgets, shorter timeframes and with more features. In order to succeed in this challenging environment, teams need to leverage best practices, which are procedures shown my experience to produce optimal results. In this course, we will explore modern day best practices that … Continue reading CEC – Best Practices for Designing Real-Time Embedded Systems
CEC – Best Practices for Designing Real-Time Embedded Systems first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860128/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860128/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T13:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (gnupnp and postgresql), Fedora (dino, microcode_ctl, and xen), Mageia (apache, gsoap, libgd, openssh, perl-Image-ExifTool, python-bleach, and qt4 and qtsvg5), openSUSE (chromium, containerd, docker, runc, djvulibre, htmldoc, kernel, libjpeg-turbo, libopenmpt, libxml2, spice, squid, and ucode-intel), Red Hat (dhcp and glib2), SUSE (apache2, inn, java-1_8_0-openjdk, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (nettle).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimizing device standby power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470246</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/minimizing-device-standby-power/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T13:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With IoT, connectivity becomes increasingly important as it allows mantaining proper communication and, as a result, standby consumption is turning into a real challenge. Smartphones...
The post Minimizing device standby power appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maurizio Di Paolo Emilio</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[짐 크레이머 전기차 주식 추천, 짐 크레이머는 테슬라보다 포드를 추천하는데…]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581219</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581219/%ec%a7%90-%ed%81%ac%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b4%eb%a8%b8-%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:43:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Risks Are Often Underestimated — It Is Not Only the Chip Crisis that Threatens Embedded Manufacturers]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.segger.com/risks-are-often-underestimated-it-is-not-only-the-chip-crisis-that-threatens-embedded-manufacturers/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.segger.com/risks-are-often-underestimated-it-is-not-only-the-chip-crisis-that-threatens-embedded-manufacturers/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the chip crisis and the standstill of assembly lines in the automotive industry, supplier management has become a hot topic. Beyond the repeated shortage of semiconductors, there are other risks worth taking into consideration when selecting suppliers. The quality of a supplier for embedded hardware and software can determine the success or failure of a project. This article describes countermeasures for common threats and concludes how SEGGER’s emPower OS is the perfect risk minimizer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>SEGGER Microcontroller RSS Feed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: The IoT goes to Congress]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8494</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-the-iot-goes-to-congress/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T10:00:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello! This week we start with Congress, where the U.S. Senate Judiciary Committee held hearings related to interoperability and lock-in tied to smart home devices. We drew special attention to testimony by Jonathan Zittrain, who wrote a long, but insightful statement about the development of the web, the benefits gained when using interoperable protocols, and […]
The post Podcast: The IoT goes to Congress appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[손정민 사건 리포트(상): 클릭 저널리즘과 음모론의 탄생]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81040</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/6WKQoqBUoFg/81040"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T05:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[서울 반포한강공원에서 실종된 뒤 숨진 채 발견된 고 손정민 씨 사망사건은 언론의 큰 관심 사안이었습니다. 현장상황을 기록한 폐쇄회로영상 등 객관적 증거가 나오지 않았고, 사건 당일 손 씨와 술을 마신 친구 A씨도 정확한 기억이 없어 실체적 진실이 쉽게 드러나지 않았기 때문입니다. 경찰 수사에 이목이 집중됐고, 일부 언론과 유튜브 채널은 확인되지 않은 정보를 여과 없이 중계하며 논란을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SLAM without a PhD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470169</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/slam-without-a-phd/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T01:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry leaders including Microsoft, Google and Facebook have all integrated Simultaneous Localization and Mapping (SLAM) technology into their AR/VR headsets using low power, embedded processors, so why can’t robot developers do the same?
The post SLAM without a PhD appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Owen Nicholson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 17, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859052/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859052/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-17T00:58:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 17, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Fedora and supply-chain attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859965/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859965/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T21:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The specter of more events like the SolarWinds
supply-chain attacks is something that concerns many in our
communities—and beyond.  Linux distributions provide a supply chain that
obviously needs to be protected against attackers injecting malicious code
into the update stream.  This problem recently came up on the Fedora devel
mailing list, which led to a discussion covering a few different topics.
For the most part, Fedora users are protected against such attacks, which
is not to say there is nothing more to be done, of course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연도별 크린토피아 매출 및 크린토피아 가맹점수 추이]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581220</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581220/%ec%97%b0%eb%8f%84%eb%b3%84-%ed%81%ac%eb%a6%b0%ed%86%a0%ed%94%bc%ec%95%84-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T18:00:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860005/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860005/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T15:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.12.11, 5.10.44, 5.4.126, 4.19.195, 4.14.237, 4.9.273, and 4.4.273 have been released.  They all contain
important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비즈니스 모델 못지않게 광고 모델 중요성을 보여준 크린토피아 사례]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581197</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581197/%ed%81%ac%eb%a6%b0%ed%86%a0%ed%94%bc%ec%95%84-%ec%82%ac%eb%a1%80"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T15:25:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/860004/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/860004/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T15:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (prosody, python-urllib3, and xen), Fedora (dino, dotnet3.1, dotnet5.0, and vmaf), Oracle (gupnp, kernel, and kernel-container), Red Hat (gupnp), Scientific Linux (kernel), SUSE (java-1_8_0-openjdk, kernel, snakeyaml, and xorg-x11-libX11), and Ubuntu (bluez).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software supply chain remains vulnerable]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470211</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/software-supply-chain-remains-vulnerable/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SolarWinds megahack underscores what security mavens have been warning about for years: The software supply chain is complex, vulnerable, somewhat invisible and insufficiently protected....
The post Software supply chain remains vulnerable appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ann R. Thryft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t buy a smart lock any time soon]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8484</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/dont-buy-a-smart-lock-any-time-soon/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T13:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Earlier this week, Level introduced a new, less-expensive smart lock. It’s smaller and, at $249, cheaper than the current $329 Level Lock Touch Edition. Level removed the touch and keycard functionality to reduce the cost and price on this new model. I haven’t reviewed it as was just announced and I’m sure it works as […]
The post Don’t buy a smart lock any time soon appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개성공단 북한 노동자는 ‘최저임금’ 적용 받을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81025</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/gFN5O7XL-3A/81025"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T09:47:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 북한 기업이 남한 기업을 상대로 남한 법원에서 패소 판결을 받았다. 북한 기업이 남한 기업을 상대로 한 첫 국내 민사소송이라는 이유로 언론의 주목을 받았다. 하지만 특별히 이 판결 자체로 주목하거나 비판할 점은 없어 보인다. 패소한 이유가 증거가 부족했다는 것인데, 그런 이유로 패소하는 재판은 남한 기업 사이의 소송에서도 비일비재하기 때문이다. 그럼에도 불구하고 이 판결을 통해 북한을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Audacity gets a CLA]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859599/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859599/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T00:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Audacity multi-track audio
editor and recorder got its start in the previous century;  it is a popular
application that is available for multiple platforms, and it is licensed under the
GPLv2 or later.  But Audacity has been acquired by 
a newly
formed organization called Muse Group;
that event has caused something of an uproar in its community.  The problem, at
least in part, is
the new Contributor
License Agreement (CLA) required to contribute to Audacity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid Anxiety and Hybrid Optimism: The Near Future of Work]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1046</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/hybrid-anxiety-optimism-future-of-work/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T00:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to the pandemic, tech companies have announced a wide range of policies concerning remote work. Apple, Facebook, Google, and Salesforce have embraced hybrid models, allowing for some remote work but requiring that all employees work from the office on certain days (or that certain employees work from the office every day). On the... Read More
The post Hybrid Anxiety and Hybrid Optimism: The Near Future of Work appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Besart Copa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extinction Isn’t an End: Mining Ancient Innovation for Future Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=906</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/extinction-mining-ancient-innovation-future-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-16T00:00:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The study of biology has yielded incalculable human riches: We selectively breed animals and plants, we avert apocalyptic pandemics and ecosystem collapses, we forecast debilitating illnesses, we prolong our lifespans, and in some cases, we understand and control our own bodies down to the level of individual bits of our DNA. All of this is... Read More
The post Extinction Isn’t an End: Mining Ancient Innovation for Future Solutions appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Richardson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FSFE: REUSE Booster helps Free Software projects with licensing and copyright]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859885/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859885/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T18:50:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Free Software Foundation Europe introduces REUSE
Booster. REUSE is a set of best
practices to make Free Software licensing easier. "With REUSE
Booster, we go one step further. We invite Free Software projects to register for getting help by the
FSFE's legal experts. As the name suggests, this will boost the process of
adopting the best practices as well as general understanding of licensing
and copyright." The registration deadline is July 8.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[linux.dev mailboxes for kernel developers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859859/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859859/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T16:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konstantin Ryabitsev has announced
a new service providing @linux.dev mailboxes for people to use
with kernel development.  The documentation page
has more information.  "This is a BETA offering. Currently, it is
only available to people listed in the MAINTAINERS file. We hope to be able
to offer it to everyone else who can demonstrate an ongoing history of
contributions to the Linux kernel (patches, git commits, mailing list
discussions, etc)."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859842/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859842/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:50:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (389-ds-base, dhcp, firefox, glib2, hivex, kernel, postgresql, qemu-kvm, qt5-qtimageformats, samba, and xorg-x11-server), Fedora (kernel and kernel-tools), Oracle (kernel and postgresql), Red Hat (dhcp and gupnp), Scientific Linux (gupnp and postgresql), SUSE (postgresql10 and xterm), and Ubuntu (imagemagick).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A possible copyright-policy change for glibc]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/859802/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/859802/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T14:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNU C Library developers are asking
for comments on a proposal to stop requiring developers to assign their
copyrights to the Free Software Foundation.  This mirrors the recent change by GCC, except that the
community is being consulted first.  "The changes to accept patches
with or without FSF copyright assignment 
would be effective on August 2nd, and would apply to all open branches.

The glibc stewards, like the GCC SC, continue to affirm the principles of
Free Software, and that will never change."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국 스킨케어 시장을 석권한 시세이도 중국 전략 4가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581187</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581187/%ec%8b%9c%ec%84%b8%ec%9d%b4%eb%8f%84-%ec%a4%91%ea%b5%ad-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T13:54:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ESP RainMaker now in Arduino]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/cf1474526172</id>
        <link href="https://medium.com/the-esp-journal/esp-rainmaker-now-in-arduino-cf1474526172?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T13:43:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its launch in April 2020, we have been making quite some improvements to ESP RainMaker, mostly around the feature set. Along with…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-access edge computing standards combine to offset security threats]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470155</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/multi-access-edge-computing-standards-combine-to-offset-security-threats/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T13:18:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end Multi-access Edge Computing (MEC) security requires consideration of the impact on the elements coming from all stakeholders involved in the system and all available...
The post Multi-access edge computing standards combine to offset security threats appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dario Sabella</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Otis is rethinking elevators for smarter buildings]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8468</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/otis-is-rethinking-elevators-for-smarter-buildings/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T13:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Climate change, COVID, and the need for smarter, more productive buildings has prompted elevator (and escalator) maker Otis to redesign the elevator. This week, the company launched what it calls its Gen3 elevator platform, which lets architects and/or building managers add smarts, voice interaction, gesture control, and predictive routing to their elevators. Some of the […]
The post Otis is rethinking elevators for smarter buildings appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Technology Saves the World]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1024</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/technology-saves-the-world/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T11:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Only 15 months ago — March 13, 2020 — COVID-19 became a national emergency in the United States. My assumption at the time was that COVID lockdowns could extend as long as five years, the previous speed record for modern vaccine development, with many millions of deaths — a generational cataclysm. While COVID certainly has... Read More
The post Technology Saves the World appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amelia Salyers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국민의힘의 감사원 조사 ‘꼼수’와 언론의 이중잣대]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=81002</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/l3Hgy_R3CYg/81002"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T04:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[참여연대·민주사회를 위한 변호사모임이 3월 2일 한국토지주택공사(LH) 직원들의 광명·시흥 신도시 사전투기 의혹을 발표하면서 불거진 부동산 투기 의혹은 공직 사회 전반으로 확산됐습니다. 청와대와 여당이 전수조사를 자처하면서 진화에 나섰고, 야당은 국토부 장관 사퇴와 국정조사까지 요구하며 공세를 펼쳤습니다. 특히 국회의원 부동산 전수조사 요구가 거세지자 더불어민주당과 국민의힘은 3월 23일 ‘3+3협의체’를 구성해 국회의원 부동산 전수조사·LH 특검·국정조사 추진을 논의했으나 조사주체, 방식 등에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬데믹 이후 트렌드를 보여주는 IF 디자인 어워드 2021 수상작 10선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581165</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581165/if-%eb%94%94%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%b8-%ec%96%b4%ec%9b%8c%eb%93%9c-2021-%ec%88%98%ec%83%81%ec%9e%91-10%ec%84%a0"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On Workplace Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=985</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/on-workplace-productivity/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What does it mean to be productive? At the beginning of the pandemic, when many workers went remote, some managers were tempted to start counting things — whether hours, objects, or other things. But they’re about 100 years and two industrial revolutions too late: In the mechanical and electrical revolutions, productivity was indeed a measure... Read More
The post On Workplace Productivity appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Besart Copa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Marshall Plan to Solve the Global Vaccine Shortfall]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=993</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/marshall-plan-to-solve-global-vaccine-shortfall/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While COVID-19 vaccinations in the U.S. are continuing apace, calls are growing for a more ambitious strategy to rapidly vaccinate the entire world, and especially in developing nations. Legal proceedings around this issue were triggered in October last year, when India and South Africa circulated a WTO Trade-Related Aspects on IP Rights (TRIPS) petition calling... Read More
The post A Marshall Plan to Solve the Global Vaccine Shortfall appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Besart Copa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[In Online Ed, Content Is No Longer King—Cohorts Are]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=927</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/cohort-based-courses/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:05:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re in a post-content age. It used to be that original educational content was scarce: a decade ago, such content was a major selling point for universities and accelerators.  Today, however, educational content is cheap and abundant on YouTube, in newsletters, on blogs, and on social media. People view learning-related content on YouTube 500 million... Read More
The post In Online Ed, Content Is No Longer King—Cohorts Are appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Finance: What It Is, Why It Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=954</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/cryptos-fourth-wave-defi-poised-for-breakthrough/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s been a lot of hype, buzz, skepticism, confusion, and excitement around decentralized finance aka “DeFi,” the ecosystem of blockchain-enabled products and services that replace traditional financial intermediaries with freely accessible, autonomous, and transparent software.  While it’s still early days for DeFi (just a couple years in), its associated economy is already large and consequential:... Read More
The post Decentralized Finance: What It Is, Why It Matters appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Law As Code: A Legal System Shaped By Software]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=745</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/law-as-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Americans spend more on legal fees than any other country in the world. In the United States, legal costs — the price of resolving disputes — made up around 2.3 percent of the entire economy, totaling approximately $429 billion just five years ago.  But the high price of justice isn’t an abstract economic concept. A... Read More
The post Law As Code: A Legal System Shaped By Software appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Choosing Your North Star Metric]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=771</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/north-star-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When learning to ride a motorcycle, you’re taught that where your eyes go, your bike goes. Look to your right and you’ll drift right. Look left, go left. There’s a lot of power in where you focus your attention.  That’s why nailing your North Star Metric(s) — the top-line metrics that all company priorities are... Read More
The post Choosing Your North Star Metric appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Games Is Instant]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=763</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/instant-games/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:01:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 2000s, hundreds of millions of people devoured web games like Bejeweled and FarmVille, powered by Adobe Flash. In contrast to siloed console or PC games, these browser-based Flash games were incredibly accessible: they could be played instantly by clicking a web link and shared easily via email or messages. Yet as smartphones and... Read More
The post The Future of Games Is Instant appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Quick Pulse Check on Direct Listings]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=1027</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/direct-listings-pulse-check/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:01:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[And then there were… six. Over the past three years, we’ve had exactly six direct listings since Spotify pioneered their use in its current form by technology companies. It led to many questions around the what, the why, and the how of direct listings — as well as the differences and tradeoffs between all the... Read More
The post A Quick Pulse Check on Direct Listings appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Amelia Salyers</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Great Zoom Migration Upended the Housing Market]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=879</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/the-zoom-migration-impacts-housing/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-15T00:01:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The three most important attributes of property are location, location, location. This expression has been around for a while, but 2020 to 2021 — emerging from COVID-19 — has been turning the maxim upside down. Now, maybe it’s WiFi, location, location. COVID is spurring one of the most profound changes in commercial and residential real... Read More
The post How the Great Zoom Migration Upended the Housing Market appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lauren Murrow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Application Optimization: Simple Edits Speeded Up PVS-Studio and Reduced Memory Consumption by 70%]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0836/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/4Qu7879lC5o/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We know many ways to detect performance problems, such as extremely low speed and high memory consumption. Usually tests, developers, or testers detect such applications' drawbacks. In the worst case, users find weaknesses and report back. Alas, detecting defects is only the first step. Next, we should localize the problem. Otherwise, we won't solve it. Here comes a question - how to find weak points that lead to excessive memory consumption and slow down in a large project? Are there such at all? Maybe it's not about the application? So now you're reading a story how PVS-Studio C# developers encountered a similar problem and managed to solve it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hybrid supercapacitors offer energy storage alternative]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470216</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/hybrid-supercapacitors-offer-energy-storage-alternative/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T19:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The rechargeable battery and the supercapacitor each have relative pros and cons, but a hybrid design that merges both technologies into a single structure can...
The post Hybrid supercapacitors offer energy storage alternative appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Schweber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling telemetry for custom models in Intel DevCloud for the Edge]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4470131</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/enabling-telemetry-for-custom-models-in-intel-devcloud-for-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While edge computing has seen an exponential growth in the last few years, developers are experiencing issues in implementing AI and edge software solutions. Here’s...
The post Enabling telemetry for custom models in Intel DevCloud for the Edge appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daya Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our latest updates on Fully Homomorphic Encryption]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/9T13AYszQNQ/our-latest-updates-on-fully-homomorphic-encryption.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/9T13AYszQNQ/our-latest-updates-on-fully-homomorphic-encryption.html"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T17:00:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Miguel Guevara, Product Manager, Privacy and Data Protection Office.
   

 As developers, it’s our responsibility to help keep our users safe online and protect their data. This starts with building products that are secure by default, private by design, and put users in control. Everything we make at Google is underpinned by these principles, and we’re proud to be an industry leader  in developing, deploying, and scaling new privacy-preserving technologies that make it possible to learn valuable insights and create helpful experiences while protecting our users’ privacy.  
That’s why today, we are excited to announce that we’re open-sourcing a first-of-its-kind, general-purpose transpiler for Fully Homomorphic Encryption (FHE), which will enable developers to compute on encrypte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We now know what we don’t know about Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=8465</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/we-now-know-what-we-dont-know-about-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are still a lot of unknowns with regard to the new Matter interoperability standard, but we have a much better sense of what we don’t know in the wake of a panel hosted this week by Silicon Labs. During the event, which I moderated (and was paid by Silicon Labs to both create and moderate), we heard from product […]
The post We now know what we don’t know about Matter appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[근래 두드러진 아마존, 월마트 등 유통업체 광고사업 강화 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581156</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581156/%ec%9c%a0%ed%86%b5%ec%97%85%ec%b2%b4-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0%ec%82%ac%ec%97%85-%ea%b0%95%ed%99%94"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T12:18:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[루시드 전기차가 거실같은 미래 컨셉의 루시드 전시장을 만든 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=581141</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/581141/%eb%a3%a8%ec%8b%9c%eb%93%9c-%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8%ec%9d%98-%eb%af%b8%eb%9e%98-%ec%bb%a8%ec%85%89-%eb%a3%a8%ec%8b%9c%eb%93%9c-%ec%a0%84%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-06-14T11:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>