<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2021-11-19T20:18:38.669Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.11.3</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.com/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 19, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9350</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-19-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T18:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung SmartThings adds whole-home energy monitoring: It seems like there’s a gold rush of sorts going on in electricity monitoring. The latest prospector is Samsung SmartThings, which this week announced three new partnerships to bring whole-home energy monitoring to customers. The company says products and services from Copper Labs, Eyedro, and Wattbuy are now integrated with […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 19, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: FPGA launches, poor IoT vulnerability disclosure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471629</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-fpga-launches-poor-iot-vulnerability-disclosure/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:54:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes two new FPGA announcements, one for entry level and the other for HPC, plus a look at how the IoT industry is doing on vulnerability disclosure, the latest on Nvidia and Arm, plus news of products, funding, people and events.
The post embedded news week: FPGA launches, poor IoT vulnerability disclosure appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] In search of an appropriate RLIMIT_MEMLOCK default]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876288/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876288/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T17:41:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One does not normally expect a lot of disagreement over a 13-line patch
that effectively tweaks a single line of code.  Occasionally, though, such
a patch can expose a disagreement over how the behavior of the kernel
should be managed.  This patch
from Drew DeVault, who is evidently taking a break from stirring up
the npm community, is a case in point.  It brings to light the question
of how  the kernel community should pick default values for configurable
parameters like resource limits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876528/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876528/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T14:29:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (chromium, grafana, kubectl-ingress-nginx, and opera), Debian (netkit-rsh and salt), Fedora (freeipa and samba), Mageia (opensc, python-django-filter, qt4, tinyxml, and transfig), openSUSE (opera and transfig), Red Hat (devtoolset-11-annobin, devtoolset-11-binutils, and llvm-toolset:rhel8), SUSE (php72 and php74), and Ubuntu (mailman and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renesas enters FPGA market with sub-5000 gate devices for consumer & IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471621</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/renesas-enters-fpga-market-with-sub-5000-gate-devices-for-consumer-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T11:49:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Renesas ForgeFPGA family targets high-volume applications needing less than 5,000 logic gates, with initial device sizes costing less than $0.50 in volume and with standby power of less than 20 microamps.
The post Renesas enters FPGA market with sub-5000 gate devices for consumer & IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lynx MOSA.ic now manages multiple hybrid IT/OT mission critical systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471610</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/lynx-mosa-ic-now-manages-multiple-hybrid-it-ot-mission-critical-systems/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T10:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lynx Software Technologies’ MOSA.ic now adds more flexible management of multiple devices and systems from cloud or on-premise servers, and provides air-gap between OT and IT networks.
The post Lynx MOSA.ic now manages multiple hybrid IT/OT mission critical systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[또! 공군 성추행 은폐 의혹 (ft. 보수 언론의 무관심)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82712</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82712"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T09:27:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 5월 성추행과 군의 2차 가해로 숨진 이 모 중사가 사망하기 열흘 전 또 다른 공군 부사관이 비슷한 피해를 당한 뒤 사망했다는 사실이 뒤늦게 드러났습니다. 군인권센터는 11월 15일 공군이 강제추행 피해 정황을 확인하고도 피해 부사관을 ‘스트레스로 인한 사망’으로 종결했다가 가해자를 늑장 기소했다는 의혹을 제기했습니다. 공군은 이 중사 사망으로 비판이 높아지자 재발 방지를 대대적으로 약속하면서도 다른 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AP 특파원의 여섯 가지 조건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82687</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82687"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T08:47:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AP특파원 4명 중 3명은 미국 내에 있는 1) AP 지국에서 기자로서 경력을 시작한다. 지역에서는 고등학교 운동 경기나 주의회 등을 취재하러 다니고, 방송이나 야간 근무도 하며 온갖 잡일을 한다. 그런 생활을 하다가 2) ‘AP 테스트’라고 불리는 글쓰기 시험을 보고, 이 시험에 합격한 이들은 3) 뉴욕으로 와서 포린데스크나 월드데스크에서 국제뉴스 편집자로 일한다. 그렇게 편집자로 활동하다가 자리가 나면 4) 특파원으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[야구장, 축구장엔 수만 명씩 모이는데 집회는 500명 미만?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82676</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82676"/>
        <updated>2021-11-19T07:16:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[코로나19 하에서 시민들이 사회적 거리두기를 해온 지가 벌써 내년이면 2년이 되어갑니다. 그 동안에 많은 시민들은 2020년 작년 보수세력의 ‘광복절 집회’와 뒤이은 수도권의 폭발적인 감염 확산을 야기했다는 많은 언론보도를 보셨을 것입니다. 또, 지난 11월 13일, 민주노총이 서울시의 전면 금지에도 불구하고 ‘전국노동자대회’를 불시에 동대문에서 개최했고, 그 일대 교통이 마비되어 결혼식에 늦었다는 사연도 언론에서 접하셨을 것입니다. 아무리 ‘위드 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xilinx doubles Alveo HBM, adds clustering for HPC & big data workloads]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471600</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/xilinx-doubles-alveo-hbm-adds-clustering-for-hpc-big-data-workloads/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T21:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xilinx said its new Alveo U55C card is purpose-built for HPC and big data workloads, offering the highest compute density and HBM capacity in the Alveo accelerator portfolio.
The post Xilinx doubles Alveo HBM, adds clustering for HPC & big data workloads appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Carla car simulator helped us level up the static analysis of Unreal Engine 4 projects]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0888/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0888/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the mechanisms of static analysis is method annotations of popular libraries. Annotations provide more information about functions during errors detecting. CARLA is an impressive open-source project in C++ that helped us implement this mechanism to our analyzer. Subsequently, the simulator became a test-target for the improved PVS-Studio static analyzer. CARLA is an open-source simulator for autonomous driving research. CARLA has been developed from the ground up to support development, training, and validation of autonomous driving systems. In addition to open-source code and protocols, CARLA provides open digital assets (urban layouts, buildings, vehicles) that were created for this purpose and can be used freely. The simulation platform supports flexible specification of sensor suites and environmental conditions. The project is cross-platform and contains almost 78,000 lines of C++ code. In the project repository, we also found code written in Python, XML, YAML, DOS Batch, CMake and other languages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What to do in response to a kernel warning]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876209/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876209/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:39:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel provides a number of macros internally to allow code to generate
warnings when something goes wrong.  It does not, however, provide a lot of
guidance regarding what should happen when a warning is issued.  Alexander
Popov recently posted a
patch series adding an option for the system's response to warnings;
that series seems unlikely to be applied in anything close to its current
form, but it did succeed in provoking a discussion on how warnings should
be handled.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two more stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876425/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876425/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T17:13:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released two more stable kernels. 5.14.20 reverts three patches from the
5.14.19 release, while 5.10.80 is one of the
massive updates mentioned yesterday.  The
other massive release mentioned, 5.15.3, is still under
review and can be expected in the next day or two.  As usual, the
kernels released contain important fixes and users should upgrade.

Update: 5.15.3 was also released.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[With Decentralized Identity, Your Reputation Travels With You Across Cyberspace]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2484</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/decentralized-identity-on-chain-reputation/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T15:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the second installment of a two-part series on reputation systems in web3. Read part one here. Web3 is based on the premise that each internet user will have a unique internet identifier, like an email address, that can be natively linked to any piece of software and stored on a blockchain. As part... Read More
The post With Decentralized Identity, Your Reputation Travels With You Across Cyberspace appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Scott Kominers and Jad Esber</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: McKinsey reevaluates IoT’s impact]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9347</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-mckinsey-reevaluates-iots-impact/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show has a lot of big numbers starting with $12.6 trillion, which is at the upper end of what McKinsey believes the economic impact from IoT will be by 2030. We cover the latest report, which is a reassessment of McKinsey’s famous 2015 report on the IoT that said it would be worth […]
The post Podcast: McKinsey reevaluates IoT’s impact appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876413/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876413/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T13:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (binutils, firefox, flatpak, freerdp, httpd, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, kernel, openssl, and thunderbird), Fedora (python-sport-activities-features, rpki-client, and vim), and Red Hat (devtoolset-10-annobin and devtoolset-10-binutils).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대화의 파토스와 에토스 vs. 글의 로고스]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82657</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82657"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T09:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[70년대 말 미국은 바야흐로 수사학의 르네상스였다고 해도 과언이 아니었다. 매년 수십 종의 그리스로마 수사학 저술들을 번역출간되면서 아리스토텔레스로부터 출발한 고전수사학이 본격적으로 부활했다. 마치 자신들에게 부재하는 글쓰기전통을 빠르게 채워 넣고자 하는 듯, 미국 대학들은 고전수사학의 내용과 형식을 대대적으로 차용하기 시작했다. 결국, 미국의 글쓰기 연구는 고대그리스 이소크라테스 학파의 문체술까지 거슬러올라가 전통을 확보하는 데 성공한다. 아리스토텔레스는 다양한 시민 활동 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[더팩트의 ‘스토킹’ 오보, 그걸 옹호하는 TV조선]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82648</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82648"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T08:21:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인터넷매체 ‘더팩트’가 11월 15일 오후 6시 7분 [단독/이재명 부인 김혜경 씨 ‘깜짝 변신’, ‘낙상 사고’ 후 첫 외출 포착]이라는 보도를 내놨습니다. 이재명 더불어민주당 대선후보 배우자 김혜경 씨가 낙상사고 6일 만에 외출하는 모습을 취재했다며 사진기사를 내보낸 겁니다. 더팩트가 사진 속 검은 망토 차림 여성을 ‘김혜경 씨’로 특정하면서 김 씨 낙상사고 이후 쏟아진 풍문이나 허위 조작 정보에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 18, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875755/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875755/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-18T00:28:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 18, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rollercoaster: group messaging for mix networks]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876239/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876239/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T19:36:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even encrypted data sent on the internet leaves some footprints—metadata
about where packets originate, where they are bound, and when they are sent. 
Mix networks are
meant to hide that metadata by routing packets through various intermediate
nodes to try to thwart the traffic analysis used by nation-state-level
adversaries to identify "opponents" of various kinds. Tor is perhaps the
best-known mix network, but there are others that make different
tradeoffs to increase the security of their users.  Rollercoaster
is a recently announced mechanism that extends the functionality of mix
networks in order to more efficiently communicate among groups.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build AI-powered customer conversations in Google Maps and Search with Google's Business Messages]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/build-ai-powered-customer-conversations.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/build-ai-powered-customer-conversations.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T18:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sean Falconer, Staff Developer Relations Engineer Sean Falconer 
 Google’s Business Messages let customers message a business directly from Google Search, Google Maps, and any brand-managed property. Developers of Business Messages can leverage tools like Dialogflow to create AI-powered conversational experiences, where customers can chat with lifelike virtual agents that understand, interact, and talk in natural ways. Meanwhile the business can leverage real life agents when needed. 
In this article, I’ll give a brief overview of Business Messages, how to get started developing with the platform, and then walkthrough how to set up an AI-powered conversion using the Bot-in-a-Box feature.  
Let’s get started! 
What is Google's Business Messages?
  
Business Messages is a mobile co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer IoT: vulnerability disclosure practice “unacceptably low”]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471591</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/consumer-iot-vulnerability-disclosure-practice-unacceptably-low/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Despite small year-on-year improvements, progress on vulnerability disclosure for consumer IoT security is unacceptably low according to the IoT Security Foundation. 
The post Consumer IoT: vulnerability disclosure practice “unacceptably low” appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876327/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876327/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T16:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (389-ds-base and libxml2), Debian (atftp, axis, and ntfs-3g), Fedora (digikam, freerdp, guacamole-server, and remmina), openSUSE (java-11-openjdk, kernel, samba, and tomcat), SUSE (firefox, java-11-openjdk, kernel, libarchive, samba, and tomcat), and Ubuntu (accountsservice, hivex, and openexr).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Controller for HomeKit: The smart home app for power users]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9330</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/controller-for-homekit-the-smart-home-app-for-power-users/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T15:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple iPhone users with a smart home are surely familiar with the HomeKit platform as well as Apple’s Home app. Home is a simple but effective way to manage and use HomeKit devices. And it works well. But there’s room for improvement and that’s exactly what Controller for HomeKit, a third-party iOS app, brings to […]
The post Controller for HomeKit: The smart home app for power users appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876285/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876285/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T13:19:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.14.19 and 5.4.160 stable kernels have been released;
these updates contain a huge number of important fixes.  The equally
massive 5.15.3
and 5.10.80
updates were also intended for release but, as the result of some problems
that turned up in testing, they will be going through one
more round of review first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting your embedded software against memory corruption]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471585</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/protecting-your-embedded-software-against-memory-corruption/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T12:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The aim of this article is to provide a software method that explains how to deal with corruption of memory data sets stored in non-volatile...
The post Protecting your embedded software against memory corruption appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lendaro Francucci</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[congatec and SYSGO team up for functional safety & security on COM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471576</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/congatec-and-sysgo-team-up-to-for-functional-safety-security-on-com/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T11:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[congatec and SYSGO partnership for Arm and x86 based computer-on-module (COM) solutions aims to simplify development process of safety and security-critical systems, with certification support for functional safety of electronic systems.
The post congatec and SYSGO team up for functional safety & security on COM appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Release 3.0 of the IoT Security Assurance Framework Announced]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21387</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/release-3-0-of-the-iot-security-assurance-framework-announced/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T09:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Business ready: extends use into supply chain and aligns with more security standards November 17th, 2021 The IoT Security Foundation today announced the availability of Release 3.0 of it's ever-popular IoT Security Assurance Framework. The Framework is a practical resource that helps IoT vendors provide fit-for-purpose security in their products and services. It is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[상속세 개정 논의에 부쳐: 가업상속공제와 물납제도 손봐야]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82639</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82639"/>
        <updated>2021-11-17T02:55:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기획재정부가 지난 12일 국회 기획재정위원회 조세소위원회에 ‘상속세 주요 쟁점에 대한 검토의견 보고서’를 제출했다. 정부의 상속세 개편 방향은 연부연납(*), 가업상속공제(*) 등 세부 내용을 담고 있으며, 국회는 이를 바탕으로 15일부터 상속세 개편 논의를 진행하고 있다. 극심한 불평등과 양극화에, 코로나19로 유래 없는 가혹한 경제 현실을 마주한 국민에게 소득재분배 기능을 하는 상속세 개편 논의는 매우 중요하다. 부의 집중과 편중 심화를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>경실련</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain Networks and the Human Factor: How to Know Whether They’re Accessible]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2497</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/blockchain-networks-and-the-human-factor-how-to-know-whether-theyre-accessible/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T23:30:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As blockchain technology rapidly gains the attention of a mass audience, the conversation is still centered solely around technical topics related to the scalability of a network — transactions per second, latency, and throughput, for example.  To successfully build consumer-scale experiences, however, developers must think beyond performance metrics and consider the human factor: Accessibility —... Read More
The post Blockchain Networks and the Human Factor: How to Know Whether They’re Accessible appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dieter Shirley and Benjamin Ebner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huge Storage Boxes Update]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=11819</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2021/11/16/huge-storage-boxes-update/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today I release a huge update of my storage boxes system for 3d-print. This update not only further improves the geometries of the models, but also extend the available sizes and variants. There are now 1000+ model files in the full set you can buy in the shop. As a buyer of one of the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Trojan Source and Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875964/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875964/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:50:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Trojan Source vulnerabilities have been
rippling through various development
communities since their disclosure on 
November 1.  The oddities that can arise when handling Unicode, and
bidirectional Unicode in particular, in a programming 
language have led Rust, for
example, to check for
the problematic code points in strings and comments and, by default,
refuse to compile if they are present.  Python has chosen a different path,
but work is underway to help inform programmers of the kinds of pitfalls that
Trojan Source has highlighted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio checks the code quality in the .NET Foundation projects: LINQ to DB]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0887/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0887/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The .NET Foundation is an independent organization, created by Microsoft, to support open-source projects around the DotNet platform. Currently, the organization gathered many libraries under its wing. We have already tested some of these libraries with the help of PVS-Studio. The next project to check with the analyzer - LINQ to DB.  LINQ to DB is a database access framework based on LINQ. LINQ to DB has collected the best of its predecessors. It allows you to work with various DBMS, whereas LINQ to SQL back in the day allowed you to work only with MS SQL. It's not as heavy and complicated as LINQ to SQL or Entity Framework. LINQ to DB provides more control and quick access to data. The framework is not that big: it's written in C# and contains more than 40,000 lines of code. LINQ to DB is also one of the .NET Foundation projects. We have previously checked the projects of this organization: Windows Forms, Xamarin.Forms, Teleric UI for UWP, etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[결론이 주는 함축]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222570517749</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222570517749"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T20:28:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주장해라. 그리고 그 근거를 제시하라. 특히 철학에서 더 그래야 한다. 이 간단한 주문 사항에 대해서 반발하는 이유가 도대체 무엇이란 말인가? 게다가 타당한 근거를 제시하라고 주문하지도 않았다. 그냥 주장했다면 적어도 그 이유나 논거를 제시해야 한다고 말했다. 그 다음이야 비로소 그 논거가 타당한지, 정당한지, 설득력이 있는지 따질 수 있다. 논증이 결여되어 있는, 즉 주장만이 있는 그 철학 분야에 대해 그 나름의 배경 지식을 갖고 있다면, 내 스스로 그 논증을 만들 수 있다. 그런데 이것이 가능하기 위해서도 단지 주장만 일방적으로 제시되어 있는지, 아니면 그 주장 배후에 암시적으로 그 주장에 대한 논거가 있는지 판단해야.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manage your passes from Google Pay’s Business Console]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/manage-your-passes-from-google-pay.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/manage-your-passes-from-google-pay.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by: 
Ryan Novas, Product Manager, Google Pay’s Business Console
Jose Ugia, Developer Relations Engineer, Google Pay
    

 Last year we launched Google Pay’s Business Console, a platform that helps developers discover, integrate with, and manage Google Pay features for their businesses. Since then, integrating Google Pay products has become easier and faster, with features like a common business profile and a unified dashboard.  
Today, we are adding Passes as a new section to Google Pay’s Business Console, so you can manage all your Google Pay resources from one place. You can find the new Passes section in the console’s left-hand navigation bar, and from there, access your tickets, loyalty programs, offers and other passes resources. 
Google Pay’s Business Console features a more …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876227/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876227/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T16:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libxml-security-java), Fedora (botan2), openSUSE (drbd-utils, kernel, and samba), Red Hat (kernel and webkit2gtk3), SUSE (drbd-utils and samba), and Ubuntu (vim).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scythe has a cool name and a good idea for security]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9327</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/scythe-has-a-cool-name-and-a-good-idea-for-security/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:55:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I talk to companies offering connected devices, I often ask them how they design their products with security in mind. I usually get a lot of information about encryption, secure elements on the chips, and bug bounty programs. Some of the companies I talk to actively hire researchers to do penetration testing on the […]
The post Scythe has a cool name and a good idea for security appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software quality demands both static code analysis and dynamic testing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471566</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/software-quality-demands-both-static-code-analysis-and-dynamic-testing/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T14:36:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Static code analysis and dynamic testing of executable software separately uncover only a part of the existing defects in code, requiring use of both methods...
The post Software quality demands both static code analysis and dynamic testing appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Royd Lüdtke</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대장동 의혹 언론인, 소속 언론은 어떻게 보도했을까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82628</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82628"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T09:43:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대장동 개발 특혜 의혹이 잦아들지 않고 있습니다. 경기경제신문이 2021년 8월 31일 ‘대장동 사업에 참여해 높은 수익을 올린 민간사업자 화천대유와 이재명 경기도지사와의 연관성을 제기’하는 의혹 보도를 내놓으면서 시작됐는데요. 장기표 당시 국민의힘 대선 예비후보가 9월 12일 해당 의혹을 언급하며 이재명 경기도지사에게 진상규명을 요구했고, 조선일보는 9월 13일 화천대유 설립에 참여한 언론인 출신 김만배 씨와 이재명 지사의 연관성을 제기하는 보도를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[포털 ‘퇴출’ 연합뉴스의 적반하장]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82619</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82619"/>
        <updated>2021-11-16T07:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 12일, 포털 내 언론의 입점과 퇴출을 심사하는 뉴스제휴평가위원회(이하 ‘제평위’)는 광고성 보도자료를 일반기사인 것처럼 포털에 전송한 연합뉴스에 ‘강등’을 결정했다. 한 언론사의 취재 결과 연합뉴스는 홍보사업팀을 통해 광고성 보도자료를 기사 형태로(이하 ‘기사형 광고’) 2,000여 건이나 포털에 전송해온 것으로 알려졌다. 연합뉴스는 이번 결정으로 인해 최소 1년간 포털 검색을 제외한 기사 송출을 할 수 없다. 연합뉴스는 제평위의 결정에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.9 hotfix release is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/11/python-399-hotfix-release-is-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/11/python-399-hotfix-release-is-now.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T22:09:00.004Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get it here: https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-399/

Python 3.9.9 is the eighth maintenance release of the legacy 3.9 series. Python 3.10 is now the latest feature release series of Python 3. Get the latest release of 3.10.x here.

3.9.9 was released out of schedule as a hotfix for an argparse regression in Python 3.9.8 which caused complex command-line tools to fail recognizing sub-commands properly. Details in BPO-45235. There are only three other bugfixes in this release compared to 3.9.8. See the changelog for details on what changed.

Upgrading to 3.9.9 is highly recommended if you’re running Python 3.9.8.

The next Python 3.9 maintenance release will be 3.9.10, currently scheduled for 2022-01-03.

We apologize for the inconvenience

…and still hope you’ll enjoy the new release!

Your friendly release team,

Ned Deily @nad

Steve Dower @steve.dower

Łukasz Langa @ambv]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.34.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876154/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876154/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T20:06:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.34.0 of the Git source-code management system is out.
"It is comprised of 834 non-merge commits since
v2.33.0, contributed by 109 people, 29 of which are new faces".  See
this
GitHub blog post for a look at some of the more significant changes in
this release:


	ort does just that: it’s a full-blown rewrite of the merge strategy
	that aims to emulate the same concepts behind recursive while
	avoiding many of its long-standing performance and correctness
	problems. In a merge containing many renames, ort outperforms
	recursive by 500x. For a series of similar merges (like in a rebase
	operation), the speedup is over 9000x since ort can cache and reuse
	results from previous merges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upload massive lists of products to Merchant Center using Centimani]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/upload-massive-lists-of-products-to-merchant-center-using-Centimani.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/upload-massive-lists-of-products-to-merchant-center-using-Centimani.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T17:21:00.036Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Hector Parra, Jaime Martínez, Miguel Fernandes, Julia Hernández
     Merchant Center lets merchants manage how their in-store and online product     inventory appears on Google. It allows them to reach hundreds of millions     of people looking to buy products like yours each day. 

    To upload their products, merchants can make use of feeds, that is, files     with a list of products in a specific format. These can be shared with     Merchant Center in different ways: using Google Sheets, SFTP or FTP shares,     Google Cloud Storage or manually through the user interface. These methods     work great for the majority of cases. But, if a merchant's product list     grows over time, they might reach the usage limits of the feeds. Depending     on the case, quota extensions could…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] 5.16 Merge window, part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875135/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875135/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T16:21:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released
5.16-rc1 and ended the 5.16 merge window on November 14, as
expected.  At that point, 12,321 non-merge changesets had been pulled into
the mainline; about 5,500 since our summary of
the first half of the merge window was written.  As is usually the case,
the patch mix in the latter part of the merge window tended more toward
fixes, but there were a number other changes as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876135/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876135/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:27:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ffmpeg and tomcat9), Fedora (et and kernel), openSUSE (binutils, rubygem-activerecord-5_1, samba, and tinyxml), Oracle (freerdp and httpd:2.4), Red Hat (devtoolset-11-gcc, gcc-toolset-10-binutils, kernel, kernel-rt, and kpatch-patch), and Scientific Linux (freerdp).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta’s flexible ReSkin sensor has untapped potential in the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9243</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/metas-flexible-reskin-sensor-has-untapped-potential-in-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T15:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While looking for new research on robotics last week, I caught the news from Facebook — I mean, Meta — about its new flexible sensor. It unveiled what it calls ReSkin technology for tactile sensing, created in conjunction with Carnegie Mellon University researchers. I think this technology could have a lot of potential in the smart […]
The post Meta’s flexible ReSkin sensor has untapped potential in the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news for the week ending Nov. 5, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9321</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-for-the-week-ending-nov-5-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T14:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s time for IoT platform vendors to shine! Enterprise IoT is moving out of its custom-built phase, and now customers are fine with off-the-shelf solutions with connectivity built in, according to a survey released last week from Oracle. Oracle surveyed 800 executives who have already deployed some IoT project about their thoughts, finding that how […]
The post IoT news for the week ending Nov. 5, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aarch64 Linux kernel fuzzing - syzkaller]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/9075747</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/9075747"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T13:04:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개요
https://github.com/google/syzkaller/
syzkaller 는 QEMU 기반으로 운영체제를 부팅한 후 Host 와 Guest 사이에 ssh 연결을 수립하고 system call fuzzing 을 수행하는 도구다. 일반적으로 syzkaller 는 x86 리눅스 위에서 테스트 대상 x86 리눅스를 QEMU로 테스트하는 방식으로 많이 사용된다. 그러나 이 글에서는 Aarch64 리눅스를 테스트하고자 한다.
전체적인 과정은 공식 메뉴얼을 따랐지만, 설명이 친절한 편이 아니어서 직접 삽질을 하면서 다시 정리해보았다.


1. Kernel Build (with KASAN)
테스트 하고자 하는 리눅스 커널을 빌드한다. 앞선 글에서 설명했으나, 그때는 별다른 보안 옵션을 설정하지 않았다. 지금은 KASAN, KCOV 등의 새니타이징 기능을 켜고 퍼즈 테스트 성능을 측정할 수 있도록 하는 부분이 다르다. 
일단 x86에서 진행하는 것이라면 크로스 컴파일을 통해 Aarch64 리눅스 커널을 빌드할 필요성이 있다. 크로스 컴파일을 위한 툴 체인을 받아야 한다. 
Linaro toolchain 
https://releases.linaro.org/components/toolchain/binaries/latest/aarch64-linux-gnu/
$ wget http://releases.linaro.org/components/toolchain/binaries/latest-7/aarch64-linux-gnu/gcc-linaro-7.5.0-2019.12-x86_64_aarch64-linux-gnu.tar.x…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advanced verification: unlocking the door to a new era of AI chips]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471570</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/advanced-verification-unlocking-the-door-to-a-new-era-of-ai-chips/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at how chip manufacturers will have to adjust hardware architecture in order to accommodate ever-growing demand for increased AI functionality. 
The post Advanced verification: unlocking the door to a new era of AI chips appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kiran Vittal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경제 공포 마케팅: OECD·IMF 보고서 왜곡하는 언론 (ft. 결론은 규제 완화)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82602</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82602"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T09:31:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OECD(경제협력개발기구)는 11월 8일 [장기게임: 2060년까지 재정전망 구조개혁 필요성 강조] (The Long Game: Fiscal Outlooks to 2060 Underline Need for Structural Reform) 보고서를 발표했습니다. 2000년부터 2060년까지 장기 재정전망을 담은 보고서로 1인당 잠재 실질 GDP(국내총생산)와 잠재 실질 GDP 성장률, 고용동향 등을 담고 있습니다. 대부분 언론이 이를 주요하게 다루는 동시에 한 달 전 발표된 IMF(국제통화기금) [재정 점검 보고서: […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 5.16-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/876072/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/876072/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T07:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.16-rc1 kernel prepatch is out and the
merge window is closed for this cycle.


	Anyway, it's not a huge release, although it's also not a
	remarkably small one like 5.15 was (ok, "remarkably small" is
	relative, when even such small releases have 10k+
	commits).. There's a bit of everything in here, and you can look to
	the appended mergelog for some kind of flavor, but I guess the
	folio work is worth mentioning, since it's an unusually core thing
	that we don't tend to see most releases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++20: Heterogeneous Lookup in (Un)ordered Containers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/heterogeneous-access-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/heterogeneous-access-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Would you like to gain 20…35 or even 50% speed improvements when searching in associative containers? In this blog post, we’ll explore a technique called “heterogenous access” that offers such impressive speedups. We’ll explore ordered containers, and the support for unordered collections added recently in C++20.
Recap on heterogeneous lookup in ordered containers
Let’s bring the example and have a look at how this feature works for ordered containers.
If you have the following code:
std::map<std::string, int> intMap { 
    { "Hello Super Long String", 1 }, 
    { "Another Longish String", 2 }, 
    { "This cannot fall into SSO buffer", 3 }
};

std::cout << "Lookup in intMap with by const char*:\n";
std::cout << intMap.contains("Hello Super Long String") << '\n';


In the above code, altho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Individuals matter]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/people-matter/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/people-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most common mistakes I see people make when looking at data is incorrectly using an overly simplified model. A specific variant of this that has derailed the majority of work roadmaps I've looked at is treating people as interchangeable, as if it doesn't matter who is doing what, as if individuals don't matter.
Individuals matter.
A pattern I've repeatedly seen during the roadmap creation and review process is that people will plan out the next few quarters of work and then assign some number of people to it, one person for one quarter to a project, two people for three quarters to another, etc. Nominally, this process enables teams to understand what other teams are doing and plan appropriately. I've never worked in an organization where this actually worked, where this actuall…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공감과 감명에 대한 논증적 정당화]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222568352620</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222568352620"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T21:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어떤 주장이 있다. 그 주장을 듣고 공감하면서 감명을 받는다. 그 공감과 감명의 정체가 무엇인지 스스로 생각해 보아야 한다. 가령 공자의 <논어> 첫 머리가 다음처럼 시작한다. 배우고 때맞춰 익히면 또한 기쁘지 않겠는가. 그렇다. 배우고 때에 맞게 익히고 연습하는 것이다. 그렇게 하면 기쁘다. 그런데 왜 기쁘단 말인가? 왜 배우고 때에 맞게 익히고 연습하는 것이 중요하단 말인가? 이런 질문을 하지 않은 채, 공자의 구절을 그대로 암송하거나 수동적으로 수용할 수 있다. 그러나 이렇게 해서 그 구절을 자기의 것으로 <소화>한다고 할 수 있는가? 나는 아니라고 생각한다. 박이문은 노장 사상뿐만 아니라, 공자의 <논어.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio to check the RPCS3 emulator]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0886/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0886/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RPCS3 is an interesting project that emulates the PS3 console. It is actively evolving. Recently we heard the news that the emulator learned how run all the games from the console's catalog. That's a good excuse to analyze the project. We'll see which errors remained after new fixes were added to the project. The project is quite hefty. It contains about 300 thousand lines of C++ code and relies upon many external dependencies that include the following: For the GUI part, the project uses Qt - however, that is taken from the system library. The screenshot below demonstrates the full list of dependencies:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Spilling the Beans: C/C++ Header Files]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33956</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/11/14/spilling-the-beans-c-c-header-files/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-14T12:34:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Header files in C/C++ are defining the interface between different modules. In this article I share some tips and tricks how create such interface files. Creating Header File Most IDEs have a helper to create header files, including Eclipse. What … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유럽 법원 “구글에 물린 반독점 벌금 옳았다”]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73734</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/11/13/eucompetitiongoogle/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=eucompetitiongoogle"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T23:30:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유럽연합 규제 당국이 구글을 상대로 법원에서 승소했습니다. 법원의 이번 판결에 힘입어 유럽연합은 앞으로 구글을 비롯한 빅테크 기업을 상대로 반독점 규제를 강화할 것으로 보입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[독단주의자의 역리]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222567488653</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222567488653"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T19:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주장이 있다. 그러나 그 논거가 없다. 논거가 없다는 것은 그 주장을 참으로 받아들일 단서가 주어지지 않았다는 것이다. 김광수의 <논리와 비판적 사고>에서 이것이 ‘독단주의의 역리’에 부딪치게 된다고 말한다. <독단(dogmatism)은 자적 사생아의 숨겨진 아버지이다. 독단에 빠진 사람은 자신의 주장이 옳다고 하면서도, 그 근거를 제시하지 않을 뿐만 아니라, 근거의 검토를 허용하지 않는다. 자신의 주장에 대한 근거를 검토하려는 것을 자신에 대한 도전으로 여긴다. 그 도전은 어리석고, 헛되고, 기분 나쁘고, 이단적인 것으로 여긴다. 만일 그가 친절하다면, 자명한 진리를 의심하는 꿈에서 깨어나라고 진지하게 조언하기도 하.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There actually is a compelling reason for Facebook to continue using facial recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9307</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/there-actually-is-a-compelling-reason-for-facebook-to-continue-using-facial-recognition/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T14:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week on the IoT Podcast, we discussed the news of Facebook ceasing the use of facial recognition across the photos its users upload. From our perspective, this was a big win for the Facebook user community. Why? Users had no control over whether Facebook would scan photos uploaded by others and then tag all […]
The post There actually is a compelling reason for Facebook to continue using facial recognition appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust data structures with circular references]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rust-data-structures-with-circular-references/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/rust-data-structures-with-circular-references/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-13T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>To implement its safety guarantees, the Rust compiler keeps careful track
of ownership and references throughout a program. This makes writing certain
kinds of data structures challenging; in particular, data structures that have
circular references.</p>
<p>Let's start with a simple binary tree:</p>
<div class="highlight"><pre><span></span><span class="k">struct</span> <span class="nc">Tree</span><span class="w"> </span><span class="p">{</span><span class="w"></span>
<span class="w">    </span><span class="n">root</span>: <span class="nb">Option</span><span class="o">&lt;</span><span class="n">Node</span><span class="o">&gt;</span><span class="p">,</span><span class="w"></span>
<span class="p">}</span><span class="w"></span>

<span class="k">struct</span> <span class="nc">Node</span><span class="w"> </span><span class="p">{</span><span class="w"></span>
<span class="w">    </span><span class="n">data …</span></pre></div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 순수 지성개념과 초월적 연역]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222566749395</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222566749395"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T20:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<우리는 앞에서 공간과 시간 개념에 대해서, 이것들이 선험적인 인식으로서 그럼에도 어떻게 대상들과 관계를 맺어야만 하는가, 그리고 어떻게 모든 경험에 독립해서 대상에 대한 종합적인 인식을 가능하게 하는가를 가벼운 수고만으로도 이해할 수 있었다. 감성의 그러한 순수한 형식들에 의해서만 하나의 대상은 현상할 수, 다시 말해 경험적 직관의 객관일 수 있기 때문에, 공간과 시간은 현상으로서의 대상을 가능하게 하는 선험적인 조건을 함유하는 순수 직관이고, 이 아래에서 종합은 객관적 타당성을 가지는 것이니 말이다.> 공간과 시간 개념은 선험적 인식이다. 그럼에도 그것은 대상과 관계 맺는다. 따라서 그것은 선험적 종합.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: Nvidia GTC & metaverse, wireless & sustainability]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471552</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-nvidia-gtc-metaverse-wireless-sustainability/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T20:08:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes coverage from Nvidia GTC, CW (Cambridge Wireless), plus embedded news, products, funding and events.
The post embedded news week: Nvidia GTC & metaverse, wireless & sustainability appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Groups optimize smart metering IoT with OMS over LoRaWAN]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471548</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/groups-optimize-smart-metering-iot-with-oms-over-lorawan/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T18:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LoRa Alliance and OMS-Group to standardize smart metering IoT applications, with a standard use of the Open Metering System language over LoRaWAN, reducing complexity and cost of integration for utilities.
The post Groups optimize smart metering IoT with OMS over LoRaWAN appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[u-blox MQTT Flex lets you bring your own SIM to IoT sensor networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471544</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/u-blox-mqtt-flex-lets-you-bring-your-own-sim-to-iot-sensor-networks/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T18:25:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bring your own SIM strategy enables users to take advantage of MQTT communication without the operational, logistical, or cost impact of changing their mobile network operator.
The post u-blox MQTT Flex lets you bring your own SIM to IoT sensor networks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Samsung H-Cube 2.5D technology integrates 6 HBMs for HPC applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471539</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-samsung-h-cube-2-5d-technology-integrates-6-hbms-for-hpc-applications/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T17:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[H-Cube applies advanced 2.5D silicon interposer technology and hybrid-substrate structure, allowing efficient integration of 6 HBMs, and lowering barriers to entry in the HPC/AI market.
The post New Samsung H-Cube 2.5D technology integrates 6 HBMs for HPC applications appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ClusterFuzzLite: Continuous fuzzing for all (Google Security blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875945/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875945/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T17:49:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Google Security blog, Jonathan Metzman announced the release of ClusterFuzzLite, which is "a continuous fuzzing solution that runs as part of CI/CD workflows to find vulnerabilities faster than ever before".   ClusterFuzzLite is a descendant of OSS-Fuzz, which we looked at in 2017.

Large projects including systemd and curl are already using ClusterFuzzLite during code review, with positive results. According to Daniel Stenberg, author of curl, “When the human reviewers nod and have approved the code and your static code analyzers and linters can't detect any more issues, fuzzing is what takes you to the next level of code maturity and robustness. OSS-Fuzz and ClusterFuzzLite help us maintain curl as a quality project, around the clock, every day and every commit.”

[...] To learn more, check out the ClusterFuzzLite documentation. ClusterFuzzLite currently supports GitHub Actions, Google Cloud Build and Prow. We built this with CI system extensibility in mind, and adding support for other CI systems is straightforward. Please contact us if you’re interested in contributing support, or have any questions, feedback or feature requests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some upcoming memory-management patches]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875587/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875587/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The memory-management subsystem remains one of the most complex parts of
the kernel, with an ongoing reliance on various heuristics for
performance.  It is thus not surprising that developers continue to try to
improve its functionality.  A number of memory-management patches are
currently in circulation; read on for a look at the freeing of page-table
pages, kvmalloc() flags, memory clearing, and NUMA "home nodes".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875932/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875932/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T15:08:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of eight stable kernels: 5.15.2, 5.14.18, 5.10.79, 5.4.159, 4.19.217, 4.14.255, 4.9.290, and 4.4.292.  They contain a relatively small set
of important fixes, but, as usual, users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875931/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875931/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T14:39:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (node-tar, postgresql-11, postgresql-13, and postgresql-9.6), Fedora (autotrace, botan2, chafa, converseen, digikam, dmtx-utils, dvdauthor, eom, kxstitch, pfstools, php-pecl-imagick, psiconv, q, R-magick, radeontop, rss-glx, rubygem-rmagick, synfig, synfigstudio, vdr-scraper2vdr, vdr-skinelchihd, vdr-skinnopacity, vdr-tvguide, and WindowMaker), Mageia (kernel, kernel-linus, and openafs), openSUSE (kernel), Red Hat (freerdp), SUSE (bind and kernel), and Ubuntu (openexr, postgresql-10, postgresql-12, postgresql-13, and samba).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia GTC: New Jetson module offers 200 TOPS for embedded edge AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471535</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nvidia-gtc-new-jetson-module-offers-200-tops-for-embedded-edge-ai/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T13:11:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Jetson AGX Orin module built on Nvidia Ampere architecture claims to be smallest and most powerful AI supercomputer for embedded edge computing.
The post Nvidia GTC: New Jetson module offers 200 TOPS for embedded edge AI appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nvidia Jetson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia GTC: New 400 Gbps InfiniBand networking platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471530</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nvidia-gtc-new-400-gbps-infiniband-networking-platform/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T11:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New at Nvidia GTC is a 400Gbps InfiniBand switch and networking platform which features secure, cloud-native, multi-tenant, bare-metal performance for AI, data analytics, and HPC applications
The post Nvidia GTC: New 400 Gbps InfiniBand networking platform appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Aarch64 Linux Kernel Debug]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11156632</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11156632"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T08:34:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미루고 미루던 리눅스 커널 취약점 연구를 올해가 가기 전에 최소한 '시작'은 해보려고 한다. 
아직 초보인데, Defenit팀의 김현우(V4bel)님께서 인프런에서 진행하시는 강좌가 정말 큰 도움이 되었다.
https://www.inflearn.com/course/%EB%A6%AC%EB%88%85%EC%8A%A4-%EC%BB%A4%EB%84%90-%ED%95%B4%ED%82%B9/
해당 강좌는 Intel x86_64 환경을 기준으로 되어있는데, 이를 Aarch64 리눅스로 하여 열심히 삽질 중이다. 변환했을 때 똑같이 적용되는 것도 있고, 안 되는 것도 많다..


우선 Aarch64 환경에서 커널 빌드 및 디버깅을 하기 위한 절차를 기록해둔다. 대부분의 내용은 위에서 언급한 강좌에서 김현우님께서 가이드해주신 방법을 참고했으며, Aarch64 로 변환할 때 필요한 수정사항들을 내가 작성했다(이 게시물은 강사님의 허락을 받고 기록해두는 것이다.)
 
(참고로 1~3번 과정을 생략하고, 내가 올려둔 파일을 다운로드 하셔도 됨)
1. 리눅스 커널 빌드
우선 리눅스 커널을 직접 빌드할 수 있는 환경이 마련되어야 한다. 강의에서는 인텔 리눅스 상에서 인텔 리눅스를 빌드하는 방식으로 진행되었다. 그러나 Aarch64 아키텍처용 리눅스를 빌드하려면 방법이 달라진다. 대략 두가지 방법이 있다.
1) Intel 리눅스상에서 cross-compiler 를 사용해서 Aarch64 리눅스 이미지를 빌드하는 방법.
2) Aarch64 리눅스 상에서 Aarch64 리눅스를 빌드하는 방법.
그동안은 대부분 1의 방법이 선호되었다. 왜냐…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글쓰기가 어려운 이유 (ft. 생각, 말, 글)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82593</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82593"/>
        <updated>2021-11-12T04:10:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[흔히 우리는 ‘명료한 사고에서 명료한 글이 나온다’고 생각한다. 하지만 자신이 무슨 말을 하려고 하는지 분명히 알고 있다고 해도, 자신이 쓴 글이 명료하지 않다는 것을 깨닫는 경우가 많다. 열심히 글을 썼는데 상대방이 그것을 읽고 무슨 말이냐고 묻는 상황은 참으로 난감하다. 물론 사적인 메모나 편지를 쓸 때는 글 쓰는 것이 어렵지 않다. 하지만 공적인 보고서나 논문 같은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[All hail bug reports: how we reduced the analysis time of the user's project from 80 to 4 hours]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0885/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0885/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[People often see work in support as something negative. Today we'll look at it from a different perspective. This article is about a real communication of 100+ messages, exceptions, the analysis that didn't complete in three days... Actually, bug reports are great If a bug report is adequately handled from both sides, it means that both the user and the software developer are interested in solving the problem. If both sides achieve the desired result, it's a win-win situation. Before we proceed to the story, here's a little introduction. We are the PVS-Studio team. We develop the analyzer that searches for errors and potential vulnerabilities in C, C++, C#, and Java code. Yours truly is the team lead of the C# analyzer development team, the author of articles and posts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Play-to-Earn’ Gaming and How Work is Evolving in Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2473</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/play-to-earn-gaming-and-how-work-is-evolving-in-web3/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T19:44:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today’s episode we’re talking about an emerging model of gaming called play to earn, in which players can make actual money based on how much time and effort they put into a game. Play to earn is also part of broader trends — the changing relationship between players and platforms, new incentives for participants... Read More
The post ‘Play-to-Earn’ Gaming and How Work is Evolving in Web3 appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jeffrey Zirlin, Gabby Dizon, Arianna Simpson and Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Exposing Trojan Source exploits in Emacs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875229/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875229/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T16:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the "Trojan Source" vulnerabilities
have, thus far, generated far more publicity than examples of actual
exploits, addressing the problem still seems like a good thing to do.
There are several places where defenses could be put into place; text
editors, being the place where developers look at a lot of code, are one
obvious example.  The discussion of how to enhance Emacs in this regard has
made it clear, though, that there are multiple opinions about how an editor
should flag potential attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twelve Years of Go (The Go blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875817/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875817/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T16:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On November 10, the Go programming language community celebrated the 12th anniversary of its release as open-source software.  The post covers a number of different topics, including the consolidation of web sites at go.dev, releases and their features over the last year, as well as a look to the future:

In February, the Go 1.18 release will expand the new register-based calling convention to non-x86 architectures, bringing dramatic performance improvements with it. It will include the new Go fuzzing support. And it will be the first release to include support for generics.

Generics will be one of our focuses for 2022. The initial release in Go 1.18 is only the beginning. We need to spend time using generics and learning what works and what doesn’t, so that we can write best practices and decide what should be added to the standard library and other libraries. We expect that Go 1.19 (expected in August 2022) and later releases will further refine the design and implementation of generics as well as integrating them further into the overall Go experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rohde & Schwarz and MediaTek deliver Wi-Fi 6E production test]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471527</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/rohde-schwarz-and-mediatek-deliver-wi-fi-6e-production-test/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rohde & Schwarz CMP180 radio communications test platform is integrated into MediaTek ATE tool to offer production test solution for Wi-Fi 6E devices.
The post Rohde & Schwarz and MediaTek deliver Wi-Fi 6E production test appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Three IoT acquisitions and the infrastructure bill]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9303</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-three-iot-acquisitions-and-the-infrastructure-bill/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T14:00:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show focuses on three big deals happening in the IoT sector and a meaty enterprise IoT report. First up, we discuss ADT buying SunPro Solar for $825 million, which represents yet another deal bringing energy management to the smart home. We then talk about Level Home’s acquisition, the state of smart home deals, […]
The post Podcast: Three IoT acquisitions and the infrastructure bill appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875813/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875813/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T13:18:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (icinga2, libxstream-java, ruby-kaminari, and salt), Fedora (awscli, cacti, cacti-spine, python-boto3, python-botocore, radeontop, and rust), Mageia (firefox, libesmtp, libzapojit, sssd, and thunderbird), openSUSE (samba and samba and ldb), SUSE (firefox, pcre, qemu, samba, and samba and ldb), and Ubuntu (firejail, linux-bluefield, linux-gke-5.4, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-oem-5.10, linux-oem-5.14, and python-py).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NXP and Ford collaborate on connected cars]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471523</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nxp-and-ford-collaborate-on-connected-cars/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T12:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NXP to provide vehicle networking, gateway and i.MX 8 Series processors to enable enhanced services, convenience and over-the-air updateable vehicles
The post NXP and Ford collaborate on connected cars appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시간]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222565350570</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222565350570"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T10:34:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[레비나스의 <시간과 타자> ‘서문’을 아주 쪼금 읽다가 생각한다. 시간에 대해서 나는 어떤 생각을 갖고 있는가? 나는 시간에 대해 철학적으로 중요하다고 생각하는 것인가? 도대체 시간에 대한 철학적 문제들이란 무엇인가? 기껏해야 내가 시간에 대해 갖고 있는 생각은 칸트의 그것, 즉 시간과 공간 형식이 경험의 구성 조건이라는 것이다. 시간에 대해서 레비나스가 다음처럼 주장한다. (1) 시간은 무한성과 자족성을 존재자에게 보장해 줄 수 없는 관계이다. (2) 시간은 사회성을 뜻하는 관계이다. (3) 시간은 존재자의 존재라는 존재의 지평이 아니라, 존재 저편의 방식으로, 즉 타자에 대한 사유 관계이다. (4) 시간은 타인의 얼굴.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[천국 문 앞에서도 AP 기자를 만날까 봐 무섭군]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82582</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82582"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T07:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[해외뉴스를 보다보면 AP라는 통신사가 작성한 기사를 본 적이 있을 것이다. AP(The Associated Press)는 국제뉴스 취재를 목표로 설립된 비영리 뉴스협동조합이다. 1846년 뉴욕을 기반으로 하는 다양한 신문사들이 멕시코 전선과 유럽 소식을 더 빠르게 전송받기 위해 자금을 모아서 설립했다. 하지만 20세기 초반까지 AP는 외국에 직접 나가 취재하기보다는 로이터(Reuters)와 같은 기존의 뉴스통신 카르텔에서 뉴스를 받아서 기사를 작성했다. AP의 위상  […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>크레센도</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[14년째 표류하는 차별금지법 (일간지 보도 분석)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82567</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82567"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T06:25:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2007년 국회에 차별금지법이 처음 발의됐습니다. 노무현 정부 시절 정부 입법으로 처음 발의된 차별금지법은 14년간 발의와 폐기를 반복하며 아직도 국회 문턱을 넘지 못하고 있습니다. 제21대 국회에서는 장혜영 정의당 의원과 권인숙·박주민·이상민 더불어민주당 의원 등이 대표발의한 4건의 차별금지법안이 발의돼 있습니다. 지난 6월 10만 명 동의로 달성된 ‘차별금지법 제정에 관한 국민동의 청원’이 국회 법제사법위원회 심사를 기다리고 있습니다. 국민동의 청원 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 11, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875075/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875075/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-11T00:41:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 11, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The strong and weak forces of architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/strong-weak-arch.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/strong-weak-arch.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Good technical design decisions are very dependent on context. Teams that
    regularly work together on common goals are able to communicate regularly
    and negotiate changes quickly. These teams exhibit a strong force of
    alignment, and can make technology and design decisions that harness that
    strong force. As we zoom out in a larger organisation an increasingly
    weak force exists between teams and divisions that work independently
    and have less frequent collaboration. Recognising the differences in these
    strong and weak forces allows us to make better decisions and give better
    guidance for each level, allowing for more empowered teams that can move
    faster.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: DefaultTrialRetire]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/DefaultTrialRetire.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/DefaultTrialRetire.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within each normal-sized team, limit the choice of alternatives for any class
	of technology to three. These are: the current sensible default, the one we're
	experimenting with as a trial, and the one that we hate and want to retire.
The conversation goes like this: We want to introduce a new messaging
  technology. How many do we have already in place? Oh we have three in active
  use, including one that's considered legacy and we're partway through
  migrating off and one that we experimented with previously but didn't gain
  traction. Ok, so we're at our limit now. If we want to add another messaging
  tech then we have two choices. Either migrate all of our apps off the legacy
  tech, or properly rid ourselves of the failed experiment. This is quite
  closely related to the idea of capping the number of Innovation Tokens in
  use within your teams.
At a team level these kinds of limits are relatively easy
  to maintain and discuss and act upon, because we have common priorities and
  ways of working and high trust, high bandwidth communication. At the scope of
  the whole organisation the challenge is similar, but getting alignment takes a
  lot longer and doing actual migration and consolidation work can take a long
  time - so we sometimes have to allow for more variation in technology. We also use 
  different techniques to discuss and communicate the status of our preferred technologies.
An approach we use at MYOB to engage our whole organisation in broader decisions about
  technology is by publishing our own MYOB Technology Radar, following the
  format of the Thoughtworks Technology Radar.
  This approach of building our own radar
  involves taking input from all of our verticals and teams, and making a clear
  statement on what technologies we encourage teams to adopt, trial, or more
  importantly which ones to keep clear of.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the leap to pursue a passion in Machine Learning with Leigh Johnson #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:03:00.011Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
Leigh Johnson turned her childhood love of Geocities and Neopets into a web development career, and then trained her focus on Machine Learning. Now, she’s a staff software engineer at Slack, a Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning, and founder of Print Nanny, an automated failure detection system and monitoring system for 3D printers. 
Meet Leigh Johnson, Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning.
   
GDE Leigh Johnson
 The early days
Leigh Johnson grew up in the Bronx, NY, and got an early start in web development when she became captivated by Geocities and Neopets in elementary scho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taking the leap to pursue a passion in Machine Learning with Leigh Johnson #IamaGDE]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/dlcSC-NJWtQ/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/dlcSC-NJWtQ/taking-leap-to-pursue-passion-in.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T18:03:00.011Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
Leigh Johnson turned her childhood love of Geocities and Neopets into a web development career, and then trained her focus on Machine Learning. Now, she’s a staff software engineer at Slack, a Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning, and founder of Print Nanny, an automated failure detection system and monitoring system for 3D printers. 
Meet Leigh Johnson, Google Developer Expert in Web and Machine Learning.
   
GDE Leigh Johnson
 The early days
Leigh Johnson grew up in the Bronx, NY, and got an early start in web development when she became captivated by Geocities and Neopets in elementary scho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Late-bound argument defaults for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875441/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875441/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T17:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python supports default values for arguments to functions, but those
defaults are evaluated at function-definition time.  A proposal to add
defaults that are evaluated when the function is called has been discussed
at some length on the python-ideas mailing list.  The idea came about, in part,
due to yet another resurrection of the proposal
for None-aware operators in Python.  Late-bound defaults would help
with one use case for those operators, but there are other, stronger
reasons to consider their addition to the language.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875708/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875708/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T15:40:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (openjdk-8 and samba), Fedora (community-mysql, firefox, and vim), openSUSE (binutils, kernel, and tinyxml), Red Hat (annobin, autotrace, babel, bind, binutils, bluez, compat-exiv2-026, container-tools:2.0, container-tools:3.0, container-tools:rhel8, cups, curl, dnf, dnsmasq, edk2, exiv2, file, file-roller, firefox, gcc, gcc-toolset-10-annobin, gcc-toolset-10-binutils, gcc-toolset-10-gcc, gcc-toolset-11-annobin, gcc-toolset-11-binutils, gcc-toolset-11-gcc, glib2, glibc, GNOME, gnutls and nettle, go-toolset:rhel8, grafana, graphviz, grilo, httpd:2.4, jasper, java-17-openjdk, json-c, kernel, kernel-rt, kexec-tools, kpatch-patch, lasso, libgcrypt, libjpeg-turbo, libsepol, libsolv, libssh, libtiff, libwebp, libX11, linuxptp, lua, mingw-glib2, mutt, ncurses, NetworkManager, openjpeg2, openssh, openssl, pcre, pcs, php:7.4, python-jinja2, python-lxml, python-pillow, python-pip, python-psutil, python27:2.7, python3, python36:3.6, python38:3.8 and python38-devel:3.8, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9, qt5, resource-agents, rpm, rust-toolset:rhel8, spamassassin, sqlite, squid:4, tcpdump, tpm2-tools, vim, virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel, and zziplib), and SUSE (binutils and kernel).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Overlooked Levels of the Creator Economy]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2450</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/creator-economy-levels/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T15:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It seems like everyone today is a creator — whether artist, developer, or other individuals following their craft — yet the creator economy still has room to grow. Despite being a multibillion-dollar market fueled by over 50 million people, this movement is much deeper than its monetization platforms, and bigger than the small percentage of... Read More
The post The Overlooked Levels of the Creator Economy appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Runcie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Level raises $100M and acquires a smart apartment company]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9295</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/level-raises-100m-and-acquires-a-smart-apartment-company/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T13:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Level Home, the maker of a slick smart lock, has raised an additional $100 million in a Series C round of funding, as well as completing an all-stock deal to buy multi-family residential software company Dwelo. The two moves are part of a master plan by Level Home CEO John Martin to grow into a […]
The post Level raises $100M and acquires a smart apartment company appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can blockchain accelerate IoT adoption?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471500</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/can-blockchain-accelerate-iot-adoption/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T12:02:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Blockchain can empower IoT with the needed security and transparency and is already playing an important role in many IoT applications. With the arrival of...
The post Can blockchain accelerate IoT adoption? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harikrishna Kundariya</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[의심의 ‘한국’철학]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222564295930</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222564295930"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T09:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[니체가 말한다. 철학은 철학하는 자가 자기를 불태워 새롭게 하는 곳에 시작된다. 그런데 니체가 이런 말을 할 자격이 있는가? 도대체 그가 생각했던 철학이란 무엇인가? 나는 철학적 논증을 명백하게 보여주지 않는 자를 ‘철학자’라고 부르기 주저한다. 좋게 말하면 문학적 ‘사상가’일 것이다. 물론 니체를 좋아하는 사람들이나 니체 전공자들은 나를 비판할 것이다. “한국을 철학화한다.” 이 주장이 무슨 의미인가? 이 주장이 말이 되는 것인가? 도대체 어떻게 하는 것이 한국을 철학화하는 것인가? 그 구체적 내용과 실질적 결과를 보여주는 것이 중요하다. 단지 구호와 선언은 공허하기 짝이 없다. 한국철학을 해야 한다는 당위적 주장.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samba 4.15.2, 4.14.10, 4.13.14 security releases available]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875565/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875565/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T07:47:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a set of new Samba releases out there.  They fix a long and
intimidating list of security issues and seem worth upgrading to for any
but the most protected of Samba servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MSA’ 문제를 보완하는 설계와 디자인 트렌트]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82553</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82553"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T06:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 50여 년 동안 소프트웨어 아키텍처 및 애플리케이션 호스팅 모델은 메인프레임에서 마이크로서비스 및 서버리스로의 주요 전환을 경험했다. 메인프레임에서 최신 클라우드 네이티브 아키텍처(CNCF)에 이르기까지 다양한 호스팅 모델은 비즈니스 앱을 개발, 배포 및 유지 관리하는 방식에 영향을 미쳤다. IT 서비스 업계에서 새로운 호스팅 모델을 발견할 때마다 팀은 아키텍처의 이점을 최대한 활용하는 데 어려움을 겪었다. 이로 인해 아키텍처 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘MSA’ 문제를 보완하는 설계와 디자인 트렌트]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82553</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/ch0DpmXKwoM/82553"/>
        <updated>2021-11-10T06:49:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 50여 년 동안 소프트웨어 아키텍처 및 애플리케이션 호스팅 모델은 메인프레임에서 마이크로서비스 및 서버리스로의 주요 전환을 경험했다. 메인프레임에서 최신 클라우드 네이티브 아키텍처(CNCF)에 이르기까지 다양한 호스팅 모델은 비즈니스 앱을 개발, 배포 및 유지 관리하는 방식에 영향을 미쳤다. IT 서비스 업계에서 새로운 호스팅 모델을 발견할 때마다 팀은 아키텍처의 이점을 최대한 활용하는 데 어려움을 겪었다. 이로 인해 아키텍처 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to choose a static analysis tool]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0884/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0884/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tools to improve and control code quality can be a key success factor in a complex software project implementation. Static analyzers belong to such tools. Nowadays, you can find various static analyzers: from free open-source to cross-functional commercial solutions. On the one hand, it's great – you can choose from many options. On the other hand – you have to perform advanced research to find the right tool for your team. Before we talk about selection criteria, let's briefly discuss the methodology. Static analysis is an automated method to find errors in source code by means of specialized programs. The purpose of such analysis is to identify unsafe and problem parts of the project that can lead to more serious consequences – vulnerabilities. Keep in mind that users are not QA engineers. Bugs must not get into the release. That is why it's better to use a static analyzer regularly. Run the analyzer once – get lots of messages. Believe us, you don't want to sort them out. Moreover, to find and fix some errors you have to use more expensive methods at the following project stages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to choose a static analysis tool]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0884/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/Vv6z-LN8fhU/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tools to improve and control code quality can be a key success factor in a complex software project implementation. Static analyzers belong to such tools. Nowadays, you can find various static analyzers: from free open-source to cross-functional commercial solutions. On the one hand, it's great – you can choose from many options. On the other hand – you have to perform advanced research to find the right tool for your team. Before we talk about selection criteria, let's briefly discuss the methodology. Static analysis is an automated method to find errors in source code by means of specialized programs. The purpose of such analysis is to identify unsafe and problem parts of the project that can lead to more serious consequences – vulnerabilities. Keep in mind that users are not QA engineers. Bugs must not get into the release. That is why it's better to use a static analyzer regularly. Run the analyzer once – get lots of messages. Believe us, you don't want to sort them out. Moreover, to find and fix some errors you have to use more expensive methods at the following project stages.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Concurrency in Julia]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875367/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875367/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T18:04:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Julia programming language has
its roots in high-performance scientific computing, so it is no surprise
that it has facilities for concurrent processing. Those features are not
well-known outside of the Julia community, though, so it is interesting to
see the different types of parallel and concurrent computation that the
language supports. In addition, the upcoming release of Julia
version 1.7 brings an improvement to the language's
concurrent-computation palette, 
in the form of "task 
migration".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875531/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875531/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T15:43:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (firefox, grafana, jenkins, opera, and thunderbird), Debian (botan1.10 and ckeditor), openSUSE (chromium, kernel, qemu, and rubygem-activerecord-5_1), SUSE (qemu and rubygem-activerecord-5_1), and Ubuntu (docker.io, kernel, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.11, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.11, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.11, linux-hwe-5.11, linux-kvm, linux-oem-5.13, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.11, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, and linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 논증적으로 생각하기]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222563292829</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222563292829"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T09:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 전제와 결론을 가진 논증으로 요약해 보라. 신탁은 내가 가장 현명하다고 이야기했습니다. 이 이야기를 들었을 때, 나는 신의 말은 무엇을 뜻하는가? 신의 수수께끼를 어떻게 해석할 것인가? 하고 자문해 보았습니다. 왜냐하면 나는 크든 작든 간에 지혜가 없다는 것을 알고 있기 때문입니다. 신이 내가 가장 현명한 사람이라고 말할 때 그는 무슨 말을 하려고 한 것일까? 그는 신이고, 따라서 거짓말을 할 수는 없는 일입니다. 거짓말을 한다는 것은 신에게는 어울리지 않는 일입니다. 오랫동안 숙고한 끝에 이 문제를 푸는 방법을 생각해 냈습니다. 만일 나 자신보다 더 현명한 사람을 찾아내기만 한다면 나는 신탁의 소리를 반박할 수 있을.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테크놀로지는 어떻게 미군을 변화시켰나]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82537</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82537"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T05:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[궁극의 군대]는 1945년 핵 혁명부터 2000년 무렵의 정보혁명까지 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계를 다룬 책이다. 저자인 토머스 G. 맨켄은 기술사를 다루는 정석적인 서술 방법을 취하는데, 기술’결정론’ 혹은 기술결정론의 무의미함을 논하기보다는 과학과 기술의 발전이라는 자체적인 동력과 그것을 수용하는 조직과 문화, 인식의 변화가 어떻게 함께 가는지를 설명한다. 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계  핵무기나 컴퓨터가 전장을 완전히 바꾸어놓았다는 서술이나, 핵무기나 컴퓨터의 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>임명묵</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테크놀로지는 어떻게 미군을 변화시켰나]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82537</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/QpvqTbuFw_8/82537"/>
        <updated>2021-11-09T05:46:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[궁극의 군대]는 1945년 핵 혁명부터 2000년 무렵의 정보혁명까지 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계를 다룬 책이다. 저자인 토머스 G. 맨켄은 기술사를 다루는 정석적인 서술 방법을 취하는데, 기술’결정론’ 혹은 기술결정론의 무의미함을 논하기보다는 미 미군과 기술 발전의 상호관계  핵무기나 컴퓨터가 전장을 완전히 바꾸어놓았다는 서술이나, 핵무기나 컴퓨터의 등장과 관계 없이 전장은 항상 똑같다는 반론보다 중요한 것은, 육해공군이라는 개별 조직이 그런 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>임명묵</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Early Memories of Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://jameshunt.us/?p=424</id>
        <link href="https://jameshunt.us/writings/early-memories-of-computers/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T18:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of my earliest memory of computers starts on an airplane.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LXD 4.20 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875447/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875447/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T17:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LXD team has announced
the release of version 4.20 of the LXD system container and virtual
machine manager.

This is one very busy release with a lot of new features.

VM users will be happy to see the initial implementation of live migration and core scheduling support. Container users are getting new configuration keys to set sysctls.

Then the bulk of the new features are all network related with peer network relationships, network zones for auto-generated DNS and SR-IOV accelerated OVN networks.

And lastly, on the clustering front, it’s now possible to better control what servers will be receiving new workloads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Intel AMX support in 5.16]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874846/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874846/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T16:25:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The x86 instruction set is large, but that doesn't mean it can't get bigger
yet.  Upcoming Intel processors will feature a new set of instructions
under the name of "Advanced Matrix Extensions" (AMX) that can be used to
operate on matrix data.  After a somewhat bumpy development
process, support for AMX has found its way into the upcoming 5.16 kernel.
Using it will, naturally, require some changes by application developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy holidays! Here’s our 2021 gift guide!]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9252</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/happy-holidays-heres-our-2021-gift-guide/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T14:00:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m pretty sure that, for most people, 2021 isn’t going to be one of fond remembrances. For Kevin and I, it has been a year of reckoning, as people continue to lose trust in technology and the companies that sell consumer gadgets. Add to that the ongoing pandemic and the in-your-face reality of climate change, […]
The post Happy holidays! Here’s our 2021 gift guide! appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875420/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875420/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T13:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (containerd, redis, and sqlalchemy), Fedora (kernel, radeontop, rpki-client, and webkit2gtk3), openSUSE (java-1_8_0-openj9, libvirt, mailman, transfig, and webkit2gtk3), Oracle (thunderbird), SUSE (libvirt), and Ubuntu (icu).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글쓰기 십계명: 명확한 글쓰기 10가지 원칙]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82517</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82517"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T07:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제1원칙 이야기 속 행위자를 짧고 구체적인 명사에 담아 문장의 주어로 삼아라. 살아 움직이는 생명체가 주어가 되면 더 좋다. “행위자가 없으면 아무것도 없는 것이다.” (무명)    제2원칙 행위자의 주요 행동을 묘사하는 구체적인 동사를 서술어로 삼아라. 우리는 ‘누가 무엇을 한다’는 스토리텔링을 가장 잘 이해한다. “나는 생각한다. 고로 존재한다.” (데카르트)   제3원칙 주어와 동사를 최대한 문장 앞부분에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[글쓰기 십계명: 명확한 글쓰기 10가지 원칙]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82517</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/72cjtKQBXd4/82517"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T07:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제1원칙 이야기 속 행위자를 짧고 구체적인 명사에 담아 문장의 주어로 삼아라. 살아 움직이는 생명체가 주어가 되면 더 좋다. “행위자가 없으면 아무것도 없는 것이다.” (무명)    제2원칙 행위자의 주요 행동을 묘사하는 구체적인 동사를 서술어로 삼아라. 우리는 ‘누가 무엇을 한다’는 스토리텔링을 가장 잘 이해한다. “나는 생각한다. 고로 존재한다.” (데카르트)   제3원칙 주어와 동사를 최대한 문장 앞부분에 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤영삼</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 More Ways to Refactor new/delete into unique ptr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/more-refactor-into-uniqueptr/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/more-refactor-into-uniqueptr/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first part of our refactoring series, we covered (smart) pointers inside a function body; today, I’d like to show you cases for return types, data members, and a few others.
Let’s jump in and replace some new() and delete!
See the first part
This article is the second in the series about refactoring with unique_ptr. You can read the first part here:
6 Ways to Refactor new/delete into unique ptr - C++ Stories
Basic assumptions
The code presented here will usually contain explicit new and delete, and we’d like to reduce their use and wrap resources (pointers) into RAII.
We’ll try to follow the rule: R.11: Avoid calling new and delete explicitly from the Core C++ Guidelines:
The pointer returned by new should belong to a resource handle (that can call delete). If the pointer returned b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[October 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/1ebb97d9e53b</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/october-2021-1ebb97d9e53b?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T03:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[September 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/63d16d437db5</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/september-2021-63d16d437db5?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T03:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ESP BOT</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Culturally transmitted skills and values]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/culture/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/culture/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three major tools that companies have to influence behavior are incentives, process, and culture. People often mean different things when talking about these, so I'll provide an example of each so we're on the same page (if you think that I should be using a different word for the concept, feel free to mentally substitute that word).
Getting people to show up to meetings on time
Incentive: dock pay for people who are late
Process: don't allow anyone who's late into the meeting
Culture: people feel strongly about showing up on time



Getting people to build complex systems
Incentive: require complexity in promo criteria
Process: make process for creating or executing on a work item so heavyweight that people stop doing simple work
Culture: people enjoy building complex systems and/or build…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undefined behavior, carried through the years]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0883/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0883/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine: something in code goes wrong, you start searching for a bug and then it turns out that there was another bug behind this. Have you ever been in this situation? Searching for bugs is cool. It's almost like you're Sherlock Holmes and it's a detective story. Something from an extensive list of seemingly harmless classes and functions causes a program's unexpected and undefined behavior. And you, with your sharp eyes and experiments, are trying to find the "criminal".  We published and translated this article with the copyright holder's permission. The author is Eugene Zakharov (fnc12@me.com). The article was originally published on Habr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Undefined behavior, carried through the years]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0883/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/ilNokXp9iio/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine: something in code goes wrong, you start searching for a bug and then it turns out that there was another bug behind this. Have you ever been in this situation? Searching for bugs is cool. It's almost like you're Sherlock Holmes and it's a detective story. Something from an extensive list of seemingly harmless classes and functions causes a program's unexpected and undefined behavior. And you, with your sharp eyes and experiments, are trying to find the "criminal".  We published and translated this article with the copyright holder's permission. The author is Eugene Zakharov (fnc12@me.com). The article was originally published on Habr.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s in my smart home: November 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9182</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/whats-in-my-smart-home-november-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T14:00:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: This story was published in the newsletter on October 22, but never made it to the site. So we updated the headline and published it here two weeks later. Slightly more than a year ago, I shared what was in my smart home. I started out by saying, “Wow, what a difference three years […]
The post What’s in my smart home: November 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding RGBW Wings and Enclosure to a Debug Probe]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33750</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/11/07/adding-rgbw-wings-and-enclosure-to-a-debug-probe/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-07T12:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m using debug probes on a daily base. They have to be functional, and I value functionality over aesthetics. For cost reasons many debug probe vendors either only provide a bare PCB without enclosure, or the enclosure is made of … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some weekend stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875297/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875297/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T20:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
5.15.1,
5.14.17,
5.10.78,
5.4.158, and
4.19.216
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Close Look at a Spinlock]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.regehr.org/?p=2173</id>
        <link href="https://blog.regehr.org/archives/2173"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T19:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The spinlock is the most basic mutual exclusion primitive provided by a multiprocessor operating system. Spinlocks need to protect against preemption on the current CPU (typically by disabling interrupts, but we’ll ignore that aspect in this post) and also against attempts by other cores to concurrently access the critical section (by using atomic memory operations).… Continue reading A Close Look at a Spinlock]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>regehr</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[드라마와 현실]]></title>
        <id>http://wallflower.egloos.com/4202872</id>
        <link href="http://wallflower.egloos.com/4202872"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T19:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<오징어 게임>을 본 미국의 지인은 고도로 발전한 자본주의를 영위하는 한국에서 이런 자본주의 비판 드라마가 제작된다는 것이 아이러니하다고 전했다. 나에게 취재를 요청한 미국 방송의 기자는 드라마에서 그려지는 게임이 얼마나 실제의 한국과 닮아 있는지 물었다. .... 글 전체보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이택광</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need third-party apps to update HomeKit device firmware?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9266</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/do-you-need-third-party-apps-to-update-homekit-device-firmware/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T16:25:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Sean called in to the voicemail hotline with a HomeKit question. He appreciates the ability to add HomeKit devices to his smart home directly through Apple’s Home app. He wants to know if the device maker’s applications are required to upgrade the firmware on those devices. Unfortunately, the answer […]
The post Do you need third-party apps to update HomeKit device firmware? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing multiple implementations of a trait in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/testing-multiple-implementations-of-a-trait-in-rust/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/testing-multiple-implementations-of-a-trait-in-rust/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-06T12:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I've been hacking on a small practice project in Rust where I implement the same
data structure in several different ways. When testing this project, I want to
run exactly the same set of tests on several types that implement the same
trait.</p>
<p>As a demonstrative example, let's take the …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.8 and 3.11.0a2 are now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/11/python-398-and-3110a2-are-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2021/11/python-398-and-3110a2-are-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T23:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tcl/Tk updates

With the recent release of macOS 12 Monterey, we noticed that tkinter
 file dialogs are failing to show up on this new operating system, 
including in our built-in IDLE. Thanks to rapid help from the Tk team, 
and Marc Culler in particular, we were able to fix the issue by bundling
 Python 3.9.8 and Python 3.11.0a2 with a fixed Tcl/Tk version. In 3.9.8 
it’s a patched 8.6.11 release while 3.11.0a2 is rocking the 
bleeding-edge 8.6.12rc1.

Since the issue also affected our latest stable version, 3.10.0, an 
updated macOS installer for this version was issued. You can recognize 
it by the post2 version appendix: python-3.10.0post2-macos11.pkg.
 We didn’t have to bump the version number of Python itself since there 
are no Python source differences between this pac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.9.8 and 3.11.0a2 are now available]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/uo3G1CE85vk/python-398-and-3110a2-are-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PythonInsider/~3/uo3G1CE85vk/python-398-and-3110a2-are-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T23:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tcl/Tk updates

With the recent release of macOS 12 Monterey, we noticed that tkinter
 file dialogs are failing to show up on this new operating system, 
including in our built-in IDLE. Thanks to rapid help from the Tk team, 
and Marc Culler in particular, we were able to fix the issue by bundling
 Python 3.9.8 and Python 3.11.0a2 with a fixed Tcl/Tk version. In 3.9.8 
it’s a patched 8.6.11 release while 3.11.0a2 is rocking the 
bleeding-edge 8.6.12rc1.

Since the issue also affected our latest stable version, 3.10.0, an 
updated macOS installer for this version was issued. You can recognize 
it by the post2 version appendix: python-3.10.0post2-macos11.pkg.
 We didn’t have to bump the version number of Python itself since there 
are no Python source differences between this pac…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유럽 대륙철학 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222559991054</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222559991054"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T21:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사이먼 크리츨리(Simon Critchley), 혹은 사이몬 크리칠리의 작은 책 <대륙철학>(2001)이 <유럽 대륙철학>(2016)이라는 제목으로 번역되어 있다. 데리다와 레비나스 학자라고 할 수 있는, 그러나 이제는 아주 폭넓은 저술가라고 할 수 있는 그의 책들이 제법 우리말로 번역되어 있다. <죽은 철학자들의 서(書)>, <믿음 없는 믿음의 정치>, <데이비드 보위>, <자살에 대하여> 등이다. <유럽 대륙철학>은 대륙 철학을 분석철학과의 관련에서 해명하고 있다. 특히 분석철학적, 혹은 ‘영국적’이라는 부를 수 있는 요소에 대립되는 대륙철학적, 유럽적 요소들이 어떻게 서로를 존중하면서 함께 있을 수 있.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: podcast, new GPU, quantum IP, smart building IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471489</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-podcast-new-gpu-quantum-ip-smart-building-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T19:46:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes embedded edge with Nitin podcast featuring a brand new GPU, quantum computing developments and IoT for smart buildings, plus usual product news including automotive, tools and software.
The post embedded news week: podcast, new GPU, quantum IP, smart building IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryabitsev: lore+lei: part 1, getting started]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875239/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875239/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T18:21:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konstantin Ryabitsev introduces
the "local email interface" (lei) functionality for the lore archive of
kernel mailing lists.


	Even though it started out as merely a list archival service, it
	quickly became obvious that lore could be used for a lot more. Many
	developers ended up using its search features to quickly locate
	emails of interest, which in turn raised a simple question — what
	if there was a way to “save a search” and have it deliver all new
	incoming mail matching certain parameters straight to the
	developers' inbox?

	You can now do this with lei.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for Nov. 5, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9263</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-nov-5-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T18:00:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phyn launches a smaller, cheaper leak detection system: Phyn, which makes devices that can scan for leaks and even shut off water in case of leak detection, has launched a new product. The Phyn Plus, Smart Water Assistant + Shutoff, is a smaller, cheaper version of the original Phyn water monitor and shutoff device that sold for […]
The post IoT news of the week for Nov. 5, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The balance between features and performance in the block layer]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874643/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874643/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:47:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Back in September, LWN reported on a series
of block-layer optimizations that enabled a suitably equipped system to
sustain 3.5 million I/O operations per second (IOPS).  That
optimization work has continued since then, and those 3.5 million IOPS
would be a deeply disappointing result now.  A recent disagreement over the
addition of a new feature has highlighted the potential cost of a heavily
optimized block layer, though; when is a feature deemed important enough to
outweigh the drive for maximum performance?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875212/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875212/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:26:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (python3.5, redis, and udisks2), Fedora (rust), openSUSE (binutils, java-1_8_0-openj9, and qemu), Oracle (firefox and httpd), Red Hat (thunderbird), Scientific Linux (thunderbird), and SUSE (binutils, qemu, and systemd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Conill: an inside look into the illicit ad industry]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875189/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875189/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T14:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ariadne Conill shares
some experience of working in the online advertising industry.


	The cycle of patching on both sides is ongoing to this day. A
	friend of mine on Twitter referred to this tug-of-war as “core
	war,” which is an apt description: all of the involved actors are
	trying to patch each other out of being able to commit or detect
	subterfuge, and your browser gets slower and slower as more
	mitigations and countermeasures are layered on. If you’re not using
	an ad blocker yet, stop reading this, and install one: your browser
	will suddenly be a lot more performant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Imagination launches first mobile GPU core with level 4 ray tracing]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471482</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/imagination-launches-first-mobile-gpu-core-with-level-4-ray-tracing/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T13:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New flagship GPU from Imagination Technologies brings desktop-quality ray tracing to mobile for the first time and is industry’s first Level 4 RTLS ray tracing architecture.
The post Imagination launches first mobile GPU core with level 4 ray tracing appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ADLINK launches rugged AI-enabled video analytics platform for railway]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471477</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/adlink-launches-rugged-ai-enabled-video-analytics-platform-for-railway/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T11:38:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Built on the industrial version of Nvidia’s Jetson AGX Xavier module, the AVA-RAGX provides a compact, rugged AI-enabled solution for both onboard and wayside railway applications that delivers reliability and performance in harsh operating environments.
The post ADLINK launches rugged AI-enabled video analytics platform for railway appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블루투데이, 여성·평화운동가 ‘종북’ 낙인 사건 (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82499</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82499"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T08:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[북한과 관계가 악화하던 2015년 5월, 세계 여성·평화 운동가들은 걸어서 비무장지대(DMZ)를 통과하는 ‘위민클로스DMZ(WomenCrossDMZ)’를 기획했습니다. 당시 퍼포먼스엔 반세기 넘게 미국 여성운동을 이끌어 온 클로리아 스타이넘, 노벨평화상 수상자 메어리드 코리건 매과이어(1976년 수상), 리마 보위(2011년 수상)뿐만 12개국 30명의 여성·평화운동가가 참여했습니다. 평화운동가를 ‘종북’으로 낙인찍다  일부 정치세력이 자신과 반대되는 의견을 가진 집단을 매도하고 고립시키기 위해 사용한 말이 있습니다. 2010년대 유행한 말은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블루투데이, 여성·평화운동가 ‘종북’ 낙인 사건 (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82499</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/yHT6DHo-5fw/82499"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T08:57:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[북한과 관계가 악화하던 2015년 5월, 세계 여성·평화 운동가들은 걸어서 비무장지대(DMZ)를 통과하는 ‘위민클로스DMZ(WomenCrossDMZ)’를 기획했습니다. 당시 퍼포먼스엔 반세기 넘게 미국 여성운동을 이끌어 온 클로리아 스타이넘, 노벨평화상 수상자 메어리드 코리건 매과이어(1976년 수상), 리마 보위(2011년 수상)뿐만 12개국 30명의 여성·평화운동가가 참여했습니다. 평화운동가를 ‘종북’으로 낙인찍다  일부 정치세력이 자신과 반대되는 의견을 가진 집단을 매도하고 고립시키기 위해 사용한 말이 있습니다. 2010년대 유행한 말은 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab servers are being exploited in DDoS attacks (The Record)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875154/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875154/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-05T02:27:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Record is reporting
on massive exploitation of an oldish vulnerability in GitLab instances.


	While the purpose of these attacks remained unclear for HN
	Security, yesterday, Google’s Menscher said the hacked servers were
	part of a botnet comprising of “thousands of compromised GitLab
	instances” that was launching large-scale DDoS attacks.


The vulnerability was fixed
in April, but evidently a lot of sites have not updated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반도체 부족 사태가 불러온 자동차 기업과 테크 기업 간 협업]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73694</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/11/04/semiconductorcartech/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=semiconductorcartech"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자동차가 점점 디지털 기기로 바뀌면서 두 산업이 협력했을 때 얻을 수 있는 과실이 커지고 있습니다. “테크 기업은 자동차 기업이, 자동차 기업은 테크 기업이 필요합니다.” 전문가들은 반도체 산업과 자동차 산업이 서로 의존하는 관계를 넘어 경계가 모호해지고 있다고 평가합니다. 포드자동차는 애플과 테슬라 출신의 임원을 영입하고, 인텔과 퀄컴은 자동차 산업에 진출하고 있습니다. 과연 두 산업의 미래는 어떻게 될까요? 월스트리트저널의 기사를 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>malecon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Buffers, a brutal protocol from Google, vs. PVS-Studio, a static code analyzer]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0882/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0882/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Buffers is a very popular, cool, and high-quality product that is mostly developed by Google. This is a good challenge for the PVS-Studio static code analyzer. Finding at least something is already an achievement. Let's give it a shot. I am writing about Protocol Buffers (protobuf) as part of a long-term series of articles about checking open-source projects. The library implements a protocol for structured data serialization. This is an effective binary alternative to the XML text format. The project seemed like an intriguing challenge for the PVS-Studio analyzer, because Google takes a very serious approach to the quality of the C++ code it produces. Take, for example, the "Safer Usage of C++" document that has been actively discussed recently. Additionally, many developers use protobuf in their projects - which means the protobuf product is well-tested. Finding at least a couple of mistakes in this project is a challenge that we have taken upon us. So what are we waiting for? Time to find out what PVS-Studio can do!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Buffers, a brutal protocol from Google, vs. PVS-Studio, a static code analyzer]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0882/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/5M9qvLkHmTo/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Protocol Buffers is a very popular, cool, and high-quality product that is mostly developed by Google. This is a good challenge for the PVS-Studio static code analyzer. Finding at least something is already an achievement. Let's give it a shot. I am writing about Protocol Buffers (protobuf) as part of a long-term series of articles about checking open-source projects. The library implements a protocol for structured data serialization. This is an effective binary alternative to the XML text format. The project seemed like an intriguing challenge for the PVS-Studio analyzer, because Google takes a very serious approach to the quality of the C++ code it produces. Take, for example, the "Safer Usage of C++" document that has been actively discussed recently. Additionally, many developers use protobuf in their projects - which means the protobuf product is well-tested. Finding at least a couple of mistakes in this project is a challenge that we have taken upon us. So what are we waiting for? Time to find out what PVS-Studio can do!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ksmbd: a new in-kernel SMB server (SAMBA+ blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875132/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875132/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T17:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over at the SAMBA+ blog, the performance of the new ksmbd kernel SMB server and Samba in user space are compared:

ksmbd claims performance improvements on a wide range of benchmarks: the graphs on this page show a doubling of performance on some tests. There was also the notion that an in-kernel server is likely an easier place to support SMB Direct, which uses RDMA to transfer data between systems.

Clearly, those number are impressive, but at the same time recent improvements in Samba's IO performance put this into perspective: by leveraging the new "io_uring" Linux API Samba is able to provide roughly 10x the throughput compared to ksmbd.

Time will tell whether it's better to reside in kernel-space like ksmbd or in user-space like Samba in order to squeeze the last bit of performance out of the available hardware.


There are two graphs that show some impressive results for Samba.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개발자 동무, 철의 장막 뒤에서 디버깅 하기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/debugging-behind-the-iron-curtain/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/debugging-behind-the-iron-curtain/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T16:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jake Poznanski의 글 Debugging Behind the Iron Curtain…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Katerina Skroumpelou (Athens, Greece)]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/iamagde-katerina-skroumpelou-athens.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/iamagde-katerina-skroumpelou-athens.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T16:08:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Developers Experts program is a global network of highly experienced technology experts, influencers, and thought leaders who actively support developers, companies, and tech communities by speaking at events and publishing content.
  
Katerina Skroumpelou, who is based in Athens, Greece, is a Senior Software Engineer at Narwhal Technologies, a consulting firm whose product Nx lets developers build multiple full-stack applications and share code among them in the same workspace. She is a Google Developer Expert in Maps and Angular.  
   
 Becoming a Google Maps Platform developer
Skroumpelou has always had a deep love of maps. 
“My father used to have old maps books, and I’ve always been obsessed with knowing where I am and having an understanding of my surroundings, so I’ve alw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Katerina Skroumpelou (Athens, Greece)]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/Nop4lSh5mzA/iamagde-katerina-skroumpelou-athens.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/Nop4lSh5mzA/iamagde-katerina-skroumpelou-athens.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T16:08:00.006Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Developers Experts program is a global network of highly experienced technology experts, influencers, and thought leaders who actively support developers, companies, and tech communities by speaking at events and publishing content.
  
Katerina Skroumpelou, who is based in Athens, Greece, is a Senior Software Engineer at Narwhal Technologies, a consulting firm whose product Nx lets developers build multiple full-stack applications and share code among them in the same workspace. She is a Google Developer Expert in Maps and Angular.  
   
 Becoming a Google Maps Platform developer
Skroumpelou has always had a deep love of maps. 
“My father used to have old maps books, and I’ve always been obsessed with knowing where I am and having an understanding of my surroundings, so I’ve alw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Future of Kidtech: A Web Browser for the Under-10 Set]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2385</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/web-browser-for-kids/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T15:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ninety-eight percent of American kids under the age of 10 have access to a smartphone or tablet in their home; 45 percent even have their own device. Over the past decade, modern touchscreen devices have become both intuitive and affordable enough that they’ve gone mainstream among children around the world. But despite this high usage... Read More
The post The Future of Kidtech: A Web Browser for the Under-10 Set appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Keith Schacht</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Horgan: Linux x86 Program Start Up]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875108/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875108/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T14:51:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Patrick Horgan explains
the process of starting a program on Linux in great detail.



	Well, __libc_start_main calls __libc_init_first,
	who immediately uses secret inside information to find the
	environment variables just after the terminating null of the
	argument vector and then sets a global variable __environ
	which __libc_start_main uses thereafter whenever it needs
	it including when it calls main. After the envp
	is established, then __libc_start_main uses the same trick
	and surprise! Just past the terminating null at the end of the
	envp array, there's another vector, the ELF auxiliary
	vector the loader uses to pass some information to the process. An
	easy way to see what's in there is to set the environment variable
	LD_SHOW_AUXV=1 before running the program.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] 5.16 Merge window, part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874683/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874683/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T14:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of this writing, Linus Torvalds has pulled exactly 6,800 non-merge
changesets into the mainline repository for the 5.16 kernel release.  That
is probably a little over half of what will arrive during this merge
window, so this is a good time to catch up on what has been pulled so far.
There are many significant changes and some large-scale restructuring of
internal kernel code, but relatively few ground-breaking new
features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/875106/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/875106/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T14:17:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (ansible, chromium, kernel, mupdf, python-PyMuPDF, rust, and zathura-pdf-mupdf), openSUSE (qemu and webkit2gtk3), Red Hat (firefox and kpatch-patch), Scientific Linux (firefox), SUSE (qemu, tomcat, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (firefox and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Ecobee’s big deal and climate-friendly chips]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9258</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-ecobees-big-deal-and-climate-friendly-chips/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T13:00:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The big news in IoT this week was the announced acquisition of Ecobee by Generac, so Kevin and I share our thoughts on the deal and what it means for the smart home. After that, we were excited to see Amazon launching a smart air quality monitoring device for $70 as well as publically state […]
The post Podcast: Ecobee’s big deal and climate-friendly chips appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shortlist Announced for the IoT Security Champion Award 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21363</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/shortlist-announced-for-the-iot-security-champion-award-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T09:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are delighted to announce the finalists for the 3rd IoT Security Foundation Champion Award. This award seeks to celebrate organisations which demonstrate stewardship when it comes to IoT security. In alphabetical order, they are: Angoka CENSIS Crypto Quantique EXPLIoT We would also like to thank all other organisations which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>-</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consumer IoT sector – basic cybersecurity hygiene practice still not happening]]></title>
        <id>https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/?p=21344</id>
        <link href="https://www.iotsecurityfoundation.org/consumer-iot-sector-basic-hygiene-practice-still-not-happening/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T09:00:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 4th, 2021: New Report on Industry Adoption of Vulnerability Disclosure Practice Published. The IoT Security Foundation has published its 4th report which examines the practice of vulnerability disclosure in Consumer IoT - with an extension into enterprise and the B2B model. The report is seen as a cybersecurity progress barometer of the sector]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘사실적시 명예훼손’ 합헌 유감: 민주적 대안이 필요하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82487</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82487"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T08:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리 사회는 한창 ‘가짜뉴스’로 인해 골머리를 앓았다. 일부의 목적을 위해 생산·가공된 거짓과 그로인한 피해는 시민의 진실을 향한 사회적 열망을 키워갔다. 최근 크게 논의됐던 ‘언론중재법’ 역시 진실을 추구하고자 하는 시민의 바람을 엿볼 수 있는 대목이었다. 그러나 우리 법체계에서는 진실을 말하는 것조차 조심스러울 수밖에 없는 현실이다. 형법 제307조 제1항에 명시된 이른바 ‘사실적시 명예훼손’이 존재하기 때문이다. 형법 제307조 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘사실적시 명예훼손’ 합헌 유감: 민주적 대안이 필요하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82487</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/F9m_I5YIMyY/82487"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T08:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리 사회는 한창 ‘가짜뉴스’로 인해 골머리를 앓았다. 일부의 목적을 위해 생산·가공된 거짓과 그로인한 피해는 시민의 진실을 향한 사회적 열망을 키워갔다. 최근 크게 논의됐던 ‘언론중재법’ 역시 진실을 추구하고자 하는 시민의 바람을 엿볼 수 있는 대목이었다. 그러나 우리 법체계에서는 진실을 말하는 것조차 조심스러울 수밖에 없는 현실이다. 형법 제307조 제1항에 명시된 이른바 ‘사실적시 명예훼손’이 존재하기 때문이다. 형법 제307조 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 4, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874214/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874214/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-04T01:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 4, 2021 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamentals of image quality tuning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471474</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-fundamentals-of-image-quality-tuning/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T22:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tuning an image pipeline for a particular camera system requires an understanding of each pipeline stage and how each stage can be optimized for a...
The post The fundamentals of image quality tuning appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nazneen A</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Trojan Source: tricks (no treats) with Unicode]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874951/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874951/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T22:21:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new security vulnerability that was disclosed
on November 1 has some interesting properties.  "Trojan Source", as it has been
dubbed, is effectively an attack on human perceptions, especially as they
are filtered through the tools used for source-code review.  While the
specifics of the flaw are new, this kind of trickery is not completely
novel, but Trojan Source finds another way to confuse the humans who are
in the loop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Communities: Q3 ‘21 highlights and achievements]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/machine-learning-communities-q3-21.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/machine-learning-communities-q3-21.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by HyeJung Lee, DevRel Community Manager and Soonson Kwon, DevRel Program Manager
 Let’s explore highlights and achievements of vast Google Machine Learning communities by region for the last quarter. Activities of experts (GDE, professional individuals), communities (TFUG, TensorFlow user groups), students (GDSC, student clubs), and developers groups (GDG) are presented here. 
Key highlights
     
     30 days of ML with Kaggle is designed to help beginners study ML using Kaggle Learn courses as well as a competition specifically for the participants of this program. Collaborated with the Kaggle team so that +30  the ML GDEs and TFUG organizers participated as volunteers as online mentors as well as speakers for this initiative.  
     Total 16 of the GDE/GDSC/TFUGs run community o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Machine Learning Communities: Q3 ‘21 highlights and achievements]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/sACFMd3VPww/machine-learning-communities-q3-21.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/sACFMd3VPww/machine-learning-communities-q3-21.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by HyeJung Lee, DevRel Community Manager and Soonson Kwon, DevRel Program Manager
 Let’s explore highlights and achievements of vast Google Machine Learning communities by region for the last quarter. Activities of experts (GDE, professional individuals), communities (TFUG, TensorFlow user groups), students (GDSC, student clubs), and developers groups (GDG) are presented here. 
Key highlights
     
     30 days of ML with Kaggle is designed to help beginners study ML using Kaggle Learn courses as well as a competition specifically for the participants of this program. Collaborated with the Kaggle team so that +30  the ML GDEs and TFUG organizers participated as volunteers as online mentors as well as speakers for this initiative.  
     Total 16 of the GDE/GDSC/TFUGs run community o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874980/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874980/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T15:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (CuraEngine, curl, firefox, php, and vim), openSUSE (apache2, pcre, salt, transfig, and util-linux), Oracle (.NET 5.0, curl, kernel, libsolv, python3, samba, and webkit2gtk3), and Red Hat (flatpak).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm is researching machine learning at the edge]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9253</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/qualcomm-is-researching-machine-learning-at-the-edge/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T14:12:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regular newsletter readers know that I am beyond excited about machine learning (ML) at the edge. Running algorithms on gateways — or even on sensors — instead of sending data to the cloud to be analyzed can save time, bandwidth costs, and energy, and can protect people’s privacy. So far, ML at the edge has […]
The post Qualcomm is researching machine learning at the edge appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building and Running a DAO: Why Governance Matters]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2352</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/building-and-running-a-dao-why-governance-matters/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T14:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As DeFi and NFT communities grow enormously in size, how to govern decentralized protocols takes on added importance. Now and over the next few years, one of the most immediate challenges facing these communities is to figure out governance — the act of managing collective decision-making in order to optimize funds and operations. Governance requires... Read More
The post Building and Running a DAO: Why Governance Matters appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarun Chitra</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debunking the leading autonomous vehicle myths]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471509</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/debunking-the-leading-autonomous-vehicle-myths/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Autonomous Vehicles (AVs) have the potential to improve road safety, provide mobility for those unable to drive and yield other benefits. Today these goals remain...
The post Debunking the leading autonomous vehicle myths appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Koopman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[읽기 불편한 글]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222557750248</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222557750248"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T12:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<서발턴은 말할 수 있는가>(2016)에 실려 있는 로절린드 모리스의 <서문>을 읽는다. 그런데 잘 이해되지 않는다. 혹은 읽기가 매우 불편하다. 아마 이 책이 서 있는 맥락에 대한 배경 지식이 부족하기 때문일 것이다. 그러나 그런 측면도 분명히 있겠지만, 설명하는 방식이나 문체, 글쓰기가 내 취향이 아니다. 로절란드 모리스는 인류학과에 소속되어 있는 학자이다. 그녀는 매스 미디어, 근대성, 문화 정치, 시각성과 재현, 폭력의 의미화, 젠더 등에 대한 에세이를 썼다고 한다. 이상하게 이런 주제들을 다루고 있는 글에 대해서 거의 읽기 힘들었다는 인상을 가지고 있다. 따라서 나에게 철학적으로 직접 도움이 되지 않는 이런.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노태우 사망, 그리고 대충 잊고 화해하자는 언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82479</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82479"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T08:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제13대 대통령 노태우 씨가 10월 26일 병세 악화로 사망했습니다. 노태우 씨는 12·12군사쿠데타를 주도하고, 5.18민주화운동을 무력으로 진압했으며 전두환 씨와 함께 군부독재시대를 이끈 인물입니다. 6·10민주항쟁이 이뤄낸 직선제 개헌을 통해 제13대 대선에서 대통령에 당선된 노 씨는 재임 기간 서울올림픽 개최, 남북한 유엔 동시 가입, 한반도 비핵화 공동선언 등 성과를 남겼습니다. 그러나 내란죄, 수천억 원 대 비자금 조성 등으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노태우 사망, 그리고 대충 잊고 화해하자는 언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82479</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/jP7ry5dsnR8/82479"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T08:55:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제13대 대통령 노태우 씨가 10월 26일 병세 악화로 사망했습니다. 노태우 씨는 12·12군사쿠데타를 주도하고, 5.18민주화운동을 무력으로 진압했으며 전두환 씨와 함께 군부독재시대를 이끈 인물입니다. 6·10민주항쟁이 이뤄낸 직선제 개헌을 통해 제13대 대선에서 대통령에 당선된 노 씨는 재임 기간 서울올림픽 개최, 남북한 유엔 동시 가입, 한반도 비핵화 공동선언 등 성과를 남겼습니다. 그러나 내란죄, 수천억 원 대 비자금 조성 등으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[데이터 거버넌스와 분석 거버넌스 (ft. 여섯 가지 선행과제)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82461</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82461"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T08:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정부 기관이나 기업 조직의 모든 리더는 데이터가 중요하다는 사실을 알고 있다. 그것이 없이는 조직을 경쟁에서 앞서 나가게 할 디지털 혁신이 있을 수 없다. 새로운 수익원을 창출하는 분석도 할 수 없을 뿐만 아니라 기본적인 사업 운영도 어렵다. 그러나 데이터가 이러한 이니셔티브에 힘을 실어주려면 그 자체가 고품질화되고 및 관련성을 쉽게 이용할 수 있는 분석이 뒷받침되어야 한다. 우수한 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[데이터 거버넌스와 분석 거버넌스 (ft. 여섯 가지 선행과제)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82461</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/7HosanKydoI/82461"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T08:22:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정부 기관이나 기업 조직의 모든 리더는 데이터가 중요하다는 사실을 알고 있다. 그것이 없이는 조직을 경쟁에서 앞서 나가게 할 디지털 혁신이 있을 수 없다. 새로운 수익원을 창출하는 분석도 할 수 없을 뿐만 아니라 기본적인 사업 운영도 어렵다. 그러나 데이터가 이러한 이니셔티브에 힘을 실어주려면 그 자체가 고품질화되고 및 관련성을 쉽게 이용할 수 있는 분석이 뒷받침되어야 한다. 우수한 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Events and Jobs Pages on Interrupt]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/events-and-jobs-pages</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/events-and-jobs-pages"/>
        <updated>2021-11-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Interrupt now has a community-curated Events and Jobs page! We’ve pre-populated it a bit and we invite and welcome you to submit job listings and events that you believe are relevant to the embedded engineering space.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Adding package information to ELF objects]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874642/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874642/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T23:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it is often relatively straightforward to determine what package
provided a binary that is misbehaving—crashing for instance—on Fedora and
other Linux distributions, there are situations where it may be harder to
do so.  A feature recently proposed for Fedora 36—currently
scheduled for the end of April 2022—would embed information into the
binaries themselves to show where they came from.  It is part of a
multi-distribution effort to standardize how this information is stored in
the binaries (and the libraries they use) to assist crash-reporting and other tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio searches for bugs in the DuckStation project]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0881/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0881/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often check retro games. In our company, many developers like to find interesting projects for themselves. They feel nostalgic when they're studying these projects. But we need to run retro games on something, right? This time we checked a project that helps to run old games on modern hardware. DuckStation is an emulator of the Sony PlayStation console. The emulator, according to its website, has a version for Windows, Linux, and for Android smartphones. And recently it was launched on Xbox Series X and S. The project itself contains slightly less than a million lines of C and C++ code. DuckStation doesn't release updates. Its developers regularly commit changes. So, we had to fixate the SHA of the commit: 13c5ee8. We checked the project and found a lot of warnings - 170 of the High level and 434 of the Medium level. Let's look at the 10 most exciting of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio searches for bugs in the DuckStation project]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0881/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/7dHRJ63N0bg/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often check retro games. In our company, many developers like to find interesting projects for themselves. They feel nostalgic when they're studying these projects. But we need to run retro games on something, right? This time we checked a project that helps to run old games on modern hardware. DuckStation is an emulator of the Sony PlayStation console. The emulator, according to its website, has a version for Windows, Linux, and for Android smartphones. And recently it was launched on Xbox Series X and S. The project itself contains slightly less than a million lines of C and C++ code. DuckStation doesn't release updates. Its developers regularly commit changes. So, we had to fixate the SHA of the commit: 13c5ee8. We checked the project and found a lot of warnings - 170 of the High level and 434 of the Medium level. Let's look at the 10 most exciting of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874850/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874850/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T20:10:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 5.14.16, 5.10.77, 5.4.157, 4.19.215, 4.14.254, 4.9.289, and 4.4.291 have been released.  They contain
important fixes and users should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNC Elm Wood Boxes with V-Carving and Inlays]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33769</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/11/02/cnc-elm-wood-boxes-with-v-carving-and-inlays/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T19:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One thing to create with a desktop CNC are boxes: wooden boxes with inlays: Of course there are many other useful things you can o with a CNC and wood. But creating some nice boxes, suitable as a gift or … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 94.0 and Firefox ESR 91.3.0]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/874832/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/874832/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T17:34:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 94.0 has been
released. Linux users should see improved
WebGL performance and reduced power consumption for many workloads. The
about:unloads
page shows the user information about open tabs and allows them to release
system resources by unloading tabs without closing them.  Site
Isolation provides better protection against side-channel attacks. See
the announcement for more new features in this release.

Firefox ESR
91.3 is also available, with various stability, functionality,  and security
fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wi-Fi HaLow is now certified and ready for action]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9234</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/wi-fi-halow-is-now-certified-and-ready-for-action/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T15:13:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At long last, the Wi-Fi Alliance has certified the new Wi-Fi HaLow standard designed to provide connectivity for the internet of things. Chips and evaluation kits that meet the standard are already ready from Morse Micro, and we can expect devices next year. But does the IoT need a new connectivity standard? About five and […]
The post Wi-Fi HaLow is now certified and ready for action appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add some smarts to your under cabinet lights]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9223</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-add-some-smarts-to-your-under-cabinet-lights/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T14:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On our most recent IoT Podcast, Michael called in to our voicemail hotline with a question about his under cabinet light strips. He’s looking for a switch or other option to add some smarts to them, although he’s using a set of smart LIFX light strips. If Michael is going to use a switch, it […]
The post How to add some smarts to your under cabinet lights appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compliance in a DevOps Culture]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/devops-compliance.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/devops-compliance.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T13:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating the necessary security controls and audit capabilities to
      satisfy compliance requirements within a DevOps culture can capitalize on
      CI/CD pipeline automation, but presents unique challenges as an
      organization scales. Understanding the second order implications and
      unintended consequences caused by the chosen implementation is key to
      building an effective, secure, and scalable solution. My colleague Carl
      Nygard describes how to think of these choices through a
      series of four patterns for handling compliance.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[스포티파이 주가 전망, 뮤직 스트리밍 전망과   스포티파이 비즈 모델 확장은 장기 성장성 증명 & 목표주가 ⬆️]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584459</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584459/%ec%8a%a4%ed%8f%ac%ed%8b%b0%ed%8c%8c%ec%9d%b4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-%ec%8a%a4%ed%8f%ac%ed%8b%b0%ed%8c%8c%ec%9d%b4-%eb%b3%b4%ea%b3%a0%ec%84%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T10:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[급증하는 인스타그램 광고 매출, 페이스북 광고 매출의 절반을 차지하면서 페이스북 핵심 사업군으로 등장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584453</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584453/%ec%9d%b8%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%80%ea%b7%b8%eb%9e%a8-%ea%b4%91%ea%b3%a0-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T10:10:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[웬만하면 ‘먹거리 X파일’을 이길 수 없다: 벌집 아이스크림(’14), 정육식당(’15), 대왕 카스텔라 (’17)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82447</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82447"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T09:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2000년대 중반, MBC [불만제로UP]과 KBS [소비자 고발] 등을 시작으로 이른바 ‘예능형 소비자 고발 프로그램’이 잇따라 등장하며 상품 평가에 대한 자세한 정보를 알고 싶어하던 시청자 수요를 충족시키며 큰 인기를 끌었습니다. 이들 프로그램은 실제로 소비자 권익 향상에 긍정적인 영향을 주었는데요. 반면 ‘황토팩 사건’처럼 사실을 과장하거나 전문성이 떨어지는 접근으로 멀쩡한 업체에 막대한 피해를 주기도 했습니다. 채널A [먹거리 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[웬만하면 ‘먹거리 X파일’을 이길 수 없다: 벌집 아이스크림(’14), 정육식당(’15), 대왕 카스텔라 (’17)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82447</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/Vy58z_r-s60/82447"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T09:26:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2000년대 중반, MBC [불만제로UP]과 KBS [소비자 고발] 등을 시작으로 이른바 ‘예능형 소비자 고발 프로그램’이 잇따라 등장하며 상품 평가에 대한 자세한 정보를 알고 싶어하던 시청자 수요를 충족시키며 큰 인기를 끌었습니다. 이들 프로그램은 실제로 소비자 권익 향상에 긍정적인 영향을 주었는데요. 반면 ‘황토팩 사건’처럼 사실을 과장하거나 전문성이 떨어지는 접근으로 멀쩡한 업체에 막대한 피해를 주기도 했습니다. 채널A [먹거리 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[On “Trojan Source” Attacks]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/trojan</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/trojan"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T03:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Code review is the answer to this and many other problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[페이스북 리브랜딩, 메타로 변경은 ‘대담하며 위험한 도박’으로 진지한 메타버스 전략과 소셜 미디어 논쟁에서 벗어나려는 전략]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584444</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584444/%ed%8e%98%ec%9d%b4%ec%8a%a4%eb%b6%81-%eb%a6%ac%eb%b8%8c%eb%9e%9c%eb%94%a9-%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80%eb%a1%9c-%eb%b3%80%ea%b2%bd%ec%9d%98%ed%8e%98%ec%9d%b4%ec%8a%a4%eb%b6%81-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T03:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[apt.llvm.org - moving from physical server to the cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2021-11-02-apt.llvm.org-moving-from-physical-server-to-the-cloud/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2021-11-02-apt.llvm.org-moving-from-physical-server-to-the-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I would like to explain how I migrated
apt.llvm.org from physical hardware hosted in
a datacenter to the Google cloud. This has resulted in better security
and faster builds for LLVM Debian/Ubuntu nightly builds.
Previous infrastructure
About 10 years ago, Nick Lewycky from Google offered to replace my mix
of old and terrible servers with 16 blade servers in a chassis and a
control server. Below are pictures of the front and back of these
servers, which have served us faithfully for 10 years:
 
The hosting was sponsored by IRILL, at
Inria, next to Versailles.
This setup was running using a PXE install with preseed to set up
everything on the 16 blades.
While it served us very well for years, it is now holding us back.
Some of the blades are dying;
Old hardware - it takes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The LLVM Project Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in October]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/october-2021-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/october-2021-roundup"/>
        <updated>2021-11-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
October.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[11/1] 월가 애널리스트 투자 의견을 모아보다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584188</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584188/11-1-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80-%ec%95%a0%eb%84%90%eb%a6%ac%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%93%a4%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ec%9d%84-%eb%aa%a8%ec%95%84%eb%b3%b4%eb%8b%a4"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T23:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[닉 클레그 “페이스북 혼자서는 문제를 풀 수 없습니다”]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73680</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/11/01/wsjclegg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wsjclegg"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T22:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[월스트리트저널이 지난 주말판에 "소셜미디어, 어떻게 고칠 수 있을까?(How to Fix Social Media)"라는 제목아래 여러 전문가의 칼럼을 한데 실었습니다. 메타(Meta)로 이름을 바꾼 (구) 페이스북의 글로벌 사업 부사장 닉 클레그의 글을 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[에이미 클로부샤르 “이제는 도무지 못 미더워진 빅테크”]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73673</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/11/01/wsjklobuchar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=wsjklobuchar"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T22:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[월스트리트저널이 지난 주말판에 "소셜미디어, 어떻게 고칠 수 있을까?(How to Fix Social Media)"라는 제목아래 여러 전문가의 칼럼을 한데 실었습니다. 지난해 미국 대선 민주당 경선에 참여했던 에이미 클로부샤르 상원의원의 글을 소개합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[철학적 탐구와 역사적 탐구]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222555932439</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222555932439"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T20:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[철학 전공자의 논문이 마치 역사학자가 쓴 역사 논문 같다는 것을 어떻게 평가해야 하는가? 역사적 탐구는 있지만, 철학적 탐구는 실종되어 역사적 고찰로 대체되어 있다. 그 결과, 논문이 주장하는 바가 분명치 않거나 혹은 주장하는 바가 없거나, 당연하지만 그저 막연한 제안으로 끝나고 있다. 처음 글을 읽었을 때, 나는 당연하게 저자가 철학에 관심이 있는 역사학자인지 알았다. 그런데 한국철학 전공이다. 한국철학 혹은 동양철학은 철학개념이나 철학적 탐구를 역사나 개념의 고고학으로, 기원과 발생에 대한 탐구로 대체하면서 바로 그것이 진정한 <철학>이라고 주장하는 것인가? 과거를 서술하고 설명하는 과정에서 주장이나 논.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[맞수 인텔과 AMD 비교, 이제 AMD 투자보다 인텔 투자가 낫다는 주장이 제기되다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584435</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584435/%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%94%ea%b3%bc-amd-%eb%b9%84%ea%b5%90-amd-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-vs-%ec%9d%b8%ed%85%94-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T19:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Kotlin support for protocol buffers]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/announcing-kotlin-support-for-protocol.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/11/announcing-kotlin-support-for-protocol.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T18:21:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Deanna Garcia and Louis Wasserman - Software Developers, and Developer Advocate, James Ward
      
Google’s commitment to Kotlin
  
At Google, we’re investing deeply in the Kotlin language and ecosystem. Android development is now Kotlin first, our engineering teams work on language evolution through the Kotlin Foundation, and inside of Google we’re using Kotlin more and more to build our backend services. We love Kotlin for its expressiveness, safety, simple async support through coroutines, and easy bidirectional interoperability with the Java programming language. 
Kotlin for protocol buffers
  
Last year, we open sourced Kotlin support for gRPC, the open source Remote Procedure Call (RPC) framework that powers thousands of microservices at Google. We’re excited to deepen our …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Kotlin support for protocol buffers]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/x3Eu7IlBdIc/announcing-kotlin-support-for-protocol.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/x3Eu7IlBdIc/announcing-kotlin-support-for-protocol.html"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T18:21:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Deanna Garcia and Louis Wasserman - Software Developers, and Developer Advocate, James Ward
      
Google’s commitment to Kotlin
  
At Google, we’re investing deeply in the Kotlin language and ecosystem. Android development is now Kotlin first, our engineering teams work on language evolution through the Kotlin Foundation, and inside of Google we’re using Kotlin more and more to build our backend services. We love Kotlin for its expressiveness, safety, simple async support through coroutines, and easy bidirectional interoperability with the Java programming language. 
Kotlin for protocol buffers
  
Last year, we open sourced Kotlin support for gRPC, the open source Remote Procedure Call (RPC) framework that powers thousands of microservices at Google. We’re excited to deepen our …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BNPL 선도자 어펌, 파트너 증가 정체로 어펌 점유율이 하락하고 있다 by 모건스탠리]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584427</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584427/bnpl-%ec%84%a0%eb%8f%84%ec%9e%90-%ec%96%b4%ed%8e%8c-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8-%ed%95%98%eb%9d%bd"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T17:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Consulting: Empowerment & Championing]]></title>
        <id>https://jameshunt.us/?p=419</id>
        <link href="https://jameshunt.us/writings/joining-vivanti/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T16:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, I start a new chapter in my career as a technologist and problem-solver, as I officially join Vivanti as a founding member and Principal Consultant. In honor of the occasion, I want to tell you a story about one of my earliest consulting screw-ups]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jhunt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[21년 10월 수출 분석, 수출 피크아웃 주장은 타당할까?  수출증가율 전망 27% vs 수출증가율 24%]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584422</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584422/21%eb%85%84-10%ec%9b%94-%ec%88%98%ec%b6%9c-%eb%b6%84%ec%84%9d-%ec%88%98%ec%b6%9c-%ed%94%bc%ed%81%ac%ec%95%84%ec%9b%83-%ec%a3%bc%ec%9e%a5%ec%9d%80-%ed%83%80%eb%8b%b9%ed%95%a0%ea%b9%8c-%ec%88%98"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T13:46:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서(恕) 혹은 배려]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222555485515</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222555485515"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T10:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개인적으로 <논어>에서 중요한 것이 충서(忠恕) 혹은 서(恕)라고 생각한다. 공자가 증자에게 말한다. 내 도는 하나로 관통되어 있다. 다른 이들이 증자에게 묻는다. 그것이 무엇인가? 바로 충서(忠恕)이다. 그런데 이 충서에 대해서 공자는 더 이상 명백하게 말하지 않는다. 반면에 서(恕)는 아니다. 공자는 서(恕)에 대해서 분명하게 말한다. 그것은 우리가 평생토록 추구할 만한 것이다. 己所不欲(기소불욕) 勿施於人(물시어인), 즉 자기가 원하는 것이 아니면 남에게 베풀지 마라. 한자사전을 찾아보면 서(恕)는 ‘용서’, ‘어질다’, ‘동정(同情)’, ‘남의 처지에 서서 동정(同情)하는 마음’ 등의 뜻이다. 공자가 말한 서(恕), 혹.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[같은 실적인데 GM 주가보다 포드 주가가 더 오르는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584412</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584412/%ed%8f%ac%eb%93%9c-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T09:45:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조각모음: 2021년 9월, 10월]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/defragment-sep-2021-to-oct/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/defragment-sep-2021-to-oct/"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T07:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이제 앞으로 더 바빠질 예정이라서 9월, 1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[M1 Mach-O 바이너리 리버싱]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11085234</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/11085234"/>
        <updated>2021-11-01T05:16:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mach-O 는 macOS에서 사용하는 바이너리 형식 포맷이다. 기존에는 애플도 인텔 칩셋을 사용했기 때문에 바이너리도 인텔용 바이너리로 사용되었다.
그러나 2020년 M1칩을 발표하면서부터 macOS는 ARM64로 전환되었고, 이에 따라 바이너리 형식 역시 ARM64를 따르게 되었다. 물론 원래부터 iOS를 구동하는 아이폰 및 아이패드가 ARM 디바이스였으므로 완전히 새로운 내용은 아니다. 다만 성능 차원에서 훨씬 뛰어난데다가 컴퓨터용 운영체제인 macOS가 ARM64를 지원하게 되었고, 2021년 계속해서 M1 Max 등 새로운 칩셋들을 계속 ARM64로 고수하고 있으므로 향후에는 결국 ARM64 기반의 Mach-O가 완전히 자리잡을 것으로 보인다.
한편 M1 칩셋 환경을 대상으로 하는 M1 악성코드가 출현하고 있다(참고 : GoSearch22). 그러므로 M1 환경에서 악성코드 분석이라던지 취약점 분석을 하기 위해서는 M1용 바이너리를 역공학(reverse engineering) 하는 방법을 필수적으로 숙지해야 할 것이다.
물론 리버싱 실무에서 사실상의 표준 도구로 사용되는 IDA Pro 같은 경우 이미 ARM64 macOS 에 대한 지원 업데이트를 출시했다. .. 역시 자본주의 사회에서는 돈이 .. 최고다..  이 글에서는 IDA를 사용하지 않고, 순수하게 디스어셈블 도구를 사용하여 어셈블리 언어 수준의 분석을 수행해보는 것으로 한다.


1. C 언어로 Hello World 예제 작성하기
2014년 애플은 swift 프로그래밍 언어를 발표했다. 원래 iOS 앱이나 macOS 앱은 Objective-C…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a PVS-Studio developer defended a bug in a checked project]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0880/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0880/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PVS-Studio developers often check open-source projects and write articles about that. Sometimes, when writing an article, we come across interesting situations or epic errors. Of course, we want to write a small note about it. This is one of those cases. At the moment I'm writing an article about checking the DuckStation project. This is an emulator of the Sony PlayStation console. The project is quite interesting and actively developing. I found some interesting bugs and want to share a story about one with you. This article demonstrates: PVS-Studio has issued a warning: V726 An attempt to free memory containing the 'wbuf' array by using the 'free' function. This is incorrect as 'wbuf' was created on stack. log.cpp 216]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a PVS-Studio developer defended a bug in a checked project]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0880/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/wHV5QmHUnyk/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PVS-Studio developers often check open-source projects and write articles about that. Sometimes, when writing an article, we come across interesting situations or epic errors. Of course, we want to write a small note about it. This is one of those cases. At the moment I'm writing an article about checking the DuckStation project. This is an emulator of the Sony PlayStation console. The project is quite interesting and actively developing. I found some interesting bugs and want to share a story about one with you. This article demonstrates: PVS-Studio has issued a warning: V726 An attempt to free memory containing the 'wbuf' array by using the 'free' function. This is incorrect as 'wbuf' was created on stack. log.cpp 216]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기존 업체외 질적으로 다른 테슬라 경쟁력 세가지, Piper Sandler의 테슬라 목표주가 상향 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584393</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584393/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ea%b2%bd%ec%9f%81%eb%a0%a5%ea%b3%bc-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ed%96%a5"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T13:15:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KT 장애, 개발자가 읽어야 할 포인트]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=10999</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2021/10/31/core_point_for_kt_fail_over/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T12:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(그림)”유선 통신망은 보안망이라 인터넷에 공개된 무선망 구성도만 추가해봅니다.” 이 글은 이제 갓 입문한 초보개발자들이 읽었으면 해서 정리해 보았습니다. 2021.10.25일.큰 장애가 있었습니다.KT 에서 네트워크 작업을 하다 오류가 났죠.모바일인터넷, 유선인터넷이 모두 안되었습니다. 피해범위는 전국 규모였습니다.인터넷 결제가 되지 않으니 음식점이 난리 났구요.인터넷이 되지 않으니, 카톡도 쓸 수 없었습니다. 다행히 은행은 동작했습니다.은행은 이런 경우를 대비해서 이중화된 회선을 운영합니다.대금결제가 안되면 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유영모의 노자]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222554309798</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222554309798"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T09:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유사성보다는 차이성에 주목하는 것이 철학적으로 더 생산적이라고 지적했다. https://blog.naver.com/sellars/222533344369 차이성을 무시할 때, 우리 근대철학에서 볼 수 있듯이 모든 것이 하나가 되는 현상을 목도할 수 있다. 이렇게 지적할 때, 그냥 떠오른 인물이 유영모와 함석헌이었다. 진짜 그들이 그런 주장을 하는지 그들 저술을 차분하게 읽어보아야 하지만, 사실 읽어보고 싶은 마음은 거의 없다. 노자에 대한 논문 하나를 읽다가 다음과 같은 구절을 발견한다. <20세기 한국의 현실에서 노자는 분명 하나의 전통이자 상식이 되었다. 그 출발은 오히려 대학의 ‘철학’이 아닌 다른 공간에서 싹터 나왔다. 1958년 최초의 한글 노.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 애플 실적을 읽는 월가 IB들의 애플 투자의견 및 애플 주가 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584372</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584372/3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%a0%ed%92%80-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%9b%84-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T07:53:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[책을 읽는다는 것]]></title>
        <id>http://wallflower.egloos.com/4202693</id>
        <link href="http://wallflower.egloos.com/4202693"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T00:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[십 여년 전 일본에 가면 인상적이었던 장면이 바로 지하철에서 너도 나도 책을 읽고 있는 모습이었다. 아담한 문고본을 펼쳐 들고 주위를 아랑곳하지 않고 책에 눈을 박고 있는 노인들의 모습도 심심찮게 볼 수 있었다. 나만 그 장면들을 기억에 새겼던 것은 아니었을 것이.... 글 전체보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이택광</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오징어 게임 신드롬]]></title>
        <id>http://wallflower.egloos.com/4202692</id>
        <link href="http://wallflower.egloos.com/4202692"/>
        <updated>2021-10-31T00:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<오징어 게임>에 대한 비평은 아니고, "영업용" 칼럼이다. 중앙선데이에 실렸다. 많은 이들이 "한국적 이야기" 덕분에 <오징어 게임>이 성공했다고 주장하지만, 내 생각은 다르다. 이미 <킹덤>이나 <반도>의 사례에서 확인했듯이, <오징.... 글 전체보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이택광</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘메타’를 소개합니다 – 마크 주커버그(번역)]]></title>
        <id>https://ebadak.news/?p=2785</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2021/10/30/founders-letter-meta/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-30T05:02:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[앞으로 우리는 페이스북 퍼스트가 아닌, 메타버스 퍼스트 회사가 될 것입니다. 앞으로 우리의 새로운 서비스들을 활용하는데 있어 페이스북 계정의 활용이 강제가 되지 않을 것이라는 뜻입니다. 우리의 새로운 브랜드가 서비스들에 녹아들때, 더 많은 분들이 ‘메타’라는 브랜드의 의미와 우리가 지향하는 미래에 대해 공감해주실 수 있다면 좋겠습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rick Kim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for October 29, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9218</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-october-29-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T18:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LEGO inspired Volvo to make a smart, modular wheel loader: Volvo Construction Equipment has built a 5-ton electric wheel loader that was inspired by a LEGO Technic model. Volvo and LEGO created a partnership back in 2018 to help design LEGO Technic kits. But the engineers at both companies saw the LEGOs as an inspiration […]
The post IoT news of the week for October 29, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: Arduino contest, LC3/MPEG 5 codecs, UWB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471434</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-arduino-contest-lc3-mpeg-5-codecs-uwb/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T17:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes EEWeb design contest, low complexity video and audio, and UWB certification, plus acquisitions, funding, people and new products.
The post embedded news week: Arduino contest, LC3/MPEG 5 codecs, UWB appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Round Corner Template Set for Woodworking]]></title>
        <id>https://luckyresistor.me/?p=11623</id>
        <link href="https://luckyresistor.me/2021/10/29/round-corner-template-set-for-woodworking/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T17:21:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I like to have rounded corners in my woodworking projects. It seems many people like to soften the spiky ends of their panels because there is a huge range of templates for routing. If you own a 3d printer, it is handy you can print just the template with the size you actually need....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucky Resistor</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily connect Google Pay with your preferred payment processor]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/easily-connect-google-pay.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/easily-connect-google-pay.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T17:00:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Stephen McDonald, Developer Relations Engineer, Google Pay
  

  
Easily connect Google Pay with your preferred payment processor
  
Adding Google Pay as a payment method to your website or Android application provides a secure and fast checkout option for your users. To enable Google Pay, you will first need a Payment Service Provider (PSP). For the integration this means understanding how your payments processing stack works with Google Pay APIs.  
End-to-end PSP samples
 To make integration easier, we’ve launched a new open source project containing end-to-end samples for a range of PSPs, demonstrating the entire integration process - from client-side configuration, to server-side integration with the PSPs, using their respective APIs and client libraries where applicable. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily connect Google Pay with your preferred payment processor]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/YZS5SSgmgUE/easily-connect-google-pay.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/YZS5SSgmgUE/easily-connect-google-pay.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T17:00:00.008Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Stephen McDonald, Developer Relations Engineer, Google Pay
  

  
Easily connect Google Pay with your preferred payment processor
  
Adding Google Pay as a payment method to your website or Android application provides a secure and fast checkout option for your users. To enable Google Pay, you will first need a Payment Service Provider (PSP). For the integration this means understanding how your payments processing stack works with Google Pay APIs.  
End-to-end PSP samples
 To make integration easier, we’ve launched a new open source project containing end-to-end samples for a range of PSPs, demonstrating the entire integration process - from client-side configuration, to server-side integration with the PSPs, using their respective APIs and client libraries where applicable. The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Span is tackling our outdated grid one breaker box at a time]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9215</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/span-is-tackling-our-outdated-grid-one-breaker-box-at-a-time/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T16:18:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the urgency of the climate crisis becomes increasingly clear, technology firms are pushing harder toward solutions designed to boost electrification and the use of renewable energy. Solar panels have become more common, for example, as have smart thermostats and a focus on energy-saving services, in both homes and offices. But there are generations of aging […]
The post Span is tackling our outdated grid one breaker box at a time appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Successful real-time acoustic processing requires careful planning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471432</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/successful-real-time-acoustic-processing-requires-careful-planning/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T14:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low latency, real-time acoustic processing is a key factor in many embedded processing applications, among them voice preprocessing, speech recognition, and active noise cancellation (ANC)....
The post Successful real-time acoustic processing requires careful planning appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Katz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Novel energy harvesting tech could reshape medical devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471422</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/novel-energy-harvesting-tech-could-reshape-medical-devices/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T14:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Medical devices have come a tremendously long way over the years, saving lives and helping people manage illnesses. However, one primary downside is that their...
The post Novel energy harvesting tech could reshape medical devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[너무 쉬운 낙인: 친동생 살해 누명 사건 (2003), 칼부림 목사 누명 사건 (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82430</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82430"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T00:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여기 두 사건이 있습니다. 빚진 돈 때문에 친동생을 죽였다고 누명 쓴 형이 있고, 동료 목사와의 다툼 중에 칼부림했다고 ‘칼부림 목사’로 낙인 찍힌 목사가 있습니다. 당사자에게는 사회적 인격이 파괴되는 중대한 사건이었습니다. 하지만 몇몇 언론에게는 그저 경찰 보도자료를 받아쓰기하면서 아직 혐의에 불과함에도 불구하고 ‘범인으로 단정’해버리고, 자기 신분도 밝히지 않고 형사과장에게 전화 걸어 받은 부정확한 답변을 그저 기사로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[너무 쉬운 낙인: 친동생 살해 누명 사건 (2003), 칼부림 목사 누명 사건 (2015)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82430</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/tQyDyqczdao/82430"/>
        <updated>2021-10-29T00:15:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여기 두 사건이 있습니다. 빚진 돈 때문에 친동생을 죽였다고 누명 쓴 형이 있고, 동료 목사와의 다툼 중에 칼부림했다고 ‘칼부림 목사’로 낙인 찍힌 목사가 있습니다. 당사자에게는 사회적 인격이 파괴되는 중대한 사건이었습니다. 하지만 몇몇 언론에게는 그저 경찰 보도자료를 받아쓰기하면서 아직 혐의에 불과함에도 불구하고 ‘범인으로 단정’해버리고, 자기 신분도 밝히지 않고 형사과장에게 전화 걸어 받은 부정확한 답변을 그저 기사로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 친구가 될 수 없는 이유(2/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73647</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/10/28/m-friends2/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-friends2"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T22:55:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(Brendan Mackie, 리얼라이프) 원문 보기 인류는 소속감의 위기가 올 때마다 새로운 기술을 이용해 여기에 대응해 왔습니다. 르네상스 시대에는 손편지가 있었습니다. 초기 산업 사회는 클럽이 그 역할을 했습니다. 1950년대에는 TV가 있었고, 이제 사람들은 스마트폰에서 소속감을 찾고 있습니다. 1950년대 유행한 친밀감 쇼처럼, 오늘날의 준사회적 미디어 역시 친밀감을 목적으로 만들어집니다. 방송인은 대화하듯 말하며, 자신의 사적인 삶에 관해 이야기하고, 자신의 설정된 약점을 밝힙니다. 침실이나 컴퓨터 앞에서 이야기하며, 때로 자신의 가족이나 친구들과 같이 나타나는 등 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 친구가 될 수 없는 이유(1/2)]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73646</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/10/28/m-friends1/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=m-friends1"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T22:54:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[팟캐스트와 같은 “준사회적(parasocial)” 미디어들은 친구 관계와 물질적인 관계를 뒤섞고 있다. (Brendan Mackie, 리얼라이프) 원문 보기   지난 10년 동안 인터넷의 유명인에게 일방적인 친밀감을 느끼는 현상은 매우 흔해졌습니다. 이는 준사회적(parasocial) 관계라는 것으로, 사회적 관계와 거의 비슷하지만 다른 관계, 혹은 다소 뒤틀린 사회적 관계라는 뜻입니다. 예를 들어 미국의 코미디언 존 멀레이니의 팬들은 그의 농담에 웃을 때 만큼이나 그가 겪은 최근의 힘든 일을 걱정합니다. 블랙핑크나 트와이스와 같은 K팝 그룹의 팬들(각각 Blinks 와 Onces)은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Warnings of Static Analyzer]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0879/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0879/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone who runs the static analyzer on a project for the first time is slightly shocked by hundreds, thousands or even tens of thousands of warnings. It may be frustrating. Is my code so terrible? Or is the analyzer lying? In any case, filtering by the severity changes the situation, not completely though. That's why we thought about how we could improve the first experience with the analyzer. Let me show you the new feature step by step... What does a person, who runs code through a static analyzer for the first time, encounter? When run on large projects, a static analyzer produces a huge number of warnings for various code fragments. Yes, it may be an enormous number of warnings. Of course, there will be false positives among them. Alas, static analysis cannot exist without false positives. Therefore, it was necessary to create a new approach that would simplify the process when one is just starting out with the analyzer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Warnings of Static Analyzer]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/0879/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/lCLSrYO4bWo/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone who runs the static analyzer on a project for the first time is slightly shocked by hundreds, thousands or even tens of thousands of warnings. It may be frustrating. Is my code so terrible? Or is the analyzer lying? In any case, filtering by the severity changes the situation, not completely though. That's why we thought about how we could improve the first experience with the analyzer. Let me show you the new feature step by step... What does a person, who runs code through a static analyzer for the first time, encounter? When run on large projects, a static analyzer produces a huge number of warnings for various code fragments. Yes, it may be an enormous number of warnings. Of course, there will be false positives among them. Alas, static analysis cannot exist without false positives. Therefore, it was necessary to create a new approach that would simplify the process when one is just starting out with the analyzer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[구글 클라우드 넥스트 ’21: 구글이 강조한 세 가지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82414</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82414"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T19:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[구글 클라우드 넥스트는 구글이 매년 개최하는 클라우드 분야 전문 컨퍼런스다. 2021년에는 10월 12일에서 14일까지 개최됐다. 오프닝 키노트에서 선다 피차이(구글&알파벳 CEO)와 토마스 쿠리안(구글 클라우드 CEO)은 새로운 제품과 기능, 확장 계획 및 파트너십 등을 주제로 광범위하게 발표했다. 선다 피차이는 현재 구글 클라우드가 28개 리전에 있는데 향후 10개를 더 늘릴 예정이고, 19개의 해저 케이블을 통해 모두 연결할 것이라고 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[구글 클라우드 넥스트 ’21: 구글이 강조한 세 가지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82414</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/7kkFpcvtpRY/82414"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T19:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[구글 클라우드 넥스트는 구글이 매년 개최하는 클라우드 분야 전문 컨퍼런스다. 2021년에는 10월 12일에서 14일까지 개최됐다. 오프닝 키노트에서 선다 피차이(구글&알파벳 CEO)와 토마스 쿠리안(구글 클라우드 CEO)은 새로운 제품과 기능, 확장 계획 및 파트너십 등을 주제로 광범위하게 발표했다. 선다 피차이는 현재 구글 클라우드가 28개 리전에 있는데 향후 10개를 더 늘릴 예정이고, 19개의 해저 케이블을 통해 모두 연결할 것이라고 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Martin Kleppe]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/iamagde-martin-kleppe.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/iamagde-martin-kleppe.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T19:19:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE series presents: Google Maps Platform
 The Google Developers Experts program is a global network of highly experienced technology experts, influencers, and thought leaders who actively support developers, companies, and tech communities by speaking at events and publishing content.
    
Martin Kleppe is a co-founder of Ubilabs, a Google Cloud partner since 2012. He is the head of development, responsible for R&D and technical strategy. He talks with customers to understand their challenges and which location technologies will best serve them. He also works with partners like Google to determine the best ways to combine the latest technologies. 
Ubilabs – a data and location technology consultancy specializing in product and software development, visualization, implementation, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Martin Kleppe]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/44sEoBU2PGs/iamagde-martin-kleppe.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/44sEoBU2PGs/iamagde-martin-kleppe.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T19:19:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE series presents: Google Maps Platform
 The Google Developers Experts program is a global network of highly experienced technology experts, influencers, and thought leaders who actively support developers, companies, and tech communities by speaking at events and publishing content.
    
Martin Kleppe is a co-founder of Ubilabs, a Google Cloud partner since 2012. He is the head of development, responsible for R&D and technical strategy. He talks with customers to understand their challenges and which location technologies will best serve them. He also works with partners like Google to determine the best ways to combine the latest technologies. 
Ubilabs – a data and location technology consultancy specializing in product and software development, visualization, implementation, and …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cadence HiFi DSP targets always-on hearables and wearables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471414</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-cadence-hifi-dsp-targets-always-on-hearables-and-wearables/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T18:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence introduces Tensilica HiFi 1 DSP to provide better voice and music processing performance with optimal neural network capability in a compact footprint with ultra-low energy.
The post New Cadence HiFi DSP targets always-on hearables and wearables appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s Next for Creator Platforms? Learning to Sell]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?p=2268</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/creator-platforms-neglect-the-sell/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T15:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If there’s one main idea driving excitement in the “creator economy,” it’s this: Creators with large audiences on platforms like Instagram, TikTok, Twitter, and YouTube could generate orders of magnitude increases in revenue if they had better ways to charge fans for content directly, rather than relying on ads or merch sales.  A wave of... Read More
The post What’s Next for Creator Platforms? Learning to Sell appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nathan Baschez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The IoT Online Conference (2021)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=13695</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/the-iot-online-conference-2022/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T14:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The IoT Online Conference is back, and this time the core focus is on IoT embedded systems and edge computing. This post will explore what will be happening at this year’s conference and how teams and developers can benefit. The IoT Online Conference Overview The IoT Online Conference will be taking place December 8 – … Continue reading The IoT Online Conference (2021)
The IoT Online Conference (2021) first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Energy harvesting sensors are finally real]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9212</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-energy-harvesting-sensors-are-finally-real/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T13:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s show kicks off with news from many of the big smart home players offering their plans for the Matter smart home protocol. First, we discuss Google’s plans, before focusing on Samsung’s latest announcements and then a surprise update from Eero, which is owned by Amazon. Sticking with Amazon, we also cover the news […]
The post Podcast: Energy harvesting sensors are finally real appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[K를 생각한다] 서평에 답하며]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82394</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82394"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T10:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“위대한 정신은 숭배받기보다는 비판받기를 원한다.” (니체)   요즘 토론은 점점 더 귀한 멸종위기동물처럼 느껴집니다. 서로 치열하게 싸우더라도 상대를 존중하는 미덕은 사라진지 오랩니다. 오직 승리만이 목적이고, 증오만이 동력인 전장터만 여기저기 흩어져 있습니다. ‘스트리트 우먼 파이터’의 멋진 배틀은 많은 이에게 감동을 주었습니다. ‘배틀 필드’에는 댄서들의 열정과 투쟁심이 넘쳤습니다. 하지만 모든 싸움이 끝나고, 댄서들은 마치 따뜻한 자매처럼, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>임명묵</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[K를 생각한다] 서평에 답하며]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82394</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/-BpsSZSTAEw/82394"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T10:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“위대한 정신은 숭배받기보다는 비판받기를 원한다.” (니체)   요즘 토론은 점점 더 귀한 멸종위기동물처럼 느껴집니다. 서로 치열하게 싸우더라도 상대를 존중하는 미덕은 사라진지 오랩니다. 오직 승리만이 목적이고, 증오만이 동력인 전장터만 여기저기 흩어져 있습니다. ‘스트리트 우먼 파이터’의 멋진 배틀은 많은 이에게 감동을 주었습니다. ‘배틀 필드’에는 댄서들의 열정과 투쟁심이 넘쳤습니다. 하지만 모든 싸움이 끝나고, 댄서들은 마치 따뜻한 자매처럼, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>임명묵</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블로그 업데이트]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/blog-update-2021-fall/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/blog-update-2021-fall/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T09:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gatsby v…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software tools determine edge AI accelerator success]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471448</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/software-tools-determine-edge-ai-accelerator-success/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T00:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unlike GPUs, which have established programming models and software toolchains, AI processors face a shortfall in software support.   While artificial intelligence (AI) advancements are...
The post Software tools determine edge AI accelerator success appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rehan Hameed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Functional Duplications]]></title>
        <id>http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/10/28/functional-duplication.html</id>
        <link href="http://blog.cleancoder.com/uncle-bob/2021/10/28/functional-duplication.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I broke out my old Space War game a few days ago and decided to make a few changes to speed the game up and make it more fun to play.  In so doing I discovered a very interesting bug.
One of the changes I made was to populate the initial space with a few random bases scattered here and there.  This would allow the player some extra resources with which to battle the Klingons while building up a network of more bases.
While I was playing the modified game, it crashed.  Hard.
Now I wrote this with TDD, and I was very disciplined about the cleanliness of the code, and the test coverage.  So this was unexpected.  So I dug up all my old debugging skills from the pit in which I had buried them, and started to work out what was going on.
It wasn't long before I realized that crash was occuring be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Clean Code Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5G fits needs of industrial IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471454</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5g-fits-needs-of-industrial-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T18:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why is the industrial IoT such a good fit for 5G? Here are some of the characteristics that make the two a match. When considering...
The post 5G fits needs of industrial IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samsung SmartThings is making all the right moves when it comes to the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9198</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/samsung-smartthings-is-making-all-the-right-moves-when-it-comes-to-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T14:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Given the smart home successes of Amazon, Apple, and Google, I’ve generally considered Samsung to be an also-ran in the consumer IoT space. Yes, I used Samsung SmartThings hardware and software to power my smart home in the past. Yes, it worked. But Samsung’s innovation levels seemed to lag and then it got out of […]
The post Samsung SmartThings is making all the right moves when it comes to the IoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3년째 같은 기사: 클릭 저널리즘의 현주소]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82382</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82382"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T08:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국 저널리즘이 통째로 흔들리고 있다는 진단은 새롭지 않다. 심각한 위기에 놓였다는 경고마저 진부한 소리로 들린다. 디지털과 모바일로 옮겨간 미디어 환경 변화와 기민하지 못한 언론사 수익구조는 ‘저널리즘 품질 저하’로 이어지고 있다는 탄식이 시도 때도 없이 나온다. 지난 한 주 “1.5룸 청소하고 100만원 받았다”는 온라인 커뮤니티 출처 ‘복붙(복사하여 붙여쓰기)’기사는 뉴스 생산에서 비가시적이지만 영향력을 행사하는 디지털 대응 전략이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3년째 같은 기사: 클릭 저널리즘의 현주소]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82382</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/9mGsaepeRBA/82382"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T08:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국 저널리즘이 통째로 흔들리고 있다는 진단은 새롭지 않다. 심각한 위기에 놓였다는 경고마저 진부한 소리로 들린다. 디지털과 모바일로 옮겨간 미디어 환경 변화와 기민하지 못한 언론사 수익구조는 ‘저널리즘 품질 저하’로 이어지고 있다는 탄식이 시도 때도 없이 나온다. 지난 한 주 “1.5룸 청소하고 100만원 받았다”는 온라인 커뮤니티 출처 ‘복붙(복사하여 붙여쓰기)’기사는 뉴스 생산에서 비가시적이지만 영향력을 행사하는 디지털 대응 전략이 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김용판의 ‘허위’ 돈다발 사진, 조선일보의 ‘박철민’ 받아쓰기 (ft. 무책임 선동 끝판왕)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82370</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82370"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T07:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10월 18일 국회 행정안전위원회 경기도 국정감사에서 김용판 국민의힘 의원이 ‘이재명 지사가 받은 돈뭉치’라며 제보받은 사진을 공개했습니다. 5만 원 권과 1만 원 권 돈다발이 렌터카, 라운지 바 명함 등과 함께 놓인 사진입니다. 김 의원은 성남지역 폭력조직 국제마피아파 측근들로부터 이재명 더불어민주당 대선 후보가 20억 원가량을 받았다고 주장하며 그 근거로 국제마피아파 출신 박철민 씨에게서 받았다는 진술서와 사실확인서, 돈다발 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김용판의 ‘허위’ 돈다발 사진, 조선일보의 ‘박철민’ 받아쓰기 (ft. 무책임 선동 끝판왕)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82370</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/nf8IyOiaYD8/82370"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T07:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10월 18일 국회 행정안전위원회 경기도 국정감사에서 김용판 국민의힘 의원이 ‘이재명 지사가 받은 돈뭉치’라며 제보받은 사진을 공개했습니다. 5만 원 권과 1만 원 권 돈다발이 렌터카, 라운지 바 명함 등과 함께 놓인 사진입니다. 김 의원은 성남지역 폭력조직 국제마피아파 측근들로부터 이재명 더불어민주당 대선 후보가 20억 원가량을 받았다고 주장하며 그 근거로 국제마피아파 출신 박철민 씨에게서 받았다는 진술서와 사실확인서, 돈다발 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive guide to go generate]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/a-comprehensive-guide-to-go-generate/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2021/a-comprehensive-guide-to-go-generate/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T03:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Developers have strong tendencies to automate repetitive tasks, and this applies
to writing code as well. Therefore, the topic of <em>metaprogramming</em> is a hot
area of development and research, and hails back to Lisp in the 1960s. One
specific aspect of metaprogramming that has been particularly useful is
<em>code-generation</em>, or …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automatically format and lint code with pre-commit]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/pre-commit</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/pre-commit"/>
        <updated>2021-10-27T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article provides some background and guidelines for using pre-commit to
automatically format and lint C-language firmware codebases. We’ll cover general
guidelines and go over an example set of checks that can be helpful when working
on firmware code.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic Math: C# super feature available in .NET 6 Preview 7]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0878/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0878/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 10th, 2021, Microsoft announced the .NET 6 Preview 7 release. We published and translated this article with the copyright holder's permission. The author is DistortNeo. The article was originally published on Habr. [The link to the .NET 6 Preview 7 announcement.]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generic Math: C# super feature available in .NET 6 Preview 7]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0878/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/tZ4oqKXP0uY/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On August 10th, 2021, Microsoft announced the .NET 6 Preview 7 release. We published and translated this article with the copyright holder's permission. The author is DistortNeo. The article was originally published on Habr. [The link to the .NET 6 Preview 7 announcement.]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[16 Minutes: Steam Halts Web3 Games; FDA Approves Prostate Cancer AI]]></title>
        <id>https://future.a16z.com/?post_type=podcast&amp;p=2264</id>
        <link href="https://future.a16z.com/podcasts/16-minutes-steam-halts-web3-games-fda-approves-prostate-cancer-ai/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T19:12:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to 16 Minutes, our show where we talk about tech trends in the news! We have two segments today: 1) The announcement recently that Valve Software, which operates the massive gaming platform Steam, added a rule barring games that use blockchain technologies or that allow users to exchange cryptocurrencies or NFTs – this rule... Read More
The post 16 Minutes: Steam Halts Web3 Games; FDA Approves Prostate Cancer AI appeared first on Future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Lai, Eddy Lazzarin, Vineeta Agarwala, Jay Rughani, Eliezer Van Allen and Zoran Basich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Bhavesh Bhatt]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/iamagde-bhavesh-bhatt.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/iamagde-bhavesh-bhatt.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T17:00:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
Bhavesh Bhatt is a data scientist and a YouTuber based in Mumbai, India. He began his career as an engineer and transitioned to machine learning and data science. Now, he trains other data scientists to be successful in their careers. Bhavesh is known for his popular YouTube videos and an open source app he created to help Indian citizens locate vaccination appointments near them in the spring of 2021. He has been a GDE since 2019. 
Meet Bhavesh Bhatt, Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning and Data Science.
    
The Early Days
Bhavesh Bhatt has always been technical and has always enjoyed experimenting…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#IamaGDE: Bhavesh Bhatt]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/pPSsd5yxtl4/iamagde-bhavesh-bhatt.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/pPSsd5yxtl4/iamagde-bhavesh-bhatt.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T17:00:00.007Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to #IamaGDE - a series of spotlights presenting Google Developer Experts (GDEs) from across the globe. Discover their stories, passions, and highlights of their community work.
Bhavesh Bhatt is a data scientist and a YouTuber based in Mumbai, India. He began his career as an engineer and transitioned to machine learning and data science. Now, he trains other data scientists to be successful in their careers. Bhavesh is known for his popular YouTube videos and an open source app he created to help Indian citizens locate vaccination appointments near them in the spring of 2021. He has been a GDE since 2019. 
Meet Bhavesh Bhatt, Google Developer Expert in Machine Learning and Data Science.
    
The Early Days
Bhavesh Bhatt has always been technical and has always enjoyed experimenting…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google and Amazon speak very differently about Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9177</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/google-and-amazon-speak-very-differently-about-matter/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T14:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to the Matter smart home interoperability standard, there’s so much we don’t know. But thanks to news this week from Amazon and Google, it’s clear that two of the biggest players in the smart home are approaching the protocol with varying degrees of enthusiasm. On Thursday at its Smart Home Summit event, Google […]
The post Google and Amazon speak very differently about Matter appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foreword to "The Art of Agile Development"]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/art-agile-foreword.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/art-agile-foreword.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Shore has revised his book "The Art of Agile Development". I'm
      pleased to write a foreword for this book as it is solid guide to learning
      how to get past faux-agile and develop the skills you need to get the
      benefits of the agile way of work. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[늦게 도착한 정의: 고(故) 변희수 하사 전역처분 취소 판결]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82350</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82350"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T07:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“피고(육군참모총장)가 망 변희수에 대하여 한 2020. 1. 23.자 전역 처분을 취소한다.”   10월 7일 법정에서 재판장이 위 주문 낭독을 들으며 정말로 여러 가지 생각이 들었다. 당연히 이루어져야 할 판단이 이루어졌다는 안도감, 그럼에도 그 판결이 나오기까지 너무나 오랜 시간이 걸리고, 그 과정에서 당사자가 함께 하지 못했다는 슬픔, 이후에 남겨진 과제에 대한 고민 등이 복합적으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[늦게 도착한 정의: 고(故) 변희수 하사 전역처분 취소 판결]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82350</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/rnfqfeuMbio/82350"/>
        <updated>2021-10-26T07:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“피고(육군참모총장)가 망 변희수에 대하여 한 2020. 1. 23.자 전역 처분을 취소한다.”   10월 7일 법정에서 재판장이 위 주문 낭독을 들으며 정말로 여러 가지 생각이 들었다. 당연히 이루어져야 할 판단이 이루어졌다는 안도감, 그럼에도 그 판결이 나오기까지 너무나 오랜 시간이 걸리고, 그 과정에서 당사자가 함께 하지 못했다는 슬픔, 이후에 남겨진 과제에 대한 고민 등이 복합적으로 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Developer Student Lead Increased Representation in Campus Clubs Through Community]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/chloe--toronto-diversity-inclusion.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/chloe--toronto-diversity-inclusion.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T17:00:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kyle Paul, Google Developer Student Club Regional Lead CA & US
          
When Chloe Quijano arrived at the University of Toronto to study Applied Sciences, she immediately noticed that few of the professors or teaching assistants in the program looked like her. She noticed a lack of relatable role models online and on social media as well. 
Chloe felt strongly about the importance of representation.  Whether based on race, gender, ethnicity, sexual orientation or disability status, she understood the importance of being able to find relatable role models in her field--and the implications of a lack of diversity.  "It holds back the students wishing to go into the field," she says.   
   
Bureau of Labor Statistics findings on women in computing occupations
  
Worse, she points o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Developer Student Lead Increased Representation in Campus Clubs Through Community]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/c-9G_vB9cnQ/chloe--toronto-diversity-inclusion.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/c-9G_vB9cnQ/chloe--toronto-diversity-inclusion.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T17:00:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kyle Paul, Google Developer Student Club Regional Lead CA & US
          
When Chloe Quijano arrived at the University of Toronto to study Applied Sciences, she immediately noticed that few of the professors or teaching assistants in the program looked like her. She noticed a lack of relatable role models online and on social media as well. 
Chloe felt strongly about the importance of representation.  Whether based on race, gender, ethnicity, sexual orientation or disability status, she understood the importance of being able to find relatable role models in her field--and the implications of a lack of diversity.  "It holds back the students wishing to go into the field," she says.   
   
Bureau of Labor Statistics findings on women in computing occupations
  
Worse, she points o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When Updating an Untested Module, Take the Opportunity to Add Tests]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=16550</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2021/10/25/when-updating-an-untested-module-take-the-opportunity-to-add-tests/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[25 October 2021 by Phillip JohnstonI want to come clean: I’ve spent most of my career to date manually testing the code I’ve written. This might surprise people who have known me or read my work for years, because I have spent the majority of my career extolling the benefits of CI pipelines and automated … 
Continue reading "When Updating an Untested Module, Take the Opportunity to Add Tests"
The post When Updating an Untested Module, Take the Opportunity to Add Tests appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 명예훼손 소송의 입증책임: ‘공인’이면 YES, ‘사인’이면 NO]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82344</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82344"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T08:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[바쁜 독자를 위한 요약:  미국 연방대법원은 명예훼손 소송의 원고가 누구인가(국가, 공무원 등 ‘공인’인가, 아니면 그냥 개인, 즉 ‘사인’인가)에 따라 명예훼손의 입증책임을 달리 부과합니다. 즉, 국가기관이나 공인이 명예훼손 소송을 제기한 경우에 그 원고가 “현실적 악의”를 입증할 책임을 집니다. (대표 사례: 뉴욕타임스 vs. 설리번 사건, 1964) 하지만 반대로 개인, ‘사인’이 명예훼손 소송을 제기한 경우에는 명예훼손의 “현실적 악의”를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국 명예훼손 소송의 입증책임: ‘공인’이면 YES, ‘사인’이면 NO]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82344</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/vCp3UBjZbAQ/82344"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T08:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[바쁜 독자를 위한 요약:  미국 연방대법원은 명예훼손 소송의 원고가 누구인가(국가, 공무원 등 ‘공인’인가, 아니면 그냥 개인, 즉 ‘사인’인가)에 따라 명예훼손의 입증책임을 달리 부과합니다. 즉, 국가기관이나 공인이 명예훼손 소송을 제기한 경우에 그 원고가 “현실적 악의”를 입증할 책임을 집니다. (대표 사례: 뉴욕타임스 vs. 설리번 사건, 1964) 하지만 반대로 개인, ‘사인’이 명예훼손 소송을 제기한 경우에는 명예훼손의 “현실적 악의”를 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>언론인권센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ Smart Pointers and Arrays]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2021/smartptr-array/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2021/smartptr-array/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-25T05:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart pointers are very versatile and can hold pointers not only to single instances but also to arrays. Is that only a theoretical use case? or maybe they might be handy in some cases? Let’s have a look.
Smart pointers for T[]
At C++ Stories, you can find lots of information about smart pointers - see this separate tag for this area. For completeness, I’d like to mention an interesting issue on smart pointers and arrays.
If you want to create a unique_ptr, you can write:
class Object { };

// unique_ptr
auto ptr = std::make_unique<Object>();
auto intPtr = std::make_unique<int>();

// or shared_ptr
auto shared = std::make_shared<Object>();
auto intShared = std::make_shared<int>();


In the example, you see pointers to a single instance of Object or an integer.
Similarly, if you want to hav…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we sympathize with a question on StackOverflow but keep silent]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0877/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0877/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the stackoverflow.com website, we frequently see questions about how to look for bugs of a certain type. We know that PVS-Studio can solve the problem. Unfortunately, we have to keep silent. Otherwise, StackOverflow moderators may consider it as an obvious attempt to promote our product. This article describes a particular case of such a situation that makes us suffer deeply. The following question: "Scan-Build for clang-13 not showing errors" asked by kratos from India, made me write this article. This person asks how to look for patterns of the following type: Here's the code cited as an example:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How we sympathize with a question on StackOverflow but keep silent]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/0877/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/2tQM9cNHJgo/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-24T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the stackoverflow.com website, we frequently see questions about how to look for bugs of a certain type. We know that PVS-Studio can solve the problem. Unfortunately, we have to keep silent. Otherwise, StackOverflow moderators may consider it as an obvious attempt to promote our product. This article describes a particular case of such a situation that makes us suffer deeply. The following question: "Scan-Build for clang-13 not showing errors" asked by kratos from India, made me write this article. This person asks how to look for patterns of the following type: Here's the code cited as an example:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Visual Studio Code for C/C++ with ARM Cortex-M: Part 10 – Assembly Stepping]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=33727</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2021/10/23/visual-studio-code-for-c-c-with-arm-cortex-m-part-10-assembly-stepping/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-23T09:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Visual Studio Code is a great IDE, but does not (yet?) implement features for true embedded usage. Or things are there to some level, but hard to use. One of these things is how to step in the … Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded news week: robotics, rainforests and IoT security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471366</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-news-week-robotics-rainforests-and-iot-security/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T18:29:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A roundup of this week’s embedded news includes robotics, IoT security and onboarding, automotive wireless charging and building automation.
The post embedded news week: robotics, rainforests and IoT security appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for October 22, 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9186</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-october-22-2021/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T17:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ioXt Alliance certifies 60 new devices: The ioXt Alliance, which is a nascent security standard for connected devices including handsets and smart TVs, has certified 60 Android devices. The devices range from Pixel smartphones from Google to rugged handsets from Zebra Technologies. The ioXt Alliance standard tries to do away with both the “nutrition-style […]
The post IoT news of the week for October 22, 2021 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[애플 개인정보보호 정책 변화의 직격탄을 맞은 3분기 스냅 실적과 향후 스냅 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584126</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584126/21%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%8a%a4%eb%83%85-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T16:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Synchronized GPU priority scheduling]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/873334/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/873334/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T14:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the early days, Unix-like systems have implemented the concept of
process priorities, where higher-priority processes are given more
CPU time to get their work done.  Implementations have changed, and
alternatives (such as deadline scheduling)
are available for specialized situations, but the core priority (or, in an
inverted sense, "niceness") concept 
remains essentially the same.  What should happen, though, in a world where
increasing amounts of computing work is done outside of the CPU?  Tvrtko
Ursulin has put together a
patch set showing how the nice mechanism can be extended to GPUs as
well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating atomic synchronization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471363</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/accelerating-atomic-synchronization/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T14:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synchronizing multiple cores on a single chip or in a system requires atomic operations and hardware that enforces these operations. Synchronization The motivation for atomic...
The post Accelerating atomic synchronization appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Bauch</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Staying data compliant in the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471356</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/staying-data-compliant-in-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T13:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Customers want assurance that their data is protected and being used in their best interests. 
The post Staying data compliant in the IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ludovic Rembert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/873746/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/873746/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T13:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (apache, chromium, nodejs, nodejs-lts-erbium, nodejs-lts-fermium, and virtualbox), Fedora (vsftpd and watchdog), Oracle (java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, and redis:6), and Ubuntu (libcaca, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.4, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, linux-azure-5.8, and mailman).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 램리서치 실적, 빼어난 이익과 부진한 매출은 향후 전망을 불안케 한다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584120</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584120/21%eb%85%84-3%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%9e%a8%eb%a6%ac%ec%84%9c%ec%b9%98-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T11:48:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[법무부와 과기부의 ‘얼굴 도둑질’, 그 규모는 1억 7천만 건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82337</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/82337"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T07:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[법무부와 과학기술정보통신부가 출입국 심사와 공항 보안을 이유로 얼굴 인식 및 행동 인식 기술을 활용한 실시간 원격 감시시스템을 개발하고, 이 과정에서 1억 7천만 건이 넘는 내·외국인의 얼굴 사진과 출입국 심사 정보를 정보 주체의 아무런 동의 없이 국가와 민간기업의 인공지능 학습용 데이터로 이용한 것으로 드러났습니다. 우리는 위법할 뿐만 아니라 국제 인권규범에도 현저히 위배되는 생체인식 감시시스템의 구축을 즉각 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[법무부와 과기부의 ‘얼굴 도둑질’, 그 규모는 1억 7천만 건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=82337</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/slownews/~3/emHwlhQTFbI/82337"/>
        <updated>2021-10-22T07:18:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[법무부와 과학기술정보통신부가 출입국 심사와 공항 보안을 이유로 얼굴 인식 및 행동 인식 기술을 활용한 실시간 원격 감시시스템을 개발하고, 이 과정에서 1억 7천만 건이 넘는 내·외국인의 얼굴 사진과 출입국 심사 정보를 정보 주체의 아무런 동의 없이 국가와 민간기업의 인공지능 학습용 데이터로 이용한 것으로 드러났습니다. 우리는 위법할 뿐만 아니라 국제 인권규범에도 현저히 위배되는 생체인식 감시시스템의 구축을 즉각 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>진보넷</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Can Now Directly Read Data Logs From Tesla Vehicles (Jalopnik)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/873675/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/873675/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T23:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Jalopnik automotive site has posted an
article on a
(relatively) new set
of open-source tools that can extract log data from Tesla cars.


	Since Tesla cars run a Debian-based operating system, navigating
	through their file systems is somewhat trivial to anyone who’s
	spent a weekend messing with virtual Linux machines (or watching
	Mr. Robot). Actually accessing the car’s memory, however, is
	considerably harder: all cases require at least partially
	disassembling the dashboard, and some even require disassembly of
	the car’s media control unit.

	Once that’s done, however, the data trove is incredible.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내가 죽고 싶었을 때, 아버지가 내게 해준 말 한마디]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73573</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/10/21/suicidalthoughts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=suicidalthoughts"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T22:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[원문보기 뉴스페퍼민트 에디터이기도 했던 정신과 전문의 나종호 님이 오랜만에 글을 번역해 자신의 브런치에 올렸습니다. 환자 본인들의 이야기를 실어 질병에 대한 낙인을 해소하는 걸 목표로 하는 사이트 themighty.com의 기사입니다. 역자의 허락을 구해 뉴스페퍼민트에도 글을 싣습니다. 나종호 님이 전에 뉴스페퍼민트에 소개했던 글은 여기서 볼 수 있습니다. 원문에 있는 편집자의 말을 보면, “자살을 생각해본 적이 있는 사람은 이 글을 읽고 자살에 관한 생각이 다시 들 수 있다.”는 경고와 함께 급한 도움을 청하고 싶을 때 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP Top Ten and Software Composition Analysis (SCA)]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0876/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0876/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OWASP Top Ten 2017 category A9 (which became A6 in OWASP Top Ten 2021) is dedicated to using components with known vulnerabilities. To cover this category in PVS-Studio, developers have to turn the analyzer into a full SCA solution. How will the analyzer look for vulnerabilities in the components used? What is SCA? Let's try to find the answers in this article! One of the priority areas for PVS-Studio development is to cover categories from the OWASP Top Ten 2017 in the C# analyzer. We also plan to cover the Top Ten 2021 in the future. The most unusual for us is the A9:2017 category - Using Components with Known Vulnerabilities. This category has the A6 position in the preliminary version of OWASP 2021. The rule implementation for this category is an important task for our analyzer. It allows us to classify PVS-Studio as an SCA (Software Composition Analysis) tool. Which approach to implementation should we choose? Let's figure it out! The A9 threat category (It turned into A6 in the preliminary OWASP 2021 version) is dedicated to using components with known vulnerabilities. These are the components that have the corresponding entries in the CVE database. CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures) is a database of records about real-life vulnerabilities in software, hardware, service components, etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OWASP Top Ten and Software Composition Analysis (SCA)]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/0876/</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/viva64-blog-en/~3/TMrecqc_OYg/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OWASP Top Ten 2017 category A9 (which became A6 in OWASP Top Ten 2021) is dedicated to using components with known vulnerabilities. To cover this category in PVS-Studio, developers have to turn the analyzer into a full SCA solution. How will the analyzer look for vulnerabilities in the components used? What is SCA? Let's try to find the answers in this article! One of the priority areas for PVS-Studio development is to cover categories from the OWASP Top Ten 2017 in the C# analyzer. We also plan to cover the Top Ten 2021 in the future. The most unusual for us is the A9:2017 category - Using Components with Known Vulnerabilities. This category has the A6 position in the preliminary version of OWASP 2021. The rule implementation for this category is an important task for our analyzer. It allows us to classify PVS-Studio as an SCA (Software Composition Analysis) tool. Which approach to implementation should we choose? Let's figure it out! The A9 threat category (It turned into A6 in the preliminary OWASP 2021 version) is dedicated to using components with known vulnerabilities. These are the components that have the corresponding entries in the CVE database. CVE (Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures) is a database of records about real-life vulnerabilities in software, hardware, service components, etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from www.viva64.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend Google Apps Script with your API library to empower users]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/extend-google-apps-script-with-your-api.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/extend-google-apps-script-with-your-api.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T20:59:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Keith Einstein, Product Manager
   
Google is proud to announce the availability of the DocuSign API library for Google Apps Script. This newly created library gives all Apps Script users access to the more than 400 endpoints DocuSign has to offer so they can build digital signatures into their custom solutions and workflows within Google Workspace. 
The Google Workspace Ecosystem
  
Last week at Google Cloud Next ‘21, in the session “How Miro, DocuSign, Adobe and Atlassian are helping organizations centralize their work”, we showcased a few partner integrations called add-ons, found on Google Workspace Marketplace. The Google Workspace Marketplace helps developers connect with the more than 3 billion people who use Google Workspace—with a stunning 4.8 billion apps installed to d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extend Google Apps Script with your API library to empower users]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/cpS96IrO_Bc/extend-google-apps-script-with-your-api.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/cpS96IrO_Bc/extend-google-apps-script-with-your-api.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T20:59:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Keith Einstein, Product Manager
   
Google is proud to announce the availability of the DocuSign API library for Google Apps Script. This newly created library gives all Apps Script users access to the more than 400 endpoints DocuSign has to offer so they can build digital signatures into their custom solutions and workflows within Google Workspace. 
The Google Workspace Ecosystem
  
Last week at Google Cloud Next ‘21, in the session “How Miro, DocuSign, Adobe and Atlassian are helping organizations centralize their work”, we showcased a few partner integrations called add-ons, found on Google Workspace Marketplace. The Google Workspace Marketplace helps developers connect with the more than 3 billion people who use Google Workspace—with a stunning 4.8 billion apps installed to d…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인스타그램과 청소년의 정신건강]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=73565</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2021/10/21/npc_instagrammentalhealth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npc_instagrammentalhealth"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T20:00:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난주 뉴욕타임스 오피니언란은 인스타그램이 10대 소녀들에게 끼치는 영향에 대한 논의로 뜨거웠습니다. 먼저 10월 8일, 뉴욕타임스의 에디터이자 영화감독인 린지 크라우스는 “10대 소녀에게 인스타그램은 악의 소굴(cesspool)”이라는 제목의 글을 올렸습니다. 논의를 촉발한 건 우리 모두 알고 있는 페이스북 내부고발자 프랜시스 하우건의 폭로였습니다. 하우건은 페이스북이 10대 소녀들의 정신건강에 인스타그램이 미치는 해악을 알면서도 그 연구 결과를 일부러 숨겼다고 주장했습니다. 사실 소셜미디어가 10대 청소년의 정신 건강에 나쁜 영향을 미친다는 주장은 그리 새로운 것이 아닙니다. 소셜미디어는 그 자체로 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Rust 1.56.0 and Rust 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/873655/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/873655/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T19:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust language project has announced the release of stable version 1.56.0 and the Rust 2021 edition. 

We wrote about plans for the Rust 2021 Edition in May. Editions are a mechanism for opt-in changes that may otherwise pose backwards compatibility risk. See the edition guide for details on how this is achieved. This is a smaller edition, especially compared to 2018, but there are still some nice quality-of-life changes that require an edition opt-in to avoid breaking some corner cases in existing code.


See the detailed 
release notes for 1.56.0 for lots more information on the release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Smart Home Developer Summit – New tools and features to build, innovate, and grow with Google]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/google-smart-home-developer-summit-new-tools-and-features-to-grow-with-Google.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2021/10/google-smart-home-developer-summit-new-tools-and-features-to-grow-with-Google.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T17:04:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Michele Turner, Senior Director of Product for Google’s Smart Home Ecosystem 
  
Earlier this year at Google I/O, we told you that our goal is to make Google the best place for smart home developers like you to build, innovate, and grow. Today, I'm excited to show you all the new ways we're improving the tools and opportunities you'll have to build you best experiences with Google, by:  
 
Expanding our platform and tools to make it easier for you to learn and build devices that do more with Google.  
Providing a site where you can preview the new tools that are coming over the next year to help you build your devices, apps, and integrations.  
Supporting Matter & Thread across our entire ecosystem, including Nest and Android.  
Developing more automation capabilities, including …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Smart Home Developer Summit – New tools and features to build, innovate, and grow with Google]]></title>
        <id>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/blM5_heJVBc/google-smart-home-developer-summit-new-tools-and-features-to-grow-with-Google.html</id>
        <link href="http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/GDBcode/~3/blM5_heJVBc/google-smart-home-developer-summit-new-tools-and-features-to-grow-with-Google.html"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T17:04:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Michele Turner, Senior Director of Product for Google’s Smart Home Ecosystem 
  
Earlier this year at Google I/O, we told you that our goal is to make Google the best place for smart home developers like you to build, innovate, and grow. Today, I'm excited to show you all the new ways we're improving the tools and opportunities you'll have to build you best experiences with Google, by:  
 
Expanding our platform and tools to make it easier for you to learn and build devices that do more with Google.  
Providing a site where you can preview the new tools that are coming over the next year to help you build your devices, apps, and integrations.  
Supporting Matter & Thread across our entire ecosystem, including Nest and Android.  
Developing more automation capabilities, including …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 테슬라 실적을 보는 월가의 시선, 테슬라 투자의견과 테슬라 목표주가는 어떻게 변하고 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584106</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584106/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ea%b3%bc-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T16:30:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Development using Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.beningo.com/?p=13678</id>
        <link href="https://www.beningo.com/embedded-development-using-visual-studio-code/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T15:31:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several years ago, I never would have believed that embedded developers would use a tool like Visual Studio Code. Using a Microsoft product to develop embedded software seems ridiculous. Yet, I find myself using Visual Studio Code for development more than I use any other integrated development environment! In this post, I’ll share a little … Continue reading Embedded Development using Visual Studio Code
Embedded Development using Visual Studio Code first appeared on Beningo Embedded Group.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes from the 2021 Git Contributors' Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/873629/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/873629/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T15:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For those who are curious about where the development of Git is headed:
Johannes Schindelin has posted an
extensive set of notes from the just-concluded Git Contributors'
Summit.


We held our second all-virtual Summit over the past two days. It was the
traditional unconference style meeting, with topics being proposed and
voted on right before the introduction round. It was really good to see
the human faces behind those email addresses.

32 contributors participated, and we spanned the timezones from PST to
IST.


Be sure to go into the thread for the full notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Controlling the CPU scheduler with BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/873244/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/873244/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T14:15:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the BPF virtual machine has been supported by Linux for most of
the kernel's existence, its role for much of that time was limited to, as
its full
name (Berkeley packet filter) would suggest, filtering packets.  That began to change in 2012 with the introduction
of seccomp() filtering, and the pace picked up in 2014 with the arrival
of the extended BPF virtual machine.  At this point, BPF hooks have found their
way into many kernel subsystems.  One area that has remained BPF-free,
though, is the CPU scheduler; that could change if some version of
this patch
set from Roman Gushchin finds its way into the mainline.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/873601/rss</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/873601/rss"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T14:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (python-babel, squashfs-tools, and uwsgi), Fedora (gfbgraph and rust-coreos-installer), Mageia (aom, libslirp, redis, and vim), openSUSE (fetchmail, go1.16, go1.17, mbedtls, ncurses, python, squid, and ssh-audit), Red Hat (java-1.8.0-openjdk and java-11-openjdk), Scientific Linux (java-1.8.0-openjdk and java-11-openjdk), SUSE (fetchmail, git, go1.16, go1.17, ncurses, postgresql10, python, python36, and squid), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-dell300x, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon, linux, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-oem-5.10, and linux-oem-5.13).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Return of the connected bunny!]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=9173</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-return-of-the-connected-bunny/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T13:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We kick off this week’s podcast with a focus on chips and hardware starting with an explainer on Arm’s new Total Solutions for IoT and why it will help developers and device makers speed up time-to-market for connected products. We then talk about plans to put Linux on Arduino devices that were outed in a […]
The post Podcast: Return of the connected bunny! appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure OCF-over-Thread is key to scalable IP based smart building IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4471349</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/secure-ocf-over-thread-is-key-to-scalable-ip-based-smart-building-iot/"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T11:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Cascoda announced the first certified OCF-over-Thread module for secure IP-based mesh networks, we look at the why the technology is significant in addressing interoperability and security in smart building IoT.
The post Secure OCF-over-Thread is key to scalable IP based smart building IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 백만대 생산체제 구축 성공, 자동차 업계 정복이란 놀라운 이정표가 꿈만은 아니다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=584060</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/584060/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%eb%b0%b1%eb%a7%8c%eb%8c%80-%ec%83%9d%ec%82%b0%ec%b2%b4%ec%a0%9c-%ea%b5%ac%ec%b6%95"/>
        <updated>2021-10-21T10:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>