<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://mononn.github.io/newsfeed/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2023-07-21T20:12:29.711Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://mononn.github.io/newsfeed/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://mononn.github.io/newsfeed/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Exceptions in BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938435/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938435/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T15:06:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BPF virtual machine in the kernel has been steadily gaining new
features for years, many of which add capabilities that C programmers do
not ordinarily have.  So, from one point of view, it was only a matter of
time before BPF gained support for exceptions.  As it turns out, though,
this "exceptions" feature is aimed at a specific use case, and its use in
most programs will be truly exceptional.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938878/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938878/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T14:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (golang, nodejs16, nodejs18, and R-jsonlite), Red Hat (java-1.8.0-openjdk and java-17-openjdk), SUSE (container-suseconnect, redis, and redis7), and Ubuntu (wkhtmltopdf).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should you abstract your RTOS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479936</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/should-you-abstract-your-rtos/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T14:27:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you start your next project, you should carefully consider whether you really want your application to be tightly coupled to your RTOS. According to...
The post Should you abstract your RTOS? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 테슬라 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591235</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591235/2q-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T06:35:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[구명조끼조차 주지 않는 사회라면… 생존수영 교사의 제언]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=94034</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/94034"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T04:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[서이초 교사 사망 사건에 부쳐] 실천교사교사모임 천경호 회장… 공문 없는 날? 행정청의 대외적 구호에 일선 교사들은 분노합니다. 저는 생존수영 업무를 맡은 초등 담임교사입니다 저는 실천교육교사모임(이하 ‘실천교사’) 회장 교사 천경호입니다. 저는 생존수영 업무를 맡고 있는 초등학교 4학년 담임교사입니다. 아침 8시 30분 전부터 등교하는 아이들을 맞이하기 위해 7시 50분에 교실에 들어서서 교실 바닥 청소를 하고, 아이들을 데려다...
The post 구명조끼조차 주지 않는 사회라면… 생존수영 교사의 제언 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>천경호</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[교사가 신음하며 죽어가는 교실에서…]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=94027</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/94027"/>
        <updated>2023-07-21T02:14:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[서이초 교사 사망 사건에 부쳐] 돌아가신 선생님의 명복을 빕니다. 하루 종일 다른 일로 바빠서 뉴스를 보지 못했다. 이제야 소식을 접했다. 나란 인간은 평소 매우 비겁하고 비겁하다 못해 소심한 인간이라 SNS가 들끓든, 세상이 뒤집히든, 정치로 나라가 온통 시끄럽든 눈을 감고 귀를 막고 살고 있다. 그저 한 평생을 숨죽이고 눈에 띄지 않게 조용히 살다가, 때가 되면 얼른...
The post 교사가 신음하며 죽어가는 교실에서… appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>지니샘</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지지율 급락, 문재인 때리기로 위기 돌파 노린다: 슬로우레터 7월21일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=94013</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/94013"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T21:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“교사는 을이 아니다.” 김남국 제명하라. “생각 없는 국민들이 말이 되네 생각할 것.” 문재인 때리기, 외교 문서까지 들췄다. 지지율은 트리플 급락. 해법과 대안. 리필숍에 자격증 있는 관리사 필요한가. 교도소를 바꾸자. 오늘의 TMI. 은퇴 부자들, 울산과 과천에 산다. 아쿠타카와 상을 받은 중증 장애인의 조크. 해외 직구 1억 건 넘는다. 밑줄 쳐 가며 읽은 칼럼. 의심하는 게 합리적이다....
The post 지지율 급락, 문재인 때리기로 위기 돌파 노린다: 슬로우레터 7월21일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ryujinx: re-checking the Nintendo Switch emulator using PVS-Studio]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1059/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1059/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch's popularity hasn't waned, and with exclusive games winning awards, the desire to play them is only growing. However, not everyone has the opportunity to try out this portable gaming console. Ryujinx — a Nintendo Switch emulator — solves this problem. Today we are going to check its code using the PVS-Studio analyzer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Google Wallet]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/whats-new-in-google-wallet.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/whats-new-in-google-wallet.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T17:00:00.054Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jose Ugia – Developer Relations Engineer






During Google I/O 2023, and in our recent blog post, we shared some new pass types and features we’re adding to Google Wallet and discussed how you can use them to build and protect your passes more easily, and enhance the experience for your customers.
Read on for a summary of what we covered during the event, or check out the recording of our session on YouTube: What's new in Google Pay and Google Wallet.



Secure pass information with private passes
We’re glad to expand Generic Passes, adding support for sensitive data with the new generic private pass API. Generic private passes on Google Wallet are one more way we’re protecting users’ information, keeping their sensitive digital items safe. These types of passes require you to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Much ado about SBAT]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938422/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938422/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, the shortest patches lead to the longest threads; for a case in
point, see this
three-line change posted by Emanuele Giuseppe Esposito.  The purpose of
this change is to improve the security of locked-down systems by adding a
"revocation number" to the kernel image.  But, as the discussion revealed,
both the cost and the value of this feature are seen differently across the
kernel-development community.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938711/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938711/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T14:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (sysstat), Gentoo (openssh), Mageia (firefox/nss, kernel, kernel-linus, maven, mingw-nsis, mutt/neomutt, php, qt4/qtsvg5, and texlive), Red Hat (java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, and kpatch-patch), Slackware (curl and openssh), SUSE (curl, grafana, kernel, mariadb, MozillaFirefox, MozillaFirefox-branding-SLE, poppler, python-Flask, python310, samba, SUSE Manager Client Tools, and texlive), and Ubuntu (curl, ecdsautils, and samba).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: How to make IoT more consumer-friendly]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12682</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-how-to-make-iot-more-consumer-friendly/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T13:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we dig in on two topics that will make the internet of things friendlier for consumers. The first is the newly announced cybersecurity label plan from the White House that will create a way for consumers to see if their planned IoT purchase meets adequate cybersecurity standards. The second is our suggestion that […]
The post Podcast: How to make IoT more consumer-friendly appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zigbee bulbs: Replace them with Matter or stay with Zigbee?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12391</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/zigbee-bulbs-replace-them-with-matter-or-stay-with-zigbee/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T11:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast episode we took a voicemail from Michael on our podcast hotline. Michael has invested in Zigbee lights up to this point and he’s heard about some challenges that still face Matter devices some challenges that still face Matter devices. So the question really is, what Zigbee bulbs would […]
The post Zigbee bulbs: Replace them with Matter or stay with Zigbee? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The essential guide to embedded systems security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/?p=13736</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/quality/the-essential-guide-to-embedded-systems-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T09:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded systems security is essential to keeping embedded systems safe from any malicious behaviour. In a world where such systems are […]
The post The essential guide to embedded systems security appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bluefruit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[잊겠지만, 잊을 수 없는 이야기: 서이초 교사 사망 사건에 부쳐]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93892</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93892"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T08:25:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[꽤 오래 전의 일이다. 우리는 교권침해 피해자였습니다 교사인 아내가 학교에서 학생들 활동을 지도하고 있었는데, 일진으로 유명한 한 아이가 그 공간 한 켠에 놓인 소파에 드러누워 일어나지 않고 있었다. (그 아이가 전날 음주를 하고 그런 상태가 되었다는 것은 나중에 알게 된 사실이다.) 당연하겠지만, 활동 중에 아이가 드러누워 있으면 교사는 상태를 체크하고 조치를 취해야 한다. 그런데 이...
The post 잊겠지만, 잊을 수 없는 이야기: 서이초 교사 사망 사건에 부쳐 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hingomaster</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Delve features in RHEL 9.2]]></title>
        <id>7a77dfe6-885d-41e4-8f9f-843ec9e54e03</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/20/new-delve-features-rhel-92"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Delve, the Go debugger, ships with the go-toolset package in Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL). The go-toolset package in RHEL 9.2 contains Delve version 1.9.1, which contains many improvements and features.
Delve 1.9.1 is also the last release to contain the old versioning scheme; new releases of Delve will mirror the corresponding Go release . versioning, only diverging for point releases. So, for example, the latest release of Delve is 1.20.x which corresponds to the 1.20.x release of Go. Delve releases a new minor version when the Go project releases a new version's first RC (Release Candidate). Once that version of Go is released in RHEL, the corresponding version of Delve is also released.
New features
Each new release of Delve boasts many new features, fixes, and improvements. Let's t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Parker</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy applications using Ansible Automation Platform]]></title>
        <id>d3919bed-ea2c-4657-863d-ee1c80f89fc3</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/20/how-deploy-applications-using-ansible-automation-platform"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will demonstrate how to streamline the application deployment process on a Red Hat Enterprise Linux machine using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform.
Prerequisites
Two local VM’s configured with SSH connectivity.
Bridged networking enabled for the VMs.
Ansible Automation Platform installed on the host VM.
Our VMs are named vm1-host and vm2 respectively. Edit the /etc/hosts file on vm1-host to include the other VM as a device on the network. You can find its IP by using the command ip -a and then checking the inet address. In my case, it was the following address:
192.168.17.4 vm2
You can try the following command to ping the other VM to check if the connection works.
ping vm2 
After that, enable SSH and copy them to all the VMs using the following commands:
ssh-keygen
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tathagata Paul, Himanshu Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to balance per-CPU upcall dispatch mode in Open vSwitch]]></title>
        <id>8cdce30c-414d-4d73-b63f-953d4924da75</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/20/how-balance-cpu-upcall-dispatch-mode-open-vswitch"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Open vSwitch has moved away from using per-vport dispatch mode to using per-CPU dispatch mode. But this mode had issues with upcall handler thread imbalance and CPU mismatch error messages. These issues were mostly found in systems with tuned CPUs.
This article explains two main fixes that my patch series applied to Open vSwitch that alleviated these issues. The first fix resulted in the ovs-vswitchd sending an array of a size that the Open vSwitch kernel module will accept and not trigger the CPU mismatch error message. The second fix added additional upcall handler threads in cases of tuned CPUs to create a more balanced workload for the upcall handler threads.
History of dispatch modes in Open vSwitch
In July 2021, my former colleague, Mark Grey, introduced per-CPU dispatch mode to Open…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Santana</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 순수이성 비판 강의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223161478686</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223161478686"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T05:23:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[+ 이제 형이상학을 사고방식의 혁명에 따라 거꾸로 수행해야 한다. 흥미로운 것은 사변 형이상학에 대해서 비판함에도 불구하고, 여전히 어떤 형이상학의 가능성에 대해서 칸트가 추구하고 있다는 것이다. 칸트가 다음처럼 말한다. <이제 형이상학에서 우리는 대상들의 직관과 관련해서 비슷한 방식을 시도해 볼 수 있다. 직관이 대상의 성질에 따라야 하는 것이라면, 나는 어떻게 그것에 관해서 선험적으로 알 수 있는가를 통찰하지 못한다. 그러나 대상이, 감관의 대상으로서 우리 직관 능력에 따른다면, 나는 이 가능성을 아주 잘 생각할 수 있다. 그러나 이 직관들이 인식이어야 한다면, 나는 이 직관에 머무를 수 없고, 표상인 그것을 대.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KBS를 망가뜨리면 우리는 더 행복해질까?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93799</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93799"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T03:42:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[나는 10년 전 KBS를 그만 둔 전직 기자다. 미국에서 운전을 할 때 가급적 음악보다 라디오를 틀어 놓는다. 사람하고 얘기할 일도 자주 없는데 운전할 때라도 영어를 들어 보겠다는 마음인데, (당연히) 뭐라고 떠드는지 도통 알 수가 없다. 대개 꾹 참고 듣지만, 정 견디기 힘들 때면 김광석이나 잔나비 같은 음악을 재생한다. 노래든 말이든 스피커에서 한국어가 나오면 그렇게 속이...
The post KBS를 망가뜨리면 우리는 더 행복해질까? appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김경래</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 20, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938053/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938053/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-20T02:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 20, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 도시가 놀이터 되면 오프라인도 살아날 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77012</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/19/npsp_playgroundcity/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_playgroundcity"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 29일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 하버드의 경제학자 에드워드 글레이저는 2011년 베스트셀러 “도시의 승리”에서 도시를 인간이 만든 최고의 발명품이라 칭했습니다. 그의 도시 예찬은 인간이 모일수록 더 좋은 환경이 만들어진다고 말하는 점에서 인간에 대한 믿음과 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“무능한 야당과 무심한 용산”, 조중동의 불만이 끓어오르고 있다: 슬로우레터 7월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93779</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93779"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T22:01:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[검찰이 또 피의사실을 흘린다. 미국 잠수함에 올라탄 윤석열, 조중동은 감격. 수색 작업하던 해병, 급류에 휩쓸려 죽었다. 내년 최저임금은 9860원. 한국 경제성장률 또 후려쳤다. 원전 폐쇄를 불법으로? 김수현 기소 논란. 해법과 대안. 대중교통 달마다 최대 4만5000원 깎아준다. 오늘의 TMI. 코로나 확진 하루 3만 명. 얻어맞는 교사 5년 동안 1133명. 홍콩 오피스 투자 90% 손실 충격. 밑줄...
The post “무능한 야당과 무심한 용산”, 조중동의 불만이 끓어오르고 있다: 슬로우레터 7월20일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rust for embedded]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938409/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938409/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T19:26:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advantages of the Rust programming language are generally well-known;
memory safety is a feature that has attracted a lot of developer attention
over the last few years.  At the inaugural Embedded
Open Source Summit (EOSS), which is an umbrella event for numerous
embedded-related conferences, Martin Mosler presented on using Rust for an
embedded project.  In the talk, he showed how easy it is to get up and
running with a Rust-based application on a RISC-V-based development board.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two large stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938617/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938617/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T16:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.4.4 and
6.1.39
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains a large number of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Life in the Roku smart home is pretty basic]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12679</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/life-in-the-roku-smart-home-is-pretty-basic/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve spent two weeks playing around with Roku’s smart home gear (which is Wyze hardware running a software overlay provided by Roku) and I can tell you it’s fine. If you’re the type of person who wants to experience the smart home circa 2013 with the addition of a services plan and an integration to […]
The post Life in the Roku smart home is pretty basic appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How platform teams get stuff done]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/platform-teams-stuff-done.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/platform-teams-stuff-done.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T14:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Platform teams have a unique reliance on other teams to ensure adoption
     of their platform - getting code changes into other teams' codebase is
     critical to their success. Pete Hodgson structures how
     platform teams collaborate into phases
     of migration, consumption, and evolution. He describes what's different in
     each of these phases, the operating models to adopt, and which cross-team
     collaboration patterns work best.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938596/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938596/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T13:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bind9, libapache2-mod-auth-openidc, and python-django), Fedora (nodejs18 and redis), Red Hat (python3.9 and webkit2gtk3), Scientific Linux (bind and kernel), SUSE (cni, cni-plugins, cups-filters, curl, dbus-1, ImageMagick, kernel, libheif, and python-requests), and Ubuntu (bind9, connman, curl, libwebp, and yajl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PC 가짜 논쟁의 종착지: 답은 작품에 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93695</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93695"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T07:26:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. 디즈니 실사판 ‘인어공주'(2023)를 둘러싼 PC(정치적 올바름)와 작품의 원전성에 관한 논란은 앞선 글에서 정리한 것처럼 ‘가짜 논쟁’이었습니다. 애니메이션 버전의 ‘인어공주'(1989)도 안데르센의 인어공주라는 원전에 대한 하나의 해석판이었죠. 물론 원전은 그 자체로 불가침의 성물은 아닙니다. 좋은 작품은 시간과 공간을 뛰어넘어 항상 ‘당대의 관객’과 함께 숨쉬고 대화합니다....
The post PC 가짜 논쟁의 종착지: 답은 작품에 있다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in the Red Hat UBI OpenJDK containers]]></title>
        <id>965ad223-1a40-4290-852c-3ecbd932dc4a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/19/whats-new-red-hat-ubi-openjdk-containers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 6, we shipped the latest feature update to the OpenJDK containers with a number of new features:

	
All the containers are rebased onto the latest Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) point releases: RHEL 8.8 and RHEL 9.2.
We’ve improved the handling of the JAVA_APP_NAME configuration option to accept app names containing spaces (OPENJDK-1551).
We've updated the included version of Apache Maven from 3.6 to 3.8 (OPENJDK-1464).
We shipped the first source containers for the legacy RHEL 7-based OpenJDK containers. For more information on source containers, see this Red Hat Customer Portal article.
This release also includes the most recent Critical Patch Update (CPU) versions of OpenJDK 8, 11, and 17 (8u372, 11.0.19, and 17.0.7, respectively), which we independently shipped in April.
Maximum heap size
Last time we blogged about plans to change the default value for the configuration option JAVA_MAX_MEM_RATIO in the June update of the Universal Base Image (UBI) 8 images.
This option corresponds to the JVM argument -XX:MaxRAMPercentage, and we planned to change the default from 50.0 to 80.0 (80% of detected RAM) (OPENJDK-559), aligning the default with the UBI9 images.
Unfortunately, this change didn't make the cut for the June update, and the default value remains 50%. We are now targeting the August update for this change.
Customers who want to preview the new value can set it explicitly: JAVA_MAX_MEM_RATIO=80.0.
What's next
The next OpenJDK CPU is scheduled for July 18, 2023. We'll ship updated containers shortly afterward. As usual, those container updates will be solely for the updated OpenJDK and will not contain changes to the container scripts themselves. Our next container feature update is planned for August.
We do all our planning in the open on the Red Hat Issue Tracker. If there's something you'd like to see, get in touch, either by leaving a comment or (for an image change) filing an issue.
What's new in the Red Hat UBI OpenJDK containers appeared first on Red Hat Developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jonathan Dowland</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to retrieve packet drop reasons in the Linux kernel]]></title>
        <id>c81250ec-0fca-472f-9d40-943ba5153745</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/19/how-retrieve-packet-drop-reasons-linux-kernel"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding why a packet drops in the Linux kernel is not always easy. The networking stack is wide and reasons to refuse a given packet are multiple and include invalid data from a protocol, firewall rules, wrong checksum, full queues, qdisc or XDP actions, and many more reasons. It is possible to look at indicators such as MIB counters and statistic counters, but often those are generic and triggered for different reasons, but most importantly their coverage is small, and it's impossible to match a specific packet to a given counter increase. 
Socket buffer drop reasons
The socket buffer, SKB (struct sk_buff) is the main data structure representing a packet in the Linux kernel networking stack. When a packet is dropped in the Linux kernel, in most cases, it means its associated socket …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine Tenart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[소셜미디어 금지 실험, 청소년을 구원할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77402</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/19/npsp_socialmediabanutah/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_socialmediabanutah"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T06:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국 유타주가 청소년의 소셜미디어 사용을 금지하는 법안을 통과했습니다. 공화당이 다수당인 주의회와 공화당 소속 스펜서 콕스 주지사가 뜻을 모아 법안을 처리했는데, 뉴욕타임스 오피니언 칼럼니스트 제인 코스턴이 콕스 주지사를 인터뷰했습니다. 인터뷰를 번역하고, 소셜미디어 금지가 원하는 긍정적인 효과로 이어질 수 있을지 분석해 봤습니다. 전문번역: 휴대폰으로부터 아이들을 구하겠다는 한 보수 정치인 해설: 소셜미디어 금지 실험, 청소년을 구원할 수 있을까]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asynchronous Rust on Cortex-M Microcontrollers]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/embedded-async-rust</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/embedded-async-rust"/>
        <updated>2023-07-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we explore the inner workings of Futures, cooperative
scheduling, and Async Rust executors, highlighting their significance in
optimizing resource utilization. Moreover, we introduce the Rust Embassy
project, an innovative framework designed to unlock the power of asynchronous
programming on microcontrollers.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[삼성 눈치 봤나, 질게 뻔한데 엘리엇 취소소송 냈다: 슬로우레터 7월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93716</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93716"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T23:41:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“강이 범람한다” 경고 24번 있었다. “이권 카르텔 보조금으로 수해 복구한다”고? 그래도 추경은 안 한다. 출생신고 안 된 아이 최소 249명 사망. 미국 핵잠수함이 들어왔다. 러시아가 틀어쥔 우크라이나 곡물. 엘리엇 투자자 소송에 취소 소송 냈다. 더 깊게 읽기. 감리가 문제다. 강준만이 MBC를 저격했다. 해법과 대안. 위기 대응, 매뉴얼이 문제다. 미국은 “과할 정도로 대처한다.” 쓰레기를 항공유로 만들기까지...
The post 삼성 눈치 봤나, 질게 뻔한데 엘리엇 취소소송 냈다: 슬로우레터 7월19일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cython 3.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938536/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938536/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T21:50:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
3.0 of Cython (described
as "a programming language that makes writing C
extensions for the Python language as easy as Python itself") has been
released.  Changes include support for Python through 3.11 (but 2.6 support
was dropped), the implementation of a number of PEPs, initial support for
the CPython limited API, better exception handling, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[광고 및 저술 수입]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223160153276</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223160153276"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T20:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[블로그에 ‘애드 포스트’라는 광고 프로그램이 나타나도록 했다. 제헌절 날 하루 동안 111원을 벌었다. 땅을 파도 100원도 안 나온다는 말을 실감하도록 만들어 준다. 먼저 뜬 광고는 내가 살고 있는 동네를 중심으로 고기집, 술집, 카페, 빵집 등이 나오고, 학원, 스튜디오, 미용실 등 다양하게 광고가 나온다. 하단에 달린 두 번째 광고는 블로그의 주제어에 따라 달라지는 것 같다. 순수이성 비판에 대해 포스트를 썼는데, 순수이성 비판에 대한 강의들이 소개된다. 애드 포스트는 정직하게 내가 111원 벌었다고 공지해 준다. 이제 절판된 내 첫 책은 두 번 인세를 받은 것 같다. 마지막 인세를 받은 후에도 오래 동안 책이 간행되었음에도 인.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SambaXP 2023 videos posted]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938524/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938524/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T18:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2023 sambaXP conference was held May 10 and 11 in Goettingen, Germany.
Videos
of the talks held there have now been posted on YouTube; topics covered
include an io_uring update, fuzzing, passwordless services, GPL compliance,
and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware conversion of convolutional neural networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479927</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/hardware-conversion-of-convolutional-neural-networks/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T17:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Concluding this series on convolutional neural networks (CNNs), we explain the hardware conversion of a CNN and specifically the benefits of using an AI microcontroller...
The post Hardware conversion of convolutional neural networks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ole Dreessen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reaping IoT benefits with smart agriculture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479922</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/reaping-iot-benefits-with-smart-agriculture/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We discuss wireless IoT technologies in agriculture and the role of the Wi-SUN open-source, open-standard protocol in serving as a foundational LPWAN technology for smart...
The post Reaping IoT benefits with smart agriculture appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chad Steider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A Q&A about the realtime patches]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938236/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938236/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T14:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a session at the 2023 Real Time Linux Summit, Thomas Gleixner answered
questions about the realtime feature of the kernel, its status, and the Real-Time Linux
project's plans for the future.  The talk was billed as a "Q&A about
PREEMPT_RT" with a caveat: "anything except printk() and
documentation".  As might be guessed, the first two questions were on just
those topics, but there were plenty of other questions (and answers) too.
The summit was 
held in conjunction with the inaugural Embedded
Open Source Summit in Prague, Czechia at the end of June.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938488/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938488/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T13:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (java-1.8.0-openjdk), Red Hat (bind, bind9.16, curl, edk2, java-1.8.0-ibm, kernel, kernel-rt, and kpatch-patch), SUSE (iniparser, installation-images, java-1_8_0-ibm, kernel, libqt5-qtbase, nodejs16, openvswitch, and ucode-intel), and Ubuntu (linux-oem-6.0 and linux-xilinx-zynqmp).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralizing the Practice of Architecture at Xapo Bank]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/xapo-architecture-experience.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/xapo-architecture-experience.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T11:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's common to see a centralized architecture function that sets
     standards and oversees development projects. Such teams often suffer from
     being far removed from the issues of implementation with long
     feedback loops that slow down the flow of work. To counter these problems,
     many organizations have explored a decentralized approach to yield
     alignment between teams without these problems. One such organization is
     Xapo bank, which did this using ideas taken from Domain-Driven Design, Team
     Topologies, and the Architectural Advice Process.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Zephyr: Devicetrees]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1547.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1547.php"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T11:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last blog post, (Getting Started With Zephyr: Kconfig), we saw how the "Kconfig" infrastructure can be used to enable and disable specific Zephyr subsystems. Specifically, we observed the three main elements of the Kconfig infrastructure. First, we saw how the Kconfig infrastructure is formulated and an example of a Kconfig file to enable the LED subsystem. Second, we saw how specific...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The White House details its IoT cybersecurity label plan]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12659</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/the-white-house-details-its-iot-cybersecurity-label-plan/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T09:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The White House unveiled its plan for a U.S. Cyber Trust Mark that will certify that the IoT device marked with the label has met a set of security criteria developed to protect consumers’ networks and device data. The U.S. Cyber Trust Mark will be a voluntary program administered by the Federal Communications Commission, and […]
The post The White House details its IoT cybersecurity label plan appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to Red Hat Trusted Application Pipeline]]></title>
        <id>8db0b99d-6fde-4045-8df9-663f310eee2b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/18/introduction-red-hat-trusted-application-pipeline"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Red Hat Summit 2023, the engineering team announced two projects that will change the way developers and ops develop and deploy their applications to Red Hat OpenShift. These projects are the Red Hat Trusted Application Pipeline and the Red Hat Developer Hub. They are a little different from the usual Red Hat products in that they directly address critical composite problems in the DevSecOps space that customers are starting to experience issues.
Red Hat has long been acknowledged as the provider of enterprise strength frameworks and platforms, notably Red Hat Enterprise Linux and OpenShift, the enterprise distribution of Kubernetes. Both are incredibly powerful product sets, but to get the most out of them, we have to understand and use them as experts would. Most developers and ops pe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ian Lawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to run a custom server task in Red Hat Data Grid]]></title>
        <id>d88d032d-2289-48ea-a518-eea26fcb73be</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/18/how-run-custom-server-task-red-hat-data-grid"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custom server tasks can be deployed to the Red Hat Data Grid server for remote execution from the command line interface (CLI) and Hot Rod or REST clients. Tasks can be implemented as custom Java classes or as scripts in languages such as JavaScript.
In this article, we will deploy a Java class that will evict and reload the cache in order to pick up modified entries in the original database table from which we loaded the cache. Data Grid will automatically load new entries added to the database table, however modified rows will require reloading using a server task, as shown in the following example.
How to deploy PostgreSQL with a custom image
SQL cache stores let you load Red Hat Data Grid caches from existing database tables. Data Grid offers two types of SQL cache stores: table and qu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Torbjorn Dahlen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAC 2023: AI and hardware talent dominate debate]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479911</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/dac-2023-ai-and-hardware-talent-dominate-debate/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T06:35:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industry is concerned about shortage of talent to address the chip design and manufacturing needed to address the explosion in demand for AI and generative AI compute.
The post DAC 2023: AI and hardware talent dominate debate appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SDIO RX: Bugs found w/ Formal methods]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/formal/2023/07/18/sdrxframe.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/formal/2023/07/18/sdrxframe.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-18T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This post is the second post regarding my new SDIO/eMMC
controller.  The SDIO protocol is commonly
used on SD cards, and the eMMC protocol for eMMC chips.  The two protocols
are so similar that, when using
this controller, they will differ in
software only.  Today’s bottom line is that, although the
controller is still quite new and only
barely silicon proven, this week I had the chance to formally verify the
receive portion
of the controller and so I thought I might write about what took place.
My goal will be to answer the question of whether this extra step of doing
formal verification was worth it or not.
This SDIO controller is being written as
part of the Klusterlab project.  I’ve been
calling this same project the ETH10G
project, because at its core it is a 10Gb
Ethernet switch.
The…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세상이 다시 반짝이기 시작했다 – ‘오늘도 그림’ (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93654</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93654"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T23:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“모두 우려했지만 동네서점은 인기가 있었다. 그리고 모두가 우려한 대로 인생 전체가 흔들릴 만큼 큰 실패와 고통도 겪게 됐다. 외형적으로는 사업의 실패라는 고통, 관계적으로는 가장 사랑하는 가족들과의 갈등에서 오는 두려움, 내적으로는 나라는 인간의 무능하고 저급한 정신의 민낯을 맞닥뜨리며 받은 충격과 실망 등이 한꺼번에 밀려들었다” 뚜루(김진아), [오늘도 그림], 리토스: 2023 나는 매일매일 내 인생을 비난했다 서울 상암동...
The post 세상이 다시 반짝이기 시작했다 – ‘오늘도 그림’ (2023) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 쾌락에 고통이 뒤따른다는 건 과학적 진실]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76964</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/17/npsp_marijuanalegalization/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_marijuanalegalization"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T22:59:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 24일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 마리화나(대마)는 양가적 감정을 불러일으키는 대표적인 단어입니다. 대마는 우리나라에서 법적으로 마약이며, 따라서 한국인은 전 세계 어디서건 대마초를 피울 경우 처벌받게 됩니다. 특히 마약을 사용하는 것은 단순한 불법 행위가 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“어이가 없다”는 윤석열에 “국가는 왜 존재하는가” 묻는다: 슬로우레터 7월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93675</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93675"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T21:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[막을 수 있었다. 산사태도 결국 인재였다. 홍수 때마다 4대강 공방, “찬반 모두 성립 안 된다.” 지하차도 버스 기사의 사연. 물가도 요동친다. “언급 않는 게 좋을 것 같다.” 중국 경제 6.3% 성장했는데도 “충격”. ‘그냥 쉰다’는 청년 61만 명, 70%가 부모와 함께 산다. 더 깊게 읽기. 집값 올랐는데 재산세는 줄었다, 이래도 되나. 학폭 피해 고교생 32% “날마다...
The post “어이가 없다”는 윤석열에 “국가는 왜 존재하는가” 묻는다: 슬로우레터 7월18일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[공지] 자유/오픈소스 소프트웨어 이야기를 종료합니다]]></title>
        <id>https://joone.net/?p=4820</id>
        <link href="https://joone.net/2023/07/17/%ea%b3%b5%ec%a7%80-%ec%9e%90%ec%9c%a0-%ec%98%a4%ed%94%88%ec%86%8c%ec%8a%a4-%ec%86%8c%ed%94%84%ed%8a%b8%ec%9b%a8%ec%96%b4-%ec%9d%b4%ec%95%bc%ea%b8%b0%eb%a5%bc-%ec%a2%85%eb%a3%8c%ed%95%a9%eb%8b%88/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T18:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>joone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coroutines for Go]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/coro</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/coro"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why we need coroutines for Go, and what they might look like.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chat APIs now generally available to all Workspace developers]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-chat-apis-now-generally-available-to-workspace-developers.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-chat-apis-now-generally-available-to-workspace-developers.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T17:00:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mike Rhemtulla, Product Manager





  
Programmatically manage spaces, memberships, messages, reactions and attachments

  
Last year, we announced new APIs in Developer Preview that enabled developers to programmatically create Chat spaces and add members on behalf of users. These APIs, in addition to the message, reaction, and attachments APIs are now generally available to all Workspace developers.
Google Chat has become a critical connectivity tool for hybrid organizations as well as a powerful tool for streamlining workflows. The Google Chat API allows developers to build user facing apps that integrate workflows into Chat and provide contextual information right into the conversation. Chat apps let users receive details and link previews directly from connected internal an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plan for death at the start of building your connected device]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12656</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/plan-for-death-at-the-start-of-building-your-connected-device/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T15:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week brings us the tale of yet another connected device that may become a useless chunk of scrap because its maker is going out of business. In this case, the affected product is the VanMoof e-bike, which cost buyers $5,000 and requires a working app for many of the bike’s functions. VanMoof has gone […]
The post Plan for death at the start of building your connected device appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Debian looks forward to 2038]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938149/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938149/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T14:29:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 19, 2038, the time_t value used on many 32-bit Linux
systems will overflow and wrap around, causing those systems to believe
they have returned to 1901.  Much work has gone into preparing many layers of the
system for this event, but not all distributions have completed their
preparations.  One of those is Debian but, as was seen in a conversation in
May, the Debian developers are now grappling with the problem in a serious
way.  Along the way, they appear to have made an interesting decision
regarding which systems will (or will not) be updated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938375/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938375/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T14:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (gpac, iperf3, kanboard, kernel, and pypdf2), Fedora (ghostscript), SUSE (bind, bouncycastle, ghostscript, go1.19, go1.20, installation-images, kernel, mariadb, MozillaFirefox, MozillaFirefox-branding-SLE, php74, poppler, and python-Django), and Ubuntu (cups, linux-oem-6.1, and ruby2.3, ruby2.5, ruby2.7, ruby3.0, ruby3.1).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘푸틴의 위기’가 시진핑에게 미칠 영향은… 대만 침공 재고?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77377</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/17/npsp_xiputin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_xiputin"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T07:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[푸틴 대통령이 고용한 용병 ‘바그너 그룹’의 쿠데타 이후 푸틴 대통령의 위기가 크게 불거졌습니다. 바그너 그룹과 러시아 정규군이 서로 총을 겨누는 최악의 사태는 피했지만, 이번 일을 계기로 푸틴의 위상은 크게 꺾였고, 훗날 돌이켜 보면 이번 일이 푸틴이 실각하는 시작이 될 수 있다는 분석도 있습니다. 푸틴의 위기를 아마도 씁쓸하게 바라보고 있을 사람이 중국의 시진핑 주석입니다. 지난해 근간의 관행을 깨고 3연임을 강행한 시진핑 주석에게 푸틴은 미국의 패권에 맞서는 ‘동지이자 절친’입니다. 이번 사건으로 새로운 국면을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DAC 2023: RISC-V is not in the future, it’s now]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479902</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/dac-2023-risc-v-is-not-in-the-future-its-now/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T06:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A snippet of the RISC-V panel discussion at DAC 2023 in San Francisco, with panellists from Intel, OpenHW Group, Imperas, Ventana Micro, Meta, and RISC-V International 
The post DAC 2023: RISC-V is not in the future, it’s now appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[숭배와 혐오의 이분법을 넘어서: 로알드 달, 르 귄, 그/그녀]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93307</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93307"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T04:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. 작품은 ‘그때/거기’의 세계에서 태어나 항상 새롭게 변화하는 ‘지금/여기’의 세계를 통과합니다. 운 좋게 살아남았다면 말이죠. 그렇게 평론가와 독자는 변화된 가치와 기준으로 작품을 끊임없이 규정하죠. 그들은 작품을 닫아버리려 합니다. 그들은 작품을 매번 자신의 기념비로 만들려고 시도하죠. 하지만 작품은 자신을 닫아버리려는 비평적 권력과 욕망에 저항해 항상...
The post 숭배와 혐오의 이분법을 넘어서: 로알드 달, 르 귄, 그/그녀 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.5-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938328/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938328/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-17T00:57:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second 6.5 prepatch is out for testing.
"No surprises here: this thing looks very normal."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“참사 때마다 무정부 상태” “박근혜도 이 정도는 아니었다.”: 슬로우레터 7월17일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93593</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93593"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T22:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[30초면 지나가던 터널, 빠져나오지 못했다. 빛 바랜 우크라이나 이벤트. 거짓 해명이 더 키운 김건희 명품 쇼핑 논란. 국경일이지만 공휴일이 아닌 날. “필드에서 뛰던 사람, 심판할 수 있나.” 오늘의 TMI. 가장 많이 일하는 나라는 한국. 포켓몬 카드 529억 장 팔렸다. “트위터 광고 매출 반토막.” 집값 회복도 강남이 주도. 자이아가라, 흐르지오, 캐리비안 자이. TBS 지키는 최일구 시급은...
The post “참사 때마다 무정부 상태” “박근혜도 이 정도는 아니었다.”: 슬로우레터 7월17일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Research ideas for 2023/2024]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8005</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/07/16/research-ideas-for-2023-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T21:25:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Students sometimes ask me for suggestions of interesting research problems in software engineering. A summary of my two recurring suggestions, for this year, appears below; 2016/2017 and 2019/2020 versions. How many active users does a program or application have? The greater the number of users, the greater the number of reported faults. Estimates of program […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NULL pointer protection with ARM Cortex-M MPU]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1546.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1546.php"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T19:34:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second of the Ten Commandments for C Programmers says:

2. Thou shalt not follow the NULL pointer, for chaos and madness await thee at its end.

This post explains how you can set up the ARM Cortex-M MPU (Memory Protection Unit) to protect thy code from dragons, demons, core dumps, and numberless other foul creatures awaiting thee after thou dereference the NULL...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 자유를 향한 싸움의 실용적 기술로서 고전 읽기]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223158098979</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223158098979"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T18:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제목이 아주 매력적이다. 고전 읽기가 자유를 향한 싸움의 실용적 기술이 되어야 한다는 것이다. 아마 이러한 당위는 될 수 있다는 가능성을 암암리 가정하는 것처럼 보이기도 한다. 이런 의미에서 고전 읽기가 우리 삶을 위한 무기가 될 수 있다. 그것은 자유를 향한 싸움이라는 삶의 무기이다. 논문에 의하면, 고전 읽기가 가만히 앉아서 우리 삶을 성찰하고 음미하는 것이 아니라, 실용적 싸움의 기술서이어야 하고 전략서가 되어야 한다. 니체는 이러한 학문을 ‘즐거운 학문’이라고 부른다. 고전 읽기는 당연히 이런 학문이 되어야 하고, 아마 될 수 있을 것이다. 반면에 <국가가 추진하는 각종 인문학 및 고전 교육 강화사업, 기업에서.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: inheritance in C and C++]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479898</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-inheritance-in-c-and-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T12:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today’s video lesson #30 shows how to reuse the Shape class created in the last lesson instead of creating such classes from scratch. In the...
The post Programming embedded systems: inheritance in C and C++ appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting Modbus RTU to TCP with Waveshare RS485 to Ethernet converter]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2023-07-16:/waveshare-rs485-to-wifi-ethernet-converter.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/waveshare-rs485-to-wifi-ethernet-converter.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been planning to connect my Modbus electricity meter to Home Assistant for a while. Unfortunately my Home Assistant machine is placed far away from the breaker panel and I wanted to avoid running extra cabling. Modbus RTU to Modbus TCP conversion has been a solved problem for a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[386BSD 개발한 윌리암 졸리츠(William Jolitiz) 부고 소식]]></title>
        <id>https://joone.net/?p=4812</id>
        <link href="https://joone.net/2023/07/14/386bsd-%ea%b0%9c%eb%b0%9c%ed%95%9c-%ec%9c%8c%eb%a6%ac%ec%95%94-%ec%a1%b8%eb%a6%ac%ec%b8%a0william-jolitiz-%eb%b6%80%ea%b3%a0-%ec%86%8c%ec%8b%9d/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T21:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제 블로그에서도 등장했던 윌리암 졸리츠(William Jolitiz)가 2022년 65세 나이로 세상을 떠난 소식을 우연히 386bsd.org에 방문해서 알았습니다.   두 부부의 386BSD 개발 이야기는 여러가지로 흥미로웠는데, 우선 부부가 직접 오픈소스 프로젝트를 운영했고, 386BSD가 이후 여러 x86용 BSD 유닉스의 기반이 되었고, 리누스 토발즈가 리눅스 커널을 개발할 때 그들이 Dr. Dobb’s Journal에 쓴 개발 관련 글을 참고합니다.   아내 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>joone</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for July 14, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12645</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-july-14-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T20:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT steps on the gas for Mercedes-Benz: Yes, I’m as sick of hearing about ChatGPT as you are. Still, the large language model service is worth paying attention to as more companies make use of it. Among the latest is Mercedes-Benz, which this week announced a test of ChatGPT for intelligent vehicle production. The idea is […]
The post IoT news of the week for July 14, 2023 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The proper time to split struct page]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937839/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937839/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T14:30:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The page structure sits at the core of the kernel's
memory-management subsystem; one such structure exists for every page of
installed RAM.  This structure is increasingly seen as a problem, though,
and phasing it out is one of the many side projects associated with the folio conversion.  One step in that direction
is currently meeting some pushback from memory-management developers,
though, who think that some of these changes are coming too soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938233/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938233/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-14T13:55:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (lemonldap-ng and php-dompdf), Red Hat (.NET 6.0, .NET 7.0, firefox, and thunderbird), Scientific Linux (firefox and thunderbird), SUSE (ghostscript, installation-images, kernel, php7, python, and python-Django), and Ubuntu (linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-ibm, linux-oracle, mozjs102, postgresql-9.5, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux to diverge (slightly) from RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938165/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938165/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:57:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux has announced that
the distribution will no longer be a strict clone of Red Hat Enterprise
Linux, but will maintain ABI compatibility.


	For a typical user, this will mean very little change in your use
	of AlmaLinux. Red Hat-compatible applications will still be able to
	run on AlmaLinux OS, and your installs of AlmaLinux will continue
	to receive timely security updates. The most remarkable potential
	impact of the change is that we will no longer be held to the line
	of “bug-for-bug compatibility” with Red Hat, and that means that we
	can now accept bug fixes outside of Red Hat’s release cycle. While
	that means some AlmaLinux OS users may encounter bugs that are not
	in Red Hat, we may also accept patches for bugs that have not yet
	been accepted upstream, or shipped downstream.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 순수이성비판 강의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223155723912</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223155723912"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:25:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[논리학, 수학, 자연과학 등이 모두 학문의 안전한 길을 걷고 있습니다. 그런데 그 안전한 길을 걷고 있는 이유가 각각 차이가 있습니다. 특히 칸트가 주목하는 것은 수학과 자연과학, 즉 물리학이 학문의 안전한 길을 걷고 있는 이유입니다. 기본적 생각은 우리가 대상에다 우리의 생각이나 개념을 집어넣었다는 것입니다. 그런데 여기서 말하는 <우리>가 무엇을 말하는 것인가요? 진짜 우리가 집어넣은 것인가요? 수학의 경우, 칸트가 다음처럼 이야기합니다. <그가 개념 자체에 따라 선험적으로 집어넣어 생각했고, 구성이나 작도에 의해 표시했던 것을 산출해야 함을, 그리고 어떤 것을 안전하게 선험적으로 알기 위해 사물에다 그 개.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘시럽급여’? ‘쉴드’ 치다 지친 조선일보의 분노: 슬로우레터 7월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93270</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93270"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T22:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“멍청함의 가장 충격적이고 가장 추잡한 면모는 멍청함이라는 것이 과학과 기술과 진보에 의해 사라지는 것이 아니라 진보와 더불어 그것 또한 진보한다는 것입니다.” 밀란 쿤데라, ‘소설의 기술’, 민음사: 2013. 무엇을 위한 전쟁인가. ‘티슈 노동자’들의 파업과 의료 공백. “김건희 고속도로, 오히려 땅값 떨어진다.” 어버이연합 없으니 자유총연맹으로? 4대강 뒤집기도 다시 턴다. 더 깊게 읽기. 월급보다 많은 실업급여? “통계적 착시다.”...
The post ‘시럽급여’? ‘쉴드’ 치다 지친 조선일보의 분노: 슬로우레터 7월14일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.71.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938120/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938120/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T16:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.71.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Changes this time
include the C-unwind
ABI, an upgrade to musl 1.2, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Stabilizing per-VMA locking]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937943/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937943/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T15:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel-development process routinely absorbs large changes to
fundamental subsystems and still produces stable releases every nine or ten
weeks.  On occasion, though, the development community's luck runs out.
The per-VMA locking work that went into the
6.4 release is a case in point; it looked like a well-tested change that
improved page-fault scalability.  There turned out to be a few demons
hiding in that code, though, that made life difficult for early adopters of
the 6.4 kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938108/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938108/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T14:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ruby-doorkeeper), Fedora (mingw-nsis and thunderbird), Red Hat (bind9.16, nodejs, nodejs:16, nodejs:18, python38:3.8 and python38-devel:3.8, and rh-nodejs14-nodejs), Slackware (krb5), SUSE (geoipupdate, installation-images, libqt5-qtbase, python-Django1, and skopeo), and Ubuntu (knot-resolver, lib3mf, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-ibm, linux-oracle, linux-azure-fde, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, and scipy).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[나이는 정말 아무것도 아니다: ‘우리는 매일 새로워진다’ (2018)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93240</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93240"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T09:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 베라 왕 베라는 원래 피겨 스케이팅 선수였다. 하지만 올림픽 대표 후보에서 탈락했다. 그는 패션 잡지 [보그] 에디터로 취직했다. 잘나갔다. 15년 만에 회사를 그만둘 무렵, 그가 편집장 자리를 놓고 경쟁한 인물이 안나 윈투어. 맞다. [악마는 프라다를 입는다]의 그분이다. 베라는 마흔에 결혼하면서 난관에 부딪쳤다. 맘에 드는 웨딩드레스가 없었다. 베라 왕이라는 전설적 웨딩드레스 디자이너가 늦깍이로 탄생한 것이...
The post 나이는 정말 아무것도 아니다: ‘우리는 매일 새로워진다’ (2018) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[신나면 망한다: ‘미제 똥물’ 전설에서 ‘밥.꽃.양.’의 현실까지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93145</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93145"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T07:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. 처음 보았을 때 나는 이 영화가 여성주의 영화라고 생각했다. 심각한 영화였지만 어쩔 수 없이 지루했고 그래서 꾸벅꾸벅 졸기도 했다. 그때 나는 카메라의 시선이 공정하지 않다고 생각했다. 특히 남성 노동자들을 보는 시선이 왜곡돼 있다고 생각했다. 영화 속의 남성 노동자들은 못 생기고 거칠고 비열했다. 혐오스럽고...
The post 신나면 망한다: ‘미제 똥물’ 전설에서 ‘밥.꽃.양.’의 현실까지 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A developer’s path to success with OpenShift and containers]]></title>
        <id>e01ea10c-6333-49c0-8681-48b4641c4ebe</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/13/developers-path-success-openshift-and-containers"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am a developer new to containers, Kubernetes, or CI/CD. Where should I start?
This article provides five pathways including resources to succeed on your container journey.
Highlighted material:
The following materials are free with no prerequisites.
These materials are foundational for you to start working on your next project ASAP.
Training materials will take up to five hours to complete.
1. Start building your skills with containers and OpenShift
To start with containers, understand what containers are and how CI/CD can automate the software development lifecycle. 
Documentation: Understanding containers 
Blog: The present and future of CI/CD with GitOps on Red Hat OpenShift 
Documentation: Understanding Cloud Native Applications
Start building your skills
Gather hands-on experience w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Valentina Rodriguez Sosa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[누가 네이버를 흔드는가, 뉴스 알고리즘을 둘러싼 논쟁.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93111</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93111"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T01:22:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[핵심 요약 (바쁜 독자용) 7월13일 뉴스공장 인터뷰입니다. 최근 네이버가 뉴스 알고리즘을 발표했죠? 국민의힘에서 네이버가 뉴스 알고리즘을 조작했다는 의혹을 제기하자, 뉴스 알고리즘 추천에 영향을 미치는 요인들을 공개한 건데요. 슬로우뉴스 이정환 대표와 함께 자세히 짚어보도록 하겠습니다. “네. 종이신문을 1주일에 한 번이라도 봤다는 사람이 9.7%, 날마다 본다는 사람은 3.3%입니다. 그렇다고 뉴스를 보지 않느냐, 포털 뉴스 이용률은 92.3%입니다. 포털뉴스...
The post 누가 네이버를 흔드는가, 뉴스 알고리즘을 둘러싼 논쟁. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 13, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937458/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937458/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-13T01:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 13, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Testing for storage and filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937830/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937830/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T22:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kdevops
kernel-testing framework has come up at several earlier summits, including 
in two separate sessions at last year's event.
Testing kernel filesystems and the block layer, not to mention lots of
other kernel subsystems, has become increasingly
important over time.
  So it was no
surprise that Luis Chamberlain led a 
combined storage and filesystem session at the
2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem,
Memory-Management and BPF Summit to talk more about testing, the
resources needed for it, and what can be done to improve it.  It was the
final session for this year's summit, so this article completes our coverage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오염수 탱크에 계속 보관, 3000억 원이면 된다.: 슬로우레터 7월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93094</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93094"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T21:51:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오염수 방류에 동의했다. 북한 미사일, 이번에는 달랐다. 한국 경제 규모, 13위로 밀렸다. ‘시럽급여’? 원희룡이 물러나야 해결된다. “이러다 망한다”, 지지부진한 민주당 혁신. 의료 파업이 시작됐다. 오늘의 TMI. TV 수신료 분리 첫날, 한전에 문의 전화 5만 건. 주택연금 가입률 2.4%. 버스는 1500원, 지하철은 1400원. 보험금 안 내주고 버티는 건 ‘깃털’ 과징금 때문. 주담대가 늘고 있다. 일본에서 연봉...
The post 오염수 탱크에 계속 보관, 3000억 원이면 된다.: 슬로우레터 7월13일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convening public benefit and charitable foundations working in open domains (OSI blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/938021/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/938021/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T21:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Open Source Initiative (OSI) blog, the organization has announced the Open Policy Alliance (OPA), which is meant to bring together various non-profit organizations to help educate and inform US policy makers about open-source software and its needs:

The need to create such a program is more urgent today due to the rise of new regulations in the software industry and adjacent open domains around the world. Cyber security, the societal impact of AI, data and privacy are important issues for legislators globally. At the same time, the COVID-19 pandemic drove collaborative development to unprecedented levels and took Open Source software, open research, open content and data from mainstream to main stage. Moving forward, developing these important public policies whilst not harming the ecosystem requires an understanding of how the Open Source ecosystem works. Ensuring stakeholders without historic benefit of representation are included in those discussions becomes paramount to that end.

The OPA will focus on educating public policy makers on Open Source to inform their development and deliberation of new policy concepts. There are unintended consequences that come from a lack of understanding of how open collaboration works in practice. The OPA will address this as well as the historic absence of contribution from underrepresented groups. The interest areas of the OPA community will complement those of Digitable Public Goods Alliance, a UNICEF multi-stakeholder initiative with a mission to accelerate the attainment of sustainable development goals in low- and middle-income countries that OSI joined earlier this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Heroes of Code and Magic: VCMI game engine analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1058/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1058/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might wish to feel nostalgic and play your favorite old game, but certain things in such games may seem outdated. So, to breathe new life into an old project, some enthusiasts set the goal to recreate and improve its source code. We decided to use the PVS-Studio static analyzer and check how VCMI developers cope with this task.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Call for Bloggers!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1545.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1545.php"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T16:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you passionate about embedded systems? Do you have valuable insights, tips, or stories to share with the embedded community? Do you want to reach a large and engaged audience of embedded enthusiasts and professionals?
We are currently looking at adding a few more inspired writers to our team of bloggers.  
By blogging on EmbeddedRelated.com, you will not only contribute...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to automate many devices at a given time with Alexa]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12622</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/how-to-automate-many-devices-at-a-given-time-with-alexa/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T15:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a recent Internet of Things Podcast we took a voicemail question on our podcast hotline regarding Alexa. Our caller wants to know how to have multiple devices do something at a specific time, or at sunrise or sunset. Although the process isn’t as intuitive as it should be, this can be done. Here’s how […]
The post How to automate many devices at a given time with Alexa appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6월 CPI 요약과 월가의 반응]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591210</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591210/6%ec%9b%94-cpi"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T14:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937972/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937972/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T12:55:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (erlang, symfony, thunderbird, and yajl), Fedora (cutter-re, kernel, rizin, and yt-dlp), Red Hat (grafana), SUSE (kernel and python-Django), and Ubuntu (dotnet6, dotnet7 and firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[곳간에서 진보난다: 정치적 올바름과 반(反)페미니즘 그리고 성평등은커녕]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93024</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93024"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T09:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. ‘정치적 올바름'(Political Correctness; PC)은 그 조어의 단순함에도 불구하고, 결코 만만한 용어, 만만한 개념이 아닙니다. 인어공주에 관한 이야기를 마치고 나서, 정치적 올바름에 관해 캡콜드 님께 물었습니다. 정치적 올바름의 어원: 반어 혹은 조롱 민노: 정치적 올바름이라는 말은 어떤 억압이랄까, 피곤함이랄까, 경직성이랄까, 그런 부정적인 느낌을 내포하고...
The post 곳간에서 진보난다: 정치적 올바름과 반(反)페미니즘 그리고 성평등은커녕 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a GCP instance via workflow and Ansible]]></title>
        <id>ab8d83e0-9dfe-48a8-b0d9-d571bfbb7181</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/12/how-create-gcp-instance-workflow-and-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our previous article, we explored how to use the Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform to create an instance in Google Compute Engine. We saw how Ansible Automation Platform can streamline the process of deploying instances in GCP, making it more efficient and less error-prone.
In this article, we'll explore how to simplify the process of creating Instances in GCP by using workflow templates with Ansible Automation Platform. Workflow templates can help us to standardize the process of creating VMs and reduce the amount of manual intervention required. We'll dive into the details of how to use workflow templates with Ansible Automation Platform to further optimize our infrastructure management in Azure.
If you're following along with our series, you may recall that we previously discussed …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepankar Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create a GCP instance using Ansible Automation]]></title>
        <id>8ffc980c-46a6-470e-b3b8-c49bd74d9fc3</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/12/how-create-gcp-instance-using-ansible-automation"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This series covers the end-to-end process of creating an instance on GCP using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. This 3-part series includes:
Part 1: How to create an instance on GCP using Ansible CLI
Part 2: How to create a GCP instance using Ansible Automation
Part 3: How to create a GCP instance via workflow and Ansible
In our previous article, we explored how to use the Ansible Automation Platform CLI to create an instance in GCP. This time, we'll take things a step further and leverage the power of the Ansible Automation Platform to automate the process. The Ansible Automation Platform is a powerful tool that enables you to manage your infrastructure more efficiently, with less manual intervention. By using the Ansible Automation Platform, we can create a streamlined process for de…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepankar Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to create an instance on GCP using the Ansible CLI]]></title>
        <id>db5556aa-b189-409a-9e92-a77ccdafba55</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/12/how-create-instance-gcp-using-ansible-cli"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This series covers the end-to-end process of creating an instance on Google Cloud Platform (GCP) using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. This 3-part series includes:
Part 1: How to create an instance on GCP using Ansible CLI
Part 2: How to create a GCP instance using Ansible Automation
Part 3: How to create a GCP instance via workflow and Ansible
By the end of this article, you will have a clear understanding of how to use the Ansible Automation Platform CLI to automate the creation of GCP instances, which will save you time and reduce the risk of manual errors. Let's get started!
Prerequisites
Ansible installed on your system.
An active GCP Account with sufficient permissions.
Ansible google cloud collection installed on your system.
We will start by setting up the necessary credential…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepankar Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSJ, 인공지능 반도체 혁명에서 엔비디아 도전자들]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591203</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591203/%ec%9d%b8%ea%b3%b5%ec%a7%80%eb%8a%a5-%eb%b0%98%eb%8f%84%ec%b2%b4-%ed%98%81%eb%aa%85%ea%b3%bc-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%eb%8f%84%ec%a0%84%ec%9e%90"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T05:12:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Matter, Thread, and Memfault]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/memfault-matter</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/memfault-matter"/>
        <updated>2023-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’m Markus, software engineer @ Tridonic, where we are working on Internet-connected wireless lighting solutions based on the Matter standard. To be able to monitor the reliability of those devices we’ve been using Memfault and tied it into Matter/Thread and its UDP/IPv6 stack based on the Nordic Connect SDK. In the following, I’ll show you the modifications we’ve done to enable Memfault in an IPv6 solution.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 지금의 정치적 양극화에 미디어는 얼마나 책임이 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76935</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/11/npsp_conservativemedia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_conservativemedia"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T22:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 22일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 4월의 마지막 토요일 저녁, 백악관 기자단 만찬이 열렸습니다. 출입처 제도가 없는 미국에서 백악관은 등록된 기자만 드나들며 궁극의 취재원이라 할 수 있는 대통령을 취재할 수 있는 독특한 부처입니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘그 땅 몰랐다’로 면피 안 된다: 슬로우레터 7월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=93001</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/93001"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T22:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2500원으로 KBS 때리기. “‘그 땅 몰랐다’로 면피 안 된다.” 오염수 처리 성능 검증 없었다. 서울에 비가 와야 뉴스가 된다. 스웨덴 나토 가입, 튀르키예가 웃는다. 북한이 남조선 대신 ‘대한민국’이란 표현을 썼다. 추락사한 노동자, 그 아들도 추락사. 16억 원 들인 짝퉁 거북선, 해체하는 데 1800만 원. 신문 발행 부수 다시 꺼내나. 오늘의 TMI. 폭우 때문에 이재명-이낙연 미팅...
The post ‘그 땅 몰랐다’로 면피 안 된다: 슬로우레터 7월12일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.0 beta 4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/07/pleased-to-announce-release-of-python-3.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/07/pleased-to-announce-release-of-python-3.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T20:08:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.12 beta 4.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3120b4/
This is a beta preview of Python 3.12


Python 3.12 is still in development. This release, 3.12.0b4, is the final of four beta release previews of 3.12.

Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their projects to support the new feature release.

We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects to test with 3.12 during the beta phase and report issues found to [the Python bug tracker (https://github.com/python/cpython/issues) as soon as possible. While the release is planned to be feature complete entering the beta phase, it is possible that features may be modified or, in r…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Dev Library Letters: 21st Edition]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-dev-library-letters-21st-edition.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/google-dev-library-letters-21st-edition.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T19:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by  Swathi Dharshna Subbaraj, Google Dev Library






In this newsletter, we highlight the best projects developed with Google technologies that have been contributed to the Google Dev Library platform. We hope this will spark some inspiration for your next project!
Highlights of the Month

In the past two months, we asked contributors to look back, revisit, and update their older Dev Library contributions as a best practice. Most contributors took the time to revise their content and incorporate recent releases. This campaign encourages developers to update their repositories with the latest Google technologies, which is advantageous to users and the broader developer community.

Here are some of the standout up-to-date projects:



Sheets Compose Dialogs by Maximilian Keppeler


…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Storing Data in Control Flow]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/pcdata</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/pcdata"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Write programs, not simulations of programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrating Google Dev Library’s Women Contributors in AI/ML]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/celebrating-google-dev-library-women-contributions-in-ai-ml.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/celebrating-google-dev-library-women-contributions-in-ai-ml.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T16:00:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Swathi Dharshna Subbaraj, Google Dev Library






Women have made remarkable progress in advancing AI/ML technology through their contributions to open source projects. They have developed and maintained tools, algorithms, and frameworks that enable researchers, developers, and businesses to create and implement cutting edge AI/ML solutions. 
To celebrate those achievements, Google Dev Library has featured outstanding contributions from developers worldwide. It has also provided an opportunity to showcase contributions from women developers who are working on AI/ML projects. Read on to learn their projects and insights.
Contributors in Spotlight

Suzen Fylke


Suzen is a machine learning engineer with a passion for helping mission-driven and socially-minded companies leverage AI…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The FUSE BPF filesystem]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937433/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937433/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:30:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Filesystem
in Userspace (FUSE) framework can be used to create a "stacked"
filesystem, where the FUSE piece adds specialized functionality
(e.g. reporting different file metadata) atop an
underlying kernel filesystem.  The performance of such filesystems leaves a
lot to be desired, however, so
the FUSE
BPF filesystem has been proposed to try to improve the performance to
be close to that of the underlying native filesystem.  It came up in the
context of a session on FUSE passthrough
earlier in the
2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem,
Memory-Management and BPF Summit, but the details of FUSE BPF were more
fully described by Daniel Rosenberg in a combined filesystem and BPF
session on the final day of the summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비좁은 영웅. 대미언 샤젤 영화를 보고 든 생각]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=2664</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2023/damienchazelle/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T14:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대미언 샤젤의 차기작에는 틀림없이 교통사고 장면이 나올 것이다, 라고 단언할 수는 없다. 하지만 크고 작은 접촉 사고는 그의 필모그래피에서 확실히 눈에 띄는 클리셰 중 하나이다. 예컨대 [위플래쉬]에서 앤드류는 교통 사고 당한다. [바빌론]의 넬리는 첫 등장과 퇴장 모두 접촉 사고를 수반한다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 6.4.3 (and 6.3.13) released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937885/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937885/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:28:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.4.3 stable kernel has been released;
it contains a handful of fixes, mostly for problems associated with the per-VMA locking code.  Anybody running 6.4
probably wants this update.

Note that there is a much larger 6.3.13
update going through a longer-than-usual review process that should show up
soon.

Update: 6.3.13 is now out.  Note
that this is the last 6.3.x update.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FlowForge wants to bring a developer mindset to the IIoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12631</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/flowforge-wants-to-bring-a-developer-mindset-to-the-iiot/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T13:00:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my July 07, 2023 newsletter. You can sign up for the newsletter here.  For years I’ve watched mentions of the Node-RED open source programming language proliferate in industrial environments. For those unfamiliar with Node-RED, it’s a way to wire together devices, web services, and application programming interfaces (APIs) in […]
The post FlowForge wants to bring a developer mindset to the IIoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE to create a fork of RHEL]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937863/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937863/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:57:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE has announced
that it is getting into the business of creating RHEL clones and investing
$10 million in the project.


	SUSE remains fully committed to investing in its highly regarded
	Linux solutions such as SLE and openSUSE that countless satisfied
	enterprise customers and the community rely on. At the same time,
	it acknowledges that enterprises and the open source community
	deserve choice and freedom from vendor lock-in. SUSE has a long
	history in empowering and supporting users with mixed Linux
	environments.

	SUSE is committed to working with the open source community to
	develop a long-term, enduring compatible alternative for RHEL and
	CentOS users. SUSE plans to contribute this project to an open
	source foundation, which will provide ongoing free access to
	alternative source code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937879/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937879/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T12:55:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (mediawiki and node-tough-cookie), Red Hat (bind, kernel, kpatch-patch, and python38:3.8, python38-devel:3.8), SUSE (kernel, nextcloud-desktop, and python-tornado), and Ubuntu (dwarves-dfsg and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four key features every automotive SoC design needs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479860</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/four-key-features-every-automotive-soc-design-needs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T11:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designers must ensure that their designs meet requirements for vehicles that are increasingly smarter yet dependable for the duration of their long lifespans. Vehicles can...
The post Four key features every automotive SoC design needs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alessandra Nardi and Uyen Tran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만 삭스, 생성 AI로 새운 단계 진입한 엔비디아 목표주가를 440달러에서 495달러로 상향 조정]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591187</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591187/%ec%83%88%eb%a1%9c%ec%9a%b4-%eb%8b%a8%ea%b3%84-%ec%a7%84%ec%9d%b8%ed%95%9c-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:34:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[바클레이즈, 테슬라 대안 가능성 주목, 리비안 목표주가를 22달러에서 30달러로 상향 조정]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591184</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591184/%eb%a6%ac%eb%b0%94%ec%95%88-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%eb%8c%80%ec%95%88"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:29:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA, 아마존 프라임데이 총매출액은 120억 달러(12% 증가) 에상]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591181</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591181/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ed%94%84%eb%9d%bc%ec%9e%84%eb%8d%b0%ec%9d%b4"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T09:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy a MSSQL database using Ansible Vault]]></title>
        <id>3d92a4ae-f9d6-4a0d-8f2b-0f9fe1975694</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/11/how-deploy-mssql-database-using-ansible-vault"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying and configuring a database can be a challenging task, especially when sensitive data such as passwords and API keys are involved. However, by using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform and Ansible Vault, we can streamline the process and ensure that our data is secure. In this article, we will explore how to configure and deploy a Microsoft SQL database using Ansible Vault, an Ansible Automation Platform feature.
We will walk you through the process, step-by-step, so that you can easily follow along and try it for yourself. By the end of this article, you will have a solid understanding of how to use Ansible Vault to deploy a secure database, making your deployment process more efficient and secure.
Before you begin, make sure to download and install Ansible Automation Platform, a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Deepankar Jain</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비례대표제가 필요 없다는 당신에게]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92965</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92965"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T06:02:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 5월에 국회 정치개혁특별위원회가 실시한 선거제도 공론조사 결과 참여자들의 숙의 전후 입장이 가장 드라마틱하게 변화한 문항은 비례대표 확대에 관한 것이었다. 숙의 전에는 시민참여단 응답자 중 27%만이 국회의원 비례대표를 더 늘여야 한다고 응답했지만, 숙의 후에는 그 비율이 70%로 약 43% 포인트가 늘어난 것으로 조사되었다. 비례대표에 관심 없는 정치권과 유권자들 그러나 이러한 공론조사 결과에도 불구하고 정치권은 최근...
The post 비례대표제가 필요 없다는 당신에게 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canon PowerShoot ELPH 300 HS 짧은 사용기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/canon-elph-300-hs/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/canon-elph-300-hs/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T05:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[데이터로 보는 인구 감소와 지역 소멸.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92001</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92001"/>
        <updated>2023-07-11T03:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국은 세계 어느 나라도 경험하지 못한 인구 절벽의 구간에 진입하고 있다. 문제는 모두가 안다. 한국의 합계출산율이 지난해 0.78명까지 떨어진 걸 두고 미국의 CNN은 “한국 정부가 지난 16년 동안 인구 감소의 대책으로 2000억 달러 이상을 썼지만 효과가 없었다”고 평가했다. AP통신은 “우울한 고용 시장의 불확실성, 값비싼 주택, 성별 및 사회적 불평등, 낮은 수준의 사회적 이동성, 잔인하게 경쟁적인...
The post 데이터로 보는 인구 감소와 지역 소멸. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “나한테 불리한데 왜 그래야 하지?”를 반박할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76913</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/10/npsp_nothavingkids/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_nothavingkids"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 17일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 세계적인 지정학 전략가인 피터 자이한은 자신의 네 번째 책 ‘붕괴하는 세계와 인구학’에서 인류의 미래를 매우 어둡게 예견합니다. 그가 사용하는 논리는 두 가지입니다. 하나는 미국 주도의 세계 질서가 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“선택할 수 있다고 생각하니 삶을 버티게 됐다.”: 슬로우레터 7월11일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92888</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92888"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:08:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“김건희 고속도로는 민간 용역업체 제안.” 과학을 신봉하는 조선일보에 빠진 이야기. 엘리엇 취소 소송, 삼성이 원한다. 조국과 추미애 신당 창당설. 원전 역주행. 집값 49주째 하락, 통계가 이상하다고? “라면플레이션은 담합 맞지만 직접 압박하는 건 하수.” 해법과 대안. 빨간불 잔여 시간 표시 신호등, 교통사고 67% 줄인다. “선택할 수 있다고 생각하니 삶을 버티게 됐다.” 간호사 수 늘렸더니 나타난 변화....
The post “선택할 수 있다고 생각하니 삶을 버티게 됐다.”: 슬로우레터 7월11일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[먼저 도착한 노란봉투법: 현대차 쟁의행위 손배청구 판결 (2023.6.)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92874</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92874"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T22:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[광장에 나온 판결] 현대차노조 쟁의행위 손해배상청구 소송에서 주체별로 다르게 책임지워야 한다는 대법원 판결에 관한 비평 지난 6. 15. 대법원 제3부(주심 노정희 대법관)는 최근 노동계와 시민사회가 함께 가열차게 추진하고 있는 노동조합 및 노동쟁의조정법(이하 “노동조합법”) 제2조와 제3조의 개정운동에 커다란 뒷배가 될 만한 판결을 내어놓았다. 노동쟁의에 참여한 조합원에게 가혹한 손해배상액을 청구하고 가처분으로 그들의 삶을 옥죄었던 사업자들이 더는 법의...
The post 먼저 도착한 노란봉투법: 현대차 쟁의행위 손배청구 판결 (2023.6.) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MediaPipe: Enhancing Virtual Humans to be more realistic]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/mediapipe-enhancing-virtual-humans-to-be-more-realistic.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/mediapipe-enhancing-virtual-humans-to-be-more-realistic.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T21:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A guest post by the XR Development team at KDDI & Alpha-U






Please note that the information, uses, and applications expressed in the below post are solely those of our guest author, KDDI.


KDDI is integrating text-to-speech & Cloud Rendering to virtual human ‘Metako’ 



VTubers, or virtual YouTubers, are online entertainers who use a virtual avatar generated using computer graphics. This digital trend originated in Japan in the mid-2010s, and has become an international online phenomenon. A majority of VTubers are English and Japanese-speaking YouTubers or live streamers who use avatar designs.
KDDI, a telecommunications operator in Japan with over 40 million customers, wanted to experiment with various technologies built on its 5G network but found that getting accurate movements a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Public Key Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479855</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/understanding-public-key-infrastructure/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T21:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Public Key Infrastructure (PKI) offers a framework that ensures secure and trustworthy exchange of data over an unreliable medium. One of the earliest and still...
The post Understanding Public Key Infrastructure appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Uzair Ghole</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don&apos;t &quot;Think of the Internet!&quot;]]></title>
        <id>3606023</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3606023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:51:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘부모 찬스’ 그 자체인 기여입학제가 유지되는 이유 그리고 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77340</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/10/npsp_scotuslegacyadmission/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_scotuslegacyadmission"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난달 말 미국 대법원이 회기 마지막에 내린 굵직굵직한 판결 가운데 가장 많이 회자하는 판결이 바로 수십 년 된 소수자 우대 정책에 내린 위헌 판결일 겁니다. 그런 가운데 소수자 우대 정책보다 더 큰 문제가 흔히 “기여입학제(legacy admissions)”로 불리는 제도라는 지적도 많이 나오고 있습니다. 대법원의 소수자 우대 정책 폐지의 문제를 지적한 칼럼을 번역하고, 기여입학제에 관한 설명을 덧붙였습니다. 전문 번역: 소수자 우대 정책 철폐는 시작에 불과하다 해설: ‘부모 찬스’ 그 자체인 기여입학제가 유지되는 이유 그리고 전망]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet the students using Google technologies to address the UN’s sustainability goals around the globe]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/meet-students-using-google-technologies.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/meet-students-using-google-technologies.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Rachel Francois, Global Program Manager, Google Developer Student Clubs








Every year, university students who are members of Google Developer Student Clubs around the world are invited to create innovative solutions for real-world problems as part of the Solution Challenge. Participating students use Google products and platforms like Android, Firebase, TensorFlow, Google Cloud, and Flutter to build solutions for one or more of the United Nations’ 17 Sustainable Development Goals, which promote employment for all, economic growth, and climate action, to name a few. Agreed upon in 2015 by all 193 United Nations Member States, the goals aim to end poverty, ensure prosperity, and protect the planet by 2030.
On Demo Day, August 3, live on YouTube, the final 10 teams of the 2023…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.5 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937006/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937006/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:52:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds released
6.5-rc1 and closed the merge window for this development cycle on
July 9.  By that point, 11,730 non-merge changesets had been pulled
into the mainline for 6.5; over 7,700 of those were pulled after
the first-half merge-window summary was
written.  The second half of the merge window saw a lot of code coming into
the mainline and a long list of significant changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937803/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937803/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T14:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr, fusiondirectory, ocsinventory-server, php-cas, and thunderbird), Fedora (dav1d, perl-CPAN, and yt-dlp), Red Hat (python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (prometheus-ha_cluster_exporter and prometheus-sap_host_exporter), and Ubuntu (ghostscript, linux-azure, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, and ruby-doorkeeper).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[As the industrial IoT looks more like IT, security must change]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12628</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/as-the-industrial-iot-looks-more-like-it-security-must-change/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T13:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my July 07, 2023 newsletter. You can sign up for the newsletter here.  As tensions rise between the U.S. and China and Russia continues sponsoring cybersecurity attacks around the globe, it’s clear cybersecurity is never going back to being a niche issue CEOs and boards can foist off to a CSO or IT […]
The post As the industrial IoT looks more like IT, security must change appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware Pioneers Max 2023: a spotlight on AI hardware and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479843</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/hardware-pioneers-max-2023-a-spotlight-on-ai-hardware-and-security/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:44:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Hardware Pioneers Max 2023 exhibition and conference returns to London again this year on 13 July 2023, with a focus on AI hardware, connected devices (IoT), and security.
The post Hardware Pioneers Max 2023: a spotlight on AI hardware and security appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SVE and SVE2 enablement in SIMD library]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:3c92171a-0169-4a74-a73a-615fce235c1e</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/sve-sve2-enablement-in-simd-library"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog describes how to add Arm Scalable Vector Extension (SVE) support to a SIMD library. It also introduces SVE features and programming tips.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yibo Cai</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 expert tips for writing embedded software with ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479837</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/7-expert-tips-for-writing-embedded-software-with-chatgpt/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T11:15:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of LLMs will dramatically affect how we design embedded systems in the future. That future might not be here yet, but it may...
The post 7 expert tips for writing embedded software with ChatGPT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트위터 탈출 버튼! – ‘도둑맞은 집중력’ (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92846</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92846"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T08:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[분명 검색해서 찾을 정보가 있었다. 폰을 열었더니 카톡에 새 알림이 있다. 친구가 링크한 글로 넘어갔다. 꼬리를 물고 이어지는 뉴스 좀 보던 중 텔레그램으로 일정 조율 메시지가 왔다. 캘린더 보는데 인스타그램 알림이 떴다. 오, 친구가 가본 식당 좋아요. 백숙 먹고 싶은데 마트에 닭고기 할인 없나? 지난번 토마토 괜찮았는데 메이커스에서 재주문해야지? 페북 답글 올라왔네? 그런데 내가 왜...
The post 트위터 탈출 버튼! – ‘도둑맞은 집중력’ (2023) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automate edge device onboarding with Ansible FDO collection]]></title>
        <id>06abb28b-0e0b-4db7-ad85-71ea4eed991c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/10/automate-edge-device-onboarding-ansible-fdo-collection"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding devices at the edge differs from doing so in a data center and presents some unique challenges. Among other requirements, the device onboarding process must:
Be secure and reduce the risk of a malicious party tempering with a device or a rogue device being connected to the system.
Minimize manual intervention in order to make the process cheaper, faster, more scalable, and more secure. A zero-touch or low-touch approach also allows personnel without specialized skills to onboard devices.
The FIDO Device Onboard (FDO) specification addresses both of these requirements. Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) offers FDO packages starting with version 8.6, based on the Fedora IoT implementation of FDO. You can follow How to onboard edge devices at scale with FDO and Linux to set up an FDO …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vitaliy Emporopulo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/10, BofA, 구글 검색 점유율과 트래픽이 유지되고 있다고 평가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591174</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591174/%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80-%ea%b2%80%ec%83%89-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T06:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/10, 에버코어 ISI, 2027년까지 애플 서비스 매출 두자릿수 성장 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591172</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591172/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%84%9c%eb%b9%84%ec%8a%a4-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T06:43:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/10, 웨드부시, 2024년 초 마이크로소프트 시가총액 3조 달러 클럽 가입 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591170</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591170/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%9c%ec%86%8c%ed%94%84%ed%8a%b8-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%9d%ec%95%a1"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T06:39:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘5·18 꼬마상주’ 찍은 로숑과 쇼벨: KBS광주가 증명한 수신료의 가치]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92829</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92829"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T06:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[2023년 6월] 5·18 43년 특별기획 KBS광주 ‘1980, 로숑과 쇼벨’ 제작진을 만나다 송강호 배우 주연의 ‘천만 영화’ [택시운전사] (2017)는 5·18민주화운동의 진실을 세계에 알린 독일 외신기자 위르겐 힌츠페터 이야기를 담았다. 힌츠페터는 2003년 KBS 1TV에서 방영된 [KBS 일요스페셜] ‘80년 5월, 푸른 눈의 목격자’를 통해 대중에 알려졌는데, 이후 많은 이들이 5·18을 기록한 외신기자로 기억하고 있다. 1980년 5월, 광주에 있던...
The post ‘5·18 꼬마상주’ 찍은 로숑과 쇼벨: KBS광주가 증명한 수신료의 가치 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can we drive artificial intelligence’s exponential growth sustainably?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479821</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/can-we-drive-artificial-intelligences-exponential-growth-sustainably/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T04:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The scale of growth of AI is drawing increasing concern about factors such as cost and the environmental impact of huge machine learning technologies. Optical could be an answer to addressing this.
The post Can we drive artificial intelligence’s exponential growth sustainably? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Weil</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay | Meet the people creating apps and games in Japan]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/weareplay-meet-people-creating-apps-and-games-in-japan.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/weareplay-meet-people-creating-apps-and-games-in-japan.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Leticia Lago, Developer Marketing






#WeArePlay is on a virtual world tour: starting first with the U.S. last summer by spotlighting the stories of app and game founders from every state, then visiting India sharing stories from across the country, and more recently visiting Europe by sharing stories from countries across the region. 
Today, we’re continuing our tour with one more stop: Japan. From a snowboarding app made by a paralympian, to a game inspired by the enchanting landmarks of Gifu. Discover the people growing apps and games businesses on Google Play.
We’re starting with stories from Chubu, Chugoku & Shikoku and Kinki, with more following throughout the year. Let’s explore some of the stories from across these 3 regions. 



Takao Hayashi, founder of Ateam Entertai…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인어공주, 디즈니의 해석본은 어떻게 추억의 원본이 되었는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92749</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92749"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T01:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. 슬로우뉴스 창간 동인 캡콜드(펜실베이니아주립대학교 김낙호 교수) 님은 만화 덕후이자 미디어 전문가로 연구 분야는 언론학입니다. 캡콜드 님께 알쏭달쏭한 사회적 논란과 지적 이슈에 관해 묻고, 그 답변을 정리합니다. 첫 번째 콜드케이스는 인어공주와 인종차별 그리고 PC(정치적 올바름)에 관한 이슈입니다. 가독성을 고려해 나눠서 올립니다. 캡콜드 님과의 대화는...
The post 인어공주, 디즈니의 해석본은 어떻게 추억의 원본이 되었는가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/10, 주요 기업 주가를 보는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591166</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591166/7-10-%ec%a3%bc%ec%9a%94-%ea%b8%b0%ec%97%85-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80%eb%a5%bc-%eb%b3%b4%eb%8a%94-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%9c%ec%84%a0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T01:56:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 미국만들기]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223151604983</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223151604983"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:16:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[스피박에 대한 임옥희의 해설서를 읽으면서 로티의 <미국만들기>가 생각났다. 쉽게 찾을 수 있도록 책꽂이에서 앞 쪽으로 약간 뽑아 놓았는데, 책이 없다. 몇 시간 동안 뒤져보아도 책을 찾을 수 없다. 내가 자주 가는 동네 도서관 두 곳 모두에 책이 없다. 이런 경우가 인내심이 바닥에 이르는 경우이다. 책이 나오면 찢어버리리라. 그런데 이런 단호한 결심 이후에 늘 그렇듯이 우연하게 책이 발견된다. 따로 읽으려고 주변에 두었는데 두꺼운 책들에 눌려 보이지 않았던 것이다. 그런데 이 책의 번역이 임옥희이다. 흥미롭다. 누구 글인지 모르겠지만 책 속표지에 다음과 같은 글이 있다. <과거 미국이 저지른 죄악이 미래를 위한 해.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finite State Machine with std::variant - Vending Machine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2023/finite-state-machines-variant-vending-cpp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2023/finite-state-machines-variant-vending-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last article, we discussed Finite State Machines based on std::variant and some cool C++17 techniques. Today I want to go further and show you an example of a Vending Machine implementation.
Finite State Machine with std::variant - C++ Stories


States & Events 
  




     
    


Here’s a basic diagram that illustrates how the machine is going to work:

Following the model from the last article, each state and the event will be a separate small structure. Later we can “pack” them into std::variant.
Here are the states:
namespace state {
    struct Idle { };
    struct AmountEntered { int amount{ 0 }; int availableChange{ 0 }; };
    struct ItemSelected { std::string item; int availableChange{ 0 }; };
    struct ChangeDispensed { int change{ 0 }; };
}

using VendingState = std::vari…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.5-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937732/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937732/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T23:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.5-rc1 and closed the
merge window for this release.


	Anyway, none of it looks hugely unusual. The biggest single mention
	probably goes to what wasn't merged, with the bcachefs pull request
	resulting in a long thread (we didn't hit a hundred emails yet, but
	it's not far away).


The curious can read that long
thread in the list archives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bellegram, a wireless DIY doorbell that sends you a Telegram message]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1540.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1540.php"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T23:23:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This nice button uses the tiny M5 STAMP PICO and Cesanta's Mongoose as an HTTPS client to POST to the Telegram Bot API and send a message; the code is completely written in C. To try it, besides small fingers, you'll need to have a Wi-Fi network up and running and of course a Telegram account.



Hardware
For this demo there is no additional hardware needed, we just use the <a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기시다 만나는 윤석열, 오염수 이야기 할까 안 할까: 슬로우레터 7월10일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92786</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92786"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T22:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정치 생명 건다더니 출구 전략 찾는다. 그래서 종점은 어디로? 후쿠시마 오염수, 윤석열의 오랜 침묵. 갈등과 논란. 난민 7만 명, 네덜란드의 고민. 오염수 논란 같은 아스파탐 막걸리 논쟁. 한국 상속세가 OECD 최고? 통계 왜곡이다. 오늘의 TMI. 잠 적게 자는 나라 1위가 한국. “저는 종목 추천을 하지 않습니다.” 김봉현 탈옥 사례금이 40억 원이었다. 넷플릭스가 제작비를 깎기 시작했다....
The post 기시다 만나는 윤석열, 오염수 이야기 할까 안 할까: 슬로우레터 7월10일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The lifetime of performance coding issues]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7992</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/07/09/the-lifetime-of-performance-coding-issues/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-09T21:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coding activities that a developer might spend time on include: adding new functionality, fixing a reported fault, or fiddling with existing code with the intent of making it ‘better’ in some sense (which these days goes by the catch-all name of refactoring). Improving performance, e.g., changing software to use less cpu/memory is considered, by developers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ungrammar in Go and resilient parsing]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/ungrammar-in-go-and-resilient-parsing/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/ungrammar-in-go-and-resilient-parsing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T13:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It won't be news to the readers of this blog that I have <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/eliben/pycparser">some interest</a> in
<a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/tag/compilation">compiler</a>
<a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/tag/recursive-descent-parsing">front-ends</a>.
So when I heard about a new(-ish) DSL for
<a class="reference external" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Parse_tree">concrete syntax trees</a> (CST), I
couldn't resist playing with it a bit.</p>
<p><a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/rust-analyzer/ungrammar/tree/master">Ungrammar</a> is used
in <tt class="docutils literal"><span class="pre">rust-analyzer</span></tt> to define and access a …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기후변화로 더욱 부족해진 전기… 뒤집어 접근해보자는 제안]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77329</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/08/npsp_saveelectricity/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_saveelectricity"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T08:15:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기후변화로 매년 여름 폭염이 기승을 부리고 있습니다. 날이 더워지면 너도나도 에어컨을 틀고 전기를 쓸 일이 많아져 전력망에 부담이 가고 정전이 발생하기도 하죠. 텍사스대학교의 마이클 웨버 교수가 폭염이 찾아오는 여름철 정전 사태를 예방하기 위해 필요한 발상의 전환에 대해 칼럼을 썼습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 에너지를 절약해 기후변화의 피해를 줄이기 위해 필요한 또 다른 발상의 전환에 관해서도 정리해 봤습니다. 전문 번역: 여름철 ‘폭염 정전’을 피하려면 발상의 전환이 필요하다 해설: 기후변화로 더욱 부족해진 전기… 뒤집어 접근해보자는 제안]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[씨티, 넷플릭스 신규 구독자 8,200만명 예상하며 넷플릭스 목표 주가를 500달러로 상향 조정]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591164</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591164/%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%98%88%ec%83%81"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T04:17:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만삭스, 주가 하락 대비 포트폴리오 재정비 할 때]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591151</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591151/%ea%b3%a8%eb%93%9c%eb%a7%8c%ec%82%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ed%95%98%eb%9d%bd-%eb%8c%80%eb%b9%84-%ed%8f%ac%ed%8a%b8%ed%8f%b4%eb%a6%ac%ec%98%a4-%ec%9e%ac%ec%a0%95%eb%b9%84-%ed%95%a0-%eb%95%8c"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T02:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고참 부장 분투기, 직장 말년 직장 생활 분투기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591149</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591149/%ea%b3%a0%ec%b0%b8-%eb%b6%80%ec%9e%a5-%eb%b6%84%ed%88%ac%ea%b8%b0"/>
        <updated>2023-07-08T02:21:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[칸트 대 비트겐슈타인 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223150155123</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223150155123"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T23:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[수잔 프롬은 비트겐슈타인과 칸트에 대한 선행 연구 문헌들을 자세하게 살펴본 후, 이들이 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 공통점에 치중했다고 지적한다. 반면에 자신은 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 차이점에 주목하겠다고 주장한다. <비트겐슈타인과 칸트 사이의 차이는 이제까지의 2차 문헌들이 간과했고 공통성만 지적하느라 이념이 없어 전혀 볼 수 없었던 점에서 극히 뚜렷해진다. 정신적 작용의 문제가 바로 그것이다. 이 문제야말로 칸트에 관한 비트겐슈타인 비판의 비로소 개시될 수 있는 토대가 된다.> 수잔 프롬에 의하면 적어도 정신적 작용, 심적 작용의 문제에서 칸트와 비트겐슈타인의 차이가 아주 분명하다. 도대체 어떤 차이가 있는 것.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for July 7, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12623</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-july-7-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T19:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I would love for this to be about smart building devices: Amazon’s David Limp has posted a teaser on LinkedIn asking folks to mark their calendars for September 20, when the Devices & Services team will “share a bit more of what we’ve been working on.” He says the event will happen at Amazon’s HQ2 in Virginia, […]
The post IoT news of the week for July 7, 2023 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Going Rogue (Digital Antiquarian)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937631/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937631/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T18:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After an initial foray into the ways that open-source software has failed
to live up to its early hype,
this Digital
Antiquarian article covers the history of rogue-like games in great
detail.


	This brings us back around to a statement I made at the outset:
	that roguelikes are the exception that proves the rule of
	open-source game development — and just possibly of open-source
	software development in general. The cast of thousands who
	contribute to them do so in order to make exactly the games that
	they want to play, which in the abstract is the best of all
	possible reasons to make a game. The experience they end up with
	is, unsurprisingly, much like high-wire programming at its most
	advanced, presenting players with an immense, multi-faceted system
	to be explored and mastered.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A pair of workqueue improvements]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937416/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937416/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T14:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years, the kernel has developed a number of deferred-execution
mechanisms to take care of work that cannot be done immediately.  For many
(or most) needs, the workqueue
subsystem is the tool that developers reach for first.  Workqueues
took their current form over a dozen years
ago, but that does not mean that there are not improvements to be made.
Two sets of patches from Tejun Heo show the pressures being felt by the
workqueue subsystem and the solutions that are being tried — with varying
degrees of success.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937616/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937616/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T13:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (debian-archive-keyring, libusrsctp, nsis, ruby-redcloth, and webkit2gtk), Fedora (firefox), Mageia (apache-ivy, cups, curaengine, glances, golang, keepass, libreoffice, minidlna, nodejs, opensc, perl-DBD-SQLite, python-setuptools, python-wheel, skopeo/buildah/podman, systemd, testng, and webkit2), SUSE (bind), and Ubuntu (Gerbv, golang-websocket, linux-gke, linux-intel-iotg, and linux-oem-5.17).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable user-managed networking with ZTP]]></title>
        <id>aa148867-32ad-4620-a1b5-4de2345f0f4d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/07/enable-user-managed-networking-ztp"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article demonstrates how to configure user-managed networking via SiteConfig using the zero-touch provisioning (ZTP) deployment model. ZTP automates the steps required to configure new network devices and perform upgrades using a network switch feature.
This tutorial uses Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes with the Red Hat OpenShift Assisted Installer and Git-stored SiteConfig.
Configure the cluster network
Before installing Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform on-premise with Assisted Installer, we must configure the cluster network.
There are two options for configuring cluster networks: One is using cluster-managed networking, and the other is user-managed networking.
We select user-managed networking when we want to use a third-party vendor for configuring external…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Wuxin Zeng</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 순수이성비판 강의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223149279876</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223149279876"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T01:03:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개인적으로 재판의 <머리말>은 매우 중요한 텍스트라고 생각한다. 칸트의 철학적 생각이 잘 나타나 있는 텍스트라고 할 수 있다. 안전한 길을 가는 학문과 그렇지 않은 학문이 있다. (이미 우리가 초판의 <머리말>을 읽었기 때문에 학문의 안전한 길을 가지 않는 것이 형이상학임을 알 수 있다.) 논리학은 매우 안전한 학문이다. 이 논리학은 아리스토텔레스 이후 완결되고 완성된 것으로 보인다. (그러나 아리스토텔레스 논리학과 다른 현대 논리학이 나온다. 적어도 이 점에서 칸트가 지적했듯이 논리학이 완결되고 완성되지 않았다. 그럼에도 불구하고) 논리학에 심리학의 장, 형이상학적 장, 인간학적 장을 집어넣어 논리학을 확.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[스레드, 저커버그가 머스크에게 크게 한 방 먹였다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92616</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92616"/>
        <updated>2023-07-07T00:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[싸움구경 만큼 재밌는 게 없다. 일론 머스크(테슬라 CEO)와 마크 저커버그(메타 CEO)가 한판 붙겠다고 해서 떠들썩했는데 저커버그가 먼저 크게 한 방을 먹였다. 인스타그램이 내놓은 스레드(Threads)는 정확하게 트위터 시장을 공략하고 있는데 기세가 심상치 않다. 4시간 만에 500만 명, 7시간 만에 1000만 명, 16시간 만에 3000만 명을 넘어섰다. 5일 동안 1000만 다운로드를 기록한 챗GPT를 따라잡았다. (‘쓰레즈’가 좀 더...
The post 스레드, 저커버그가 머스크에게 크게 한 방 먹였다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 이 문제는 영영 풀지 못할 것이다, 이래도 되나?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76879</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/06/npsp_usgunviolence/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_usgunviolence"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 15일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 미국에 사는 외국인에게 좀처럼 적응이 안 되는, 가장 이해할 수 없는 미국 문화를 꼽아보라 하면, 대부분 첫손에 총기 문화를 꼽을 겁니다. 미국 사람이 가지고 있는 총기의 숫자는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora considers "privacy-preserving" telemetry]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937528/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937528/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:56:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fedora project is considering a
Fedora 40 change proposal to add limited, opt-out telemetry to the
workstation edition.  The proposal is detailed; it is clear that the
developers involved understand that this will be a hard sell in that
community.


	We believe an open source community can ethically collect limited
	aggregate data on how its software is used without involving big
	data companies or building creepy tracking profiles that are not in
	the best interests of users. Users will have the option to disable
	data upload before any data is sent for the first time. Our service
	will be operated by Fedora on Fedora infrastructure, and will not
	depend on Google Analytics or any other controversial third-party
	services. And in contrast to proprietary software operating
	systems, you can redirect the data collection to your own private
	metrics server instead of Fedora's to see precisely what data is
	being collected from you, because the server components are open
	source too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[정치생명 건다는 원희룡, 빼박 증거가 있다: 슬로우레터 7월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92604</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92604"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T22:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 땅 논란 고속도로 전면 백지화. 정치 생명 건다는 원희룡은 알고 있었다. “TV 수신료 안 내도 전기 안 끊는다.” 새마을금고가 위험하다. 죽은 것으로 확인된 유령 아기, 23명으로 늘었다. 윤석열 검찰총장 시절 특활비 월 4억 썼다. 해법과 대안. 채용과 승진 심사에 AI 쓰면 결과 공개해야. 한 부모 양육 지원은 20만 원, 보육원은 200만 원. 바닷속 금...
The post 정치생명 건다는 원희룡, 빼박 증거가 있다: 슬로우레터 7월7일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers Share How They Built Their Careers: From Machine Learning to Cloud]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/developers-share-how-they-built-their-careers-from-machine-learning-to-cloud.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/07/developers-share-how-they-built-their-careers-from-machine-learning-to-cloud.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T18:30:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lyanne Alfaro, DevRel Program Manager, Google Developer Studio





Google Developer Student Club Alums Reflect On Their Journey To Google Developer Experts
Developer Journey is a monthly series highlighting diverse and global developers sharing relatable challenges, opportunities, and wins in their journey. Every month, we will spotlight developers around the world, the Google tools they leverage, and the kind of products they are building. 
This month, we spoke with several Google Developer Experts to learn more about their path from being Google Developer Student Clubs leads to connoisseurs of their craft. 
Suvaditya Mukherjee






Mumbai, Maharashtra, India
Google Developer Expert, Machine Learning
GDSC Mukesh Patel School of Technology, Management and Engineering - Mumbai L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] BPF iterators for filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937326/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937326/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T15:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the first of two combined BPF and filesystem sessions at the
2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem,
Memory-Management and BPF Summit, Hou Tao introduced his BPF iterators
for filesystem information.  Iterators for
BPF are a relatively recent addition to the BPF landscape; they help
BPF programs step through kernel data structures in a loop-like manner, but
without running afoul of the BPF verifier, which is notoriously hard to
convince about loops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Large folios for anonymous memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937239/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937239/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T13:52:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transition to folios has transformed
the memory-management subsystem in a number of ways, but has also resulted
in a lot of code churn that has not been welcomed by all developers.  As
this work proceeds, though, some of the benefits from it are beginning to
become clear.  One example may well be in the handling of anonymous memory,
as can be seen in a pair of patch sets from Ryan Roberts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937481/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937481/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T13:50:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (golang-yaml.v2, kernel, and mediawiki), Fedora (kernel and picocli), SUSE (bind and python-sqlparse), and Ubuntu (cpdb-libs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 마이크로소프트 투자의견과 마이크로소프트 주가 전망(7/7 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591141</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591141/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%9c%ec%86%8c%ed%94%84%ed%8a%b8-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%9c%ec%86%8c%ed%94%84%ed%8a%b8-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T13:44:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: The theme of this show is wearables]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12617</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-the-theme-of-this-show-is-wearables/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T13:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s podcast focuses on wearables, from hearing aids to mixed reality headsets. We start the show talking about the potential future of Apple AirPods as a hearing aid or an additional health-focused wearable. And while on the topic of Apple, we mention that the badges on your smart home devices will say the device […]
The post Podcast: The theme of this show is wearables appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희, 언론과 함께 춤을: 홍보엔 적극, 고속도로 노선 변경 의혹엔 침묵]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92581</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92581"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T10:16:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[국토교통부가 추진 중인 서울-양평 고속도로 노선이 논란입니다. 2017년 계획 시작 단계는 물론 2년 전 예비타당성 조사에서도 양평군 ‘양서면’을 종점으로 진행 중이던 노선이 돌연 ‘강상면’으로 변경돼 추진된 것인데요. 윤석열 대통령 부인 김건희 여사 일가가 강상면 일대에 땅을 보유하고 있다는 사실이 알려지자 특혜 논란으로 번지고 있습니다. 원희룡 국토부 장관은 뒤늦게 ‘노선 변경을 결정한 적 없다’고 해명하며 원점...
The post 김건희, 언론과 함께 춤을: 홍보엔 적극, 고속도로 노선 변경 의혹엔 침묵 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Debezium SMT with Groovy to filter routing events]]></title>
        <id>4b98c474-c94a-42a4-a72b-dd804d05c761</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/06/how-use-debezium-smt-groovy-filter-routing-events"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After configuring my Kafka Connect Image with Debezium, demonstrated in Hugo Guerrero's article Improve your Kafka Connect builds of Debezium, I needed to configure a type of filter to only bring certain events from the database table to my topics. I was able to do this using Debezium SMT with Groovy.
What is Debezium SMT?
Debezium SMT (single message transform) is a filter feature provided by Debezium that is used to process only records that you find relevant. To do that, you need to include plugins the implementations of the JSR223 API (Scripting for the Java Platform) inside your Kafka Connect Image.
Note that Debezium does not come with an JSR 223 implementation, so you will need to provide the libs to use this feature. We will use the Groovy implementation of JSR 223, so you can down…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Diego Neves</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[느낌을 측정할 수 있다면 (ft. 다윈과 스키너 비판)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92534</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92534"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T04:51:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 이효석 박사 추천 좋은 책 이야기, 첫 번째 책 ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ 일곱 번째 마지막 이야기: 우리가 검사한 사람들은 모두 ‘화난’, ‘슬픈’, ‘겁에 질린’ 같은 동일한 감정 단어를 사용해 자신의 느낌을 표현했지만, 그 의미가 언제나 동일하지는 않았다. 몇몇 피험자는 이런 단어를 사용해 매우 섬세한 구별을 했다. 예컨대 그들은 슬픔과 공포를 질적으로 다른 것으로 경험했다....
The post 느낌을 측정할 수 있다면 (ft. 다윈과 스키너 비판) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 6, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936800/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936800/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-06T01:29:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 6, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 전설의 투자자는 왜 ESG에 비판적일까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76840</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/05/npsp_buffettesg/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_buffettesg"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T22:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 10일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. ESG란 환경(Environmental), 사회(Social), 지배구조(Governance)의 약자로 최근 많은 관심을 받는 기업 평가 기준입니다. 여기서 환경은 탄소 배출 문제와 같이 기후 변화에 대응하는 요소를 포함한 환경 오염과 생태계 파괴 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[피터의 원리, 무능할 때까지 승진한다는 비극: 슬로우레터 7월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92496</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92496"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T22:07:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[수신료 분리 징수, 그렇게 급했나. 97%가 찬성했다는데? 대통령실 “IAEA 보고서 존중”. 지구 역사상 가장 뜨거웠던 하루. 정부가 돈을 안 쓴다. 유인촌이 돌아온다. 호남 민심이 흔들린다. GS건설 부실 공사 논란, 1666가구 전면 재시공. 오늘의 TMI. 대구은행이 전국 은행 된다. 요즘 책값은 1만6800원이 대세. 국회의원 문자 메시지만 51억 원. 감옥에서 받은 2억 원. 실종 신고 하루 340건....
The post 피터의 원리, 무능할 때까지 승진한다는 비극: 슬로우레터 7월6일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with (Apache) NuttX RTOS Part 2 - Looking Inside and Creating Your Customized Image]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1543.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1543.php"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T20:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous article (https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1524.p...) we saw how to run NuttX RTOS using the SIMulator. Today we will see how NuttX's directory tree is organized and how to use the menuconfig to enable some applications, including some tricks to search and solve dependencies.

<p style="text-align:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937400/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937400/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T18:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.4.2,
6.3.12,
6.1.38, and
5.15.120
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Improving i_version]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937247/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937247/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T16:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The i_version
field in struct inode
is meant to track changes to the data or metadata of a file.  There are
some problems with the way that
i_version is being handled in the kernel, 
so Jeff Layton led a filesystem session at the
2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem,
Memory-Management and BPF Summit to discuss them and what to do
about them.  For the most part, there are solutions in the works that will
resolve most of the larger issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Always-on listening IP uses just µW of power]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479803</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/always-on-listening-ip-uses-just-%c2%b5w-of-power/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T16:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dolphin Design’s WhisperExtractor advanced mixed-signal architecture IP helps reduce power consumption by up to 99% at system level, enabling an always-on listening function at a power budget of just µW, with a simple 32 kHz clock.
The post Always-on listening IP uses just µW of power appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smart home labels: What works with what?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12604</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/smart-home-labels-what-works-with-what/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T15:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s hard to believe that the Matter standard launched eight months ago at this point. Yes, there are still growing pains for Matter. But at least we’re starting to see smart home devices with the Matter label on them. In fact, we’re seeing new labels on products in 2023, so I thought to share what […]
The post Smart home labels: What works with what? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin C. Tofel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The "StackRot" kernel vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937377/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937377/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:34:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ruihan Li has disclosed
a significant vulnerability introduced into the 6.1 kernel:


	A flaw was found in the handling of stack expansion in the Linux
	kernel 6.1 through 6.4, aka "Stack Rot". The maple tree,
	responsible for managing virtual memory areas, can undergo node
	replacement without properly acquiring the MM write lock, leading
	to use-after-free issues. An unprivileged local user could use this
	flaw to compromise the kernel and escalate their privileges.

	As StackRot is a Linux kernel vulnerability found in the memory
	management subsystem, it affects almost all kernel configurations
	and requires minimal capabilities to trigger. However, it should be
	noted that maple nodes are freed using RCU callbacks, delaying the
	actual memory deallocation until after the RCU grace
	period. Consequently, exploiting this vulnerability is considered
	challenging.


The disclosure contains a detailed description of the problem.  Fixes have
been merged into the
mainline and the 6.4.1, 6.3.11, and 6.1.37
stable kernel updates.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Flexible is CXL's Memory Protection?]]></title>
        <id>3606014</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3606014"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:30:30.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Termux: Linux applications on Android]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936953/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936953/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T14:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Termux is an Android app that
provides a Linux environment and terminal emulator for such devices. Most
command-line software can be used quite easily with Termux, 
and GUI software can be run by installing a few extra apps. It is an excellent
option for Android users who want to run Linux software occasionally on a
device more portable than a laptop but do not want to use a dedicated Linux
phone due to the cost or limitations of such devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LXD moves into Canonical]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937369/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937369/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T13:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LXD container-management system is no longer a part of the linuxcontainers.org project:


	Canonical, the creator and main contributor of the LXD project has
	decided that after over 8 years as part of the Linux Containers
	community, the project would now be better served directly under
	Canonical’s own set of projects.

	While the team behind Linux Containers regrets that decision and
	will be missing LXD as one of its projects, it does respect
	Canonical’s decision and is now in the process of moving the
	project over.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937368/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937368/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T13:51:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (firefox and python-reportlab), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (dnsdist, grpc, protobuf, python-Deprecated, python-PyGithub, python-aiocontextvars, python-avro, python-bcrypt, python-cryptography, python- cryptography-vectors, python-google-api-core, pyt, kernel, kubernetes1.18, libdwarf, python311, qt6-base, rmt-server, and virtualbox), and Ubuntu (containerd, firefox, and python-django).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부자들의 일탈인가, 모험가의 비극일까… 잠수정 사고를 바라보는 두 가지 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77302</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/05/npsp_titanregulation/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_titanregulation"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T13:20:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난달 북대서양 수심 4km 아래 타이타닉호의 잔해를 향해 잠수하다가 내파된 잠수정 타이탄호를 둘러싸고 많은 이야기가 나왔습니다. 특히 타이탄호를 책임진 조종사가 규제를 거추장스러운 것으로 여기며 안전 점검을 소홀히 해왔다는 사실이 드러나자, 해당 회사 오션게이트뿐 아니라 규제를 성장과 혁신을 방해하기만 하는 것으로 매도하는 견해에 대해서도 비판의 화살이 쏠렸습니다. 전문 번역: ‘타이타닉 관광’ 잠수정 타이탄호의 운명을 결정지은 속설 해설: 부자들의 일탈인가, 모험가의 비극일까… 잠수정 사고를 바라보는 두 가지 시선]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 테슬라 판매량을 보는 월가의 시선, 기대 이상 관건은 자동차 마진]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591131</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591131/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T10:17:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세일즈포스의 생성형 AI 기능: 7개 주요 모델별 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92458</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92458"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T09:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[그랜드뷰 리서치의 최신 보고서에 따르면 전 세계 클라우드 AI 시장 규모는 2030년까지 6,476억 달러에 달할 것으로 예상되며, 2023년부터 2030년까지 39.6%의 연평균 성장률을 기록할 것으로 전망한다. 지능형 가상 비서에 대한 수요, 고객 서비스 향상을 위한 AI 도입, 빅 데이터의 성장이 시장의 성장을 이끄는 주요 요인이다. 또한, 많은 대기업이 투자 및 확장을 통해 시장 성장을 주도하고 있다....
The post 세일즈포스의 생성형 AI 기능: 7개 주요 모델별 정리 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>씨앗(CEART)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[팬덤정치 시대의 정당: 문제와 해법]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92451</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92451"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T08:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“인간 사회를 지배하는 법칙들 가운데 확실한 한 가지는 참여의 평등한 조건이 확장되는 만큼 참여를 조율하고 조직할 방법과 기술들도 같은 비율로 높아져야 한다는 것이다. 그래야만 사람들은 문명화된 상태로 지낼 수 있다.” 알렉시스 드 토크빌 『미국의 민주주의』 2권 중 정치에 관해서는, 현대를 살아가는 우리들에게 정당은 매우 특별하면서도 유일한 존재다. 현대 사회에서 정당의 역할은 다양한데, 몇 가지 나열하자면...
The post 팬덤정치 시대의 정당: 문제와 해법 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Kafka Cruise Control for cluster optimization]]></title>
        <id>63131296-8036-4e40-a0a8-2ce85ee747af</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/05/how-use-kafka-cruise-control-cluster-optimization"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AMQ streams has recently promoted Cruise Control to the General Availability stage. It optimizes how Apache Kafka distributes the workload to improve performance and health. Often the Kafka clusters are deployed and grow over time, hosting multiple topics. Thanks to its robustness and elasticity reputation, the operations department tends to give it little care, monitoring the key health indicators. But they don’t know how to tune it to face the new workload.
Cruise Control can become a fundamental ally in managing your Kafka clusters and getting the most out of your hardware resources. Plus, with the AMQ streams operator, it’s just a matter of turning a key. This article explains the key principles and how to make practical use of this new exciting capability.
Unbalanced workloads
When a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donato Marrazzo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[뇌, 이야기 만들어 내는 기계]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92390</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92390"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T03:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 이효석 박사 추천 ‘좋은 책’ 이야기, 첫 번째 책 ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ 여섯 번째 이야기: “바로 지금, 당신이 ‘사과’라는 단어를 읽는 바로 그 순간, 당신의 뇌는 마치 사과가 실제로 앞에 있는 것처럼 반응한다. 당신의 뇌는 당신이 과거에 보았고 맛보았던 사과에 관한 지식들을 조합하여 당신의 감각과 운동 부위에 있는 뉴런들의 점화 방식을 바꿈으로써 당신의 머릿속에서...
The post 뇌, 이야기 만들어 내는 기계 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in June]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/june-2023-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/june-2023-roundup"/>
        <updated>2023-07-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
June.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비트겐슈타인과 칸트]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223147232050</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223147232050"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T23:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한의사 선생님이 이제 절대로 공부하지 말고 놀라고 강조한다. 공부와 반대에 있는 것, 즉 지금껏 내가 했던 것과 반대에 있던 것들을 하라고 충고한다. 나보고 사교춤을 배우라고 한다. 그러나 내가 하는 것이 어떤 의미에서 노는 것이다. 물론 그가 생각하는 노는 것과 내용이 다르지만, 나는 나름대로 즐겁게 놀고 있다. 비트겐슈타인과 칸트에 대한 자료를 정리하다가 잊었던 내가 쓴 글을 본다. 그것은 2008년에 쓴 것인데, 카벨과 말콤의 지적에 따라 비트겐슈타인의 전체 철학을 윤리적이고 종교적으로 바라볼 수 있고, 바라보아야 한다는 주장이다. https://blog.naver.com/sellars/100050208992 비트겐슈타인의 윤리 1 https://blog.nav.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[센 척 하는 윤석열, 역대 최약체 정권의 불안이 보인다: 슬로우레터 7월5일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92364</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92364"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T22:00:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[IAEA, “후쿠시마 오염수 방류해도 된다.” IAEA 보고서, 일본 정부에 첨삭 받았나. 미쓰비시가 낼 배상, 한국 정부가 공탁금을 왜 내나. “대통령이 카르텔이란 말에 꽂혀서.” 역전세 대책, 대출 늘린다. 오늘의 TMI. 기여 입학도 없애라. “미국에 희귀 광물 안 판다”, 중국의 뒤끝. 로스쿨 블랙홀. 장마라고 부르는 게 맞나. ‘시성비’ 따진다. 금괴 밀수범에 2조 원 벌금 합헌. 해법과 대안....
The post 센 척 하는 윤석열, 역대 최약체 정권의 불안이 보인다: 슬로우레터 7월5일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brockmeier: Red Hat and the Clone Wars III: The dawn of CentOS]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937317/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937317/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T19:17:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joe "Zonker" Brockmeier has been a part of the Linux community for decades;
he is now using that experience to write a series on "Red Hat and the Clone
Wars".  The first two episodes were Red
Hat and the Clone Wars and A
history of the early 2000s Linux landscape; the latest is The
dawn of CentOS:


	In 2009, the main project admin for CentOS went radio
	silent. CentOS had been spun up in the wild west days of the
	Internet, when it seemed totally fine to let one person hold the
	domain, communications channels, and funds. Oops.

	Folks depending on CentOS suddenly had a Come to Jesus moment. What
	happens if your production systems depend on a project where the
	main admin is AWOL and you have no plan for that?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 115 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937316/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937316/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T19:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
115 of the Firefox browser has been released.  New features include
support for hardware video decoding on Intel GPUs on Linux and a new
"close" option on the tab-manager dropdown.  This release is also the end
of the line for Windows 7 and 8 support, and for macOS 10.12,
10.13, and 10.14 support as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Converting NFSD to use iomap and folios]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936628/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936628/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T14:23:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chuck Lever led a filesystem session at the
2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem,
Memory-Management and BPF Summit on the Linux NFS server, which is also
known as NFSD.  He wanted to talk about converting the network filesystem
to use iomap;  that kind of
conversion
was the topic of the previous session at
the summit.  Beyond that, he wanted to discuss using folios, which has been
a frequent topic at recent LSFMM+BPF gatherings, including this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937292/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937292/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T14:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ghostscript), Fedora (apache-ivy, chromium, golang-github-schollz-croc, golang-github-schollz-mnemonicode, and webkitgtk), SUSE (amazon-ecs-init, dnsdist, libcap, python-tornado, terraform, and xmltooling), and Ubuntu (imagemagick, openldap, php7.4, php8.1, and screen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Particle’s new products adapt to the complex edge]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12593</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/particles-new-products-adapt-to-the-complex-edge/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T13:00:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my June 30, 2023 newsletter. You can sign up for the newsletter here.  First, a disclaimer. Particle is currently a sponsor of the newsletter, but this article was not paid for and represents only my editorial judgement. The company recently held its annual Spectra conference, where it released four […]
The post Particle’s new products adapt to the complex edge appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LittleFS File System with MCU Internal FLASH Memory]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=37672</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/07/04/littlefs-file-system-with-mcu-internal-flash-memory/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T11:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To read and write data on an embedded device, a file system is very useful. LittleFS is a file system optimized for constraint devices. In this article I show, how LittleFS can use the MCU internal flash memory as storage. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지금도 매일 김용균을 보내고 있다: ‘같이 가면 길이 된다’ (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92294</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92294"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T08:09:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“새로운 경제라는 것이 주문만 디지털 최첨단으로 하는 것이고 물품은 죄다 사람들이 몸으로 끌고 지고 나른다… 무슨 혁명이라 하여 흰 연기만 뿜어대는 증기선이 나왔는데 강가에 들어서는 배를 여린 유부녀들이 끌었다. 사람이 석탄이나 말보다 쌌기 때문이다.” 이상헌, 같이 가면 길이 된다, ‘광인일기, 식인의 풍습을 보았다’, 생각의힘: 2023. 중에서 하이테크 시대에 마음이 불편한 이유를 이렇게 정확하게 정리해 준다....
The post 지금도 매일 김용균을 보내고 있다: ‘같이 가면 길이 된다’ (2023) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A developer’s guide to secure coding with FORTIFY_SOURCE]]></title>
        <id>918ec339-c4e6-46d8-90a1-4892a2b0ff47</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/04/developers-guide-secure-coding-fortifysource"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Secure coding is essential to building robust and resilient software that is less susceptible to exploitation by attackers. One way to ensure secure coding is to use a feature called FORTIFY_SOURCE. In this article, we will explore FORTIFY_SOURCE and how it can be used to enhance the security of your code.
What is FORTIFY_SOURCE?
FORTIFY_SOURCE is a feature available in the GNU C Library that provides runtime protection against certain types of security vulnerabilities. Specifically, FORTIFY_SOURCE detects and prevents buffer overflow and formats string vulnerabilities, which are two common types of vulnerabilities that attackers can exploit to take control of a system or steal sensitive data.
How does FORTIFY_SOURCE work?
FORTIFY_SOURCE works by providing enhanced versions of certain C li…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sandipan Roy</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사교육 이권 카르텔 ‘굿판’, 마지막 ‘제물’은 수험생]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92283</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92283"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T03:57:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 대통령은 6월 15일 이주호 부총리 겸 교육부장관의 교육개혁 진행상황을 보고 받던 중 “공교육 교과과정에서 다루지 않는 분야의 문제는 대학수학능력시험(수능) 출제에서 배제하라”고 지시했습니다. 교육과정 외 문제를 출제하는 것은 사교육에 의존하라는 것으로 “교육 당국과 사교육이 한 편(카르텔)이란 말”이냐고 지적했는데요. 수능을 불과 5개월 앞둔 시점에서 ‘초고난도 문항 배제’, ‘쉬운 수능’으로 해석되는 윤 대통령 발언은 수험생은 물론 교육계에...
The post 사교육 이권 카르텔 ‘굿판’, 마지막 ‘제물’은 수험생 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[소리는 실재하는가, 감정은 실재하는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92262</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92262"/>
        <updated>2023-07-04T02:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 이효석 박사 추천 ‘좋은 책’ 이야기, 첫 번째 책 ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ 다섯 번째 이야기: 숲에서 나무 한 그루가 쓰러졌는데 그 소리를 들은 사람이 아무도 없다면, 소리가 난 것인가? 철학자들과 초등학교 교사들이 수도 없이 던진 이 케케묵은 물음은 인간의 경험에 관해, 그리고 특히 우리가 어떻게 감정을 경험하고 지각하는지에 관해 결정적인 단서를 제공한다. 이 수수께기에...
The post 소리는 실재하는가, 감정은 실재하는가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘마약과의 전쟁’이 놓치고 있는 게 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76832</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/03/npsp_addiction/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_addiction"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T22:59:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 8일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 저는 미국에서 중독 정신과 전문의로 일하고 있습니다. 외래 환자의 약 절반 정도는 중독 문제가 있는 환자들이고, 나머지 절반은 중독 이외의 문제로 병원을 찾아온 경우입니다. 하지만 실제 임상 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rukahs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[북극으로 건너간 모기, 생태적 재난 부른다: 슬로우레터 7월4일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92270</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92270"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T22:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“아직도 냉전적 사고에서 헤어나지 못한 사람들이 많다”. 태양광 비리 추가 적발. 반카르텔 정부. 검찰 카르텔은 괜찮은가? 부동산 바닥 쳤나? 울퉁불퉁한 바닥이다. 추미애의 총기 난사, 국민의힘은 ‘추나땡’. 프랑스를 휩쓴 인종 차별 반대 시위. 캐나다 산불 두 달째, 절반이 통제 불능. 오늘의 TMI. 대곡-소사선 개통했더니 9호선이 더 붐볐다. 샌프란시스코는 완전 자율주행 24시간 운행 요청. 일본에서는 풍선 장례식...
The post 북극으로 건너간 모기, 생태적 재난 부른다: 슬로우레터 7월4일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Examining suspicious code fragments in AWS SDK .NET]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1057/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1057/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we are dissecting AWS SDK for .NET. We will look at suspicious code fragments, figure out what's wrong with them, and try to reproduce some of the errors. Make yourself a cup of coffee and get cozy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: object-oriented programming]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479797</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-object-oriented-programming/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T19:32:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This lesson starts a new segment about Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) — an important set of concepts critical to understanding any modern software, not just modern...
The post Programming embedded systems: object-oriented programming appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing crypto authentication in accessories and disposables]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479776</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/implementing-crypto-authentication-in-accessories-and-disposables/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T15:23:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Small form-factor, self-powered cryptographic ICs will help push the authentication boundaries of disposable consumables and accessories. We look at how crypto authentication can be implemented.
The post Implementing crypto authentication in accessories and disposables appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicolas Demoulin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Documenting counted-by relationships in kernel data structures]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936728/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936728/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The C language is expressive in many ways, but it still does not have ways
to express many of the relationships between fields in a data structure.
That gap can be at least partially filled, though, if one is willing to
create and use non-standard extensions.  The adoption of of those
extensions, in the form of the __counted_by() macro, has been
merged for the 6.5 kernel release, even though the compiler feature it
depends on has not yet been finalized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perl v5.38.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937204/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937204/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 5.38.0 of the Perl language is out.  "Perl 5.38.0 represents
approximately 12 months of development since Perl 5.36.0 and contains
approximately 290,000 lines of changes across 1,500 files from 100
authors."  Significant changes include a new class feature,
Unicode 15.0 support, a new API for hooking into functions, and more; see
the
5.38.0 perldelta page for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937189/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937189/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:17:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (cups, gst-plugins-bad1.0, gst-plugins-base1.0, gst-plugins-good1.0, python3.7, and yajl), Fedora (chromium, kubernetes, pcs, and webkitgtk), Scientific Linux (open-vm-tools), SUSE (iniparser, keepass, libvirt, prometheus-ha_cluster_exporter, prometheus-sap_host_exporter, rekor, terraform-provider-aws, terraform-provider-helm, and terraform-provider-null), and Ubuntu (python-reportlab and vim).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing AI to the farthest edge requires new computing]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12590</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/bringing-ai-to-the-farthest-edge-requires-new-computing/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T13:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published in my June 30, 2023 newsletter. You can sign up for the newsletter here.  We’re in the midst of a computing shift that’s turning the back-and-forth between cloud and edge computing on its head. This new form of computing has been creeping to the forefront for the last few years, […]
The post Bringing AI to the farthest edge requires new computing appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Mismatch]]></title>
        <id>3606028</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3606028"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T12:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLM 애플리케이션 10대 취약점: OWASP 버전 0.1]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92254</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92254"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T07:59:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년 말 시작된 챗GPT 서비스는 지난 2016년 알파고가 이세돌 9단을 바둑에서 격파한 이래 인공지능의 무한한 가능성에 대해 일반인들이 실감하게 된 또 하나의 중요한 이정표가 되었다. 챗GPT 기반의 다양한 응용 분야 논의가 활발해지며 일반 인공지능(AGI: Artificial Generative Intelligence) 의 출현 가능성에 대한 전문가들의 갑론을박 현상도 목격할 수 있었다. 한편으로는 챗GPT 사용자의 폭증과 동시에 챗GPT에 관한 문제점에...
The post LLM 애플리케이션 10대 취약점: OWASP 버전 0.1 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>윤대균</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Java containers with Quarkus and Podman Desktop]]></title>
        <id>8583d285-7edc-424d-b23b-c34c531c6661</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/07/03/managing-java-containers-quarkus-and-podman-desktop"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of software development is changing quickly, and it is no different for the Java developer who needs to learn new skills to manage Java containers.
In the traditional Java development world, it was rather typical to build a Java artifact (whether it be a .jar, .war, or .ear), and "throw it over the wall" for the middleware and operations people to take care of. It kind of made sense, too, because configuring and running enterprise application servers was not always that easy, and in the end, the developer's laptop would probably not match the specs of staging or production environments so that the configuration would be different anyway. We all know the "It works on my machine" cliché, after all.
These days, things need faster and better delivery, and production issues often requ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Dubois</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[루소와 보충대리 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223145554448</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223145554448"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T06:32:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(김형효, <데리다의 해체철학>, 5장) 데리다에 의하면 루소는 플라톤처럼 말중심주의와 소리중심주의에 서있다. 루소는 현존의 형이상학적 진리를 찬양하고 있다. 현존은 이데아나 본질의 형식이 아니라, 의식 내재적, 의식의 자기 현존적 확실성이다. 루소가 말한다. <로고스는 목소리를 통해 무한할 수 있고, 자기 현존적이며 자기애정적으로 나타날 수밖에 없다.> 목소리 때문에 문자는 천박하고 외면적이고 감각적 수준에만 머무는 비현존적인 것이 된다. 그런데 말의 생생한 자기 현존이 실제로 잘 잡히질 않는다. 우리 영혼의 생생한 현존적 소리와 감정이 마치 거울 속에 있는 나를 바라보는 것과 유사하게 간주된다. (이미 데.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[매번 헌법을 고쳐나가는 그곳, 올해 주요 판결은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77263</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/07/03/npsp_scotus2023/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_scotus2023"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T04:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난주 미국 대법원은 올해 회기가 끝나기 전 굵직굵직한 사안에 관한 판결을 잇달아 쏟아냈습니다. 보통법 전통을 따르는 미국에서 대법원판결은 헌법에 준하는 판례가 되기 때문에 판결 하나하나에 관심이 쏠리기 마련입니다. 올해도 마찬가지였는데, 미리 스프에서 소개했던 사건들도 많았습니다. 이 가운데 연방 선거를 관리하는 권한이 주의회에 얼마나 있느냐를 둘러싼 판결에 관해 뉴욕대학교 법학대학원 리처드 필데스 교수가 쓴 칼럼을 번역하고, 올해 대법원의 주요 판결을 모아 정리했습니다. 전문번역: 극단적인 주장을 받아들인 건 아니지만… 안심하긴 이르다 해설: 매번 헌법을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빅테크의 표정-감정 연구는 낭비인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92222</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92222"/>
        <updated>2023-07-03T04:30:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 이효석 박사 추천 ‘좋은 책’ 이야기, 첫 번째 책 ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ 네 번째 이야기: 오늘날 있지도 않은 감정의 실체를 찾는 데 얼마나 많은 시간과 돈이 허비되고 있는지를 생각하면, 우리는 이런 망각 때문에 그만큼 더 가난해진 셈이다. 오늘날 마이크로소프트는 감정을 인식하겠다는 목표 아래 얼굴 사진을 분석한다. 애플은 최근에 인공지능 기법을 사용해 표정에서 감정을 탐지하는...
The post 빅테크의 표정-감정 연구는 낭비인가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고속도로 종점 틀었는데 알고보니 김건희 땅: 슬로우레터 7월3일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92208</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92208"/>
        <updated>2023-07-02T22:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[횟집 수조물 먹방. 국민의힘 괴담론 이면엔 이명박 트라우마. 고속도로 종점 틀었는데 알고보니 김건희 땅. “문재인이 물러나라 했다”, 추미애가 뒤늦게 터뜨린 분노. 이태원 참사 특별법 패스트트랙으로 간다. 죽은 걸로 확인된 유령 아기 9명으로. 출생통보제 도입, 문제는 사회의 책임. 유령 아기, 외국인 아이들이 빠졌다. 월례비 때렸는데 “사실상 임금” 판결. 가뭄 뒤에 물난리, “날씨가 왜 이러나.” 차관 정치...
The post 고속도로 종점 틀었는데 알고보니 김건희 땅: 슬로우레터 7월3일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Predicting the size of the Linux kernel binary]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7978</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/07/02/predicting-the-size-of-the-linux-kernel-binary/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-02T21:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How big is the binary for the Linux kernel? Depending on the value of around 15,000 configuration options, the size of the version 5.8 binary could be anywhere between 7.3Mb and 2,134 Mb. Who is interested in the size of the Linux kernel binary? We are not in the early 1980s, when memory for a […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 나이키 투자의견 및 나이키 주가 전망 보고서(7/2 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591123</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591123/%eb%82%98%ec%9d%b4%ed%82%a4-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ea%b3%bc-%eb%82%98%ec%9d%b4%ed%82%a4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-07-02T02:52:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 나이키 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 우려보다 나은 긍정적인 면이 많으나 FY24 나이키 전망은 실망스럽다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591117</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591117/23-2q-%eb%82%98%ec%9d%b4%ed%82%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-07-02T02:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three 6.x stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/937079/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/937079/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T20:50:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.4.1,
6.3.11, and
6.1.37
stable kernels have been released; each contains another set of important
fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More endpoints, more problems: how to lower network attack surfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479789</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/more-endpoints-more-problems-how-to-lower-network-attack-surfaces/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thwarting attackers requires understanding the depth of your attack surface and finding ways to lower it. Let’s explore how this is possible.
The post More endpoints, more problems: how to lower network attack surfaces appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Apu Pavithran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Nicer Coding’: Ligatures with Eclipse and Visual Studio Code]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=37684</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/07/01/nicer-coding-ligatures-with-eclipse-and-visual-studio-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T12:27:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A ligature is a font feature, combining multiple 'characters' into a single glyph. This can be very useful for programming and source code, and makes reading source code easier. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving McKinsey and Hodling Through a Startup’s Beginning to Unicorn]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2662</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2023/07/01/what-i-learned-from-leaving-mckinsey-and-hodling-through-a-startups-beginning-to-unicorn/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=what-i-learned-from-leaving-mckinsey-and-hodling-through-a-startups-beginning-to-unicorn"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T11:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After graduating from college, my first job was at McKinsey, where I spent two and a half years before joining the Sendbird startup team. Now, after eight years with Sendbird, I reflect on the journey that surpassed my time at McKinsey by more than threefold.. Surprisingly, my journey with Sendbird has exceeded my time atContinue reading "Leaving McKinsey and Hodling Through a Startup’s Beginning to Unicorn"
Leaving McKinsey and Hodling Through a Startup’s Beginning to Unicorn appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한류의 최전선과 문명의 역할: 스롱 피아비 위키를 편집하면서 든 문제의식]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92186</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92186"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T08:10:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[위키피디아 영문판은 대중 지식의 마지막 종착역이자 성전이다. 세계적으로 수백만 명의 편집자들이 최신 뉴스와 학술 성취를 바탕으로 실시간 업데이트 한다. 특히 인물에 대한 정보는 타의 추종을 불허하는데, 영문 위키피디아에 등재된 한국인이라면 자랑스러워 해도 좋을성 싶다. 일전에 한번 언급했는데, 싱가폴 대학엔 리포트 과제 제출을 ‘영문 위키 등록’으로 대체하는 교수님도 많다. 그러니까 자신이 1학기 동안 천착한 주제를 위키에...
The post 한류의 최전선과 문명의 역할: 스롱 피아비 위키를 편집하면서 든 문제의식 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정호재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate Guide to What’s New in Bluetooth version 5.2]]></title>
        <id>https://www.novelbits.io/?p=17822</id>
        <link href="https://novelbits.io/bluetooth-version-5-2-le-audio/"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T04:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction At CES 2020 (January 2020), the Bluetooth SIG introduced the latest version of Bluetooth, version 5.2. This announcement was made alongside the announcement of the next generation of Bluetooth audio, named: LE Audio. The major change introduced in version 5.2 is a new feature called Isochronous Channels (ISOC). ISOC lays the foundation for the […]
The post The Ultimate Guide to What’s New in Bluetooth version 5.2 appeared first on Novel Bits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mohammad Afaneh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인간은 불완전하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92151</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92151"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T01:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 이효석 박사 추천 ‘좋은 책’ 이야기, 첫 번째 책 ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ 세 번째 이야기: 과거에 과학자들은 뇌가 단순히 통각을 지각하고 표상하면, 보란 듯이 당신이 고통을 경험하게 된다고 생각했다. 그러나 고통의 내부 작용은 예측성 뇌에서 더 복잡하다. 고통은 신체적 손상으로 인해 일어나는 경험일 뿐만 아니라 뇌가 손상이 임박했음을 예측할 때 일어나는 경험이기도 하다. 뇌의...
The post 인간은 불완전하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting a Modbus energy meter to Home Assistant]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2023-07-01:/homeassistant-modbus-energy-meter.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/homeassistant-modbus-energy-meter.html"/>
        <updated>2023-07-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have an electricity meter that supports communication over Modbus. I wanted to add it to Home Assistant. Modbus is supported out-of-the-box by Home Assistant but I could not find an end-to-end tutorial how to connect a device and how to use a Modbus sensor for energy tracking. This article …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of reading: April - June 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/summary-of-reading-april-june-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/summary-of-reading-april-june-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T23:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<ul class="simple">
<li>&quot;WebAssembly: The Definitive Guide&quot; by Brian Sletten - a wide and shallow
overview of the WASM landscape. Logically, it can be seen as a compantion to
&quot;The Art of WebAssembly&quot; which goes deep into the WASM language and spec;
in reality, it falls short. The book is full of laborious explanations …</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 기후 위기 앞에선 어쩔 수 없는 선택을 할 수밖에]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76829</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/06/30/npsp_nuclearwaste/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_nuclearwaste"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T22:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 6일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 원자력은 우라늄과 같은 방사능 물질이 뿜어내는 열을 이용해 전기를 만들어 내는 발전방식입니다. 원자력은 적은 양의 연료로 많은 에너지를 만들어 낼 수 있으며, 발전소 유지비용이 적어 효율이 높고, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 순수이성비판 강의]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223143681783</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223143681783"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T20:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 칸트인 내가 주장하고자 하는 것은 인간 인식을 경험의 한계 너머로 확장하지 말자는 것이다. 반면에 여전히 우리 인식을 경험의 한계 너머로 확장하여 영혼의 단순한 본성이나 세계 시작의 필연성을 증명했다고 자칭하는 뻔뻔한 학자들이 있다. + 이미 우리가 전 시간 지적했듯이 칸트가 하고자 하는 것은 이성 비판이며, 즉 사변적 형이상학에 대한 비판이다. 경험에 의해 그 참과 거짓이 증명되지 않는, 혹은 증명될 수 없는 그런 것들을 지식으로 주장하는 것에 대해서 칸트가 비판하고 있다. + 데카르트는 우리 영혼이 단순하다고 주장한다. 그러나 우리는 이것에 대해서 알 수 없다. 우리는 이런 주장의 참에 대해서 알 수 있는 능력이 없.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for June 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12587</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-june-30-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T20:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mexico is embracing Mioty as a scalable industrial IoT network: FábricaDigital, a network of several large enterprises in Mexico, has signed a deal with the Mioty Alliance to make the Mioty long-range, low-power IoT network viable for businesses in its network. FábricaDigital works with companies including Google, Honeywell, Continental, and Safran Group. Mioty is a competitive technology to other […]
The post IoT news of the week for June 30, 2023 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connected device security goes from push to pull as awareness grows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479762</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/connected-device-security-goes-from-push-to-pull-as-awareness-grows/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T18:10:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PSA Certified 2023 Security Report says business and consumers are now demanding security for connected devices, but that brings cost challenges for smaller firms to implement.
The post Connected device security goes from push to pull as awareness grows appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The first half of the 6.5 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936418/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936418/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T14:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first days of the 6.5 merge window have been a bit calmer than usual,
with "only" 4,000 non-merge changesets having been pulled into the mainline
repository.  Those changesets include a fair amount of significant work,
though.  Read on for LWN's summary of the first set of changes merged for
the next major kernel release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What it takes to keep an enterprise 'Frankenkernel' alive (Register)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936976/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936976/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T13:00:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Register reports
from Jiří Benc's DevConf.cz talk on the making of the CentOS Stream
kernel.


	So, what the team are working on is a Frankenstein's monster, sewn
	together from different codebases. Although the base kernel is
	still version 5.14, it is full of backports from upstream. It has
	the XFS filesystem code from kernel 6.0, the USB subsystem –
	complete with drivers – and BPF subsystem from kernel 6.2, the
	wireless stack and all drivers from kernel 6.3, and the multipath
	TCP/IP code from kernel 6.4 – which at the time of the talk hadn't
	even been released upstream yet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[착오적 독해 혹은 오독]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223143428303</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223143428303"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T12:30:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[스피박은 <포스트식민 이성비판>에서 세 명의 철학자, 칸트, 헤겔, 마르크스를 다루고 있다. 왜 이 세 명인가? 칼 플레취는 <세 개의 세상> 결론 부분에서 다음과 같이 쓰고 있다. <우리가 해야 할 도전은 사회과학적 노동의 이러한 개념적 구획을 (즉 세 개의 세상, 제1 세계, 제2 세계, 제 3세계)그저 제쳐둘 게 아니라, 그것을 비판하는 것이다. 그리고 우리는 여기서 칸트, 헤겔, 맑스가 의미하는 비판의 과제를 이해해야 한다. 달리 말해 우리는 세계의 세상이라는 발상이 사회과학적으로 당연한 것으로 부과해 온 한계를 극복해야 한다.> 그런데 프레취(Carl Pletsch)는 3개의 세계에 맞추어 칸트, 헤겔, 마르크스를 거.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[User stories are not requirements]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/?p=13576</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/quality/user-stories-are-not-requirements/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T10:48:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We often hear, “Aren’t our requirements just our user stories?”.   This often occurs when a product’s goal or intended use changes, […]
The post User stories are not requirements appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jane Orme</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[편도체-공포 가설과 옴니제닉 모델]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92132</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92132"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T08:57:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 이효석 박사 추천 ‘좋은 책’ 이야기, 첫 번째 책 ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ 두 번째 이야기 차례: 그 후 얼마 지나지 않아 다른 과학자들은 편도체가 손상된 사람들이 공포를 경험하고 지각할 수 있는지를 연구하기 시작했다. 그중에서도 가장 집중적인 연구가 이루어진 것은 ‘SM’이라고 불린 여성의 사례였다. 이 여성은 아동기와 청소년기에 서서히 편도체가 소멸되는 우르바흐-비테(Urbach-Wiethe)병이라는 유전병을 앓고 있었다....
The post 편도체-공포 가설과 옴니제닉 모델 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936949/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936949/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T07:48:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (docker-registry, flask, systemd, and trafficserver), Fedora (moodle, python-reportlab, suricata, and vim), Red Hat (go-toolset and golang, go-toolset-1.19 and go-toolset-1.19-golang, go-toolset:rhel8, open-vm-tools, python27:2.7, and python3), SUSE (buildah, chromium, gifsicle, libjxl, sqlite3, and xonotic), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-allwinner, linux-allwinner-5.19, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.19,
 linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.19, linux-hwe-5.19, linux-ibm,
 linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux-starfive,
 linux-starfive-5.19, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure,
 linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-5.4, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-bluefield,
 linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gke, linux-gke-5.15,
 linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm,
 linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15,
 linux-nvidia, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15, linux-oracle-5.4,
 linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, and linux-oem-6.1).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ISystemTap: An interactive SystemTap notebook]]></title>
        <id>bf73469e-5859-4263-95c6-a277a732da83</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/06/30/isystemtap-interactive-systemtap-notebook"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SystemTap is a tool that streamlines the gathering of real-time information about a running Linux system. It can probe and even modify running processes in both the user and kernel spaces, so you can easily monitor your programs without recompiling and installing tools on your system. It also provides many tapsets, or prewritten libraries that aid in these tasks.
But to a beginner, SystemTap can be overwhelming, and it can be said that with this great power comes an equally great learning curve. To solve this issue, we've introduced an interactive, beginner-friendly interface called ISystemTap.
About ISystemTap
ISystemTap is a Jupyter kernel that allows for running SystemTap scripts in an easy, incremental way within Jupyterlab, a lightweight web-browser-based client for executing IPython …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan Goldberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[생성형 AI 위한 구글클라우드의 새 기능과 프로그램]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92119</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92119"/>
        <updated>2023-06-30T06:07:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마이크로소프트가 오픈AI의 기능을 포함해 클라우드 서비스 기능을 확대하고 있는 가운데 구글은 지난 구글 I/O를 통해 생성형 인공지능을 지원하기 위한 새로운 도구, 프로그램과 파트너십을 제공한다고 발표했다. 여기에는 생성형 인공지능 서비스인 버텍스 AI와 듀엣(Duet) AI, 새로운 교육 프로그램, 컨설팅 서비스, 그리고 데이터스택스, 네오4j, 트윌리오, 타입페이스 같은 회사와의 파트너십을 확장하는 것 등을 포함한다. 버텍스 AI는 지난 글(거대언어모델과 클라우드...
The post 생성형 AI 위한 구글클라우드의 새 기능과 프로그램 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>한상기</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘1등 뉴스’ ‘시청률 1위’ 앵커 해고는 무엇을 위한 결정이었나]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76793</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/06/29/npsp_tuckercarlson/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_tuckercarlson"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T22:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 3일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 오늘날 미국 정치의 특징을 설명할 때 빠지지 않는 말이 “정치적 양극화”입니다. 서로 도무지 공통 분모를 찾지 못하는 진보와 보수가 사사건건 의견이 부딪칠 때마다 서로 불편해하며, 끝내 상대방을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 마이크론 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 반도체 바닥을 통과 중이나 중국 제재는 회복 스토리를 지연시킬 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591102</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591102/23-2q-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T22:57:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[폐지줍던 노인들이 사라졌다: 슬로우레터 6월30일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92088</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92088"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T22:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[권익위원장은 검사 출신, 윤석열 직속 상사. 차관 정치. 시민단체 때리던 검찰, 업무추진비 처리는 엉망. 이동관이 명진 퇴출 주도했다. 해법과 대안. 케이블카가 교통체증 대안 될 수 있다. 118년만에 문닫는 화순 탄광. 출생통보제하면 아이 안 버릴까. 폐지줍는 노인이 사라졌다. 동성부부 임신, 쉽지 않았다. 오늘의 TMI. 중국 백만장자 3500명 싱가포르로 이주. 대구+군위군, 대도시 면적 1위. “김범석은 쿠팡의 총수다.”...
The post 폐지줍던 노인들이 사라졌다: 슬로우레터 6월30일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 open-source games written in C#: searching for bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1056/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1056/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a lot of fantastic games, but few of them are open source. In this article, we will examine the most curious bugs found in the source code of three best, to my mind, open-source games written in C#.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Change your development approach to build better products]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479758</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/change-your-development-approach-to-build-better-products/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T19:06:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know that working top down from your application code to low-level code sounds ridiculous to embedded developers, but it will result in a better...
The post Change your development approach to build better products appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Hybrid Teams]]></title>
        <id>3606015</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3606015"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T18:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay | Meet Yoshihiko from Japan. More stories from Spain, Cameroon and Malaysia]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/weareplay-meet-yoshihiko-from-japan-more-stories-from-spain-cameroon-malaysia.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/weareplay-meet-yoshihiko-from-japan-more-stories-from-spain-cameroon-malaysia.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Leticia Lago, Developer Marketing






In our latest #WeArePlay stories, meet app and game founders from around the world bringing creative new ideas to their industries. From a mountaineering app that is helping to save lives, to game studios incorporating playful cultural nods and inclusive designs in their titles.




In our latest film, meet Yosihiko from Japan who founded YAMAP - an app for mountain climbers. After the 2011 Great East Japan Earthquake, he was inspired to bring people closer to nature and save lives. Despite having no programming experience, he and his team created a platform which enables mountaineers to safely check their location and share their climb activity logs, even when there’s no phone signal. The app has become very popular with climbers, who have…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Emacs for Android]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936576/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936576/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T14:40:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Emacs editor is not tied to the Linux kernel; indeed, it was created
some years before Linux existed.  The Emacs code base is intended to be
portable, and the editor runs, with varying levels of support, on a wide
variety of systems.  Recently, an energetic developer has worked to extend
the set of supported systems to Android; the result is a working port, but
whether that port will be accepted into the Emacs mainline is the topic of
ongoing conversation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Boba AI: Some lessons and patterns learnt in building an             LLM-powered generative application]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/building-boba.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/building-boba.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it's fascinating to work directly with a Large Language Model,
     such as ChatGPT, it takes some skill and practice to learn how to prompt it
     effectively. My colleague Farooq Ali has been working on a co-pilot tool,
     Boba AI, for using an LLM to help generate ideas for product strategy. From
     this experience he as proposed eight patterns which he judges
     will be generally useful for building these kinds of AI co-pilot applications.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: Why Roku wants a smart home OS]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12584</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-why-roku-wants-a-smart-home-os/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T13:00:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week we learned a bit more about streaming provider Roku’s plans to build a smart home operating system. This is in addition to all of the new smart home devices the company has developed using Wyze hardware. Because Kevin Tofel is on vacation, I’m talking about all this with my co-host and the creator […]
The post Podcast: Why Roku wants a smart home OS appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만삭스, 미국의 중국 수출 규제에도 엔비디아는 쉽게 대체 판매처 찾을 수 있다고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591094</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591094/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a4%91%ea%b5%ad-%ec%88%98%ec%b6%9c-%ea%b7%9c%ec%a0%9c"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[번스타인, 테슬라 슈퍼차저 개방으로 2030년 120억 달러 매출 가능]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591087</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591087/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8a%88%ed%8d%bc%ec%b0%a8%ec%a0%80-%ea%b0%9c%eb%b0%a9-2"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T10:07:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936752/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936752/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T07:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and maradns), SUSE (iniparser, kubernetes1.23, python-reportlab, and python-sqlparse), and Ubuntu (accountsservice and linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15,
 linux-dell300x, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm,
 linux-oracle, linux-raspi2, linux-snapdragon).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to develop and deploy OpenShift console dynamic plugin]]></title>
        <id>bd9a9000-fb9e-437c-b1c5-986aa4c56de0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/06/29/how-develop-and-deploy-openshift-console-dynamic-plugin"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic plugins allow you to extend the Red Hat OpenShift UI at runtime, adding custom pages and other extensions. They are based on the webpack module federation. Plugins are registered with the console using the ConsolePlugin custom resource and enabled in the console operator config by a cluster administrator.
Prerequisites
Node.js
yarn
Docker or podman 3.2.0+
oc
Getting started
To clone console plugin template repo, you should update the plugin metadata, such as the plugin name in the ConsolePlugin  declaration of package.json.
"consolePlugin": {
  "name": "plugin-name",
  "version": "0.0.1",
  "displayName": "Dynamic Plugin",
  "description": "OpenShift console dynamic plugin",
  "exposedModules": {
    "ExamplePage": "./components/ExamplePage"
  },
  "dependencies": {
    "@console/p…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ajay Pratap</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 넷플릭스 투자의견과 넷플릭스 주가 전망(6/29 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591084</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591084/%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ea%b3%bc-%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T06:22:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 메타 투자의견 및 메타 주가 전망(6/29 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591082</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591082/%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T06:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“처벌 중심의 학폭위, 가해자의 반성도 피해자의 회복도 없었다.”]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92058</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92058"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T05:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[인터뷰] ‘어느날 갑자기 가해자 엄마가 되었습니다’ 저자 정승훈, “여론에 떠밀려 만든 누더기 법안, 문제의 본질을 보자.” 정승훈씨는 가해학생의 엄마였다. 정승훈씨와 그 아들이 겪었던 일은 학교폭력 사건의 복잡한 구조를 이해하는 몇 가지 힌트를 준다. 처음에는 별일 아니라고 생각했다. 어느날 아침 중학교 3학년 아들이 전화가 와서 후배를 때렸는데 학교에서 연락이 올 거라고 했다. 그게 시작이었다. 학폭위(학교폭력대책자치위원회)가 잡혔고...
The post “처벌 중심의 학폭위, 가해자의 반성도 피해자의 회복도 없었다.” appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 알파벳 투자의견과 알파벳 목표주가(6/29 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591067</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591067/%ec%95%8c%ed%8c%8c%eb%b2%b3-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ea%b3%bc-%ec%95%8c%ed%8c%8c%eb%b2%b3-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T04:41:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[구성주의의 반격: ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ (2017)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92006</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92006"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T02:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 이효석 박사와 함께하는 ‘좋은 책’에 관한 이야기, 첫 번째. 뉴스페퍼민트 이효석 대표는 슬로우뉴스와는 귀한 인연을 가진 분입니다. KAIST에서 물리학을 공부하고 양자 컴퓨터를 전공해 박사 학위를 받았으며, 하버드에서는 오늘날 AI의 배경 기술 중 하나인 정보이론을 연구했습니다. 하버드 연구원 시절 시작한 외신 번역 미디어 ‘뉴스페퍼민트’를 10년 이상 운영하며, 과학 전반의 다양한 영역과 번역 및 저작권에 대한...
The post 구성주의의 반격: ‘감정은 어떻게 만들어지는가’ (2017) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 29, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/935773/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/935773/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-29T01:58:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 29, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “너 혼자 그런다고 뭐가 바뀌니”에 대한 답은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76764</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/06/28/npsp_ethicalconsumption/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_ethicalconsumption"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T22:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 1일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 의식주(衣食住). 옷과 음식과 집. 사람이 사는 데 필요한 기본 요소 세 가지를 일컫는 말입니다. 그런데 생각해 보면, 현대 사회에서 인간이 옷, 음식, 집을 생산하고 조달하는 방법은 각각 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 마이크론 실적, 기대보다 나은 실적과 전망과  반도체 반닥론을 확인하다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591045</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591045/23-1q-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T22:50:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베트남 달랏 여행, 달마대사의 인연이 깃든 달랏 죽림사 방문기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591040</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591040/%eb%b2%a0%ed%8a%b8%eb%82%a8-%eb%8b%ac%eb%9e%8f-%ec%a3%bd%eb%a6%bc%ec%82%ac-%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T22:03:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“‘사이다 대통령’ 칭찬 아니다”, 윤석열 폭주에 보수 언론도 화들짝: 슬로우레터 6월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=92024</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/92024"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:53:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“왜 늘 이런 식으로 정책을 딜리버리하나.” “‘사이다 대통령’ 불안하다.” 메가스터디 등 동시 다발 세무조사. “이권 카르텔이라는 연극.” “문제는 자사고가 더 크다.” 호남 강타한 폭우, 오늘 수도권 북상. 오염수 시찰단 분석 결과 왜 공개 안 하나. 일베 게시판인줄, 윤석열의 막말. U자형 반등? 소비 심리 살아나나. “태양광 전력 차단, 망하라는 건가.” 오늘의 TMI. 만 나이 아직도 혼란....
The post “‘사이다 대통령’ 칭찬 아니다”, 윤석열 폭주에 보수 언론도 화들짝: 슬로우레터 6월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Champion Innovator Elyes Manai, based in Quebec City, Quebec, Canada]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/champion-innovator-elyes-manai.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/champion-innovator-elyes-manai.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T21:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Max Saltonstall, Developer Relations Engineer



In this ongoing interview series we sit down with Google Cloud Champion Innovators across the world to learn more about their journeys, their technology focus, and what excites them. Today we're talking to Elyes Manai. Elyes is a Machine Learning Consultant, Educator and Mentor. He helps companies tap into the power of data science to reduce costs and increase revenue as well as build relationships with relevant target audiences through educational content and community building.


What is a Champion Innovator?


Champion Innovators are a global network of more than 500 non-Google professionals, who are technical experts in Google Cloud products and services. Each Champion specializes in one of nine different technical categories w…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Register for Google Cloud Next ‘23 and get some sweet perks]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/register-for-google-cloud-next-23.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/register-for-google-cloud-next-23.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T16:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Hall, Vice President, Product and Industry Marketing, Google Cloud & Max Saltonstall, Developer Relations Engineer






Developers - it’s finally here . . . the Google Cloud Next ‘23 session library is live!
So many awesome sessions to choose from, it's tough!
Of course we start with the big story of the year, the thing on everyone's (everything's?) mind: AI!
Machine learning and AI


Check out "5 practical considerations for adopting AI" to get started or "Build your organization’s future on Google AI and machine learning infrastructure" for teams that are looking to expand into cross-functional AI-powered innovation.
Building modern apps


Sometimes you've got an awesome idea, and you are looking for a way to speed up getting it to market. We can help. Attend "Building f…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] JupyterLab 4.0: a development environment for education and research]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936340/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936340/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T15:55:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JupyterLab is a
web-based development environment widely used by data scientists,
engineers, and educators for data visualization, data analysis,
prototyping, and interactive learning materials. The Jupyter community has recently announced the
release of JupyterLab 4.0, introducing lots of new features and performance
improvements to enhance its capabilities both in research and educational
settings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936672/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936672/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T13:02:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.3.10,
6.1.36,
5.15.119,
5.10.186,
5.4.249,
4.19.288, and
4.14.320
stable kernels have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936671/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936671/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T12:58:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (docker-docker-registry, libcap, libx11, mediawiki, python-requests, python-tornado, sofia-sip, sqlite, and xonotic), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, libssh, libtiff, python27:2.7, python39:3.9, python39-devel:3.9, ruby:2.7, sqlite, systemd, and virt:rhel, virt-devel:rhel), SUSE (bind, cosign, guile1, lilypond, keepass, kubernetes1.24, nodejs16, nodejs18, phpMyAdmin, and sqlite3), and Ubuntu (etcd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[18년 전 세계를 놀라게 했던 ‘황우석 사태’와 그 이후]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77207</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/06/28/npsp_wshwang/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_wshwang"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T09:40:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마크 트웨인은 현실은 소설보다 이상하다고 말했습니다. 소설은 가능성에 구속되지만, 현실은 그럴 필요가 없기 때문입니다. 벌써 18년 전 소설보다 더 소설 같은 일이 바로 우리나라에서 일어났습니다. 사건의 주인공은 바로 황우석 박사입니다. 세계 최초로 줄기세포 복제에 성공하며, 난치병 환자들의 희망으로 떠올랐던 황우석 박사는 연구 과정에서 데이터를 조작하는 심각한 잘못을 저지른 것이 알려져 순식간에 추락했습니다. 그러나 명성을 얻으며 확보한 연구비로 계속 복제 사업을 진행한 황 박사는 현재 아랍에미리트에서 왕실이 애지중지하는 낙타 복제를 도맡아 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 마이크론 투자의견 및 마이크론 주가 전망(6/28 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591035</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591035/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T07:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using a Verilog task to simulate a packet generator for an SDIO controller]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2023/06/28/sdiopkt.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2023/06/28/sdiopkt.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fig 1. The KlusterLab board



One of my current projects is to test and bring up a 10Gb Ethernet
test board.  The board has been fondly named
the “KlusterLab”, because of all of the various interfaces present on it.
Among those interfaces are an SD port and an eMMC port.
Now, how shall I verify their functionality?
Building an SDIO/eMMC Controller
My first round of testing the SD port used my SPI-based SD card controller,
SDSPI.  Using that controller, the card
responded in much the way I expected, save that the first sector of the card
wasn’t what FATFS was expecting.
Since this is simply board bringup, where we are just trying to verify that the
hardware is working, I signed the component off as working.  I could obviously
write to the device, and I could read from the device.  (Okay, I…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크론 실적 발표를 앞둔 월가의 시선, 실적과 전망은 기대 이하일 것이나 마이크론 주가는 반도체 사이클에 연동될 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591029</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591029/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-06-28T03:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[첨가 – 인간주의 / 인식론적 단절]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223140792467</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223140792467"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T23:24:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[41 알튀세르는 <반인간주의>를 주장한다. <자본론>은 반인간주의로 독해해야 한다. 이러한 시도는 데라르 드 샤르댕의 영향으로 기독교화되고, 프랑크푸르트학파에 의해 인간주의화되었으며, 사르트르와 그람시에 의해 인간화되었고 역사화되었던 마르크스주의를 복원하려고 하였다. (<자본론을 읽는다>, 두레, 1991) 그런데 나는 마르크스에 대한 인간주의적 해석을 좋아한다. 비록 사회 구조가 우리에 미치는 영향을 부정할 수 없다고 해도, 동시에 우리가 사회 구조에 미치는 영향 또한 부정할 수 없는 것이다. 우리는 주체가 되어야만 한다. 우리는 개혁과 변혁의 주체가 되어야 한다. 에리히 프롬의 <마르크스의 인간.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[겁줘서 라면값 50원 깎기, 이것이 윤석열의 자유민주주의: 슬로우레터 6월28일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91984</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91984"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T22:01:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[라면 값 내렸다. 괴담과 싸우는 조선일보. 문 정부가 사드 전자파 인체 무해 확인하고 덮었다. 삼성물산, 엘리엇에 724억 원 주고 비밀합의했다. 늙어서도 집안일 줄지 않는다. 산불 끄러 가는데 마스크를 사서 쓴다. 해법과 대안. 일본은 약 줄이면 지원금 준다. 말기 환자와 임종 환자의 차이. 정신과 병상은 유지할수록 손해. 더 깊게 읽기. “수능 만점자 300명 나와도 된다.” 한쪽에서는...
The post 겁줘서 라면값 50원 깎기, 이것이 윤석열의 자유민주주의: 슬로우레터 6월28일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Converting filesystems to iomap]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/935934/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/935934/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:29:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion that largely centered around the documentation of
iomap, which provides a block-mapping interface for modern filesystems,
was led by Luis Chamberlain that the
2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem,
Memory-Management and BPF Summit. There is an ongoing process of
converting filesystems to use iomap, in order to leave buffer heads 
behind and to better support folios, so
the intent was to get feedback on the documentation from developers who are
working on those conversions.  One of the concrete outcomes of the session
was a plan to move that documentation from its current location on the
KernelNewbies wiki into
the kernel documentation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Training convolutional neural networks]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479753</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/training-convolutional-neural-networks/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T16:14:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article in a series on convolutional neural networks (CNNs), we explain how these neural networks can be trained to solve problems. This...
The post Training convolutional neural networks appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ole Dreessen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating PCIe 5.0 design challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479745</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/navigating-pcie-5-0-design-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T15:57:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are some of the main issues that designers face when working with the widely used fifth generation of PCIe. PCIe (Peripheral Component Interconnect Express)...
The post Navigating PCIe 5.0 design challenges appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ekstrand: NVK update: Enabling new extensions, conformance status & more]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936554/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936554/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faith Ekstrand has provided
an update on the status of the NVK
Vulkan driver for NVIDIA GPUs.


	Probably the single most common question I get from folks is, "When
	will NVK be in upstream mesa?" The short answer is that it'll be
	upstreamed along with the new kernel API. The new API is going to
	be required in order to implement Vulkan correctly in a bunch of
	cases. Even though it mostly works on top of upstream nouveau, I
	don't want to be maintaining support for that interface for another
	10 years when it only partially works.

	We don't yet have an exact timetable for when the new API will be
	ready. I'm currently hoping that we get it all upstream this year
	but I can't say when exactly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936549/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936549/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T14:03:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (c-ares and libx11), Fedora (chromium and kubernetes), Red Hat (python3 and python38:3.8, python38-devel:3.8), and SUSE (amazon-ssm-agent, kernel, kubernetes1.24, libvirt, nodejs16, openssl-1_1, and webkit2gtk3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4]]></title>
        <id>dcee9416-fcb2-4200-ba75-df414ff7a792</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/06/27/ansible-automation-platform-whats-new"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T13:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform 2.4 is generally available (GA). It is a simple, agentless automation platform that improves your current processes, integrates event-driven automation, and provides a sneak peek at how artificial intelligence (AI) will improve automation in the future. This article describes the new features you'll find in Ansible Automation Platform 2.4.
Event-Driven Ansible
Announced as developer preview during AnsibleFest 2022, Event-Driven Ansible is now available with Ansible Automation Platform 2.4. Event-Driven Ansible is a scalable, responsive automation capability that processes events containing discrete, actionable intelligence. It empowers teams to determine the appropriate response to an event and execute automated actions to address or remediate it.
Event-…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Himanshu Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are factories going to adopt automation quickly or nah?]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12581</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/are-factories-going-to-adopt-automation-quickly-or-nah/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T13:00:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published on June 23, 2023 in my weekly IoT newsletter. You can sign up here. Will factories embrace digital automation rapidly in the next five years, or will they continue to adopt technology in an incremental fashion? That’s the pressing question behind a recent McKinsey report that tries to identify the biggest trends […]
The post Are factories going to adopt automation quickly or nah? appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Echoes of Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>3606011</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3606011"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T12:15:29.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[요코의 사과, 토레스의 사탕, 카텔란의 바나나: 관객의 참여가 예술로 인정될 때]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91966</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91966"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T08:37:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1966 년 11월 런던 인디카 갤러리에서는 ‘미완성 회화와 사물들’ 사전 전시가 준비중이었다. 오노 요코와 존 레논의 만남 정식 전시회를 앞두고 몇 지인과 셀럽들이 초대된 그 날 자리는 오노 요코라는 예술가가 자신이 추구하던 다양한 개념 미술 작품들로 구성됐는데, 여러 작품 중에서도 천장 회화 “Yes Painting”은 그 당시 초대받았던 존 레논에게 깊은 인상과 호감을 남겼고 그만큼 많은...
The post 요코의 사과, 토레스의 사탕, 카텔란의 바나나: 관객의 참여가 예술로 인정될 때 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nomodem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Have you go these software risks covered?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/?p=13519</id>
        <link href="https://www.bluefruit.co.uk/quality/have-you-go-these-software-risks-covered/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T08:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software development is full of risks that threaten to derail your project at every step. Whether it’s technical debt or creating […]
The post Have you go these software risks covered? appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알튀세르 - 요약]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223139826656</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223139826656"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T00:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1 마르크스로 돌아가자. 마르크스에 대한 구조주의적 해석이 돌아갈 마르크스의 진정한 모습을 잘 보여주고 있다. 2 전기 마르크스와 후기 마르크스 사이에는 <인식론적 단절>이 있다. 3 단절 이후에 마르크스는 그 이전과 전혀 다른 모습을 보여준다. 이제 마르크스주의는 <과학적 이론>으로 나타난다. 더 이상 마르크스는 인간중심적, 인간주의적이지 않다. 4 마르크스에 대한 휴머니즘적 해석은 인간 주체를 강조한다. 인간이 주체가 되어 역사를 만든다. 5 그러나 아니다. 인간은 주체가 아니다. 인간은 사회 구조의 결과물이다. 더 이상 인간은 역사의 주체가 아니다. 생산 관계 속에 숨겨져 있는 구조적 관계이다. 6 하부 구조.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Two Cents #63] Generative AI — 시장 구조, 기회, moat에 대한 몇 가지 생각]]></title>
        <id>https://twocents.hur.xyz/p/two-cents-63-generative-ai-moat</id>
        <link href="https://twocents.hur.xyz/p/two-cents-63-generative-ai-moat"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T00:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023년 들어서도 Gen AI 분야의 큰 변화는 멈추지 않고 계속되고 있습니다. 특히 2023년에는 제가 [Two Cents #58]에서 “2세대 모델”이라고 부른 것의 단초가 될만한 변화들이 보이기 시작했습니다. 이는 기존에 우리가 알고 있는 moat, 성공 방정식을 근본적으로 바꿀 잠재력이 있다고 판단됩니다. 이제 3-4회에 걸쳐 Two Cents에서 이 이야기를 해 보려고 합니다. 그 네 번째 이야기는, 이러한 변화 속에서 시장의 구조, moat는 어떻게 변화하고, 그에 따라 단기적으로 그리고 장기적으로 어떤 기회가 있을까? 에 대한 생각입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin Ho Hur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[Two Cents #63] Generative AI — 시장 구조, 기회, moat에 대한 몇 가지 생각]]></title>
        <id>https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-63-generative-ai-moat</id>
        <link href="https://hur.substack.com/p/two-cents-63-generative-ai-moat"/>
        <updated>2023-06-27T00:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023년 들어서도 Gen AI 분야의 큰 변화는 멈추지 않고 계속되고 있습니다. 특히 2023년에는 제가 [Two Cents #58]에서 “2세대 모델”이라고 부른 것의 단초가 될만한 변화들이 보이기 시작했습니다. 이는 기존에 우리가 알고 있는 moat, 성공 방정식을 근본적으로 바꿀 잠재력이 있다고 판단됩니다. 이제 3-4회에 걸쳐 Two Cents에서 이 이야기를 해 보려고 합니다. 그 네 번째 이야기는, 이러한 변화 속에서 시장의 구조, moat는 어떻게 변화하고, 그에 따라 단기적으로 그리고 장기적으로 어떤 기회가 있을까? 에 대한 생각입니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jin Ho Hur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 왜 극단의 다이어트, 극단의 운동을 하는 소년소녀가 탄생했나]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76728</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/06/26/npsp_anorexia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_anorexia"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:59:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 26일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 모든 생명체는 자신의 생명을 유지하기 위해 외부의 에너지를 이용합니다. 식물은 태양빛으로부터 지구의 다른 생명체들이 이용할 수 있는 에너지원을 만들며, 다른 생명체들은 먹이를 통해 생존에 필요한 에너지를 얻습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이게 왜 킬러 문항이죠? 혼란만 더 커졌다: 슬로우레터 6월27일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91951</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91951"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T22:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[내일부터 만 나이. 이게 왜 킬러 문항이죠? 혼란만 더 커졌다. 회식과 단식. “KBS 좌편향 인사 색출”, 이동관 지시였다. 프리고진 철수는 가족에 대한 위협 때문? 민간 용병의 딜레마. 우크라이나 1760만 명이 한계 상황. 한동훈 핸드폰 분실에 강력계 형사들 출동 논란. 해법과 대안. 안 타는 쓰레기 따로 태운다. 이용료 2000원 서울형 키즈 카페, 한 달 예약 찼다....
The post 이게 왜 킬러 문항이죠? 혼란만 더 커졌다: 슬로우레터 6월27일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moulding the Embedded Systems Engineers of Tomorrow: Adapting to a Constantly Transforming Technological Terrain]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1526.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1526.php"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T19:56:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early days of my career, embedded systems engineers were the quiet heroes, armed with logic analyzers and soldering irons, capable of building the heart of devices, from simple digital watches to complex spacecraft control systems. They mastered the art of squeezing performance from minimal resources, their genius manifest in every piece of technology humming silently, unseen, but...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[McGrath: Red Hat’s commitment to open source]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936405/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936405/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T19:38:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat's Mike McGrath responds
to the many criticisms aimed at the company since it changed its policy
regarding RHEL source code.


	Ultimately, we do not find value in a RHEL rebuild and we are not
	under any obligation to make things easier for rebuilders; this is
	our call to make. That brings me to CentOS Stream, of which there
	is immense confusion. I acknowledge that this is a change in a
	longstanding tradition where we went above and beyond, and change
	like this can cause some confusion. That confusion manifested as
	accusations about us going closed-source and about alleged GPL
	violations. There is CentOS Stream the binary deliverable, and
	CentOS Stream the source repository. The CentOS Stream
	gitlab source is where we build RHEL releases, in the open for
	all to see. To call RHEL “closed source” is categorically untrue
	and inaccurate. CentOS Stream moves faster than RHEL, so it might
	not be on HEAD, but the code is there. If you can’t find it, it’s a
	bug – please let us know.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Solving "Two Sum" in C with a tiny hash table]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/06/26/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/06/26/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T19:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I came across a question: How does one efficiently solve Two Sum in C?
There’s a naive quadratic time solution, but also an amortized linear time
solution using a hash table. Without a built-in or standard library hash
table, the latter sounds onerous. However, a mask-step-index table,
a hash table construction suitable for many problems, requires only a few
lines of code. This approach is useful even when a standard hash table is
available, because by exploiting the known problem constraints, it
beats typical generic hash table performance by 1–2 orders of magnitude
(demo).
The Two Sum exercise, restated:
Given an integer array and target, return the distinct indices of two
elements that sum to the target.
In particular, the solution doesn’t find elements, but their indices. The
exercise …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code for all: 10 principles for LGBTQIA+ product inclusion]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/code-for-all-10-principles-for-lgbtqia-product-inclusion.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/code-for-all-10-principles-for-lgbtqia-product-inclusion.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T19:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Danny Rozenblit, Developer Marketing





As LGBTQIA+ Pride Month comes to a close, we will see rainbows leaving shopfronts and social media logos. The need for thoughtful inclusion, however, persists: developers have the opportunity to embrace Pride 365 days of the year by building LGBTQIA+ inclusive products, thinking about how testing and design choices affect others every day.
Ultimately, making your site, app, game, or software system more inclusive for LGBTQIA+ people can improve the user experience for everyone. Therefore, we’re showcasing 10 ways developers can build LGBTQIA+ inclusive products.
While this is a non-exhaustive list, below are some core principles to consider as you build for everyone.







Language matters


Use gender-inclusive and non-binary language

…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언제고 남성성이 끝내 ‘사망’한다면 그 부고기사는 어떤 내용일까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77200</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/06/26/npsp_alienatedmen/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_alienatedmen"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T18:15:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이달 들어 각기 다른 방식으로 남성성을 상징하던 인물 세 명이 죽었습니다. 모두 유명했던 인물로 큰 영향을 끼친 사람인 만큼 주요 언론이 일제히 부고 기사를 썼는데, 뉴욕타임스 칼럼니스트 로스 두댓이 서로 연관 없어 보이는 세 명의 죽음을 엮어 글 한 편을 썼습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 각각의 인물에 관한 배경 설명을 달았습니다. 전문 번역: 남성성을 상징하던 세 명의 죽음 해설: 언제고 남성성이 끝내 ‘사망’한다면 그 부고기사는 어떤 내용일까]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Development statistics for 6.4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936113/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936113/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T16:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.4 kernel was released
on June 25 after a nine-week development cycle.  By that point, 14,835
non-merge changesets had been pulled into the mainline kernel, a slight
increase from 6.3 (14,424 changesets) but still lower than many other
development cycles.  As usual, LWN has taken a look at those changesets,
who contributed them, and what the most active developers were up to.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arduino launches 32-bit UNO board with Wi-Fi, cloud and 96 LED matrix]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479734</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/arduino-launches-32-bit-uno-board-with-wi-fi-cloud-and-96-led-matrix/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T15:06:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following its announcement at Arduino day earlier this year, further details of its new UNO R4 32-bit development board are revealed, including the 12x8 RED LED matrix on board as well as one-click cloud connectivity for IoT applications.
The post Arduino launches 32-bit UNO board with Wi-Fi, cloud and 96 LED matrix appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Broadcom’s latest Wi-Fi 7 chips tell us about the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12571</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/what-broadcoms-latest-wi-fi-7-chips-tell-us-about-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T13:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This story was originally published on June 23, 2023 in my weekly IoT newsletter. You can sign up here. Broadcom’s claim to fame before it became a chip and software conglomerate was that it was able to integrate multiple radios on a single chip. This integration led to energy and cost savings and propelled the adoption of […]
The post What Broadcom’s latest Wi-Fi 7 chips tell us about the IoT appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 검경은, 재판 가면 질 게 뻔한데도, 수사기록을 공개하지 않는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91945</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91945"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T08:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리나라가 법에 의하여 지배되는 국가인가? 대부분 영역에서는 자랑스럽게도 ‘그렇다’라고 할 수 있지만, 수사기관이 하는 행동 중 일부는 예외인 것 같다. 그중에서도 명백하게 수사기관이 위법한 행위를 지금까지도 하고 있는 영역이 있는데, 그것은 바로 수사기록에 대한 열람등사 또는 정보공개신청을 한 경우 보이는 수사기관의 태도다. 결론부터 말하자면, 수사기관은 권리자의 정당한 정보공개신청에 대하여 대부분 비공개결정을 하지만, 이는 대부분 위법한...
The post 왜 검경은, 재판 가면 질 게 뻔한데도, 수사기록을 공개하지 않는가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936332/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936332/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T07:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bind9 and owslib), Fedora (dav1d, dotnet6.0, dotnet7.0, mingw-dbus, vim, and wabt), and SUSE (cloud-init and golang-github-vpenso-prometheus_slurm_exporter).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Red Hat OpenShift 4.13]]></title>
        <id>a6b76d2d-0282-472f-8fca-4e4fc5eb51ab</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/06/26/whats-new-red-hat-openshift-413"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift is a Kubernetes-based app-dev platform that enables developers to build, deploy, and manage containerized applications. It provides a comprehensive set of tools and services for developers, operations teams, and IT organizations to streamline application development and delivery.
Red Hat OpenShift version 4.13, the latest release, introduces several new features and enhancements that help organizations accelerate their digital transformation journey. Let's take a closer look at some of the key features of OpenShift 4.13.
Improved developer experience
OpenShift 4.13 introduces several new features that improve the developer experience and make it easier to build and deploy applications, including creating serverless functions from the developer perspective, using Red Hat O…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donna Smalls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy apps in a K8s cluster via automation controller]]></title>
        <id>92ce2ab7-2ec3-4eeb-b409-bb09e34dc3dd</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/06/26/how-deploy-apps-k8s-cluster-automation-controller"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article demonstrates how to deploy gaming applications in a Kubernetes (K8s) cluster using Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform. The minikube cluster is the best single node cluster for a personal POC. For this article, we will use a minikube cluster and Ansible Automation Platform 2.3 and a restricted set of privileges in the cluster to deploy the application in Kubernetes. Automation and orchestration are a rock solid combination that yield more promising results.
How to start minikube
Make sure you have kubectl and minikube CLI installed before getting started with the Kubernetes cluster.
$ minikube start
😄  minikube v1.26.1 on Redhat 9.1
❗  Specified Kubernetes version 1.25.7 is newer than the newest supported version: v1.24.3. Use `minikube config defaults kubernetes-version` for…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nagesh Rathod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빅토리아 시대와 다윈의 억압을 넘어서: ‘암컷들’ (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91927</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91927"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T06:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제목부터 도발적이다. [암컷들]. 그런데 부제는 더하다. “방탕하고 쟁취하며 군림하는”.  옥스퍼드에서 리처드 도킨스 제자로 동물학을 전공하던 루시 쿡은 “암컷은 착취당하는 성”, “암컷은 수줍음이 많다”, “수컷은 효율성과 적극성을, 암컷은 수동성을 상징한다”는 가르침에 의문을 가졌다. 도킨스, 그 이전에 다윈이 짜놓은 교과서다. 진화론의 경전은 여성을 시민 취급 않던 아리스토텔레스까지 거슬러 올라간다. 그는 실제 암컷들을 확인하기 위해 자연으로 향했다. 학계를 떠나...
The post 빅토리아 시대와 다윈의 억압을 넘어서: ‘암컷들’ (2023) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[타인의 불행은 나의 기쁨, ‘샤덴프로이데’ 권하는 사회]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91845</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91845"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T03:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[타인의 불행을 접하고 기쁨을 느낀 적 있는가? 나는 종종 이 감정을 느낀다. 미디어가 가장 열정적으로 어쩌면 진심을 다해 ‘우리 대신’해 주는 일은 유명 정치인과 기업인, 연예인, 스포츠 스타의 타락과 추락 그리고 불행을 추적하는 일이다. 타인의 불행과 피해가 명백한 범죄와 비행에 관한 것이라면 우리는 거기에 정의감을 결부해 만족감을 느끼지만, 그것이 딱히 범죄와 비행에 연결되지 않더라도, 그리고...
The post 타인의 불행은 나의 기쁨, ‘샤덴프로이데’ 권하는 사회 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.4 kernel has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936132/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936132/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T00:11:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released the 6.4 kernel.


	Most of the stuff in my mailbox the last week has been about
	upcoming things for 6.5, and I already have 15 pull requests
	pending. I appreciate all you proactive people.

	But that's for tomorrow. Today we're all busy build-testing the
	newest kernel release, and checking that it's all good. Right?


Headline features in this release include:
generic iterators for BPF,
the removal of the SELinux runtime disable
knob,
the removal of the SLOB memory allocator,
linear address masking support on Intel
CPUs,
process-level samepage merging control,
support for user trace events,
more infrastructure for writing kernel modules in Rust,
per-VMA locks,
and much more.
See the LWN merge-window summaries (part 1, part 2), and the (in-progress) KernelNewbies 6.4 page for
the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finite State Machine with std::variant]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2023/finite-state-machines-variant-cpp/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2023/finite-state-machines-variant-cpp/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, I’ll show you how to convert a “regular” enum-style finite state machine into a modern version based on std::variant from C++17. This technique allows you to improve design, work with value types and enhance code quality.



     
    


Let’s start with a basic example:
we want to track a game player’s health status
we’d like to respond to events like “Hit by a monster” or “Healing bonus.”
when the health point goes to 0, then we have to restart the game only if there are some remaining lives available
Here’s a basic diagram with states and transitions:




     
    


We can quickly write some basic code based on enum classes:
enum class HealthState { PlayerAlive, PlayerDead, GameOver };
enum class Event { HitByMonster, Heal, Restart };


And the state machine class:
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anthropology and building software systems]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=7967</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/06/25/anthropology-and-building-software-systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T22:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software systems are built by people, who are usually a member of one or more teams. While a lot of research effort has gone into studying the software/hardware used to build these systems, almost no effort has been invested in studying the activities of the people involved. The study of human behaviors and cultures, in […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[기후변화 충격, 수미 감자 못 먹게 될 수도 있다: 슬로우레터 6월26일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91897</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91897"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T22:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[모스크바 턱밑까지 치고 올라온 반란군, 푸틴 쫄았나. 학원이 편의점보다 3배 많다. 출생 통보제 이전에 시행령부터 고친다. 네이버 압도적인 1위 자리 흔들린다. “또 태풍 오면 알거지.” 조선일보, “횟집 회식은 좋은 아이디어.” 돌아온 이낙연, “대선 출정식 같았다.” 낙태권 폐지가 미국 대선 최대 변수. 수미 감자, 못 먹게 될 수도 있다. 정의당 재창당한다. 나이스 먹통, 기술력 부족이 원인....
The post 기후변화 충격, 수미 감자 못 먹게 될 수도 있다: 슬로우레터 6월26일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[하이데거의 시간과 시간성]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223138347982</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223138347982"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T09:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<하이데거에 의하면, 시간과 시간성을 구분해야 한다. 진정으로 의미 있는 시간은 바로 시간성이다. 인간은 시간성을 만들어가야 한다.> 시간과 시간성은 어떻게 구분되는가? 왜 하이데거는 시간이 아니라, 시간성이 진정 의미 있는 시간이라고 했는가? 인간이 시간성을 만들어 가야 한다는 것은 무슨 의미인가? <시간과 시간성은 다르다. 시간성이라는 말은 시간이 아니라, 어떤 것이 가지고 있는 시간적 성격, 혹은 시간적 구조를 가리킨다. 전자의 좋은 예는 후설의 ‘의식의 흐름’이고, 후자의 예는 하이데거의 현존재인 마음씀이다. 하이데거의 시간성은 흐름의 성격은 없고, 마음씀의 구조가 시간적이라는 것이다. 현존재의 존재.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[도서관 연체료를 없앴더니 나타난 놀라운 변화.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91852</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91852"/>
        <updated>2023-06-25T06:01:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국에서는 연체료를 받지 않겠다고 선언하는 공공 도서관이 늘고 있다. 반납 기간을 어긴 사람들에게 수백 년 동안 연체료가 거의 유일한 강제 수단이었는데 이게 효과가 없다는 판단을 뒤늦게 내리게 된 것이다. 미국에서는 2017년 내슈빌에서 시작했고 시카고와 댈러스, 샌프란시스코로 확산됐다. 2021년 뉴욕도 동참했다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 데이터가 말한다. 책이 돌아오기 시작했다. 연체료의 경제학: 1만 원 때문에 도서관을 끊었다....
The post 도서관 연체료를 없앴더니 나타난 놀라운 변화. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[순수이성 비판 강의 1]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223137599890</id>
        <link href="https://blog.naver.com/sellars/223137599890"/>
        <updated>2023-06-24T06:09:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[칸트는 A판 머리말에서 말한다. 인간 이성은 대답할 수 없는 문제로 괴롭힘을 당하고 있다. 우리는 자연스럽게, 즉 <이성의 자연 본성 자체로부터 부과된> 그런 대답할 수 없는 문제에 괴롭힘을 당하고 있다. 칸트가 말하는 우리를 괴롭히는 문제가 바로 형이상학적 문제들이다. 가장 대표적인 것이 <순수이성비판>에서 다루고 있는 네 가지 형이상학적 문제이다. 첫째, 시간과 공간은 한계를 갖고 있는가? 즉 유한한가? 아니면 무한한가? 둘째, 세계의 합성된 실체는 단순한 부분으로 이루어져 있는가? 아니면 그렇지 않은가? 셋째, 자유, 혹은 자유에 의한 인과성이 존재하는가? 아니면 자유란 없는가? 넷째, 세계의 원인인 필연적.......]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sellars</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kuhn: A Comprehensive Analysis of the GPL Issues With the Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) Business Model]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936127/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936127/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T21:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Software Freedom Conservancy blog, Policy Fellow and Hacker-in-Residence Bradley M. Kuhn analyzes the recent changes to Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) source availability in light of the GPL.  It contains some interesting information about two alleged GPL violations that came about because the company's business model is structured in a way that brings it too close to non-compliance with the license, he said:

Perhaps the biggest problem with a murky business model that skirts the line of GPL compliance is that violations can and do happen — since even a minor deviation from the business model clearly violates the GPL agreements. Pre-IBM Red Hat deserves a certain amount of credit, as SFC is aware of only two documented incidents of GPL violations that have occurred since 2006 regarding the RHEL business model. We've decided to share some general details of these violations for the purpose of explaining where this business model can so easily cross the line.

[...] In another violation incident, we learned that Red Hat, in a specific non-USA country, was requiring that any customer who lowered the number of RHEL machines under service contract with Red Hat sign an additional agreement. This additional agreement promised that the customer had deleted every copy of RHEL in their entire organization other than the copies of RHEL that were currently contracted for service with Red Hat. Again, this is a "further restriction". The GPL agreements give everyone the unfettered right to make and keep as many copies of the software as they like, and a distributor of GPL'd software may not require a user to attest that they've deleted these legitimate, licensed copies of third-party-licensed software under the GPL. SFC informed Red Hat's legal department of this violation, and we were assured that this additional agreement would no longer be presented to any Red Hat customers in the future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT news of the week for June 23, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12569</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/iot-news-of-the-week-for-june-23-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T19:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm launches two satellite-enabled chips for the IoT: Qualcomm has released two new chipsets that include satellite-capable modems for use in asset tracking or remote monitoring. Both chips include cellular and satellite capabilities. The chips support Qualcomm’s new Qualcomm Aware cloud platform, but they can also be used absent the platform. However, Qualcomm has launched its cloud platform as […]
The post IoT news of the week for June 23, 2023 appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Removing the kthread freezer]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/935602/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/935602/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T16:27:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The final day of the
2023 Linux Storage, Filesystem,
Memory-Management and BPF Summit featured three separate sessions led by
Luis Chamberlain (he also led a plenary on
day two); the first of those was a filesystem session on the status of the
kthread-freezer-removal effort.  The kthread freezer is meant to help
filesystems freeze their state in order to
suspend or hibernate the system, but since at least 2015, the freezer has been targeted for removal.  Things
did not change much a year later, nor by 
LSFMM in 2018 when Chamberlain had picked up Jiri Kosina's removal
effort; this year, Chamberlain was back to try to push things along.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Buying autonomous electric vehicles will soon be just like buying a laptop]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479724</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/buying-autonomous-electric-vehicles-will-soon-be-just-like-buying-a-laptop/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T16:27:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the future, automakers like Mercedes and BMW will be selling vehicles with marketing like Nvidia inside or Mobileye inside, just like a laptop might be bought that says Intel inside today.
The post Buying autonomous electric vehicles will soon be just like buying a laptop appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Reports from OSPM 2023, part 3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/935180/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/935180/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T14:06:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fifth conference on Power
Management and Scheduling in the Linux Kernel (abbreviated "OSPM") was
held on April 17 to 19 in Ancona, Italy.  LWN was not there,
unfortunately, but the attendees of the event have gotten together to write
up summaries of the discussions that took place and LWN has the privilege
of being able to publish them.  Reports from the third and final day of the
event appear below.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/936040/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/936040/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T13:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (asterisk, lua5.3, and trafficserver), Fedora (tang and trafficserver), Oracle (.NET 7.0, c-ares, firefox, openssl, postgresql, python3, texlive, and thunderbird), Red Hat (python27:2.7 and python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9), Scientific Linux (c-ares), Slackware (cups), SUSE (cups, dav1d, google-cloud-sap-agent, java-1_8_0-openjdk, libX11, openssl-1_0_0, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, openvswitch, and python-sqlparse), and Ubuntu (cups, dotnet6, dotnet7, and openssl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만삭스 S&P 500 전망, 4700까지 상승하나, 경기침체 시 23% 하락한 3400도 가능]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591025</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591025/%ea%b3%a8%eb%93%9c%eb%a7%8c%ec%82%ad%ec%8a%a4-sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-2"/>
        <updated>2023-06-23T01:33:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 마지막 1명까지 사라지고 나면 어떻게 기억해야 하나]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=76713</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/06/22/npsp_holocaust/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_holocaust"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T22:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 그에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. ** 오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 24일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 아직 2023년이 절반도 지나지 않았지만, 벌써 제 마음속 ‘올해의 책 후보’에 오른 책이 한 권 있습니다. ‘아버지의 해방일지’ ‘빨치산의 딸’ 정지아 작가가 지난해 펴낸 책으로, 실제 해방 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마동석이 부러운가? “국정은 때려 잡는 게 아니다”: 슬로우레터 6월23일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91828</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91828"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T21:56:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[주민등록 없는 ‘유령 아이’ 2236명 전수 조사한다. “망신주기 감사, 분노가 치밀어 오른다.” 사교육과의 전쟁, 강남 지역 의원들 속앓이. “대통령에게 제가 진짜 많이 배우는 상황이다.” “킬러 없애면 준킬러 공부해야죠.” 낮은 임금, 무엇을 포기했나 물으니. 50억 클럽 박영수 구속될 듯. 더 깊게 읽기. 대퇴사의 시대에서 대잔류의 시대로. 오늘의 TMI. 주말부터 장마 시작된다. 12세 절반이 영구치에 충치. ‘명박산성’의...
The post 마동석이 부러운가? “국정은 때려 잡는 게 아니다”: 슬로우레터 6월23일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux's response to Red Hat's policy change]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/935918/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/935918/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T20:27:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AlmaLinux organization has posted a message
describing the impact of Red Hat's decision to stop releasing the source to
the RHEL distribution and how AlmaLinux will respond.


	In the immediate term, our plan is to pull from CentOS Stream
	updates and Oracle Linux updates to ensure security patches
	continue to be released. These updates will be carefully curated to
	ensure they are 1:1 compatible with RHEL, while not violating Red
	Hat’s licensing, and will be vetted and tested just like all of our
	other releases.


Update: Rocky Linux has also sent out a
release on the subject.  "There will be no disruption or change for
any Rocky Linux users, collaborators, or partners".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Delivering AIoT is all about ecosystems and co-creation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4479710</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/delivering-aiot-is-all-about-ecosystems-and-co-creation/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T19:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With hardware and software becoming increasingly complex, higher levels of solution selling will be essential for technology vendors selling AIoT. Be prepared for more such co-creation, collaboration, ecosystems, and solutions propositions.
The post Delivering AIoT is all about ecosystems and co-creation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My ranking of every Shakespeare play]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/06/22/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/06/22/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T19:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years ago I set out on a personal journey to study and watch a
performance of each of Shakespeare’s 37 plays. I’ve reached my goal and,
though it’s not a usual topic around here, I wanted to get my thoughts
down while fresh. I absolutely loved some of these plays and performances,
and so I’d like to highlight them, especially because my favorites are,
with one exception, not “popular” plays. Per tradition, I begin with my
least enjoyed plays and work my way up. All performances were either a
recording of a live stage or an adaptation, so they’re also available to
you if you’re interested, though in most cases not for free. I’ll mention
notable performances when applicable. The availability of a great
performance certainly influenced my play rankings.
Like many of you, I had assigned …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Delegating privilege with BPF tokens]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/935195/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/935195/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T15:23:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The quest to enable limited use of BPF features in unprivileged processes
continues.  In the previous episode, an
attempt to use authoritative Linux security module (LSM) hooks for this
purpose was strongly rejected by the LSM developers.  BPF developer Andrii
Nakryiko has now returned with a new mechanism based on a
privilege-conveying token.  That approach, too, has run into some
resistance, but a solution for the strongest concerns might be in sight.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Zephyr: Kconfig]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1541.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1541.php"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T15:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a previous blog post, I introduced The Zephyr Project RTOS and demonstrated a personal best practice when starting with “Zephyr.” In that blog post, you saw how a custom West manifest file is an excellent way to ensure your code is always at a known baseline when you start development. What is the next step in your Zephyr journey after creating your custom manifest file and using...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/935872/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/935872/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T14:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (avahi, hsqldb, hsqldb1.8.0, minidlna, trafficserver, and xmltooling), Oracle (.NET 6.0, .NET 7.0, 18, c-ares, firefox, kernel, less, libtiff, libvirt, python, python3.11, texlive, and thunderbird), Red Hat (c-ares, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, less, libtiff, libvirt, openssl, and postgresql), Slackware (bind and kernel), SUSE (bluez, curl, geoipupdate, kernel, netty, netty-tcnative, ntp, open-vm-tools, php8, python-reportlab, rustup, Salt, salt, terraform-provider-aws, terraform-provider-null, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (bind9, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gke,
 linux-gkeop, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-ibm, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, and linux-ibm).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Podcast: How to add ChatGPT to the smart home]]></title>
        <id>https://staceyoniot.com/?p=12564</id>
        <link href="https://staceyoniot.com/podcast-how-to-add-chatgpt-to-the-smart-home/"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week’s podcast tackles Kevin’s real-world experience with the Google Pixel tablet and speaker dock. He liked the tablet, but as a smart home accessory it’s lacking, which is what we had originally anticipated. But it’s still a bummer, because I want a good Google Home display option as Google deprecates third-party Google Home display […]
The post Podcast: How to add ChatGPT to the smart home appeared first on Stacey on IoT | Internet of Things news and analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stacey Higginbotham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcoming our inaugural Google for Startups Accelerator: Cloud North America cohort]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/welcoming-our-inaugural-google-for-startups-accelerator-cloud-north-america-cohort.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/06/welcoming-our-inaugural-google-for-startups-accelerator-cloud-north-america-cohort.html"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T13:00:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ashley Francisco Head of Startup Ecosystem, North America, Google & Darren Mowry, Managing Director, Corporate Sales, Google







We’re kicking off a summer of accelerators by welcoming the inaugural 2023 North American Google for Startups Accelerator: Cloud cohort, our new class of cloud-native startups in the  United States and Canada.
This 10-week virtual accelerator brings the best of Google's programs, products, people and technology to startups doing interesting work in the cloud. We’re excited to offer these startups cloud mentorship and technical project support, along with deep dives and workshops on product design, customer acquisition and leadership development for technology startup founders and leaders.
We heard from some of the founders from this year’s cohort -  …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[머스크와 저커버그가 ‘현피’를 뜬다고?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=91814</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/91814"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T10:15:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[일론 머스크(테슬라 CEO)와 마크 저커버그(메타 CEO)가 맞장을 뜨기로 했다. 비유적인 표현이 아니다. 만나서 맨주먹으로 싸울 모양이다. ‘현피’는 현실 PK(Player Kill)의 줄임말이다. 온라인에서 다투던 사람들이 직접 만나서 물리적 충돌을 벌이는 걸 말한다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 어떻게 된 일이냐면. 누가 이길까.
The post 머스크와 저커버그가 ‘현피’를 뜬다고? appeared first on 슬로우뉴스.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 애플은 새로운 VR 헤드셋이 아닌 애플 AI 전략이 필요하다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=591021</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/591021/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-ai-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2023-06-22T08:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>