<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2023-12-20T20:13:07.469Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Looking back at 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954535/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954535/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another year has come to an end.  Much to our dismay, 2023 did not, in
fact, happen exactly as we predicted back in
January.  So it seems that, once again, we will have to go through the
process of looking at the predictions that we made and mocking each in
turn, before getting into what was missed altogether.  A lot happened in
2023, not all of which was predictable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LSFMM+BPF 2024 call for proposals]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955827/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955827/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Linux Storage, Filesystem, Memory-Management, and BPF Summit will
be held May 13 to 15 in Salt Lake City, Utah, USA.  The call
for proposals has already gone out, with a deadline of March 1.
"LSF/MM/BPF is an invitation-only technical workshop to map out
improvements to the Linux storage, filesystem, BPF, and memory management
subsystems that will make their way into the mainline kernel within the
coming years."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955812/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955812/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.6.8,
6.1.69,
5.15.144,
5.10.205,
5.4.265,
4.19.303, and
4.14.334
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.

Note that 5.15.145
is already in the review process, with a due date of December 22.  It
consists almost exclusively of ksmbd patches in a flurry of backporting
that was seemingly inspired by the recent marking
of ksmbd as broken in 5.15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955786/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955786/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T15:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (ansible and ansible-core), Gentoo (Minecraft Server and thunderbird), Mageia (fusiondirectory), Red Hat (gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, opensc, and openssl), Slackware (libssh and mozilla), SUSE (avahi, firefox, ghostscript, gstreamer-plugins-bad, mariadb, openssh, openssl-1_1-livepatches, python-aiohttp, python-cryptography, xorg-x11-server, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (libssh and openssh).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 2024년 소매업 전망, 2024년 소매업은 힘든 시기를 겪을 수 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593141</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593141/2024%eb%85%84-%ec%86%8c%eb%a7%a4%ec%97%85-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T08:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/20,  월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593128</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593128/12-20-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate to Red Hat JBoss Web Server 6 using Ansible]]></title>
        <id>d6b3d482-7467-41d2-a842-ba0ab52fabfb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/20/migrate-red-hat-jboss-web-server-6-using-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll discuss how to use the redhat.jws Ansible collection to automate the upgrade of a Red Hat JBoss Web Server instance from 5.7 to the version 6.0. First, we'll use Ansible to install JBoss Web Server 5.7 on the target system and then we'll use another playbook to perform the migration, thus ensuring that the target JBoss Web Server instance has been upgraded successfully.
Prerequisites
To support this demonstration you will first need to have a working Ansible environment. This involves having Ansible installed on the local (control) machine and one or several target hosts. As we are using the certified Ansible collection provided by Red Hat, Ansible needs to be configured to use Red Hat Ansible automation hub to retrieve content. Refer to the official documentation on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romain Pelisse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new oracles of GCC]]></title>
        <id>7394ef0a-fef0-4600-828e-b24c00e93b38</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/20/new-oracles-gcc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new infrastructure has been added to GCC optimizers over the past few years. This was nominally in support of Ranger, the new range generation engine that I have been working on. The primary goal is to modernize the code base and provide flexible usage options throughout the rest of the compiler.
One of the major changes was moving to an on-demand model for calculating ranges. Traditionally range information was created by the VRP (Value Range Propagation) pass and some basic global information was then made available outside this pass. The more accurate context sensitive ranges were only available within the pass. There were some attempts to integrate the old VRPs mechanisms into other passes, but these were awkward and ultimately unsatisfactory.
Ranger however can be enabled in any pas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew MacLeod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2016년 총선넷 낙선운동, 6년만에 재심 무죄]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101170</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101170"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[참여연대 사법감시센터 ‘광장에 나온 판결’] 무죄 확정된 유권자 낙선운동, 선거법 개혁의 첫걸음 지난 11월 22일 서울고등법원은 총선넷 낙선운동을 유죄로 처벌했던 지난 2018년 서울고등법원 판결(2017노3849판결)의 잘못을 인정하고 기본적으로 무죄로 바로잡는 재심결정을 내렸다. 이번 재심에 의해 파기된 항소심 판결의 원심판결은 2017년 12월 1일 서울중앙지방법원에서 내려졌다. 이렇게 시작된 지루한 법정공방이 드디어 대단원의 막을 내린 셈이다. 우여곡절이 있었지만 유권자...
The post 2016년 총선넷 낙선운동, 6년만에 재심 무죄 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering a bricked Wiznet W7500 using the bootloader]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2023-12-20:/w7500-brick-recovery.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/w7500-brick-recovery.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I "bricked" a Wiznet W7500 MCU during development. After flashing yet another build of the firmware
the J-Link disconnected suddenly and I was not able to connect to the chip again (even under reset).
What's funny is that the LEDs blinked as usual and I was able to ping my application so
the chip was far from being dead. I quickly found the suspected piece of code:
pin muxing. When changing PORTA muxing options I must have un-muxed the SWD pins. 🙁]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 연금, 정해진 미래가 만든 ‘방 안의 코끼리’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78092</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/19/npsp_pension/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_pension"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 11월 1일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 20세기 인류 평균수명의 증가는 자연에 대한 인간의 승리를 나타내는 상징입니다. 경제학자 맥스 로저에 따르면 20세기 동안 인간의 평균 수명은 1900년 32세에서 2000년 66.5세로 증가했습니다. 그리고 2020년 아프리카를 제외한 지역의 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사람들이 전두광을 보면서 윤석열을 떠올리는 이유: 슬로우레터 12월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101146</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101146"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 특검, 한동훈의 답변은. 물가에 내놓은 한동훈, 불안한 보수 언론. 윤석열의 승소는 한동훈의 작정한 패소. 김건희에서 송영길로 프레임 전환. 여론 보니 아니었나, 이낙연은 주춤. 더 깊게 읽기. “병립형 퇴행, 또 다른 윤석열 부른다.” 독립적인 인간? 도움을 요청해야 산다. 다르게 읽기. 총선 앞두고 ‘공룡 플랫폼’ 규제법. 오늘의 TMI. 노인 빈곤율 한국이 1위. “동성 커플에 축복”, 교황청...
The post 사람들이 전두광을 보면서 윤석열을 떠올리는 이유: 슬로우레터 12월20일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A hard quiz to crack for C++ programmers by Sergei Kushnirenko]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1093/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1093/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, fun seekers and brainstorming enthusiasts! It's the PVS-Studio team. Now you have an opportunity to pass a new awesome quiz on our website. It has challenging questions from the programming...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The Linux graphics stack in a nutshell, part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955376/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955376/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T17:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux graphics developers often speak of modern Linux graphics
when they refer to  a number of individual software components and how they
interact 
with each other.
Among other things, it's a mix of kernel-managed display resources, 
Wayland for compositing, accelerated 3D rendering, and decidedly not X11.
In a two-part series, we will take a fast-paced journey
through the graphics code to see how it converts application data
to pixel data and displays it on the screen. In this installment, we look
at application rendering, Mesa internals, and the
necessary kernel features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qubes OS 4.2.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955691/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955691/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.2.0 of the Qubes OS distribution has been released; changes
include a switch to Xfce for the Fedora and Debian templates, a number of
rewritten graphical applications, PipeWire support, and more.  See the release
notes for details.  (Qubes OS was last covered here in 2021).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing memory barriers in AI and HPC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481079</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/revolutionizing-memory-barriers-in-ai-and-hpc/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The insatiable demand for memory bandwidth and capacity has been dragging down the overall performance of AI and HPC applications, even with the significant advancement...
The post Revolutionizing memory barriers in AI and HPC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jianping (JP) Jiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI can assist embedded system design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481074</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-ai-can-assist-embedded-system-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you look at PCB design, it’s obvious that there is a huge opportunity for AI to make the process faster, easier, and more successful...
The post How AI can assist embedded system design appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH 9.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955680/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955680/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH
9.6 has been released.  It includes some minor improvements and a fix
for the so-called Terrapin
attack.


	While cryptographically novel, the security impact of this attack
   is fortunately very limited as it only allows deletion of
   consecutive messages, and deleting most messages at this stage of
   the protocol prevents user authentication from proceeding and
   results in a stuck connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 121.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955679/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955679/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T14:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
121.0 of the Firefox browser is out.  Along with the usual pile of
security fixes, this release add the ability to force links to be rendered
with underlines and use of Wayland by default if it is available: "This
brings support for touchpad & touchscreen gestures, swipe-to-nav,
per-monitor DPI settings, better graphics performance, and more."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955678/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955678/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T14:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (webkit2gtk), Fedora (rdiff-backup and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Mageia (cjose and ghostscript), Oracle (avahi), Red Hat (postgresql:10), and SUSE (avahi, freerdp, libsass, and ncurses).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 엔비디아는 Magnificent 7주 중에서 가장 저평가된 기술주]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593124</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593124/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ea%b3%a0%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T14:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2030년 엔비디아 시총은 애플 시총을 앞설까요?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593117</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593117/2030%eb%85%84-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%9c%ec%b4%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T13:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[질서에서 혼돈으로, 우열에서 우연으로: 별의별 아름다움에 관하여]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=95750</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/95750"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 뉴스페퍼민트 이효석 대표가 추천하는 좋은 책에 관한 이야기. 두 번째 책은 다윈의 ‘성선택’ 이론의 복권을 시도한 ‘아름다움의 진화'(리처드 프럼, 2017). 민노: [아름다움의 진화]는 자연선택과 성선택 중 후자에 관해 이야기하고 있습니다. 이효석: 네, 그런데 자연선택과 성선택을 구별하기 전에 먼저 이야기할 것이 있는데요. 사실 이 두 개념을 구별하는 방식에 이미 이 책의 핵심 주장과 또 이...
The post 질서에서 혼돈으로, 우열에서 우연으로: 별의별 아름다움에 관하여 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG그룹 경영권 분쟁 뒷이야기: “아들로 태어나지 않았다는 사실에 죄책감을 느꼈어요.”]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101110</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101110"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[컨텍스트] 유언장도 없는데 아들이 상속재산 독식, “우리 가족은 이런 식이에요.” 뉴욕타임스가 LG그룹의 경영권 분쟁을 추적한 기사를 내보내 눈길을 끈다. 구광모(LG 회장)의 어머니와 두 동생의 인터뷰도 실렸다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 사건의 개요. 지금까지의 이야기. “우리 가족은 이런 식이에요.” 핵심 쟁점: 유언장은 없고 메모는 사라졌다. 알려지지 않은 이야기. LG그룹의 해명. 뉴욕타임스의 평가.
The post LG그룹 경영권 분쟁 뒷이야기: “아들로 태어나지 않았다는 사실에 죄책감을 느꼈어요.” appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI가 추천하는 유망 자율주행 주식]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593106</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593106/%ec%9c%a0%eb%a7%9d-%ec%9e%90%ec%9c%a8%ec%a3%bc%ed%96%89-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributions to the ComplianceAsCode project for OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>6a98a921-e4d5-4b5e-bb40-7d04b0985bd0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/19/contributions-complianceascode-project-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ComplianceAsCode project provides security guidance, baselines, and associated validation mechanisms utilizing the Security Content Automation Protocol (SCAP) to achieve security hardening for various products. ComplianceAsCode provides content for Red Hat OpenShift to comply with the requirements set by local government regulations and industry standards required for deploying the solution.
The ComplianceAsCode content follows the SCAP format to help translate the generic requirements set by the regulatory frameworks into implementation specifics and automate the remediations where possible. Refer to the SCAP Security Guide for more information on SCAP format.
ComplianceAsCode content guide provides the best practices and security relevant configuration guidelines to securely configur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bharath B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/19, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593095</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593095/12-19-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T04:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern On-Target  Embedded System Testing with CMake and CTest]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39676</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/18/modern-on-target-embedded-system-testing-with-cmake-and-ctest/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post discusses the use of continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) pipelines in embedded system testing. It presents a case study on an embedded project, where the author applies automated testing using CTest, Unity testing framework, and CMake, a software building tool, to ensure the project's robustness. The post also exhibits the usage of JRun tool for execution on the hardware and provides detailed instructions on adding and running tests either manually or through Visual Studio Code. It suggests that following this approach would facilitate a modern environment for hardware testing in embedded systems. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘검은 코끼리’의 비극, “바보야, 문제는 대통령이야”: 슬로우레터 12월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101061</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101061"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김기현은 억울하다. 송영길 구속. 민주당이 한동훈 비대위원장을 반기는 이유. 39개월 동안 11번 바꿨다. 강감찬을 임진왜란 때 쓰나. 한동훈 비대위가 맞닥뜨릴 첫 질문은 김건희. 이재명의 ‘안 한다’ 리더십에 부글부글. “민주화 다음 시대정신은 절제와 공존.” 다르게 읽기. 김건희 특검법, 동아일보의 제안. 반값 아파트가 로또가 됐다. 해법과 대안. 인천에서 태어나면 1억 원 받는다. 비빌 언덕이 필요했다. 고등학생 절반이...
The post ‘검은 코끼리’의 비극, “바보야, 문제는 대통령이야”: 슬로우레터 12월19일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year's Eve show: Top 10 errors in C and C++ projects in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1092/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1092/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's December, the first snow has already fallen, and it means New Year's Eve is around the corner. Ahead of the holidays, we'll show you the most interesting errors found in the code of the popular...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking down the C++ quiz by Sergei Kushnirenko]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1091/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1091/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PVS-Studio team along with Sergei Kushnirenko prepared a quiz based on his publications. Take the quiz, challenge your focus and coding skills while looking for errors in the C++ code. This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The intersection of mlx5, netdev, and lockdown]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955001/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955001/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NVIDIA Mellanox ConnectX HW family of adapters is a complex beast,
supporting networking, InfiniBand, RDMA, and more.  As a result, the mlx5
kernel driver that supports this hardware is also complex, as is the
interface that it provides to user space.  The mlx5 developers have, for a
while now, been proposing
the addition of a new control interface, in the form of a separate virtual
device exported by the kernel, that would make vast amounts of debugging
information available.  This driver has encountered some significant
opposition on its way toward the mainline, though, raising a number of
questions about appropriate interfaces and when subsystem maintainers have
veto power over submissions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955566/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955566/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (freeimage, ghostscript, intel-microcode, spip, and xorg-server), Fedora (chromium, perl, perl-Devel-Cover, perl-PAR-Packer, polymake, PyDrive2, seamonkey, and vim), Gentoo (Leptonica), Mageia (audiofile, gimp, golang, and poppler), Oracle (buildah, containernetworking-plugins, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, kernel, kernel-container, libxml2, pixman, podman, postgresql, postgresql:15, runc, skopeo, tracker-miners, and webkit2gtk3), and SUSE (fish).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023년 미디어 이슈 결산 세계 편: 생성형 AI]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100956</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100956"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T11:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. 캡콜드에게 2023년을 돌아볼 수 있는 키워드를 뽑아달라고 요청했다. 그는 챗GPT로 상징되는 생성형 AI와 정권 유지를 위한 억압적인 담론 전략으로서 ‘가짜뉴스’를 각각 가장 중요한 세계구 이슈와 국내 이슈로 뽑았다. 그 두 개의 키워드를 중심으로 이야기했다. 이 글은 그 첫 번째 글이다. 참고로 캡콜드가 선정한...
The post 2023년 미디어 이슈 결산 세계 편: 생성형 AI appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선수와 감독으로 모두 성공한, 축구계 이단아, 과르데올라 감독 리더쉽]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593089</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593089/%ea%b3%bc%eb%a5%b4%eb%8d%b0%ec%98%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ea%b0%90%eb%8f%85-%eb%a6%ac%eb%8d%94%ec%89%bd"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T09:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이재명이 유시민의 제안을 받을까.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101004</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101004"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T07:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[컨텍스트] 양당+지역주의 타파 고민 없는 정치공학적 계산, 최병천도 유시민도 모두 틀렸다. 민주당은 결국 병립형 비례제로 갈 것인가. 최병천(신성장경제연구소 소장)이 권역별 병립형을 밀고 있고 몇 차례 논쟁이 있었지만 여전히 결론을 내리지 못한 상태다. 김어준의 ‘뉴스공장’에서 최병천을 몇 차례 띄웠고 이대로 가면 국민의힘이 과반을 얻는다는 공포가 확산되면서 병립형으로 기우는 분위기다. 이탄희(민주당 의원)가 위성정당 금지법을 발의하면서 연동형 포기는...
The post 이재명이 유시민의 제안을 받을까. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top application development articles of 2023]]></title>
        <id>8f039fd4-41a4-49b3-b631-4e381a67dd29</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/18/top-application-development-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're wrapping up our Best of 2023 series by highlighting our most popular application development articles from the past year.
The business of delivering cloud-native applications gets more complex every day. It’s no surprise that solutions for improving developer experience are in high demand, especially for enterprise teams. Red Hat Developer Hub, based on the open source Backstage project, is one such solution that provides easy access to curated tools, resources, and Golden Path templates for quicker and easier software development. By reducing complexity and automating tedious tasks, developers are free to focus on what they do best: write code and ship new features.
The 10 most popular application development articles of 2023
Our most-read articles on application development focus o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java monitoring: Exploring Cryostat 2.4 features on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>41267961-eaea-41b9-a9e7-4fc50c72ac2f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/18/java-monitoring-exploring-cryostat-24-features-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat's latest build of Cryostat 2.4, designed specifically for the Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform, brings a wealth of features and enhancements that cater to various monitoring needs for Java applications.
At its core, Cryostat 2.4 excels in comprehensive Java Flight Recorder (JFR) data management. Users can effortlessly start, stop, retrieve, archive, import, and export JFR data, all through an intuitive web console or an accessible HTTP API. This enhances the ease with which developers can handle JVM performance data. Moreover, Cryostat 2.4 provides flexibility in terms of data storage and analysis. Users can store and analyze JFR data directly on their Red Hat OpenShift or export it to external monitoring applications for a deeper dive into the data.
ARM (aarch64)
A significant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaaf, Syed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.7-rc6]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955485/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955485/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.7-rc6 for testing.
" Please do give this a test in between the last-minute xmas shopping or
whatever else is going on ..."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Image Processing Algorithms in FPGA Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1616.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1616.php"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T23:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image processing plays a crucial role in various applications, from medical imaging to computer vision and multimedia systems. Field-Programmable Gate Arrays (FPGAs) offer a versatile and efficient platform for implementing image processing algorithms. The unique features of FPGA hardware, such as parallelism and reconfigurability, enable high-performance and real-time processing, making it an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사람들 착각이 아니라 그들이 ‘진짜 현실’을 못 보는 것 아닐까요]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78366</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/17/npsp_vibecession/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_vibecession"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T23:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뉴욕타임스 오피니언 란에는 최근의 거시경제를 설명해 주는 글이 자주 올라옵니다. 이런 칼럼들은 대개 “바이든 행정부의 경제 성적표가 생각만큼 나쁘지 않다”는 결론으로 글을 맺곤 합니다. 구구절절 드는 이유를 읽다 보면 논리적으로 이해가 가다가도 한편으론 주변 사람들 사는 모습은 여전히 팍팍해 보이던데 경제가 정말 잘 돌아가고 있는 게 맞나 의구심이 들기도 합니다. 칼럼니스트 트리시 맥밀란 커텀이 이 괴리를 자세히 분석한 칼럼을 썼습니다. 소위 경제학자들이 거시경제 지표에 파묻혀 오히려 쉽게 확인할 수 있는 ‘필수 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patches for the code of Peter Turchin’s Attrition Warfare Model]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8447</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/12/17/patches-for-the-code-of-peter-turchins-attrition-warfare-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T22:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paper Empirically Testing Predictions of an Attrition on Warfare Model for the War in Ukraine, by Peter Turchin, recently showed up during one of my regular searches for software engineering data. A quick scan of the paper founded that it is very empirical, and that the analysis coding was done in R; I could […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“이러다 또 탄핵 당한다”, 한동훈 비대위 두고 갈등 폭발: 슬로우레터 12월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100978</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100978"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T22:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[탄핵 막으려 한동훈? “한동훈 되면 탄핵될 수도.” “이러다 또 탄핵 당한다.” 한동훈 정치력 시험대는 김건희. 류호정, 정의당 텔레그램에서 쫓겨났다. 적격이라던 정의찬, 없던 일로. 국민 89%가 의대 증원 찬성. 감액된 예산, 민주당이 단독 처리하나. 더 깊게 읽기. 지드래곤과 검사 처남의 전혀 다른 마약 수사. 다르게 읽기 화이트칼라 이그젬션. “민주당은 뭐했냐”고 묻는 조선일보. 오늘의 TMI. ‘오래 사는...
The post “이러다 또 탄핵 당한다”, 한동훈 비대위 두고 갈등 폭발: 슬로우레터 12월18일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Min: sched_ext: a BPF-extensible scheduler class (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955481/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955481/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changwoo Min provides
an introduction to the sched_ext scheduling class:


	Sched_ext was proposed to address the problems mentioned above. It
	allows users to write a custom scheduling policy using BPF without
	modifying the kernel code. You don't need to struggle to maintain
	the out-of-tree custom scheduler. In addition, BPF provides a safe
	kernel programming environment. In particular, the BPF verifier
	ensures that your custom scheduler has neither a memory bug nor an
	infinite loop. Also, if your custom scheduler misbehaves -- like
	failing to schedule a task for too long (say 30 seconds), the
	kernel portion of sched_ext kills your custom scheduler and falls
	back to the default kernel scheduler (CFS or EEVDF). Last but not
	least, you can update the BPF scheduler without reinstalling the
	kernel and rebooting a server.


(LWN looked at sched_ext in February 2023).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So you want custom allocator support in your C library]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/12/17/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/12/17/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of mature C libraries conventionally get to choose how memory is
allocated — that is, when it cannot be avoided entirely. The C
standard never laid down a convention — perhaps for the better —
so each library re-invents an allocator interface. Not all are created
equal, and most repeat a few fundamental mistakes. Often the interface is
merely a token effort, to check off that it’s “supported” without actual
consideration to its use. This article describes the critical features of
a practical allocator interface, and demonstrates why they’re important.
Before diving into the details, here’s the checklist for library authors:
All allocation functions accept a user-defined context pointer.
The “free” function accepts the original allocation size.
The “realloc” function accepts both old …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[논문리뷰] Row hammer 논문 리뷰]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15845156</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15845156"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T14:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이 논문은 흔히 Row-hammer attack 으로 알려져 있는 공격에 대한 연구이다. 
Kim, Yoongu, et al. "Flipping bits in memory without accessing them: An experimental study of DRAM disturbance errors." ACM SIGARCH Computer Architecture News 42.3 (2014): 361-372.
이 방식은 Hardware 에 대한 공격이라고 할 수 있다. 거의 모든 종류의 DRAM이 공통적으로 가지고 있는 이슈를 이용한 공격이다. (논문의 저자진은 삼성 및 Intel에서 인턴쉽을 수행한적이 있는 카네기 멜론 출신의 연구자들인데, 이 현상을 발견한 후 논문으로 발표를 하게 되어 회사들 입장에서는 약간 곤란했었다고 한다.)

DRAM이란 트랜지스터와 커패시터로 구성된 메모리 셀을 통해 데이터를 저장한다. 그리고 DRAM에 Access하거나 Refresh하는 방식으로 데이터를 관리한다. 원칙적으로 하나의 메모리 주소에 대한 접근은 다른 주소에 저장된 데이터에 의도하지 않은 영향을 미쳐서는 안된다. 이에 1970년대부터 DRAM 제조 업체들은 셀 간 간격을 유지하고 테스트를 통해 오류 발생 가능성을 최소화하고 있었다. 그러나 DRAM 공정 기술이 미세화됨에 따라 DRAM 셀 간의 전기적 상호 작용을 방지하기가 점점 더 어려워지고 있다. 


2014년 본 연구진의 실험에 따르면 상용 DRAM의 동일한 주소에 읽기 작업을 반복하다보면 인근 주소의 데이터를 손상시킬 수 있다는 것이 확인되었다. 마치 특정 row에 있는 부분을 해머로 계속 때리면 그 옆의 row들이 영향을 받는다는 취지에서 이름을 붙인 것이다. 일종의 Fault Injection 이라고 볼 수 있다. 
의도적으로 DRAM에 부하를 가하는 악의적인 프로그램을 통해, DRAM의 동일한 행을 활성화하는 것은 인근 행의 데이터를 손상시킬 수 있다는 사실을 인텔 및 AMD 주요 DRAM모듈(129개 중 110개)에서 확인하였다. 


해머링을 수행하다보면 트랜지스터 행에서 주변 인접한 행으로 전하가 누출되고, 그로 인해 메모리상의 특정 비트 값이 1에서 0으로, 또는 0에서 1로 뒤집힌다(flipping). 이 사소한 비트 전환으로 인해 운영체제 수준에서 권한 상승이 발생할 수도 있다. 실제로 이를 악용하여 시스템에서의 권한 상승이나 네트워크 기반 공격도 가능하다고 알려져 있다.


후속 연구에 대해서는 추후 더 다룰 예정.


참고: (유머)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[자율주행 테마주 넥스트칩, 자율주행 성장 수혜를 받는 글로벌 영상신호처리 1위 기업]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593086</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593086/%ec%9e%90%ec%9c%a8%ec%a3%bc%ed%96%89-%ed%85%8c%eb%a7%88%ec%a3%bc-%eb%84%a5%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%ec%b9%a9"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T15:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/16, 월가의 투자의견 및  주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593073</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593073/12-16-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T12:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 당신이 먹는 것의 먹는 것까지 생각해 보자는 제안]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78071</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/15/npsp_seafoodchain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_seafoodchain"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 30일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난 4월, 저는 방글라데시 라나 플라자 의류공장 붕괴 사고 10주기를 맞아 쓴 글에서 윤리적인 소비에 관해 생각할 거리를 나눴습니다. 그 글에서 저는 의식주의 공급망을 하나씩 따져보면서 음식은 신선도를 유지하지 못하면 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeMaio: Insights from the openSUSE Logo Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955366/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955366/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to the expressed unhappiness over the recent logo-selection
process in the openSUSE project (covered in this article), the project has announced
that there will be a new vote:


	During the community meeting this week where the results were
	discussed, participants expressed the view that members of the
	openSUSE Project have an opportunity to participate in the
	selection of our new logo, and that SUSE, which holds the trademark
	to the openSUSE logo, be involved with the process for selecting a
	branding decision with regard to the results. After all, this
	decision impacts the collective identity.

	To facilitate this, there is a plan to organize a vote between the
	current logo and the proposed new design, allowing our community to
	have a say in this important decision. Furthermore, members of the
	project are collaborating with SUSE on the implications of the
	branding initiatives and some have expressed the desire for SUSE’s
	input to ensure there is an aligned vision for the future of
	openSUSE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Progress toward a GCC-based Rust compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954787/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954787/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gccrs project is an ambitious
effort started in 2014 to implement a Rust compiler within The GNU Compiler
Collection (GCC).  Even though the task is far from complete, progress has
been made since LWN's previous coverage,
according to reports from the project.  Meanwhile, another hybrid and more
mature approach to GCC Rust code generation is available in rustc_codegen_gcc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955336/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955336/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T14:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bluez and haproxy), Fedora (curl, dotnet6.0, dotnet7.0, tigervnc, and xorg-x11-server), Red Hat (avahi and gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free), Slackware (bluez), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, cont, cosign, curl, gstreamer-plugins-bad, haproxy, ImageMagick, kernel, kernel-firmware, libreoffice, tiff, traceroute, tracker-miners, webkit2gtk3, and xrdp), and Ubuntu (audiofile, budgie-extras, libreoffice, strongswan, vim, and yajl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이제 『이제 공간에 주의하십시오』에 주의하십시오]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3195</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2023/book/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T09:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["이 책은 우리가 살고 느끼고 경험하는 공간을 다각도로 해석한다. 점유한다는 의미에서 공간이나 두 공간을 잇는 공간, 혹은 공간 그 아래의 공간에 대해 풀어내는 방식이 사뭇 흥미를 불러일으킨다. 독자들에게 자신이 살아가고 인식하는 공간의 종류와 특성에 대해 생각해 보게 하며, 이를 바탕으로 우리의 몸, 주변의 건물과 동네, 그리고 도시와 세계에 이르는 여러 장소의 성격을 다채롭게 보여줌으로써 공간에 대한 이해의 폭을 깊고 넓게 만들고 있다."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/15, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593059</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593059/12-15-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T03:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25 years of Postfix]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955248/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955248/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T23:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wietse Venema posted a note to the postfix-users mailing list about the 25th anniversary of the Postfix mail server.  As can be seen, it had a pivotal role in bringing more awareness of open-source software to IBM.  Beyond that, of course, it is an excellent piece of software in its own right.


As a few on this list may recall, it is 25 years ago today that the
"IBM secure mailer" had its public beta release. This was accompanied
by a nice article in the New York Times business section.

There is some literature at https://www.postfix.org/press.html that
attests how this project accelerated open-source adoption by a very
large company.


That release was even noticed by a small publication in its first year of operation.

(Thanks to Kees van Vloten.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7년 동안 초등학생 100만 명 줄어든다: 슬로우레터 12월15일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100927</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100927"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T22:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아이 키우기 힘든 세상의 참담한 미래. 출마만 하면 당선인데… 세 번째 비대위원장은 원희룡? 나경원? 이재명도 퇴진 압박. 다르게 읽기. “권역별 병립형 비례제는 개악이다” “권역별 병립형이 정치 개혁이다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명 분신, 김용 유죄 선고가 말하는 것. 학교폭력 신고 10년 만에 최다. 챗GPT, 언론사에 뉴스 이용료 낸다. 긴축 21개월, 미국 금리 내리나. 잃어버린 30년, 이제...
The post 7년 동안 초등학생 100만 명 줄어든다: 슬로우레터 12월15일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.28: support for ARM, .NET 8, analysis of Unreal Engine projects without Unity Build, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1090/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1090/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.28 has been released. Now you can run the analyzer on the ARM architecture, analyze .NET 8 projects, and check Unreal Engine projects without Unity Build — and there is more to come! See...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Ext4 data corruption hits the stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954770/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954770/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's stable-update process is intended to produce kernels that are,
well, stable; when that promise is lived up to, users can update to newer
stable updates without fear.  By any account, a bug that corrupts data on
ext4 filesystems constitutes a failure to hold to that promise.  As is so
often the case, this problem is the result of a chain of failures in a
system that works well most of the time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955130/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955130/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and rabbitmq-server), Fedora (chromium, kernel, perl-CryptX, and python-jupyter-server), Mageia (curl), Oracle (curl and postgresql), Red Hat (gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, linux-firmware, postgresql, postgresql:10, and postgresql:15), Slackware (xorg), SUSE (catatonit, containerd, runc, container-suseconnect, gimp, kernel, openvswitch, poppler, python-cryptography, python-Twisted, python3-cryptography, qemu, squid, tiff, webkit2gtk3, xorg-x11-server, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (xorg-server and xorg-server, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top automation articles for developers in 2023]]></title>
        <id>7232edba-77ff-4483-8ee2-297cfd899929</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/14/top-automation-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to Red Hat Developer’s Best of 2023 series, as we take a look back at the articles that captured developers’ attention over the past 12 months.
Automation and artificial intelligence (AI) were the talk of the town this year, with significant breakthroughs in open source and generative AI. 2023 also saw many advancements in Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform; new offerings like Ansible Lightspeed and Event-Driven Ansible increase the efficiency of teams writing automation code and let developers focus on more strategic tasks.
The 10 most popular Ansible and automation articles of 2023
Based on our most-read articles this year, developers were particularly interested in learning about Ansible Automation Platform and ways to utilize it. Our list of top articles features tutorial…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Kafka consumers]]></title>
        <id>d4a9e391-556e-4330-904b-e1f949b97e47</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/14/introduction-kafka-consumers"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes and Apache Kafka are becoming de-facto platforms for developing and deploying microservice architectures. 
Kafka is a distributed data streaming platform that enables applications to publish, subscribe to, store, and process streams of messages (or events) in real-time.
These messages are stored inside Kafka topics. A topic is a set of messages you aim to organize for consumption. Each topic is stored on disk, replicated across brokers to ensure fault tolerance, and messages within the topic are retained for a designated time. Figure 1 shows an overview of a Kafka cluster.


  Figure 1: Shows a Kafka broker with three topics, where different applications produce and consume messages from topics.
We can consider topics as a logical grouping for messages. A Kafka topic, however, i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Soto Bueno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve Go FIPS test coverage with Packit]]></title>
        <id>09c1b271-dcca-4d3c-a4a1-0186f5d6d810</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/14/how-improve-go-fips-test-coverage-packit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, Fedora contributors use Packit a lot to keep packages up to date. In general, using the service is extremely easy, but as we will see, integrating it with a complex multi-source project with an extensive cryptographic test suite like the Go FIPS project needed a little tweaking. But the effort will be worth it.
The Go FIPS CI before Packit
In the Go FIPS repository, we use GitHub Actions to test the pull requests before merging them. We run the whole test suite with each pull request's changes in several containers to ensure it works on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 7, 8, and 9. The differences between these three versions of RHEL give us fantastic coverage, but there is a limitation. We can only build on AMD64 if we rely on GitHub Actions without external systems.
Accessing a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sáez Morollón</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 14, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953980/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953980/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 14, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 예술은 정치로부터 자유로워야? 그렇게 단순하지만은 않은 문제]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78031</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/13/npsp_literaturewar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_literaturewar"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 25일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난 18일 개막된 독일의 프랑크푸르트 도서전은 세계 최대의 도서전으로 불립니다. 이 도서전에는 제3세계 여성작가의 작품 중 독일어로 번역된 작품에 주어지는 리베라투르 상이 있습니다. 올해 리베라투르 상은 팔레스타인 출신인 아다니아 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희가 무섭나? 보수 언론의 공포와 분노: 슬로우레터 12월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100901</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100901"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김기현 사퇴 카드 먹힐까. “김건희 문제, 직언할 수 있어야 한다.” “김기현 탓 아니다”, 이준석의 조언. 윤석열은 격노? 김건희 특검법 거부하면 민주당에 꽃놀이패. “욕심대로라면 제1당이 돼야 한다.” 네덜란드 반도체 동맹, 실체가 있나. 더 깊게 읽기. 학생을 버린 대학. YS의 당이 ‘서울의봄’ 흥행에 왜 떠나. 가계 부채는 문재인 정부 탓? 오늘의 TMI. “제로섬 정치 떠난다.” 돈 봉투...
The post 김건희가 무섭나? 보수 언론의 공포와 분노: 슬로우레터 12월14일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Logo and trademark issues for openSUSE]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954760/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954760/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A contest for new logos
for the openSUSE project and for
four separate distributions of it, 
Tumbleweed, Leap, Slowroll, and  
Kalpa, has turned into a
bit of an uproar in that community.  A vote
has been held on the candidates and winners have been announced, but
some are questioning why there is a need to change the existing logo (the
"Geeko" 
chameleon) at all.  In addition, there are questions about whether the
new logo will be trademarked (as previous ones have been)—and how many
years that will take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operation K. Looking for bugs in the IntelliJ IDEA code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1089/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1089/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we check the IntelliJ IDEA Community Edition project for errors and send the fixes to its developers. A large project, an open-source base, and a static analyzer that helps the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954983/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954983/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T20:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.6.7,
6.1.68,
5.15.143,
5.10.204,
5.4.264,
4.19.302, and
4.14.333
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust for Linux — in space]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954974/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954974/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust for Linux (RFL) project may not have (yet) resulted in user-visible
changes to the Linux kernel, but it seems the wider world has taken notice.
Hongyu Li has announced
that the Rust for Linux code is now part of a satellite just launched
out of China.  The satellite is running a system called RROS, which follows the old
RTLinux pattern of running a realtime kernel alongside Linux.  The realtime
core is written in Rust, using the RFL groundwork.


	Despite its imperfections, we still want to share RROS with the
	community, showcasing our serious commitment to using RFL for
	substantial projects and contributing to the community's
	growth. Our development journey with RROS has been greatly enriched
	by the support and knowledge from the RFL community. We also have
	received invaluable assistance from enthusiastic forks here,
	especially when addressing issues related to safety abstraction


(Thanks to Dirk Behme).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenPGP for application developers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954964/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954964/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new book called OpenPGP for application
developers has been released under the Creative Commons BY-SA license.


	This document is not intended for end-users or implementers of
	OpenPGP libraries (or other software that directly handles internal
	OpenPGP data structures).

	Instead, this document is focused on the second group, application
	developers, who use OpenPGP functionality in their software
	projects. It describes the properties of the OpenPGP system and its
	uses. It presupposes solid knowledge of software development
	concepts and of general cryptographic concepts. Thus, this text
	describes OpenPGP at the “library-level,” teaching concepts that
	will help software developers get started as a user of any
	implementation (e.g., OpenPGP.js, Sequoia-PGP).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954921/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954921/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T14:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (debian-security-support and xorg-server), Fedora (java-17-openjdk, libcmis, and libreoffice), Mageia (fish), Red Hat (buildah, containernetworking-plugins, curl, fence-agents, kernel, kpatch-patch, libxml2, pixman, podman, runc, skopeo, and tracker-miners), SUSE (kernel, SUSE Manager 4.3.10 Release Notes, and SUSE Manager Client Tools), and Ubuntu (gnome-control-center, linux-gcp, linux-kvm, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-6.2, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.2, linux-nvidia-6.2, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, netatalk, and pydantic).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 주가 전망, 엔비디아 주가는 2024년에도 계속 상승할 것인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593057</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593057/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 채권 수익률 하락은 주식 시장에 엄청난 호재가 될 수 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593055</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593055/%eb%b0%b0%eb%9f%b0%ec%8a%a4-%ec%b1%84%ea%b6%8c-%ec%88%98%ec%9d%b5%eb%a5%a0-%ed%95%98%eb%9d%bd%ec%9d%80-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5%ec%97%90-%ec%97%84%ec%b2%ad%eb%82%9c-%ed%98%b8%ec%9e%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가트너, 2024년 기술 트렌드 10가지 : 전략 읽기]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=13110</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2023/12/13/gartner-hype-cycle-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T08:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[가트너에서 지난 10월 17일, 2024년 트렌드를 발표했습니다. 보통 이런 자료들은 정부 쪽으로 넘어가 그 해의 정책방향에 반영됩니다.또는 은행권이나 통신사 처럼 정책방향에 발을 맞춰주는 기업들이 기술구매를 시도하기도 합니다. 당연히 프로젝트 수요가 생깁니다.다만, AI 로 넘어가면서 상황이 어려워졌습니다만… 내용이 조금 어렵습니다.초보자분들을 위해 설명해 봅니다. 01. AI Trust, Rish and Security Management (AI TRiSM) AI를 쓰면 뭐가 좋을까요?글쎄요.... Continue Reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[학생을 버린 대학: 한신대 우즈벡 학생 강제 출국 사건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100878</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100878"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아시아에서 가장 취약한 전통이 사림(士林)의 존재감이다. 그나마 조선이 나라답게 작동했던 시절이 훈구파와 사림파가 적절하게 견제하며 권력을 주고받았던 때가 마지막이었다. 물론 이러한 균형은 여러 차례의 잔혹한 사화(士禍)로 막을 내렸으며, 이후는 교조화된 노론과 외척 세력이 정치와 사회를 지배하면서 체제 몰락으로 이어졌다. 지식이라는 형이상학적 권력을 제도화한 게 대학(大學)이라는 기관인데, 당연히 중세 종교사회와 연관이 깊다. 성직자는 당대 최고 지식인이어야...
The post 학생을 버린 대학: 한신대 우즈벡 학생 강제 출국 사건 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정호재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[차트로 살펴본 빅테크의 미래 by CB Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593040</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593040/%eb%b9%85%ed%85%8c%ed%81%ac%ec%9d%98-%eb%af%b8%eb%9e%98"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: SoftwareAndEngineering]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/SoftwareAndEngineering.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/SoftwareAndEngineering.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout my career, people have compared software development to
  “traditional” engineering, usually in a way to scold software developers for not
  doing a proper job. As someone who got his degree in Electronic Engineering,
  this resonated with me early in my career. But this way of thinking is flawed
  because most people have the wrong impression of how engineering works in
  practice.
Glenn Vanderburg has spent a lot of time digging
  into these misconceptions, and I strongly urge anyone who wants to compare
  software development to engineering to watch his talk Real Software Engineering. It's also well worth
  listening to his interview on the podcast Oddly
  Influenced. Sadly I've not been able to persuade him to write this
  material down - it would make a great article.
Another good thinker on this relationship is Hillel Wayne. He interviewed a
  bunch of “crossovers” - people who had worked both in traditional engineering
  and in software. He wrote up what he learned in a series of essays, starting
  with Are We Really Engineers?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/13, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593026</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593026/12-13-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T02:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘기회의 평등’에 기반했던 아메리칸 드림에 빨간 불이 켜진 까닭은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78341</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/12/npsp_collegeamericandream/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_collegeamericandream"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T01:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“미국판 스카이 캐슬”로 불리던 바시티 블루 스캔들이 있었습니다. 미국의 부유한 기득권층이 자기 자녀에게 남들보다 앞서서 출발할 수 있는 특혜를 주려고 법까지 어겨가며 대학 입시에 부정을 저지른 일인데요, 칼럼니스트 제시카 그로즈가 왜 자식에게 물려줄 돈도 많은 부유층, 기득권층 부모들이 법을 어겨가면서까지 자녀를 명문대에 보내려 혈안이 돼 있는지 짚은 칼럼을 썼습니다. 흔히 미국을 누구든 열심히 일하면 성공할 수 있는 기회의 땅이라 부르고, 아메리칸 드림이란 말도 있지만, 계층 이동의 사다리 역할을 하는 교육에 공정함과 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LTE and IoT - How We Got Here]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/lte-and-iot</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/lte-and-iot"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I describe some of my findings from a recent investigation of how LTE technology was built for IoT systems. Complete with some history
and a few diagrams to illustrate cellular network architecture and LTE power-saving features like eDRX and PSM, this read will give a nice introduction to LTE in embedded systems.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“사소한 게 아니야”]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=84822</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/84822/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[잡스는 창과 문서, 화면 등의 상단에 위치한 제목 표시 줄에도 똑같은 관심을 쏟아 부었다. 그것들의 디자인에 대해 고뇌하면서 앳킨슨과 케어에게 수없이 반복해서 수정하게 만들었다. [중략] 앳킨슨은 회상한다. “그가 만족할 때까지 아마 스무 개가 넘는 제목 표시 줄 디자인을 만들었을 거예요.” 어느 시점에서 케어와 앳킨슨은 더 중요한 일이 있는데 잡스 때문에 제목 표시 줄에 사소한 수정을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The end of vger.kernel.org]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954783/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954783/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konstantin Ryabitsev has announced
that the movement of kernel mailing lists away from the venerable
vger.kernel.org system is nearly complete:


	Over the past few months we've migrated all of the vger.kernel.org
	mailing lists, with the exception of the Big One (linux-kernel, aka
	LKML). This list alone is responsible for about 80% of all vger
	mailing list traffic, so we left it for the last.

	This Thursday, December 14, at 11AM Pacific (19:00 UTC), we will
	switch the MX record for vger to point to the new location
	(subspace.kernel.org), which will complete the mailing list
	migration from the legacy vger server to the new infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘습관성 각설이 외유’? 윤석열 순방 왜 더 많아 보일까: 슬로우레터 12월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100862</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100862"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“습관성 각설이 외유다.” 윤석열 순방, 왜 더 많아 보일까. 쟁점과 현안. 장제원을 밟고 어디로 가나. 김기현 손절한 조선일보. 민주당은 여전히 이재명 충성 경쟁. ‘사쿠라’와 ‘김민새’. 더 깊게 읽기. 위성 정당을 막을 방법이 없다. 오늘의 TMI. 6070이 30대보다 신차 더 뽑았다. 구글 글로벌 검색어 1위 레시피 비빔밥. 억만장자 비밀금고 아부다비로 몰린다. 해법과 대안. ‘단계적 퇴출’이 빠졌다....
The post ‘습관성 각설이 외유’? 윤석열 순방 왜 더 많아 보일까: 슬로우레터 12월13일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graber: LXD now re-licensed and under a CLA]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954777/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954777/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T21:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of Canonical's takeover of the LXD container manager, and the
subsequent creation of the Incus fork, has been
simmering for a while.  Now Incus developer Stéphane Graber reports
that Canonical has changed the license and contribution terms for LXD:


	Per the commit message performing the re-licensing, all further
	contributions will be under the AGPLv3 license and all
	contributions from Canonical employees have been re-licensed to
	AGPLv3.

	However, Canonical does not own the copyright on any contribution
	from non-employees, such as the many changes they have imported
	from Incus over the past few months. Those therefore remain under
	the Apache2 license that they were contributed under.

	As a result, Canonical cannot release LXD under the AGPLv3 license
	and likely never will be able to.  LXD is now under a weird mix of
	Apache2 and AGPLv3 with no clear metadata indicating what file or
	what part of each file is under one license or the other.


He also notes that this change will put an end to the flow of patches — in
either direction — between the two projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What IoT developers need to know about cybersecurity labels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481056</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/what-iot-developers-need-to-know-about-cybersecurity-labels/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T19:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the IoT and cybercrime have grown, IoT device security has become a more prominent concern. Regulators have been slow to adapt to these trends,...
The post What IoT developers need to know about cybersecurity labels appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Project Bluefin: A customized Fedora Silverblue desktop image]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954059/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954059/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So-called "immutable" Linux distributions have been in development for
some time, but (unless you count Chrome OS) haven't gained much traction. Project Bluefin, is a heavily
customized set of Fedora
Silverblue images coming from the Universal Blue community; they are
designed to deliver a reliable Linux desktop that's as easy to use as a
Chromebook but more customizable. Bluefin's mission is to change up
the desktop experience and attract a new generation of open-source
contributors with a "cloud-native"
take on developing and delivering the operating system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: what are hierarchical state machines?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481053</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-what-are-hierarchical-state-machines/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this sixth lesson on state machines, I’d like to give you the first glimpse of modern hierarchical state machines (HSMs). In this sixth lesson...
The post Programming embedded systems: what are hierarchical state machines? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954706/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954706/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T15:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libreoffice and webkit2gtk), Fedora (java-1.8.0-openjdk and seamonkey), Oracle (apr, edk2, kernel, and squid:4), Red Hat (postgresql:12, tracker-miners, and webkit2gtk3), SUSE (curl, go1.20, go1.21, hplip, openvswitch, opera, squid, and xerces-c), and Ubuntu (binutils, ghostscript, libreoffice, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15,
 linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gke,
 linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-nvidia,
 linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4,
 linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm,
 linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, postfixadmin, python3.11, and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11월 미국 소비자물가지수(CPI) 요약과 평가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593022</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593022/11%ec%9b%94-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%86%8c%eb%b9%84%ec%9e%90%eb%ac%bc%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80%ec%88%98cpi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역대 대법관 156명 중 여성은 얼마나 될까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100848</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100848"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T13:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[민언련 이달의 좋은 보도상 수상자 인터뷰] 기획보도 ‘이토록 XY한 대법원’을 쓴 경향신문 이혜리·김희진·김혜리 기자 “당신이 성범죄 사건의 피해자가 되었다고 가정해보자.” “만약 당신이 남성이라면 성별이 같은 남성 판사를 적어도 한 명은 법정에서 만날 수 있다.” “그러나 당신이 여성이라면 이야기가 달라진다.” “재판부 전원이 여성 판사일 가능성은 전국 모든 고등법원에서 0%다.” 경향신문, ‘이토록 XY한 대법원’ (연재) 중에서 성범죄...
The post 역대 대법관 156명 중 여성은 얼마나 될까 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTN MBC KBS2, 왜 팔아먹지 못해서 안달인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100840</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100840"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T08:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아무리 생각해도 쉽게 답이 나오지 않는다. 국민의힘이나 그 전신에 해당하는 정당이 집권했을 때는 대체로 공영방송을 매각해야 한다는 뜻을 밝히거나 시도했는데 그 이유가 쉽게 떠오르지 않는다. 박근혜 전 대통령이 후보 시절인 2012년에는 정수장학회가 갖고 있는 MBC 주식을 기업에 매각하려 했다. 한바탕 소란만 피우고 끝났지만, MBC를 개인 기업이 사유하도록 하는 이른바 ‘사영화’를 추진해야 한다는 이야기는 끊임없이 제기되었다....
The post YTN MBC KBS2, 왜 팔아먹지 못해서 안달인가 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘멋진 패배’ 무용론? 전두광 닮은 현실론… 정치인 ‘이태신’을 기대하며]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100822</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100822"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T07:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 병립형 회귀 vs. 준연동형, 민주당 갈등이 실망스러운 네 가지 이유 (김형철)2. ‘멋진 패배’ 무용론? 전두광 닮은 현실론… 정치인 ‘이태신’을 기대하며 (유성진) 영화 ‘서울의봄’을 보았다. 1979년 겨울 벌어진 역사적 사실을 기초로 감독의 허구적 상상력이 더해진 영화는 반전과 반전을 거듭하며 두 시간이 넘는 러닝타임이 무색하게 그야말로 순식간에 지나갔다. 권력에 대한 욕망에 수단과 방법을 가리지 않는 ‘전두광’과...
The post ‘멋진 패배’ 무용론? 전두광 닮은 현실론… 정치인 ‘이태신’을 기대하며 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top Kubernetes articles for developers in 2023]]></title>
        <id>52463bed-3ca9-4f94-9404-4838136fa822</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/12/top-kubernetes-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we bid farewell to 2023, we’re highlighting the most popular articles published on Red Hat Developer this year.  Kubernetes continues to be a vital area of innovation; new tools and solutions intended to simplify application development and operations are proliferating, as developers seek ways to cope with the growing complexity of managing infrastructure. It was also an exciting year in the world of Red Hat OpenShift, the hybrid cloud application platform powered by Kubernetes.
  [ Learn about what’s new with Red Hat OpenShift 4.14 ] 
The 10 most popular Kubernetes articles of 2023
Read on for our most-read articles on Kubernetes topics from the past year. We’ve got a guide to using Kubernetes on OpenShift, patterns for managing and deploying Helm charts, testing libraries for Kubernet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Skupper to expose services over TLS]]></title>
        <id>7b8d1814-6134-447d-b091-32fcc4c45ffb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/12/how-use-skupper-expose-services-over-tls"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securing inter-cloud connections through end-to-end with TLS is necessary, ensuring not only the confidentiality and integrity of data exchanged between cloud environments but also safeguarding against unauthorized access. While inter-router communication in Skupper is always fortified with mutual TLS, it's essential to note that, by default, communication between services and routers does not have this encryption layer. Deploying TLS in client-router and router-service is possible to fortify the entire communication ecosystem.
Skupper ensures mutual TLS (mTLS) for inter-router communications by default, and users have the option to enhance security by enabling TLS specifically between services and the Skupper routers, with the flexibility to either auto-generate certificates through Skupp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noe Luaces</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KBS는 평정? 고 김용균 무죄 판결엔 무관심, 서해 공무원 피살 감사 발표엔 쌍심지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100810</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100810"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T05:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[민언련 언론 모니터] 2007년 17대 대선에서 진성호(당시 한나라당 간사)는 “네이버 평정” 발언을 했습니다. 박민 사장 취임 이후 KBS는 평정된 걸까요? 고 김용균 원청 무죄 판결과 서해 공무원 피살 감사 발표에 관한 방송사 리포트를 민언련이 모니터링했습니다. 2018년 12월 태안화력발전소에서 일하다 숨진 하청노동자 김용균 씨의 사망 책임을 원청에 물을 수 없다며 대법원이 12월 7일 한국서부발전 전 사장에게...
The post KBS는 평정? 고 김용균 무죄 판결엔 무관심, 서해 공무원 피살 감사 발표엔 쌍심지 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/12, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593010</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593010/12-12-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 뛰어난 업적을 남기고도 공로를 인정받지 못한 여성의 역사]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78026</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/11/npsp_goldin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_goldin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 23일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 뛰어난 재능을 보였지만 꽃 피울 기회를 얻지 못했거나, 업적을 남기고도 제대로 된 인정과 평가를 받지 못한 여성들의 명단은 성차별과 남성 중심주의의 역사만큼이나 깁니다. 자신도 뛰어난 조각가였지만, ‘로댕의 연인’으로만 알려졌던 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[나라가 망해간다는 지표와 신호, 절박하긴 한 건가: 슬로우레터 12월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100785</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100785"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[네덜란드에 간 윤석열 최대 고민은 쌍특검. ‘윤핵관’ 장제원 불출마. “윤석열과 화해? 망상이다.” 낙준연대 빅 텐트, 가능할까. 다르게 읽기. 직방 금지법 만드나. 총선 출발선이 다르다. 행복하다는 비율, 세계 꼴찌 수준인 이유. 더 깊게 읽기. 재벌 내부거래 41조 원 늘었다. 김건희 김영란법 위반, 검찰이 계속 뭉갤 수 있을까. “국감 전에 팩트체크 페이지 내려야 한다 했다.” 오늘의 TMI....
The post 나라가 망해간다는 지표와 신호, 절박하긴 한 건가: 슬로우레터 12월12일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to lure programmers to your conference booth?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1088/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1088/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will share some thoughts on what a booth staffer actually does, what types of activities visitors prefer, and how to keep the booth busy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bottomley: Solving the Looming Developer Liability Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954528/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954528/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Bottomley writes
that open-source developers are increasingly likely to be held liable for
flaws in their code and suggests a solution:


	Indemnification means one party, in particular circumstances,
	agreeing to be on the hook for the legal responsibilities of
	another party. This is actually a well known way not of avoiding
	liability but transferring it to where it belongs. As such, it’s
	easily sellable in the court of public opinion: we’re not looking
	to avoid liability, merely trying to make sure it lands on those
	who are making all the money from the code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: TestDrivenDevelopment]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/TestDrivenDevelopment.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/TestDrivenDevelopment.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Test-Driven Development (TDD) is a technique for building
	software that guides software development by writing tests. It was
	developed by Kent
	Beck in the late 1990's as part of
	Extreme Programming. In essence we follow three simple
	steps repeatedly:
Write a test for the next bit of functionality you want to add.
Write the functional code until the test passes.
Refactor both new and old code to make it well structured.


Although these three steps, often summarized as Red - Green -
  Refactor, are the heart of the process, there's also a vital initial
  step where we write out a list of test cases first. We then pick one of these
  tests, apply red-green-refactor to it, and once we're done pick the next.
  Sequencing the tests properly is a skill, we want to pick tests that drive us
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some recent and notable changes to Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954033/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954033/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust project makes incremental releases every six
weeks, a fact that makes it easy to overlook some of the
interesting changes coming to the language, such as new
ABIs, better debugger support, asynchronous traits, and
support for C strings.
The end of the year provides an opportunity to look back
over the past several months of updates, and to look
forward to what to expect in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The era of digital therapeutics is just beginning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481045</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-era-of-digital-therapeutics-is-just-beginning/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronics devices that monitor various physical phenomena – activity, pulse rates – have been available for two decades now, but more and more manufacturers are now developing digital therapeutic products. 
The post The era of digital therapeutics is just beginning appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Santo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.7-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954469/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954469/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T14:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.7-rc5 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	Nothing looks particularly scary, which is good, because if it had
	been, I wouldn't have had the capacity to deal with it last week.

	Let's hope it stays that way even as I am getting better. Because the
	holidays are almost upon us, and I'm woefully underprepared.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954454/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954454/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T14:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.6.6 and 6.1.67 stable kernels.  Both contain a single
reversion of the "wifi: cfg80211: fix CQM for non-range use" patch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954449/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954449/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T14:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (bluez, chromium, and curl), Red Hat (apr), Slackware (libxml2), and Ubuntu (squid3 and tar).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How embedded development shift is influencing future compute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481037</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-embedded-development-shift-is-influencing-future-compute/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T13:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are now leveraging secure, performance-enhancing technologies to enable small, low-power embedded systems for previously unimaginable voice, vision and vibration applications that are changing the world.
The post How embedded development shift is influencing future compute appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Williamson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 연말 테슬라 판매전략은 가격인하에서 인센티브 강화로 변경]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593004</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593004/%ec%97%b0%eb%a7%90-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5%ec%9d%80-%ec%9d%b8%ec%84%bc%ed%8b%b0%eb%b8%8c-%ea%b0%95%ed%99%94"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T12:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top Linux articles for developers in 2023]]></title>
        <id>e05def17-6b6d-4bf6-9e22-4118960fd108</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/11/top-linux-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're kicking off our annual year-end roundup with a look back at the Linux content that engaged our readers the most in 2023. Linux remains a dominant player in the cloud thanks to its stability and flexibility, and Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) continues to evolve for the containerized future, with the General Availability release of RHEL 9.3 last month.
Our 10 most popular Linux articles of 2023
Here are 10 of our most-read articles on Linux from 2023, which cover a mix of topics including containers, new milestones for RHEL, and various ways to simplify Linux systems management with the latest compilers and tools.
New improvements in Red Hat Enterprise Linux
How the new RHEL 9.2 improves the developer experience by Nikhil Mungale and Alex Krikos: This article highlights new features …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over-provisioning nodes on OpenShift Service on AWS]]></title>
        <id>0173c929-42f8-46e1-bf11-a3324971e0c5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/11/over-provisioning-nodes-openshift-service-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There might be occasions where over-provisioning your cluster will provide great benefit. If there are sudden bursts of pods being created in a short amount of time, there can be situations where a new node is spinning up but is not ready. This can cause issues as pods will stuck in a pending phase for about ten minutes whilst waiting for the new node. A solution to this is to over-provision your cluster. This enables a spare node at all times, or pre-emptily create a new node when the workflow starts to pick up.
Use cases
With this solution, pods are created that are considered low priority. When the more important workloads are created, the low priority pods get removed from the nodes. This leaves the low priority pods in a pending state. This forces Red Hat OpenShift to spawn a new node…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maz Arslan, Anton Giertli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡과 파리바게뜨, 소비자가 무섭지 않은 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100701</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100701"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T06:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 고 김용균 원청기업 및 대표 무죄 판결에 관하여… 국제노동기구 고용정책국장 이상헌 박사와 나누는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기. 5년 전. 김용균, 24살. 2018년 12월 10일 태안화력발전소 비정규직으로 일하면서 한밤중에 혼자 점검에 나섰다. 그게 마지막이었다. 석탄 운반용 컨베이어 벨트가 김용균을 삼켰다. 청년의 죽음을 우리는 슬퍼했다. 겨우겨우 중대재해처벌법을 만들었다. 지난 12월 7일, 김용균...
The post 쿠팡과 파리바게뜨, 소비자가 무섭지 않은 이유 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인간은 합리적이지만 또 비합리적인데요…]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78319</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/11/npsp_nudge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_nudge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T04:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[행동경제학을 바탕으로 한 넛지(nudges)는 지난 10년 사이 많은 주목을 받은 개념입니다. 다양한 부문에서 넛지가 도입되고 접목됐죠. 그러나 넛지의 효과를 둘러싼 논란도 처음부터 꾸준히 제기됐습니다. 행동경제학을 창시하는 데 중요한 역할을 했다고 볼 수 있는 대니얼 카네만도 비판에서 자유롭지 못하죠. 뉴욕대학교 디지털이론 연구소장 레이프 웨더비가 넛지의 효과와 한계에 관해 글을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 대세가 된 ‘넛지’, 그러나 과학적 근거는 부족하다 해설: 인간은 합리적이지만 또 비합리적인데요…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주목해야할 구글 마피아 스타트업 10개 by CB Insight]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592992</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592992/%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80-%eb%a7%88%ed%94%bc%ec%95%84-%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%80%ed%8a%b8%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T02:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six Handy Operations for String Processing in C++20/23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2023/six-handy-ops-for-string-processing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2023/six-handy-ops-for-string-processing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore six practical string processing operations introduced in C++20 and C++23. These features represent an evolution in this crucial area, covering a spectrum of operations from searching and appending to creation and stream handling.
Let’s start with a simple yet long-awaited feature…
contains(), C++23 
  




     
    


Finally, after decades of standardization, we have a super easy way to check if there’s one string inside the other. No need to use .find(str) != npos!
Before C++23:
#include <string>
#include <iostream>

int main() {
    const std::string url = "https://isocpp.org";

    if (url.find("https") != std::string::npos &&
        url.find(".org") != std::string::npos &&
        url.find("isocpp") != std::string::npos)
        std::cout << "You're us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[원전으로 탈탄소? 워싱턴포스트가 윤석열을 ‘팩폭’했다: 슬로우레터 12월11일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100736</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100736"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T22:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[살생부 돌면 김건희 특검법 반란표? “선거는 안중에도 없습니까.” 지지율 32%인데 또 외국 방문. “류호정 나가달라”, “못 나간다.” 이낙연, “이준석은 보기 드문 인재.” 더 깊게 읽기. 이준석 신당이 성공하기 어렵다고 보는 이유. 부울경·호남 이탈 80%가 청년이었다. 다르게 읽기. 문과 침공 이대로 좋은가. 유럽은 ‘마이너리티 리포트 법’ 만들었다. 해법과 대안. 워싱턴포스트의 윤석열 ‘팩폭’. 연 날려서 전기 만든다....
The post 원전으로 탈탄소? 워싱턴포스트가 윤석열을 ‘팩폭’했다: 슬로우레터 12월11일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11.7 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3117-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3117-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T16:10:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the sixth maintenance release of Python 3.11
Python 3.11.7 is the newest major release of the Python programming language, and it contains many new features and optimizations. Get it here:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3117/
Major new features of the 3.11 series, compared to 3.10

Among the new major new features and changes so far:


PEP 657 – Include Fine-Grained Error Locations in Tracebacks
PEP 654 – Exception Groups and except*
PEP 673 – Self Type
PEP 646 – Variadic Generics
PEP 680 – tomllib: Support for Parsing TOML in the Standard Library
PEP 675 – Arbitrary Literal String Type
PEP 655 – Marking individual TypedDict items as required or potentially-missing
bpo-46752 – Introduce task groups to asyncio
PEP 681 – Data Class Transforms
bpo-433030– Atomic group…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas books for 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8438</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/12/10/christmas-books-for-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T13:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s Christmas book list, based on what I read this year, and for the first time including a blog series that I’m sure will eventually appear in book form. “To Explain the World: The discovery of modern science” by Steven Weinberg, 2015. Unless you know that Steven Weinberg won a physics Nobel prize, this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA, 주식 시장 괴물 랠리가 과매수 수준에 가까워지면서 주식 시장의 ‘매수’신호가 죽었다고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592990</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592990/bofa-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5-%ea%b4%b4%eb%ac%bc-%eb%9e%a0%eb%a6%ac%ea%b0%80-%ea%b3%bc%eb%a7%a4%ec%88%98-%ec%88%98%ec%a4%80%ec%97%90-%ea%b0%80%ea%b9%8c%ec%9b%8c%ec%a7%80%eb%a9%b4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T11:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ext4 data corruption in stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954285/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954285/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T22:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a problem in multiple stable kernel releases that is causing data corruption in ext4 filesystems.  It is caused by a problematic commit that is in multiple stable kernels:

The commit got merged in 6.5-rc1 so all stable kernels that have
91562895f803 ("ext4: properly sync file size update after O_SYNC direct
IO") before 6.5 are corrupting data - I've noticed at least 6.1 is still
carrying the problematic commit.


More information can be found in a Debian bug report. It has also delayed the release of Debian 12.3 images. "Please do not upgrade any systems at this time, we urge caution for users
with UnattendeUpgrades configured."

(Thanks to Alex Ridevski for giving us a heads up on this.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sign in with GitHub in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/sign-in-with-github-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/sign-in-with-github-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It's common to see web applications that let you log in through third-party
services. &quot;Sign in with Google&quot; is particularly popular; on developer-oriented
websites, &quot;Sign in with GitHub&quot; also pops up quite a bit. In this post, I want
to briefly explore OAuth - the technology that enables these delegated logins …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 years of DOOM: new code, new bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1087/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1087/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the 30th anniversary of the first game in the DOOM series! We couldn't miss the event. To honor the occasion, we decided to see what the code of this legendary game looks like after all...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/9, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592976</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592976/12-9-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T17:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 고 이율 시대는 계속될 것이다. 그것이 경제에 미치는 영향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592965</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592965/%ea%b3%a0-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a8-%ec%8b%9c%eb%8c%80-%ec%98%81%ed%96%a5"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T10:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I have been copied on Aliexpress!]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2023-12-09:/i-have-been-copied-on-aliexpress.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/i-have-been-copied-on-aliexpress.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery. A while ago I published a design of a basic coax switch for HF antennas. To my surprise, a fellow ham messaged me that I am "famous" on Aliexpress. 🙂]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Changes]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/gochanges</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/gochanges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way Go changes, and how to improve it with telemetry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Modern C for Fedora (and the world)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954018/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954018/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T16:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It can be instructive to pull down the dog-eared copy of the first edition
of The C Programming Language that many of us still have on our
bookshelves; the language has changed considerably since that book was
published.  Many "features" of early C have been left behind, usually for
good reasons, but there is still a lot of code in the wild that is still
using those features.  A concerted effort is being made in both the Fedora
and GCC communities to fix that old code and enable some new errors in the
GCC 14 release (which is in
stage 3 of its development cycle and likely to be released by
mid-2024), but a fair amount of work remains to be done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A bunch of new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954107/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954107/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.6.5, 6.1.66, 5.15.142, 5.10.203, 5.4.263, 4.19.301, and 4.14.332 stable kernels have been released.
As usual, they contain important fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statistical Profile Extension: extracting value from SPE for SoC Telemetry]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:46715707-f121-4a6a-9bc0-ddb24d9f4e75</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/statistical-profile-extension"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We refer to the SPE performance methodology whitepaper published by Arm for details on the content of this blog.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Jeff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 미국 전기차 거품이 꺼지고 있다. 이는 수치로 증명되고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592961</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592961/%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ea%b1%b0%ed%92%88-%eb%b6%95%ea%b4%b4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954092/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954092/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T14:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium), Mageia (firefox, thunderbird, and vim), SUSE (kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-tools- container, virt-operator-container), and Ubuntu (freerdp2, glibc, and tinyxml).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 1: Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) introduction]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:65dfa3dd-b3dd-42ee-930d-1301a6ee028b</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/p1-arm-scalable-matrix-extension-introduction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog series provides an introduction to the Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) including SVE and SVE2.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zenon Xiu (修志龙）</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI 답변 – 구글 제미나이에도 마소 빙챗 사용 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592959</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592959/%eb%b9%99%ec%b1%97-%ec%82%ac%ec%9a%a9-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/8, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592943</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592943/12-8-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T03:22:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3121-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3121-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T00:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.1 is now available.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3121/
 

This is the first maintenance release of Python 3.12
Python 3.12 is the newest major release of the Python programming language, and it contains many new features and optimizations. 3.12.1 is the latest maintenance release, containing more than 400 bugfixes, build improvements and documentation changes since 3.12.0.

 
Major new features of the 3.12 series, compared to 3.11
 
New features
More flexible f-string parsing , allowing many things previously disallowed (PEP 701).
Support for the buffer protocol  in Python code (PEP 688).
A new debugging/profiling API  (PEP 669).
Support for isolated subinterpreters  with separate Global Interpreter Locks (PEP 684).
Even more improved error messages. More exc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 가자지구는 ‘창살 없는 무덤’이 돼 버릴 것인가]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77999</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/07/npsp_israelhamas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_israelhamas"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 20일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 이스라엘과 하마스 사이에 벌어진 전쟁이 시작된 지 12일째입니다. 해묵은 원한과 증오의 역사가 또다시 되풀이되고 있습니다. 이스라엘은 주변 국가의 우려와 만류를 뿌리치고, 가자지구에 지상군을 투입할 준비를 마쳤습니다. 지난 7일 기습 공격에 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“민주당 200석도 가능하다”, 설레발일까, 자신감일까: 슬로우레터 12월8일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100673</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100673"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“4년 전과 비슷하다. 이대로면 참패.” “‘수포당’으론 희망이 없다.” “민주당 200석도 가능하다.” “김용균 사망, 원청 기업은 책임 없다.” “여기서 져도 다른 데서 이긴다.” 쟁점과 현안. “공무원 ‘자진 월북’ 사건은 조작됐다.” “나치 정당이냐”, 민주당 당헌 개헌 논란. “정치가 얼마나 험난한지 배웠다.” 더 깊게 읽기. ‘로또 영장’, 문제는 발급 기준이 없다는 것. 오늘의 TMI. 김건희 7시간 통화 공개,...
The post “민주당 200석도 가능하다”, 설레발일까, 자신감일까: 슬로우레터 12월8일.  appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Few words about Java code hygiene]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1086/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1086/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While reviewing code or working on a new project, we can get annoyed by many things: style, approaches, quality. However, the most frustrating is the trite lack of code hygiene. Since the issue is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Controlling shadow-stack allocation in clone3()]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953794/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953794/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T16:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User-space shadow stacks are a relatively new feature in Linux; support was
only added for 6.6, and is limited to the x86
architecture.  As support for other architectures (including arm64 and RISC-V) approaches readiness,
though, more thought is going into the API for this feature.  As a recent
discussion on the integration of shadow stacks with the clone3() system call shows, there are
still some details to be worked out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just about every Windows and Linux device vulnerable to new LogoFAIL firmware attack
(ars technica)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953985/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953985/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
ars technica article describes how secure-boot firmware on a huge range
of systems can be subverted with a malicious image file:


	As its name suggests, LogoFAIL involves logos, specifically those
	of the hardware seller that are displayed on the device screen
	early in the boot process, while the UEFI is still running. Image
	parsers in UEFIs from all three major IBVs [independent BIOS
	vendors] are riddled with roughly a dozen critical vulnerabilities
	that have gone unnoticed until now. By replacing the legitimate
	logo images with identical-looking ones that have been specially
	crafted to exploit these bugs, LogoFAIL makes it possible to
	execute malicious code at the most sensitive stage of the boot
	process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953977/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953977/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (tzdata), Fedora (gmailctl), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (linux-firmware, postgresql:12, postgresql:13, and squid:4), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, cont, frr, libtorrent-rasterbar, qbittorrent, openssl-3, openvswitch, openvswitch3, and suse-build-key), and Ubuntu (bluez, curl, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-laptop, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-oem-6.5, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux-starfive, linux-gcp, open-vm-tools, postgresql-12, postgresql-14, postgresql-15, and python-cryptography).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이제 전직 경찰이 학폭 조사한다: 교사노조, 교총, 전교조, 좋은교사, 참학 입장은 이렇다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100464</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100464"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T05:40:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[긴급 현안 분석] 이제 2700명의 학폭전담조사관이 학교폭력을 조사한다. 이에 관한 교사노조, 교총, 전교조, 좋은교사, 참학의 입장을 들었다. (‘통칭’ 가나다순.) 이제 2700명의 학폭전담조사관이 학교폭력을 조사한다. 지난 10월 6일 대통령과 교사 간담회 이후 2개월 만이다. 2024학년도, 3월 1일부터 교육청 소속 퇴직 경찰 퇴직 교사 출신 학교폭력 전담 조사관(이하 ‘조사관’)이 학폭 사안을 경중과 학교 안팎을 가리지 않고, 모두...
The post 이제 전직 경찰이 학폭 조사한다: 교사노조, 교총, 전교조, 좋은교사, 참학 입장은 이렇다 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Zephyr: Writing Data to EEPROM]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1613.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1613.php"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T02:34:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[INTRODUCTION
In a previous blog post (Getting Started With Zephyr: Saving Data To Files), I demonstrated how to create an application using The Zephyr Project RTOS to store data on a microSD card. A microSD card can allow an embedded system to store tremendous amounts of data. The data can be stored locally when no Internet connection is present, or uploading data frequently is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 7, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953381/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953381/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 7, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tools for Learning LLVM TableGen]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2023-12-07-tools-for-learning-llvm-tablegen/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2023-12-07-tools-for-learning-llvm-tablegen/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TableGenis a language used within the LLVM project for generating a variety of files,when manual maintenance would be very difficult.
For example, it is used to define all of the instructions that can be used on aparticular architecture. The information is defined in TableGen and we canproduce many things based on that single source file. C++ code, documentation,command line options, and so on.
TableGen has been in existence sincebeforethe first official release of LLVM, over 20 years ago.
Today in the LLVM project repository there areover a thousand TableGen source files totalling over 500,000 lines of code.Making it the 5th most popular language in the repository.

Languagefilesblankcommentcode

C++2964295854218701015544445
C/C++ Header118443168064998451486165
C1053525990016035941011269
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The LLVM Project Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A schism in the OpenPGP world]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953797/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953797/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T22:16:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The OpenPGP standard for email
encryption has been around since 1997, when it was derived from the
venerable Pretty Good
Privacy (PGP) program that was released in 1991.  Since it came about,
OpenPGP has been the decentralized, interoperable way to exchange encrypted
email, though 
its use never really took off as advocates hoped. Now, though, it
would seem that a split in the OpenPGP community threatens to
fragment the OpenPGP-encrypted-email landscape, potentially leading to
interoperability woes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“꼭 이렇게 해야 하나” 조선일보의 불만: 슬로우레터 12월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100609</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100609"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T22:02:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[형님과 떡볶이. ‘검찰 선배’ 김홍일이 방통위로 온다. 조선일보의 강한 불만. 친윤 불출마는 없던 일로. 윤석열 명예훼손 혐의? 뉴스타파 대표 압수수색. 트럼프에게 “독재할 거냐” 물었더니. 다르게 읽기. 요소수 사재기, 문제는 불신. 트위치도 못 버티는 한국의 망 사용료? 더 깊게 읽기. ‘녹색 카르텔’은 관심 없나. 오늘의 TMI. 유동규 교통사고는 단순 사고. “병원이 춘절 기차역 같다.” 남산 곤돌라...
The post “꼭 이렇게 해야 하나” 조선일보의 불만: 슬로우레터 12월7일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day when Skynet becomes self-aware, and 69 reasons to chill out with colleagues. Part 2.]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1085/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1085/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it's difficult to come up with a reason for gathering and hanging out with your colleagues. You may say that we have official holidays and birthdays — yeah, that's right — but it's still...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My TDD Journey Started Dec 6, 1999]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1612.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1612.php"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T20:50:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On December 6, 1999, as an embedded developer with 20 years of experience, I attended the first Extreme Programming Immersion.  That is where I bumped into TDD. I thought: that is odd; it could not work; but what if it did? The alternative was painful, so my mind was open to finding a better way to work.
During my first 20 years, we developed software concurrently with HW and never had a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SLAM: a new Spectre technique]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953880/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953880/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T16:03:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many processor vendors provide a mechanism to allow some bits of a pointer
value to be used to store unrelated data; these include Intel's linear address masking (LAM), AMD's upper address ignore, and Arm's top-byte
ignore.  A set of researchers has now come up with a way (that
they call "SLAM") to use those features to bypass many checks on pointer
validity, opening up a new set of Spectre attacks.


	In response to SLAM, Intel made plans to provide software guidance
	prior to the future release of Intel processors which support LAM
	(e.g., deploying LAM jointly with LASS). Linux engineers developed
	patches to disable LAM by default until further guidance is
	available. ARM published an advisory to provide guidance on future
	TBI-enabled CPUs. AMD did not implement guidance updates and
	pointed to existing Spectre v2 mitigations to address the SLAM
	exploit described in the paper.


See the full
paper for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953861/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953861/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T14:33:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium, clevis-pin-tpm2, firefox, keyring-ima-signer, libkrun, perl, perl-PAR-Packer, polymake, poppler, rust-bodhi-cli, rust-coreos-installer, rust-fedora-update-feedback, rust-gst-plugin-reqwest, rust-pore, rust-rpm-sequoia, rust-sequoia-octopus-librnp, rust-sequoia-policy-config, rust-sequoia-sq, rust-sequoia-wot, rust-sevctl, rust-snphost, and rust-tealdeer), Mageia (samba), Red Hat (postgresql:12), SUSE (haproxy and kernel-firmware), and Ubuntu (haproxy, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-6.2, linux-azure, linux-azure-6.2,
 linux-azure-fde-6.2, linux-lowlatency, linux-oracle, linux-raspi,
 linux-starfive, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, linux-oem-6.1, and redis).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing the WebAssembly bitmask operations on the 64-bit Arm architecture]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:71dac4a5-061e-4268-bc35-8dcabcc201b8</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/webassembly-bitmask-operations"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We discuss some of the challenges that we face when we are trying to implement the WebAssembly SIMD bitmask operations on the 64-bit Arm architecture.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Kirilov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[보수정당이 집권하면 정말 자살과 살인이 증가할까?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100474</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100474"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T03:17:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, ‘홍보가 아니라 소통입니다’ 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기. 오늘 ‘마냐의 북라이딩’이 고른 책은 ‘왜 어떤 정치인은 다른 정치인보다 위험한가’. 그리고 질문들. 자살과 살인은 개인의 문제가 아니라 제도와 시스템의 문제, 특히 정치의 문제라고 책은 말합니다. (편집자) 여기 그래프가 하나 있다. 100년 동안 미국에서 자살하거나 살해당한 사람들의...
The post 보수정당이 집권하면 정말 자살과 살인이 증가할까? appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전두환의 쿠데타와 윤석열의 쿠데타는 어떻게 같고 다른가.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100535</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100535"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T02:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[리뷰] 서울의 봄. 어떻게 이런 일이 가능했는지 복기해 보자. 보안사령관 전두환은 소장(★★)이었고 전두환이 체포한 육군참모총장(계엄사령관) 정승화는 대장(★★★★)이었다. 전두환이 정승화를 불법 체포했던 날 저녁, 용산 육군본부 벙커에는 류병현(한미연합군사령부 부사령관, ★★★★)과 김종환(합동참모의장, ★★★★), 윤성민(육군참모차장, ★★★), 이건영(3야전군사령관, ★★★) 등 전두환보다 계급이 높은 장성들이 수두룩했지만 아무런 결단도 지시도 내리지 못했다. 전두환의 쿠데타는 실패할 뻔 했다. 상명하복 시스템의 커다란 구멍....
The post 전두환의 쿠데타와 윤석열의 쿠데타는 어떻게 같고 다른가. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전쟁 중인 나라보다 낮은 출생률, 우리가 해야 할 고민은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78296</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/05/npsp_koreadissapearing/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_koreadissapearing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T02:00:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뉴욕타임스 칼럼니스트 로스 더우댓이 쓴 칼럼 “Is South Korea Disappearing?”이 화제입니다. 이미 국내 언론에서도 여러 차례 소개가 되었죠. 칼럼을 번역하고, 예일대학교 정신의학과 나종호 교수의 해설을 실었습니다. 역사상 유례를 찾아보기 힘들 만큼 낮은 출생률도 문제지만, 높은 자살률을 보아도 한국의 젊은 세대는 감당하기 힘든 하루하루를 보내고 있는 것 같습니다. 전문 번역: 대한민국은 사라지고 있는가? 해설: 전쟁 중인 나라보다 낮은 출생률, 우리가 해야 할 고민은]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in November (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/november-2023-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/november-2023-roundup"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
November.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 명품백 몰카 영상, MBC에 실리지 못한 이유: 슬로우레터 12월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100489</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100489"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T22:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 몰카 영상 킬 당해서 사표냈다. 경향신문과 한겨레가 칭찬한 대법원장 후보자. “내가 전임 지사 부인 법카와 무슨 관계가 있나.” 한국이 우크라이나에 보낸 포탄, 유럽 전체보다 많다. 쟁점과 현안. 민주당 지역구만 줄어드나? 선거구 획정안 논란. 이낙연 출당 요구 2만 명. 방통위원장도 검사 출신. “하마스 1명 죽을 때 민간인 2명 죽으면 좋은 성적.” 오늘의 TMI. 슈퍼 에이저(super...
The post 김건희 명품백 몰카 영상, MBC에 실리지 못한 이유: 슬로우레터 12월6일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI prompt best practices for writing embedded software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481032</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ai-prompt-best-practices-for-writing-embedded-software/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T21:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ll share some best practices that should help you improve your prompts to get better results from AI models. Are you using AI yet to...
The post AI prompt best practices for writing embedded software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Supplementing CVEs with !CVEs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953738/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953738/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T20:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Common Vulnerabilities and Exploits
(CVE) system is the main mechanism for tracking various security
flaws, 
using the omnipresent CVE number—even vulnerabilities with fancy names and
web sites
have CVE numbers. But the CVE system is not without its critics and, in
truth, the incentives between the reporting side and those responsible for
handling the bugs have always been misaligned, which leads to abuse of
various kinds.  There have been efforts to
combat some of those abuses along the way; a newly announced
"!CVE" project is meant to track vulnerabilities "that are not
acknowledged by vendors but 
still are serious security issues".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024년 전망, 월가의 2024년 S&P 500 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592927</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592927/2024%eb%85%84-sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-2"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T15:05:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953783/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953783/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T14:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (roundcube), Fedora (java-latest-openjdk), Mageia (libqb), SUSE (python-Django1), and Ubuntu (request-tracker4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Testing By Example]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/testing</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/testing"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The importance of testing, and twenty tips for writing good tests.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가 IB들의 2024년 미국 경제 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592925</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592925/2024%eb%85%84-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ea%b2%bd%ec%a0%9c-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T10:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 포드 투자의견 및 포드 주가 전망(12/5 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592923</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592923/%ed%8f%ac%eb%93%9c-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-%ed%8f%ac%eb%93%9c-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T09:49:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가의 GM 투자의견 및 GM 주가 전망(12/5 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592921</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592921/gm-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-gm-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T09:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미즈호, 4분기 알파벳 실적은 월가를 실망시킬 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592913</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592913/%ec%8b%a4%eb%a7%9d%ec%8a%a4%eb%9f%ac%ec%9a%b8-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%8c%ed%8c%8c%eb%b2%b3-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T07:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/5, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592911</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592911/12-5-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T06:45:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HP가 워즈니악의 제안을 거절할 때]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=84823</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/84823/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T06:41:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자신이 설계하는 새로운 컴퓨터가 애플 사의 자산이 된다는 데 동의한 이후에도 워즈는 그것을 자신이 몸담은 HP에 먼저 제공해야 한다고 느꼈다. [중략] 그래서 워즈는 1976년 봄에 HP의 직장 상사와 경영진에게 자신의 고안물을 보여주었다. HP의 경영진은 큰 인상을 받았지만 HP에서 상품으로 개발할 수는 없다고 말했다. 컴퓨터광이 취미 생활로 만들 법한 물건에 불과하고, 또 HP가 타깃으로 삼는 고품질 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[병립형 회귀 vs. 준연동형, 민주당 갈등이 실망스러운 네 가지 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100456</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100456"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T05:32:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“선거는 승부다. 이상적인 주장으로 멋있게 지면 무슨 소용 있겠나.” (이재명, 2023년 11월 28일) 지난 11월 28일, 선거제도 개정과 관련하여 묵묵부답으로 초지일관하던 원내 제1당인 더불어민주당 이재명 대표가 드디어 입을 열었다. 이 발언은 직접적으로 병립형 비례대표제로의 회귀를 분명하게 언급한 것은 아니지만, 선거에서 승리하기 위해 병립형 비례대표제라도 받을 수 있음을 시사하고 있다. 이 발언은 준연동형 비례대표제를 유지하고 위성정당을...
The post 병립형 회귀 vs. 준연동형, 민주당 갈등이 실망스러운 네 가지 이유 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 수상 기준이 어떻길래? 올해도 이어진 노벨평화상 논란]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77964</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/04/npsp_nobelpeaceprize/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_nobelpeaceprize"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T22:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 18일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 2023년 노벨평화상은 이란의 인권 운동가 나르게스 모하마디에게 돌아갔습니다. 모하마디는 이른바 ‘히잡 시위’가 1년 넘게 이어지고 있는 이란에서 여성의 권리, 사형제도 등 다양한 부문의 인권 운동을 주도해 온 인물로, 노벨평화상을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[졌지만 잘 싸돌아다녔다, 엑스포 실패가 불길한 이유: 슬로우레터 12월5일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100432</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100432"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T22:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“변죽만 울리는 개각.” 해박한 지식과 통찰력? 지금까지 뭘 했나. 요소수 대란에서 배운 게 없다. 더 깊게 읽기. 중대재해처벌법 50명 미만 적용 미룰까. “민주당이 더 나쁘다.” 다르게 읽기. 반윤+반명 신당 가능할까. 구글폼 창당? 온라인 정당은 다르다? ‘떴다당’ 열풍. 오늘의 TMI. 카페 테이블의 스마트폰이 사라지지 않는 이유. 엘니뇨 습격으로 초콜릿 가격 폭등. 한없이 기다리는 노인들. 고령층 온라인...
The post 졌지만 잘 싸돌아다녔다, 엑스포 실패가 불길한 이유: 슬로우레터 12월5일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Day when Skynet becomes self-aware, and 69 reasons to chill out with colleagues. Part 1.]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1084/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1084/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes it's difficult to come up with a reason for gathering and hanging out with your colleagues. You may say that we have official holidays and birthdays — yeah, that's right — but it's still...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[퇴직자 투자 – 매달 월급을 한번 더 받는다는 월배당 ETF 분배율 순위]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592905</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592905/%ec%9b%94%eb%b0%b0%eb%8b%b9-etf-%eb%b6%84%eb%b0%b0%ec%9c%a8-%ec%88%9c%ec%9c%84"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T16:04:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Django 5.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953736/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953736/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T16:03:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
5.0 of the Django web framework is out.  Significant changes include database-computed
default values, field groups in the templating system, and more; see the release
notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What remains to be done for proxy execution]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953438/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953438/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T16:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's deadline scheduling class
offers a solution to a number of realtime (or generally latency-sensitive)
problems, but it is also resistant to the usual solutions for the priority-inversion
problem.  The development community has been pursuing proxy execution as a
solution to a few scheduling challenges, including this one; the problem is
difficult and progress has been slow.  LWN last looked at proxy execution in June; at the 2023 Linux
Plumbers Conference, John Stultz gave an overview of proxy execution,
the current status of the work, and the remaining problems to solve.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDB 14.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953732/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953732/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T15:54:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 14.1 of the GDB debugger is out.  Changes include initial support
for the debugger
adapter protocol, NO_COLOR support, the ability to work with
integer types larger than 64 bits, a number of enhancements to the
Python API, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bueso: LPC 2023: CXL Microconference]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953706/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953706/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T14:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Davidlohr Bueso has posted a
summary of the CXL microconference at the recently concluded Linux
Plumbers Conference.  "The goals for the track were to openly discuss
current on-going development efforts around the core driver, as well as
experimental memory management topics which lead to accommodating kernel
infrastructure for new technology and use cases."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953702/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953702/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T14:22:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (amanda, ncurses, nghttp2, opendkim, rabbitmq-server, and roundcube), Fedora (golang-github-openprinting-ipp-usb, kernel, kernel-headers, kernel-tools, and samba), Mageia (audiofile, galera, libvpx, and virtualbox), Oracle (kernel and postgresql:13), SUSE (openssl-3, optipng, and python-Pillow), and Ubuntu (firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세월호 참사, 해경 지휘부 무죄 유감: 중대재해처벌법 있어도 시민재해는 계속 된다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100417</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100417"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T06:18:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 11월 2일, 세월호 참사 당시 해양경찰 지휘부에 대한 대법원 판결이 선고되었다. 결과는 업무상 과실치사와 과실치상에 대해 김석균 당시 해양경찰청장과 김수현 서해지방해경청장, 김문홍 목포해양경찰서장 등 피고인 전원에 무죄가 인정됐다. 다만 김문홍 목포서장에 대해서는 허위공문서작성 및 행사죄와 직권남용권리행사방해죄가, 그리고 조형곤 목포서 상황담당관에 대해서는 직권남용권리행사방해죄가 유죄로 인정되었다. 대법원의 무죄 논리 대법원은 원심, 즉 제2심의 판단을 그대로 받아들였고...
The post 세월호 참사, 해경 지휘부 무죄 유감: 중대재해처벌법 있어도 시민재해는 계속 된다 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: DiffDebugging]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/DiffDebugging.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/DiffDebugging.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Regression bugs are newly appeared bugs in features of the software that have been around
  for a while. When hunting them, it usually valuable to figure out which change
  in the software caused them to appear. Looking at that change can give
  invaluable clues about where the bug is and how to squash it. There isn't a
  well-known term for this form of investigation, but I call it Diff Debugging.
Diff debugging only works if we have our code in version control, but
  fortunately these days that's the norm. But there are some more things that
  are needed to make it work effectively. We need Reproducible Builds, so that we can run old versions of
  the software easily. It helps greatly to have small commits, due to high-frequency
  integration. That way when we find the guilty commit, we …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내가 하는 차별은 다 좋아요, 얼마나 편해요!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99945</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99945"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T03:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 국제노동기구(ILO) 고용정책국장 이상헌 박사와 나누는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기 “(외국인 이주노동자를 고용하는 식당 업주가) ‘외국인 노동자의 임금을 내국인과 동등하게 지불해야 한다는 ILO 조항에서 탈퇴해야 하는 것 아니냐’며 비상대책 마련을 호소했다.” 윤석열(대통령), 2023년 10월 30일 국무회의 중에서 평범한 이웃의 이해할 수 있는 차별적 욕망과 그것에 편승하는 포퓰리즘의 정치. 이것이 이주노동자와 함께 살아야...
The post 내가 하는 차별은 다 좋아요, 얼마나 편해요! appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024년은 ‘덜지출 챌린지’ 계획해보면 어떨까요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78276</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/03/npsp_patagonia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_patagonia"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T03:00:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아웃도어 브랜드 파타고니아(Patagonia)는 자본주의와 시장의 통념을 정면으로 거스르는 기업으로 유명합니다. 기후변화에 맞서 싸우는 일의 선봉에 주저없이 나섰으며, 하나라도 더 팔아 매출을 올리려는 여느 브랜드와 달리, 한 번 사서 최대한 오래 쓸 수 있는 튼튼한 제품을 만드는 걸 목표로 삼고 실제로 “옷을 덜 사는 캠페인”을 벌이기도 했습니다. 지나친 소비가 지구에 좋을 게 없다는 이유였죠. 1973년에 파타고니아를 창립해 50년 동안 기업을 운영하다 지난해 기업의 소유권을 전부 비영리 단체와 재단에 기부한 이본 쉬나드가 뉴욕타임스에 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6.7-rc4 and stable kernels too]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953645/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953645/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T00:54:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.7-rc4 for testing.
"And things look fine for now, with a fairly
small rc4".

Meanwhile, the
6.6.4,
6.1.65, and
5.15.141
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software engineering’s F word]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8432</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/12/03/software-engineerings-f-word/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T23:19:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I know of two conversation topics that are guaranteed to make software developers feel uncomfortable, and even walk away: 1) complaining about ChatGPT’s refusable to say anything nice about Adolf Hitler, 2) enquiring why so few people are willing to talk about software engineering’s three letter F word (I actually say the F word). Academics […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“윤석열은 지금 두려운 게 아니라 외롭다”: 슬로우레터 12월4일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100374</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100374"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T21:44:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이동관 탄핵 불발, 극한 대립으로 간다. 이동관 후임은 검사 출신? 노란봉투법과 방송 3법은 거부권 행사. 김기현으로 안 된다. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명으로 총선 괜찮나. “윤석열은 일하기 편한 대통령이다.” “윤석열은 두려운 게 아니라 외롭다.” “윤석열-이준석 만나면 DJP 연합도 가능하다.” 다르게 읽기. 오일 머니 때문에 졌다고? 해법과 대안. 시골에 우울증이 더 많은 이유. 선진국이 기후 피해기금 낸다....
The post “윤석열은 지금 두려운 게 아니라 외롭다”: 슬로우레터 12월4일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Security Jawbreaker]]></title>
        <id>3631478</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3631478"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T16:26:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building with CMake Presets]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39619</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/03/building-with-cmake-presets/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T14:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I discuss the usefulness of CMake Presets in VS Code. As an open-source, cross-platform build generator, CMake provides a way to manage complex build processes. However, difficulties with CMake Kits led me explore the CMake Presets feature. Through custom JSON files, this feature simplifies the build process by allowing configuration, build, and test processes that can be integrated into the user's CI/CD pipeline. Moreover, CMake Presets simplifies the CMake and VS Code projects and enhances the use of command lines. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반도체 장비주, 어플라이드 머티어리얼즈 투자의견 및 어플라이드 머티어리얼즈 주가 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592890</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592890/%ec%96%b4%ed%94%8c%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b4%eb%93%9c-%eb%a8%b8%ed%8b%b0%ec%96%b4%eb%a6%ac%ec%96%bc%ec%a6%88-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%96%b4%ed%94%8c%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b4%eb%93%9c"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T10:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11/3, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592886</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592886/11-3-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-2"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T10:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 사이버트럭 출시를 보는 월가의 시선, 기대할 것 없다!!]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592878</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592878/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%82%ac%ec%9d%b4%eb%b2%84%ed%8a%b8%eb%9f%ad-%ec%b6%9c%ec%8b%9c-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T04:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[웨드부시, 사이버트럭이 테슬라 시가총액을 1조 달러로 끌어올릴 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592876</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592876/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%82%ac%ec%9d%b4%eb%b2%84%ed%8a%b8%eb%9f%ad-%ec%b6%9c%ec%8b%9c%eb%a1%9c-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%9d%ec%95%a1-1%ec%a1%b0%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T03:45:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한국은 사라지는가, 뉴욕타임스의 경고.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100361</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100361"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T03:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국은 사라지는가(Is South Korea Disappearing?). 뉴욕타임스 칼럼니스트 로스 다우서트(Ross Douthat)의 칼럼 제목이다. 합계출산율이 0.7명이라는 건 한 세대가 100명이라면 다음 세대에(대략 30년 뒤) 35명으로 줄어든다는 이야기다. 흑사병이 휩쓸었던 14세기 유럽보다 더 빠른 인구 감소다. 한 세대가 더 바뀌면(60년 뒤) 100명이 13명으로 줄어들게 된다. 이 정도면 스티븐 킹의 ‘더 스탠드(The Stand)’에 나오는 슈퍼 독감 수준의 인구 감소다....
The post 한국은 사라지는가, 뉴욕타임스의 경고. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ING 2024년 전망, 경제 냉각 조짐에 따라 6번 금리 인하 예상]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592869</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592869/2024%eb%85%84-%ea%b8%88%eb%a6%ac%ec%9d%b8%ed%95%98-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T02:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[퇴직자 투자 전략 – 퇴직연금 투자로 딱이라는 ACE 엔비디아채권혼합블룸버그 ETF]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592867</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592867/ace-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84%ec%b1%84%ea%b6%8c%ed%98%bc%ed%95%a9%eb%b8%94%eb%a3%b8%eb%b2%84%ea%b7%b8-etf"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T02:21:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[퇴직자 투자 전략 – 연간배당률 높은 ETF, CONY]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592865</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592865/cony-etf-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T02:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[퇴직자 투자 전략 – 연간배당률 67%라는 나스닥 추종 ETF, QQQY]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592863</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592863/qqqy-%ec%86%8c%ea%b0%9c-%eb%b0%8f-qqqy-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T02:14:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[퇴직자 투자 전략 – 월배당 ETF QYLD 소개 및 투자전략]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592860</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592860/%ec%9b%94%eb%b0%b0%eb%8b%b9-etf-qyld-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T01:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[참고용, AI가 짜준 파이썬 데이타 크롤링 프로그램]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592857</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592857/%ec%b0%b8%ea%b3%a0%ec%9a%a9-ai%ea%b0%80-%ec%a7%9c%ec%a4%80-%ed%8c%8c%ec%9d%b4%ec%8d%ac-%eb%8d%b0%ec%9d%b4%ed%83%80-%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a4%eb%a7%81-%ed%94%84%eb%a1%9c%ea%b7%b8%eb%9e%a8"/>
        <updated>2023-12-03T01:37:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “나이는 숫자에 불과”한 게 아니라는 것 말고 노화에 대해 정말 알아야 할 것들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77949</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/01/npsp_gettingold/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_gettingold"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T03:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 16일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 작가 로저 로젠블랏은 지금으로부터 25년 전, 58세의 나이로 “나이 듦의 법칙(Rules for Ageing)”을 썼습니다. 58세는 물론 적지 않은 나이입니다. 몇 년 뒤면 노인으로 불릴 것이며, 40대와 50대를 보내면서 나이가 든다는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[방통위의 비극, 이동관을 내보내도 또 다른 이동관이 온다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100335</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100335"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T03:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 이동관의 사퇴는 추진력을 얻기 위함이었다. 이동관(방송통신위원장)이 탄핵안 표결을 앞두고 사퇴했다. 대통령실은 사의 표명 3시간 만에 면직안을 재가했다. 방통위원장은 탄핵이 아니라 공석 상태가 됐다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 이유가 뭘까. 3+2라는 무늬만 합의제. 이동관이 석 달 동안 한 일. 이제 어떻게 되나. 문제의 본질은.
The post 방통위의 비극, 이동관을 내보내도 또 다른 이동관이 온다. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today I learned: How to read address zero on RISC-V]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2023-12-02:/riscv-addr-zero.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/riscv-addr-zero.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have been working on a "yet another" flashloader with standard flash operations like readback and blank checks.
The chip has flash mapped starting from address 0x0 so I wrote the code with obvious
pointers like uint32_t *p = 0x0;. I built the code with gcc like countless times before
but I did not get the behaviour I expected. The only thing "special" this time was that the CPU
was a RISC-V.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A Nouveau graphics driver update]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953144/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953144/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T16:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Support for NVIDIA graphics processors has traditionally been a sore point
for Linux users; NVIDIA has not felt the need to cooperate with the kernel
community or make free drivers available, and the reverse-engineered
Nouveau driver has often struggled to keep up with product releases.  There
have, however, been signs of improvement in recent years.  At the 2023 Linux
Plumbers Conference, graphics subsystem maintainer Dave Airlie provided
an update on the state of support for NVIDIA GPUs and what remains to be
done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953512/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953512/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T15:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium, gimp-dds, horizon, libde265, thunderbird, vlc, and zbar), Fedora (java-17-openjdk and xen), Mageia (optipng, roundcubemail, and xrdp), Red Hat (postgresql), Slackware (samba), SUSE (chromium, containerd, docker, runc, libqt4, opera, python-django-grappelli, sqlite3, and traceroute), and Ubuntu (linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15,
 linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, and linux-azure, linux-azure-6.2, linux-azure-fde-6.2, linux-gcp,
 linux-gcp-6.2).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔버 ‘집게손’ 사태: 사과한 업체, 끌려다닌 넥슨, 류호정은 헛발질]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100281</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100281"/>
        <updated>2023-12-01T03:48:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[일명 엔젤릭버스터(‘엔버’) ‘집게손 삽입 사건’이 게임업계와 게임 유저는 물론 정치권에까지 일파만파 번지고 있다. 2023년 11월 25일 S회사 직원 ‘ㄷ’가 남성혐오 발언을 하며 근무 중인 회사가 외주 제작 중이던 넥슨게임 애니메이션에 남성혐오성 상징을 의도적으로 삽입한 것이 발각된 것으로 세간에 알려진 이 사건의 발단과 초기 전개는 전혀 다른 곳에 있을 수 있다. 앞선 발단 넥슨은 메이플스토리라는 인기...
The post 엔버 ‘집게손’ 사태: 사과한 업체, 끌려다닌 넥슨, 류호정은 헛발질 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>nomodem</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[문제는 대통령이 ‘예스맨’들에 포위돼 있다는 것: 슬로우레터 12월1일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100287</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100287"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T21:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“민심에 눈높이에 못 미친 대통령실 재편.” 이재명의 분신이라던 김용의 유죄 선고. 이동관 탄핵 밀어붙인다. 인요한의 좌절. “이런 상태로 총선을 치를 수 있겠나.” “빚 많은 사람과 저소득층 굉장히 어려울 것.” 다르게 읽기. 포퓰리즘으로 가는 횡재세 논의. 엑스포 여기서 멈춘 게 다행이다? 오늘의 TMI. “의사요? 돈을 많이 벌잖아요.” 전두환은 아직 연희동에 있다. 해법과 대안. 전직 경찰들에 학폭...
The post 문제는 대통령이 ‘예스맨’들에 포위돼 있다는 것: 슬로우레터 12월1일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Google Developer Experts Share Their Favorite Tools and Advice for New Developers]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/11/global-google-developer-experts-share-their-favorite-tools-advice-for-new-developers.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/11/global-google-developer-experts-share-their-favorite-tools-advice-for-new-developers.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lyanne Alfaro, DevRel Program Manager, Google Developer Studio






Developer Journey is a monthly series highlighting diverse and global developers sharing relatable challenges, opportunities, and wins in their journey. Every month, we will spotlight developers around the world, the Google tools they leverage, and the kinds of products they are building. 
This month we speak with global Google Developer Experts in Firebase, Women Techmakers, and beyond, to learn more about their favorite Google tools, the applications they’ve built to serve diverse communities, and their best advice for anyone just getting started as a developer.
Juan Lombana






Mexico City, Mexico
Google Developer Expert, Firebase
Founder, Mercatitlán
Instagram


What Google tools have you used to build?
Go…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Issues and Improving Products After Launch]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=38367</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2023/11/30/managing-issues-and-improving-products-after-launch/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T17:47:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[30 November 2023 by Phillip JohnstonEmbedded Artistry and Memfault are joining forces to host a quarterly embedded discussion panel that is focused on the technical aspects of building embedded systems at scale. We will be featuring guest panel members who are at the cutting edge of embedded development. Our goal is to spread beneficial techniques … 
Continue reading "Managing Issues and Improving Products After Launch"
The post Managing Issues and Improving Products After Launch appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing uncertainty in building enterprise IoT solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481028</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/managing-uncertainty-in-building-enterprise-iot-solutions/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T16:16:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rapidly developing IoT solutions for enterprises requires minimum inaccuracies in order to stay competent in the market. Those who will manage to tame it faster...
The post Managing uncertainty in building enterprise IoT solutions appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Evanczuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A Rust implementation of Android's Binder]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953116/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953116/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Android system was once famous for extensive, out-of-tree kernel
enhancements.  Many of those have been eliminated or upstreamed over
the years, bringing Android much closer to the mainline kernel.  One
significant component in the "upstreamed" category is Binder, an
interprocess communication mechanism that is used only by Android.  There
are a number of factors that make Binder a good candidate for rewriting in
the Rust language; at the 2023 Linux
Plumbers Conference, Carlos Llamas and Alice Ryhl described the
motivation behind and implementation of a rewrite of Binder in Rust.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Testing of Deep-learning Systems]]></title>
        <id>3631340</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3631340"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T14:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953379/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953379/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T13:58:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium, gnutls, gst-devtools, gstreamer1, gstreamer1-doc, libcap, mingw-poppler, python-gstreamer1, qbittorrent, webkitgtk, and xen), Mageia (docker, kernel-linus, and python-django), Oracle (dotnet6.0, dotnet7.0, dotnet8.0, firefox, samba, squid, and thunderbird), Red Hat (firefox, postgresql:13, squid, and thunderbird), SUSE (cilium, freerdp, java-1_8_0-ibm, and java-1_8_0-openj9), and Ubuntu (ec2-hibinit-agent, freerdp2, gimp, gst-plugins-bad1.0, openjdk-17, openjdk-21, openjdk-lts, openjdk-8, pypy3, pysha3, and u-boot-nezha).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More than just a pretty face - a good UI is essential]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1611.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1611.php"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T10:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With almost any kind of software, the user interface (UI) is very important. With embedded devices this may be a critical issue for a wide selection of reasons, some of which may be unexpected.
We are all used to devices that have slick UIs. In the past buttons and lights seemed enough. Now we expect high-resolution touch screens at least, with virtual or augmented reality increasingly becoming...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open Source Supply Chain Security at Google]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/acmscored</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/acmscored"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A remote talk at ACM SCORED 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[외교부가 분쟁지역 취재 ‘데스킹’하는 나라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100015</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100015"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T04:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[인터뷰] 비언론인 최초로 안종필자유언론상을 수상한 김보라미 변호사를 만나 20년 가까운 공익 활동을 통해 느낀 한국 사회에 관해 묻고 들었습니다. (중략) 선진국 시스템을 보면 학생도 기자로 등록할 수 있습니다. 그런데 한국에서 언론인 보호는 정규직 언론인들만 보호하는 시스템이라는 생각이 들어서 매우 안타까운 생각이 들었고, 그때 저를 인터뷰하러 왔던 미디어오늘 기자에게 제가 이 부분을 이야기하면서 기자들이야말로 기자들을 보호하는...
The post 외교부가 분쟁지역 취재 ‘데스킹’하는 나라 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[소식] 논문 – 뉴스영화의 부정교합과 아카이브의 재고 (〈언론과 사회〉 31(4))]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3107</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2023/incongruity-of-newreels-and-rethink-the-archive/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T04:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이 글은 공간주의가 함께 기획한 "우리도 건설한다?" 연작의 잠정적인 마지막 작업물로, 플랫폼 공간주의에 게재된 아티클 "우리도 건설한다?"(2021)와 앞서 발표된 논문 "영상물을 활용한 건설ᐨ경관 연출의 정치"(2022)에서 이루어진 논의를 미디어사와 동시대 아카이브의 문제로 연장합니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 30, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/951631/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/951631/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-30T00:18:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for November 30, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LibreQoS 1.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953286/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953286/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T22:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LibreQoS project
describes itself as:


	LibreQoS is a Quality of Experience (QoE) Smart Queue Management
	(SQM) system designed for Internet Service Providers to optimize
	the flow of their network traffic and thus reduce bufferbloat, keep
	the network responsive, and improve the end-user experience.


Version
1.4 of LibreQoS was released on November 17.  "Version 1.4 is a
huge milestone. A whole new back-end, new GUI, 30%+ performance
improvements, support for single-interface mode."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대통령 귀에 달콤한 정보만 올라갔다: 슬로우레터 11월30일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100218</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100218"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘박빙 승부’라더니 외교력과 정보력의 실패. 가능성 낮다는 것 알고 있었다. “PT부터 망했다.” 쟁점과 현안. 문재인 정부 울산시장 선거 개입 유죄. 이재명의 결단? 변심? 이동관 탄핵안 상정하나. 더 깊이 읽기. 김건희 명품백 논란에서 드러난 세 가지 문제. 이스라엘의 팩트체크 타격대. 일베와 개딸, 제대로 알고는 있나. 해법과 대안. 출산율 0.6명까지 떨어지나. 부모 한 명 육아휴직을 의무로. 오늘의...
The post 대통령 귀에 달콤한 정보만 올라갔다: 슬로우레터 11월30일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] An overview of kernel samepage merging (KSM)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953141/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953141/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T21:45:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the Kernel Summit
track at the 2023 Linux
Plumbers Conference (LPC), Stefan Roesch led a session on kernel
samepage merging (KSM).  He gave an overview of the feature and described
some recent changes to KSM.  He showed how
an application can enable KSM to deduplicate its memory and how the feature
can be evaluated to  determine whether it is a good fit for new workloads.
In addition, he provided some real-world data of the benefits from his
workplace at Meta.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundcube becomes part of Nextcloud]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953228/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953228/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T15:11:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nextcloud has announced
the "acquisition" of the Roundcube webmail system.


	As a product, Roundcube has an established path to success on its
	own. With opportunities remaining to be explored, a direct merger
	between Roundcube and Nextcloud is not planned. Neither will
	Roundcube replace Nextcloud Mail or the other way around. The
	products both have strengths and weaknesses and as open source
	products they already do share some underlying libraries and tools,
	but remain independent offerings for overlapping but different use
	scenarios. Nextcloud Mail will evolve as it is, focused on being
	used naturally within Nextcloud. Roundcube will continue to serve
	its active and new users as a stand-alone secure mail client.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953226/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953226/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T14:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (gst-plugins-bad1.0 and postgresql-multicorn), Fedora (golang-github-nats-io, golang-github-nats-io-jwt-2, golang-github-nats-io-nkeys, golang-github-nats-io-streaming-server, libcap, nats-server, openvpn, and python-geopandas), Mageia (kernel), Red Hat (c-ares, curl, fence-agents, firefox, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, libxml2, pixman, postgresql, and tigervnc), SUSE (python-azure-storage-queue, python-Twisted, and python3-Twisted), and Ubuntu (afflib, ec2-hibinit-agent, linux-nvidia-6.2, linux-starfive-6.2, and poppler).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst export restrictions, RISC-V continues to advance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481012</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/amidst-export-restrictions-risc-v-continues-to-advance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T13:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The RISC-V architecture continues to advance despite uncertainties over geopolitical tensions.  
The post Amidst export restrictions, RISC-V continues to advance appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhishek Jadhav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Diary]]></title>
        <id>3631181</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3631181"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T13:00:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do trusted compute units address new era of data center ransomware?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481001</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-do-trusted-compute-units-address-new-era-of-data-center-ransomware/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T11:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware has evolved far beyond mere file encryption and Bitcoin demands, with modern ransomware leaving conventional counsel woefully inadequate in the face of rapidly evolving threats. We look at a new approach to securing data centers with self-learning, self-defending, AI-driven, trusted compute units anchored within hardware.
The post How do trusted compute units address new era of data center ransomware? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gopi Sirineni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing ASIC design tradeoffs for wearable medical devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480993</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/managing-asic-design-tradeoffs-for-wearable-medical-devices/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T10:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Custom ASICs can enable OEMs to better balance function and requirements, especially so in advanced wearable medical systems, where power budgets, functionality and form factor all operate in tight constraints.
The post Managing ASIC design tradeoffs for wearable medical devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Konstantinos Glaros</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Docker Desktop 유료화에 따른 대안 - macOS에 podman 설치]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15740043</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15740043"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T07:03:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[도커(Docker)가 부분 유료화 정책을 시행하고 있다. 
개인 사용자를 위한 Personal 은 여전히 무료이다. 그리고 도커 자체가 오픈소스이므로 리눅스상에서 도커를 설치해서 운영하는 것은 전혀 지장이 없다.
유료화가 적용되는 경우는 "Docker Desktop"에 대한 부분, 그리고 "기업 내 사용"이 문제다. 
내가 개인적으로 내 컴퓨터에 도커 데스크탑을 설치하는 것은 비용이 발생하지 않지만, 회사 컴퓨터에는 도커 데스크탑을 설치해서는 안된다. 
macOS를 사용하는 경우, Docker Desktop을 설치하면 자체적으로 Aarch64 리눅스를 가상화하여 도커를 설치하고, 도커 데몬을 그쪽에 연결하는 것으로 보인다. 이 기능은 편리하지만, 회사에서는 이 방식을 사용할 수 없다.


그래서 대안으로 선택할 수 있는 것이 podman이다. podman은 데몬 방식을 사용하지 않는다는 것이 차이점이다.
https://podman.io/
podman은 무료이고 오픈소스이어서 회사 내 사용이 문제가 없는 것으로 보인다.
macOS 환경에서 podman은 QEMU기반의 가상 머신으로 동작한다. 
podman은 brew를 통해 설치할 수 있지만, 여기에서는 GUI 기반의 installer를 통해 Desktop 버전으로 설치해보자.
(사이트: https://podman-desktop.io/downloads )
나는 Apple M2 Pro가 탑재된 MacBook Pro를 사용하고 있으므로, arm64용 dmg파일을 다운받아 설치했다.
Podman Desktop을 실행하면 podman을 초기 설치하기 위한 세팅이 진행된다. 
Podman Setup을 통해 기본으로 사용될 podman-machine를 지정하고 생성한다.
이제 podman 이 설치되었을 것이다. 터미널에서 podman --help 명령어를 확인해보자.


사용을 희망하는 '도커' 이미지를 podman으로 pull 할 수 있다. 
$ podman pull aflplusplus/aflplusplus
pull 작업이 완료되면 해당 이미지를 기반으로 컨테이너를 실행할 수 있게 된다. Desktop에서 이미지를 선택하고 Run Image를 선택하면 된다.
컨테이너 화면에서 현재 실행중인 컨테이너를 확인할 수 있고, Tty를 통해 쉘 명령어를 테스트해볼 수도 있다.
podman도 Arm64 macOS에서 구동하면, 자체적으로 Aarch64 리눅스를 기반으로 하는 컨테이너를 선택하는 것 같다.


만약 굳이 intel용 컨테이너를 구동하고 싶다면? 
$ podman pull pwntools/pwntools:stable --arch x86_64
이렇게 --arch 옵션으로 x86_64를 지정해준다.
이렇게 실행된 컨테이너는 x86_64로 작동하고 있음을 알 수 있다. 이것은 사실 macOS의 입장에서는 어차피 qemu기반으로 컨테이너가 동작하기 때문에 x86_64인 컨테이너를 실행하도록 한 것과 같다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[비례대표 개편에 윤석열의 운명이 걸렸다고 하는 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100143</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100143"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T03:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트]정치 덕후들을 위한 선거법 논란 분석. 쟁점은 세 가지다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 지난 총선을 보면 그림이 보인다. 내년 총선은 어떨까. 최근 정당 지지율을 반영한 시나리오. 시나리오 1: 국민의힘만 위성정당을 만드는 경우. 시나리오 1의 변수. 시나리오 2: 둘 다 위성 정당을 만드는 경우. 시나리오 3: 병립형으로 가는 경우. 시나리오 4: 둘 다 위성정당을 만들지 않는 경우....
The post 비례대표 개편에 윤석열의 운명이 걸렸다고 하는 이유. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving into JTAG - Overview (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part1</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part1"/>
        <updated>2023-11-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the first segment of a three-part series on JTAG, this post will give
an overview of JTAG to set up some more in-depth discussions on debugging and JTAG Boundary-Scan. We will dive into the intricacies of the interface, such as the Test Access Port (TAP), key registers, instructions, and JTAG’s finite state machine.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“인류를 위한 인공지능” 누가, 어떻게 할 것인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78255</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/11/28/npsp_openai/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_openai"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T22:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오픈AI의 CEO 샘 알트만이 이사회에서 갑자기 해고됐다가 닷새만에 복귀하는 극적인 사건이 일어난 지도 약 일주일이 지났습니다. 이번 사태를 둘러싸고 많은 분석과 전망이 쏟아져 나왔는데요, 에즈라 클라인이 뉴욕타임스에 쓴 칼럼을 번역하고, 이번 사태가 갖는 의미에 관해 해설을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 오픈AI 사태가 남긴 불안한 교훈 해설: “인류를 위한 인공지능” 누가, 어떻게 할 것인가?   * 이번 해설을 뉴욕대학교 컴퓨터과학과 조경현 교수가 아메리카노에서 정리한 인터뷰를 바탕으로 썼습니다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[진실의 위기 시대, 올해의 단어는 ‘진짜(authentic)’: 슬로우레터 11월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100124</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100124"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:55:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 명품백 논란, 간단치 않다. 국민의힘이 먼저 치고 나간 쇄신. 엑스포는 리야드로. 쟁점과 현안. 김부겸이 교통정리. 이낙연의 쓴소리. 이재명의 결단? 더 깊게 읽기. “목숨은 다 하나다.” 오늘의 TMI. 이선균과 지드래곤 혐의 입증 못 했다. 한동훈-이정재 셀카에 대상홀딩스 주가가 폭등. 올해의 단어는 ‘진짜.’ 1인 가구 절반이 빈곤. 병원에서 임종 70%, OECD 1위. 영어 유치원 10년 동안...
The post 진실의 위기 시대, 올해의 단어는 ‘진짜(authentic)’: 슬로우레터 11월29일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Using drgn on production kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952942/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952942/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T21:07:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The drgn Python-based kernel
debugger was developed by Omar Sandoval for use in his job on the kernel
team at Meta. He now spends most of his time working on drgn, both in
developing new features for the tool and in using
it to debug production problems at Meta, which gives him a view of both
ends of that feedback loop.  At the 2023 
Linux Plumbers 
Conference (LPC), he led a session on drgn in the kernel debugging
microconference, where he wanted to brainstorm on how to add some new
features to the debugger and, in particular, how to allow them to work on
production kernels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A pile of stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953126/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953126/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T19:24:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The large
6.6.3,
6.5.13,
6.1.64,
5.15.140,
5.10.202,
5.4.262,
4.19.300,
4.14.331
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.  Note that 6.5.13 is the final update for 6.5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Women in ML Symposium 2023: Meet the presenters]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/11/women-in-ml-symposium-2023-meet-the-presenters.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/11/women-in-ml-symposium-2023-meet-the-presenters.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Sharbani Roy – Senior Director, Product Management, Google






We’re back with the third annual Women in Machine Learning Symposium on December 7, 2023! 
Join us virtually from 9:30 am to 1:00 pm PT for an immersive and insightful set of deep dives for every level of Machine Learning experience. 


The Women in ML Symposium is an inclusive event for anyone passionate about the transformative fields of Machine Learning (ML) and Artificial Intelligence (AI). Meet this year’s women in ML as they uncover practical applications across multiple industries and discuss the latest advancements in frameworks, generative AI, and more.
Joana Carrasqueira, presenter for “Enabling Anyone to Build with Google AI”


Joana is a Developer Relations Lead for AI/ML at Google and her mission is to …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What open-source Azure RTOS means to developers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480989</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/what-open-source-azure-rtos-means-to-developers/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T15:32:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Azure RTOS transitions to Eclipse ThreadX under the Eclipse Foundation, it will give developers access to a high-quality, certified RTOS at no cost. The...
The post What open-source Azure RTOS means to developers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How FinOps principles can guide IoT deployment]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480985</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-finops-principles-can-guide-iot-deployment/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T15:30:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying FinOps to IoT deployment can help businesses manage their resources more effectively, optimize costs, and achieve their business objectives. As organizations make growing investments...
The post How FinOps principles can guide IoT deployment appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilad David Maayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to tackle unreliability of coding assistants]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-gen-ai.html#memo-08</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/exploring-gen-ai.html#memo-08"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the last year, lots of developers have incorporated LLM coding
     assistants into their work, finding them a useful tool. But one of the
     problems of these tools is that they are unreliable, often coming up with
     poor or outright wrong-headed suggestions. Birgitta
     Böckeler continues her exploration of GenAI for developers by
     passing on what she's learned about how think about this unreliability, and
     why it may be good to call your LLM tool “Dusty”. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953099/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953099/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T14:58:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (cryptojs, fastdds, mediawiki, and minizip), Fedora (chromium, kubernetes, and thunderbird), Mageia (lilypond, mariadb, and packages), Red Hat (firefox, linux-firmware, and thunderbird), SUSE (compat-openssl098, gstreamer-plugins-bad, squashfs, squid, thunderbird, vim, and xerces-c), and Ubuntu (libtommath, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-oracle, perl, and python3.8, python3.10, python3.11).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가짜 노동, 텅 빈 노동]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100103</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100103"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T03:24:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, ‘홍보가 아니라 소통입니다’ 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기. “4시간만 일해도 되는 사회를 만들어놓고 왜 8시간씩이나 일하는가?” 오늘 마냐의 북라이딩에서 함께 읽을 책은 [가짜 노동 – 스스로 만드는 번아웃의 세계]입니다. 책은 ‘사라진 시간’, ‘사라진 의미’, ‘시간과 의미 되찾기’라는 세 영역으로 구성되고, 그 속에서 가짜 노동을 비판하고,...
The post 가짜 노동, 텅 빈 노동 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 또다시 토요일에 시작된 전쟁… 이스라엘- 팔레스타인 갈등과 분쟁의 역사]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77935</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/11/27/npsp_hamasisrael/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_hamasisrael"/>
        <updated>2023-11-28T01:45:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 12일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 10월 7일, 하마스가 이스라엘을 급습한 테러 공격을 감행한 뒤 이스라엘의 반격으로 전쟁이 시작되자마자 올라온 칼럼들을 모아 정리한 글입니다. 양측은 포로와 인질을 맞교환하는 협상을 벌여 지난 몇일 전쟁이 시작된 이후 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[누가 ‘가짜’ 가짜뉴스를 퍼뜨리는가: 슬로우레터 11월28일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100080</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100080"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘서울의 봄’이 불러온 ‘영화 정치’. 북한, 비무장 지대에 병력 투입. “병립형으로 간다”, 민주당의 변심? 오늘 부산 엑스포 결정된다. 이주노동자 내년 16만5000명. “한국 행정망은 데이터 쓰레기장 수준” 다르게 읽기. “북한 정찰위성은 도발 맞다.” “전쟁 억지력이 평화를 만든다.” 건강보험 수가, 부정확해서 문제다. 오늘의 TMI. 청년 절반 부모와 산다. 피아노의 몰락. 마약 롤스로이스 피해자 사망. 해법과 대안. 굴...
The post 누가 ‘가짜’ 가짜뉴스를 퍼뜨리는가: 슬로우레터 11월28일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with NuttX RTOS on Three Low Cost Boards]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1610.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1610.php"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T21:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are an embedded system developer changes are you already played with Linux on some embedded board and saw how it is powerful, right?
So, I have a good news: you can have same power using NuttX on some ultra low cost board powered by a microcontroller instead of microprocessor (that normally is way more expansive).
In fact many companies already realized it before me. It explains why NuttX...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Low-code Development Productivity]]></title>
        <id>3631183</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3631183"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T15:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exclusive: Arbe releases 48 RX x 48 TX production radar processor]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480980</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/exclusive-arbe-releases-48-rx-x-48-tx-production-radar-processor/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T15:15:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbe Robotics said its radar processor is used for OEM development projects and Tier-1 B-Sample radars, and expects revenue for the year to be in $5-7 million range.
The post Exclusive: Arbe releases 48 RX x 48 TX production radar processor appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A discussion on kernel-maintainer pain points]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952146/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952146/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T15:09:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A regular feature of the Kernel Maintainers Summit is a session where Linus
Torvalds discusses the problems that he has been encountering.  In recent
years, though, there have been relatively few of those problems, so this
year he turned things around a bit by asking
the community what problems it was seeing instead.  He then addressed
them at the Summit in a session covering aspects of the development
community, including feedback to maintainers, diversity (or the
lack thereof), and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952923/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952923/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T15:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (freeimage, gimp, gst-plugins-bad1.0, node-json5, opensc, python-requestbuilder, reportbug, strongswan, symfony, thunderbird, and tiff), Fedora (chromium, galera, golang, kubernetes, mariadb, python-asyncssh, thunderbird, vim, and webkitgtk), Gentoo (AIDE, Apptainer, GLib, GNU Libmicrohttpd, Go, GRUB, LibreOffice, MiniDLNA, multipath-tools, Open vSwitch, phpMyAdmin, QtWebEngine, and RenderDoc), Slackware (vim), SUSE (gstreamer-plugins-bad, java-1_8_0-ibm, openvswitch, poppler, slurm, slurm_22_05, slurm_23_02, sqlite3, vim, webkit2gtk3, and xrdp), and Ubuntu (openvswitch and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PipeWire 1.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952848/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952848/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T14:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PipeWire, the audio/video bus meant to
replace PulseAudio, JACK, and other systems, has reached
1.0.  In celebration, Fedora Magazine is running an
interview with PipeWire creator Wim Taymans.


	PipeWire is an IPC mechanism for multimedia. The most interesting
	stuff will happen in the session manager, the modules, the
	applications and the tools around all this. I hope to see more cool
	tools to route video and set up video filters etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[컴퓨터 과학, 컴퓨터 공학, 소프트웨어 공학 : 차이점]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=12988</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2023/11/27/difference-of-cs/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T13:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이 글은 컴퓨터공학을 선택하거나, 편입하려고 하는 분들에게 쓰는 글입니다.많이들 헷갈려 하거든요. …. 개발자가 되려고 합니다. 컴퓨터 과학, 컴퓨터 공학, 소프트웨어 공학, 정보공학….아, 복잡합니다. 뭔지는 몰라도 저게 다 개발자가 된다는거죠? 흠, 그런데 막상 대학에 입학을 해보면 개발자인듯 아닌 듯.소프트웨어인 듯 아닌 듯, 그런 걸 배우게 됩니다. 사실 이제는 저게 경계선이 없습니다.각 대학의 교수님들이 계속 커리큘럼을 업데이트... Continue Reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCU-Link with Cortex-Debug and LinkServer]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39587</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/11/27/mcu-link-with-cortex-debug-and-linkserver/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-27T00:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MCU-Link, a $10 CMSIS-DAP debug probe from NXP is compatible with OpenOCD and is best used with the NXP LinkServer. In VS Code, it works with the Cortex-Debug extension, offering support for different debug probes and scripting. While it requires manual launch for an 'external' debug probe, automated server launch can be achieved via a VS Code task or via the console in the IDE.
 Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rounding in reported task implementation time]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8425</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/11/26/rounding-in-reported-task-implementation-time/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T23:25:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is lots of evidence that people often pick a round number when estimating the time needed to implement a task. Parkinson’s law suggests that reported actual implementation time will often also be a round number, e.g., report 30 minutes for a task that actually took 28 minutes. If a task is estimated to take […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘이게 대통령의 뜻이냐’는 조선일보의 질문: 슬로우레터 11월27일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100028</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100028"/>
        <updated>2023-11-26T22:09:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘이게 대통령의 뜻이냐’는 조선일보의 질문. “김기현 출마는 국민의힘 망하는 길.” 행정망 먹통, 8일만에 반쪽짜리 결론. 국정원 진짜 문제는 내부 갈등의 표출. 순방 다녀온 윤석열 앞에 놓인 과제. “이준석 창당 좋게 본다”, 35%. “KBS가 ‘대한뉴스’로 돌아갔다.” 나흘의 시한부 평화, 풀려난 인질들. 다르게 읽기. 정신병원 장기 입원이 많은 이유. 더 깊게 읽기 준연동형으로 가면 국민의힘이 35석 더...
The post ‘이게 대통령의 뜻이냐’는 조선일보의 질문: 슬로우레터 11월27일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 인공지능 그 자체보다는 여기에 대한 대응이 미래를 결정할 것]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77926</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/11/25/npsp_aiwar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aiwar"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T22:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 11일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 뇌의 신경망을 흉내내 지적인 문제를 풀게 만들겠다는 야심찬 기술이 처음 등장했을 때 이들이 실제로 인간의 지적 능력을 흉내 낼 수 있게 될 거라 생각한 사람은 많지 않았습니다. 하지만 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Overview of a 10Gb Ethernet Switch]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2023/11/25/eth10g.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2023/11/25/eth10g.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-25T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fig 1. The KlusterLab board used for the 10Gb Ethernet Switch testing



I’ve now been working with Symbiotic EDA
and PCB Arts on a 10Gb Ethernet switch
project for
NetIdee for some time.  Indeed,
I’ve discussed this project several times
on the blog.  I first brought it up in the context of building a Virtual Packet
FIFO.  The topic then came
up again during two articles on building an SDIO (SD-Card)
controller: first when discussing how to
build a Verilog test bench for
it, and then again when
discussing what bugs managed to slip past the verification, which then had to
be caught in hardware.
What we haven’t yet discussed is the switch itself, and how it works.
When discussing this project, I’ve often shown the component
diagram below.
Fig 2. The ETH10G project, from a bus component view…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patterns of Distributed Systems is published by Pearson]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/books/patterns-distributed.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/books/patterns-distributed.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T19:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[During the last four years, my colleague Unmesh Joshi
     been developing a collection of patterns to help us all better understand
     how modern distributed systems work. We've been publishing drafts of these
     patterns on this site. Now these have turned into a book, published
     by Addison-Wesley in my signature series. As such, we've now removed
     the work-in-progress drafts from this site, and have replaced them with a
     catalog of pattern
     summaries. For those with a subscription to oreilly.com, we have deep
     links from the summaries to the relevant chapter of the online book.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ETAS and Infineon automotive HSM security stack is certified by NIST CAVP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480974</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/etas-and-infineon-automotive-hsm-security-stack-is-certified-by-nist-cavp/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T14:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NIST’s CAVP certifies ETAS’ automotive embedded security software stack implemented on Infineon’s AURIX TC3xx hardware security module (HSM).
The post ETAS and Infineon automotive HSM security stack is certified by NIST CAVP appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[컨텍스트] 두들겨 맞던 다음이 뉴스 검색 결과를 바꾼 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99995</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99995"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T06:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[다음이 뉴스 검색 결과를 바꿨다. 뉴스 검색 설정에서 ‘전체’와 ‘뉴스제휴 언론사’를 선택할 수 있게 돼 있는데 23일부터 ‘뉴스제휴 언론사’를 디폴트로 지정했다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 이해를 돕기 위한 백그라운드 정보. 이유가 뭘까. 마이너 언론 때리기의 오랜 역사. 큰 그림: 조중동의 오래된 꿈. 몇 가지 질문. 핵심은 이것이다.
The post [컨텍스트] 두들겨 맞던 다음이 뉴스 검색 결과를 바꾼 이유. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“암컷” 발언이 왜 문제냐고? 알기 쉽게 설명해준다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99986</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99986"/>
        <updated>2023-11-24T01:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최강욱(전 민주당 의원)과 남영희(민주연구원 부원장)의 “암컷” 발언은 사실 많은 사람들이 저지르는 잘못이다. 잘못됐다고 지적받아도 발언 당사자들은 정말로 뭐가 문제인지 잘 모르기도 한다. 이런 것까지 하나하나 말을 해줘야 하나, 자괴감을 느낄 수 있고, 그 감정은 전적으로 타당하다. 그런데 안타깝게도 “눈 떠보니 선진국” 대한민국은 아직도 ‘이런 것까지 지적해야 하는’ 나라다. 여성을 비하한 게 아니라고? 우선 제일 큰...
The post “암컷” 발언이 왜 문제냐고? 알기 쉽게 설명해준다. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>박권일</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[강도를 옹호하냐고? 누가 합의를 먼저 깼나: 슬로우레터 11월24일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99960</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99960"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T22:07:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[결국 남북 군사합의 파기. 대통령은 만찬. “강도를 옹호하나.” “7년 만에 이겼다.” ‘암컷’ 발언에 민주당 지지율 급락. 수도권 지역 임금 격차 더 커졌다. 쟁점과 현안. 김기현의 역주행. 은마아파트 종부세 0원. 더 깊게 읽기. 3자 변제라는 꼼수, 물컵은 차지 않았다. 더 깊게 읽기. “이런 게 성공 아니겠나.” 해법과 대안. 서울 큰 병원 안 가기 잘 했네. 오죽하면...
The post 강도를 옹호하냐고? 누가 합의를 먼저 깼나: 슬로우레터 11월24일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm adds new Cortex-M processor for AI on small IoT devices​]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480967</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/arm-adds-new-cortex-m-processor-for-ai-on-small-iot-devices/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T20:20:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Cortex-M52 with Helium technology provides a significant performance uplift in DSP and ML applications for small, low power embedded devices, making it possible to deploy more compute intensive ML inference algorithms in endpoints without requiring a dedicated NPU.
The post Arm adds new Cortex-M processor for AI on small IoT devices​ appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘그냥’ 결혼하기 싫은 여성이 한국에도 많은 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78208</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/11/23/npsp_marriage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_marriage"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T16:40:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국 인구통계국(Census Bureau)에 따르면, 15세 이상 인구 가운데 100명당 결혼한 사람의 수가 1970년에는 85.9명이었는데, 2010년대 들어 30명 대로 떨어졌습니다. 미국 사람들은 왜 예전보다 결혼을 덜 하는 것일까요? 연애, 결혼, 임신 및 출산 전문 칼럼니스트 애나 루이 서스먼은 결혼을 통해 안정적인 가정을 이루고 싶어 하는 이성애자 여성은 여전히 많지만, 이들이 ‘괜찮은’ 남성 파트너를 찾지 못하고 있다고 진단합니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 미국과 크게 다르지 않은 문제를 안은 한국의 상황을 함께 조명해 봤습니다. 전문 번역: 왜들 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 alpha 2 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/11/python-3130-alpha-2-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/11/python-3130-alpha-2-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2023-11-23T00:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Well, well, well, it’s time for Python 3.13.0 alpha 2!

https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130a2/
This is an early developer preview of Python 3.13
 
Major new features of the 3.13 series, compared to 3.12
 
Python 3.13 is still in development. This release, 3.13.0a2 is the second of seven planned alpha releases.
Alpha releases are intended to make it easier to test the current state of new features and bug fixes and to test the release process.
During the alpha phase, features may be added up until the start of the beta phase (2024-05-07) and, if necessary, may be modified or deleted up until the release candidate phase (2024-07-30). Please keep in mind that this is a preview release and its use is not recommended for production environments.
Many new features for Python 3.1…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[영국 언론이 김건희 미모 극찬? 기사를 읽다 말았나: 슬로우레터 11월23일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99919</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99919"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T22:05:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 미모 칭찬? 기사를 하나만 읽었다. 만리경 1호 정상 궤도 진입. 행정망 먹통 아직 수습 안 됐다. 인요한 한 달, 실패한 1인쇼 되나. “김건희 특별법 받아도 된다.” 46일 만에 나흘 동안 휴전. 올트먼의 귀환. 수츠케버의 사다리 걷어차기. 더 깊게 읽기. 정치권 언저리의 교수들. 돈줄이 말라간다. 오늘의 TMI. 가을아, 왜 그래… 초록 낙엽의 역습. 첫눈(雪)은 눈(目)으로...
The post 영국 언론이 김건희 미모 극찬? 기사를 읽다 말았나: 슬로우레터 11월23일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Return to Grove Street. Checking the Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas engine in Unity]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1083/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1083/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Grand Theft Auto series has transformed into the iconic game franchise. San Andreas is one of the most memorable parts for many gamers. Time is running, but fans still love this game. Some still...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Happy Thanksgiving]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952354/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952354/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T16:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[November 23 is the US Thanksgiving holiday; as is our tradition, we will
not be publishing an LWN Weekly Edition this week as we will be far too
busy eating.  We wish a good holiday to all of our readers (whether they
celebrate it or not); the weekly edition will return on November 30.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Committing to Rust for kernel code]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952029/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952029/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:20:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust has been a prominent topic at the Kernel Maintainers Summit for the
last couple of years, and the 2023 meeting continued that tradition.  As
Rust-for-Linux developer Miguel Ojeda noted at the beginning of the session
dedicated to the topic, the level of interest in using Rust for kernel
development has increased significantly over the last year.  But Rust was
explicitly added to Linux as an experiment; is the kernel community now
ready to say that the experiment has succeeded?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952312/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952312/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T15:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (gimp), Fedora (audiofile and firefox), Mageia (postgresql), Red Hat (binutils, c-ares, fence-agents, glibc, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, libcap, libqb, linux-firmware, ncurses, pixman, python-setuptools, samba, and tigervnc), Slackware (kernel and mozilla), SUSE (apache2-mod_jk, avahi, container-suseconnect, java-1_8_0-openjdk, libxml2, openssl-1_0_0, openssl-1_1, openvswitch, python3-setuptools, strongswan, ucode-intel, and util-linux), and Ubuntu (frr, gnutls28, hibagent, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm,
 linux-ibm-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15,
 linux-nvidia, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-bluefield, linux-hwe-5.4,
 linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-oracle,
 linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-6.2, linux-hwe-6.2, linux-kvm,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.2, linux-raspi, linux-starfive, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux, linux-aws, linux-laptop, linux-lowlatency, linux-oem-6.5,
 linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux-starfive, linux-oem-6.1, mosquitto, rabbitmq-server, squid, and tracker-miners).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Ollama with LangChainGo]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/using-ollama-with-langchaingo/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/using-ollama-with-langchaingo/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of the most exciting areas of LLM-related development in 2023 is the
availability of powerful (and sometimes even open-source) models we can run
locally on our machines.</p>
<p>Several tools exist that make it relatively easy to obtain, run and manage
such models locally; for example <a class="reference external" href="https://ollama.ai/">Ollama</a> (written in Go …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PCIe SSD targets environments requiring reliability and endurance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480963</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-pcie-ssd-targets-environments-requiring-reliability-and-endurance/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T12:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New N3202 SSD from Swissbit is designed to deliver reliability and endurance for various applications, including data logging, database access, edge servers, or telecom & networking in industrial as well as enterprise storage applications.
The post New PCIe SSD targets environments requiring reliability and endurance appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How will cloud democratize generative AI?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480945</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-will-cloud-democratize-generative-ai/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T11:54:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores the role of the cloud in democratizing generative AI to everyone from startups to large enterprises.
The post How will cloud democratize generative AI? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mahesh Turaga</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: optimal state machine implementation in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480947</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-optimal-state-machine-implementation-in-c/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T11:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this installment in the state machine segment, I introduce the state machine implementation in C that I consider optimal according to the criteria I...
The post Programming embedded systems: optimal state machine implementation in C appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is POSIX the key to futureproofing your RTOS projects?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480958</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/is-posix-the-key-to-futureproofing-your-rtos-projects/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The future of RTOS applications may be POSIX-driven, ushering in a new era of cross-platform development in resource-constrained embedded systems. The quest for compatibility and...
The post Is POSIX the key to futureproofing your RTOS projects? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[박민 KBS 등판, ‘땡윤 뉴스’의 서막]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99907</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99907"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T08:12:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KBS가 인사와 보도 논란으로 안팎이 시끄럽습니다. 박민 신임 KBS 사장은 취임하자마자 주요 간부를 교체하고, 주요 보도·시사·교양·라디오 프로그램의 진행자와 출연진에게 갑작스러운 하차를 통보했습니다. KBS 내부에서 무도한 언론탄압이라는 목소리가 터져 나옵니다. 민주언론시민연합은 KBS의 박민 사장 취임 이후 논란을 언론이 어떻게 보았는지 살펴봤습니다. 박민 사장 보직·프로그램 인사 단행 편향성 논란에 편향 인사로 돌려막기 박민 사장은 구성원 동의가 필요한...
The post 박민 KBS 등판, ‘땡윤 뉴스’의 서막 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동성애 처벌법 합헌 유감: 합의한 성관계와 전투력이 무슨 상관?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99899</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99899"/>
        <updated>2023-11-22T07:02:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023년 10월 26일, 헌법재판소는 소위 ‘동성애 처리법'(군형법 제92조의6 추행죄) 위헌법률심판에서 해당 법이 합헌 이라고 결정했다. 벌써 네 번째 결정, 15년째 제자리걸음인 셈이다. 동성 군인간 성관계 처벌 위한 ‘동성애 처벌법’ 군형법 제92조의6은 군인과 항문성교나 그 밖의 추행을 한 군인을 징역 2년 이하의 형에 처하는 법이다. 맥락을 모르는 사람이 보면 무엇을 처벌하기 위해 존재하는 법인지 알기가 어렵다....
The post 동성애 처벌법 합헌 유감: 합의한 성관계와 전투력이 무슨 상관? appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공정한 사다리? 같은 출발선이라는 착각: 슬로우레터 11월22일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=99869</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/99869"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T22:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[북한 위성에 윤석열 황금마차가 밀렸다. 북한 정찰위성 발사, 남북 관계 더 꼬인다. 외교부 통신망도 하루종일 불통이었다. 부동산 보유세도 ‘ABM’, 부자 감세로 간다. “암컷 설친다” 발언 논란. 더 깊게 읽기. 윤석열 라인 검사의 복잡한 사정. 총수지만 임원은 아닙니다. 시진핑은 한국어 통역을 데려가지 않았다. 다르게 읽기. 연구개발 과제 성공률 95%가 말하는 것. “8년 동안 너무 많이 들어...
The post 공정한 사다리? 같은 출발선이라는 착각: 슬로우레터 11월22일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure RTOS goes open-source as Eclipse ThreadX]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4480938</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/azure-rtos-goes-open-source-as-eclipse-threadx/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T20:44:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A vendor-neutral open source RTOS certified for safety-critical applications and published under a permissive license is an “industry game changer” as Azure RTOS becomes Eclipse ThreadX under the Eclipse Foundation.
The post Azure RTOS goes open-source as Eclipse ThreadX appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU Coverage (gcov) for an Embedded Target with VS Code]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39177</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/11/21/gnu-coverage-gcov-for-an-embedded-target-with-vs-code/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T17:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article explains how to use GNU gcov (coverage) with an embedded system, utilizing Visual Studio Code. It outlines the requirement of VS Code version, toolchain, semihosting, and a debug probe. Specific details are given on linking libraries, instrumenting source files, platform configuration, etc., with example provided on GitHub. The process offers the possibility to generate test coverage data for the software, which can be viewed within VS Code via the Gcov Viewer and coverage reports generated using gcovr utility. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RFC 9498: The GNU Name System]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952122/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952122/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T16:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNU Name System has now been formalized as RFC 9498.


	GNS addresses long-standing security and privacy issues in the
	ubiquitous Domain Name System (DNS). Previous attempts to secure
	DNS (DNSSEC) fail to address critical security issues such as
	end-to-end security, query privacy, censorship, and centralization
	of root zone governance. After 40 years of patching, it is time for
	a new beginning.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.43.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952121/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952121/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T16:42:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.43.0 of the Git
source-code management system has been release.  It includes a long list of
improvements and minor new features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Trust in and maintenance of filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/951846/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/951846/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T15:06:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Linux kernel supports a wide variety of filesystems, many of which are
no longer in heavy use — or, perhaps, any use at all.  The kernel code
implementing the less-popular filesystems tends to be relatively unpopular
as well, receiving little in the way of maintenance.  Keeping old
filesystems alive does place a burden on kernel developers, though, so it
is not surprising that there is pressure to remove the least popular ones.
At the 2023 Kernel Maintainers Summit, the developers talked about these
filesystems and what can be done about them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 120.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952090/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952090/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T15:03:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
120.0 of the Firefox browser is out.  Changes include a new "copy link
without site tracking" option, the ability to enable the Global Privacy Control
feature, and some additional privacy features seemingly restricted to users
in Germany.  The browser will now also import TLS root certificates from
the operating system by default on Windows, macOS, and Android.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ekstrand: NVK reaches Vulkan 1.0 conformance]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952089/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952089/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T14:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faith Ekstrand has announced
that the NVK Vulkan driver for NVIDIA "Turing" GPUs has been certified as
being fully compliant with the Vulkan 1.0 API.


	Practically, it means that we can pass the entire Vulkan
	conformance test suite. From the Khronos perspective, it means that
	NVK now meets the bar required to claim to support the Vulkan API
	officially. (There are some legal implications to this which matter
	to the Mesa project, but most users don't care about them.) From
	the perspective of users, it means the driver should pretty much
	work on Turing and later GPUs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/952088/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/952088/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T14:52:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (activemq, strongswan, and wordpress), Mageia (u-boot), SUSE (avahi, frr, libreoffice, nghttp2, openssl, openssl1, postgresql, postgresql15, postgresql16, python-Twisted, ucode-intel, and xen), and Ubuntu (avahi, hibagent, nodejs, strongswan, tang, and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[나는 타인의 평가에서 자유로울 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>20231121-how-to-overcome-being-self-conscious</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2023/11/21/how-to-overcome-being-self-conscious/"/>
        <updated>2023-11-21T12:58:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>