<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-04-03T20:14:11.351Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux OS - CVE-2024-1086 and XZ (AlmaLinux blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/968299/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/968299/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T18:39:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AlmaLinux has announced
updated kernels for AlmaLinux 8 and 9 to address CVE-2024-1086, a
use-after-free vulnerability in the kernel that could be exploited to
gain local privilege escalation. This is notable because the fix
marks a divergence between AlmaLinux and Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL):
In January of this year, a kernel flaw was disclosed and named CVE-2024-1086.
This flaw is trivially exploitable on most RHEL-equivalent
systems. There are many proof-of-concept posts available now,
including one from our Infrastructure team lead, Jonathan Wright (Dealing
with CVE-2024-1086). In multi-user scenarios, this flaw is
especially problematic.


Though this was flagged as something to be fixed in Red Hat
Enterprise Linux, Red Hat has only rated this as a moderate
impact.
The AlmaLinux project would also like to note that it is not
impacted by the XZ backdoor. "Because enterprise Linux takes a bit
longer to adopt those updates (sometimes to the chagrin of our users),
the version of XZ that had the back door inserted hadn't made it
further than Fedora in our ecosystem."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malcolm: Improvements to static analysis in the GCC 14 compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/968297/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/968297/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T16:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Malcolm writes
about some static-analyzer features that are coming in the GCC 14
release.


	Solving the halting problem?

	Obviously I'm kidding with the title here, but for GCC 14 I've
	implemented a new warning: -Wanalyzer-infinite-loop that's able to
	detect some simple cases of infinite loops.


See also: this report from the 2023 GNU
Tools Cauldron.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/968250/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/968250/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.8.3, 6.7.12, 6.6.24, and 6.1.84 stable kernel updates have been
released. Each contains an important set of fixes. Note that 6.7.12 is
the final release for the 6.7.y series, and that branch is now
end-of-life. Users should move to the 6.8.y branch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A memory model for Rust code in the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967049/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967049/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T14:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust programming language differs from C in many ways; those
differences tend to be what users admire in the language.  But those
differences can also lead to an impedance mismatch when Rust code is
integrated into a C-dominated system, and it can be even worse in the
kernel, which is not a typical C program.  Memory models are a case in
point.  A programming language's view of memory is sufficiently fundamental
and arcane that many developers never have to learn much about it.  It is
hard to maintain that sort of blissful ignorance while working in the
kernel, though, so a recent discussion of how to choose a memory model for
kernel code in Rust is of interest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KDE6 release: D-Bus and Polkit Galore (SUSE security team blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/968220/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/968220/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T13:45:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SUSE Security Team Blog is carrying a
detailed article on SUSE's review of the KDE6 release.


	The SUSE security team restricts the installation of system wide
	D-Bus services and Polkit policies in openSUSE distributions and
	derived SUSE products. Any package that ships these features needs
	to be reviewed by us first, before it can be added to production
	repositories.

	In November, openSUSE KDE packagers approached us with a long list
	of KDE components for an upcoming KDE6 major release. The packages
	needed adjusted D-Bus and Polkit whitelistings due to renamed
	interfaces or other breaking changes. Looking into this many
	components at once was a unique experience that also led to new
	insights, which will be discussed in this article.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/968218/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/968218/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T13:41:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (py7zr), Fedora (biosig4c++ and podman), Oracle (kernel, kernel-container, and ruby:3.1), Red Hat (.NET 7.0, bind9.16, curl, expat, grafana, grafana-pcp, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, less, opencryptoki, and postgresql-jdbc), and Ubuntu (cacti).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiplexing a 1-Wire host across multiple channels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481835</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/multiplexing-a-1-wire-host-across-multiple-channels/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T13:31:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1-Wire networks with many 1-Wire nodes can require dedicated 1-Wire channels. This article discusses a method for using only one 1-Wire host in a network...
The post Multiplexing a 1-Wire host across multiple channels appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stewart Merkel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redict 7.3.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/968183/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/968183/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T13:24:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first stable release of Redict, a fork of the Redis in-memory database
under a copyleft license, has been announced.


	You may be wondering why Redict would be of interest to you,
	particularly when compared with Valkey,
	another Redis fork that was announced on Thursday.

	In technical terms, we are focusing on stability and long-term
	maintenance, and on achieving excellence within our current
	scope. We believe that Redict is near feature-complete and that it
	is more valuable to our users if we take a conservative stance to
	innovation and focus on long-term reliability instead. This is in
	part a choice we've made to distinguish ourselves from Valkey,
	whose commercial interests are able to invest more resources into
	developing more radical innovations, but also an acknowledgement of
	a cultural difference between our projects, in that the folks
	behind Redict place greater emphasis on software with a finite
	scope and ambitions towards long-term stability rather than
	focusing on long-term growth in scope and complexity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How miniaturization impacts PCB inspection]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481837</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-miniaturization-impacts-pcb-inspection/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smaller device form factors often bring PCB design challenges that can subsequently affect inspection. Making printed circuit boards (PCBs) progressively smaller is an ongoing trend...
The post How miniaturization impacts PCB inspection appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1분기 테슬라 판매량을 보는 월가의 시각, 재앙이다. 테슬라 주가는 지속 하락 가능성]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594256</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594256/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T07:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements to static analysis in the GCC 14 compiler]]></title>
        <id>37e9b438-8c34-4fae-a57c-e1ddb61ab500</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/03/improvements-static-analysis-gcc-14-compiler"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I work at Red Hat on GCC, the GNU Compiler Collection. For the last five releases of GCC, I've been working on -fanalyzer, a static analysis pass that tries to identify various problems at compile-time, rather than at runtime. It performs "symbolic execution" of C source code—effectively simulating the behavior of the code along the various possible paths of execution through it.
This article summarizes what's new with -fanalyzer in GCC 14, which I hope will be officially released sometime in April 2024.
Solving the halting problem?
Obviously I'm kidding with the title here, but for GCC 14 I've implemented a new warning: -Wanalyzer-infinite-loop that's able to detect some simple cases of infinite loops.
For example, consider the following C code:
void test (int m, int n)
{
  float arr[m][n…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Malcolm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to add debug support for Go stripped binaries]]></title>
        <id>29f06dce-0a8a-4c3d-b2b0-e5952a359a10</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/03/how-add-debug-support-go-stripped-binaries"/>
        <updated>2024-04-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A stripped binary is generally devoid of symbol and debug information. There could be many reasons why one would need to generate a stripped binary. Symbol information takes up a lot of storage space, so when there are space constraints, it makes sense to work with stripped binaries.
In the case of Go, we can create a stripped binary either by using go build ldflags="-s -w" or by using the strip command. Debugging is the other side of development, and debugging a stripped binary can be challenging. Go is unique, and unlike other languages, we can still hack our way around to obtain some amount of symbol information from the binaries. This article focuses on how we support stripped binaries in Delve, the Go debugger. 
Finding symbols in stripped binaries
Go retains some information on symbo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Parker, Archana Ravindar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선거 공보물에 윤석열과 이재명 사진이 사라진 이유: 슬로우레터 4월3일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106395</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106395"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T22:02:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“49곳이 1000표 이내로 결판.” 민주당은 ‘부자 몸조심’, 국민의힘은 ‘언더독’ 전략. 200석이 되면 할 수 있는 것. “전공의들 만나겠다.” 쟁점과 현안. “이대생 성 상납” 발언 논란, 김준혁도 버티기. “제가 이렇게 사라지게 두실 겁니까.” 다르게 읽기. 내일부터 여론조사 블랙아웃. 돈 풀어도 물가 안 잡히는 이유. 875원 대파 총선 끝나면 끝? 더 깊게 읽기. “다단계는 이종근이 전문.” 오늘의...
The post 선거 공보물에 윤석열과 이재명 사진이 사라진 이유: 슬로우레터 4월3일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple & quick search for bugs in Unity games (for C# developers)]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1111/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1111/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each of us encounters game bugs, and some games have more of them than others. Many games suffer from bugs caused by errors in code. Today, we'll see how static analysis can help easily detect errors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] How the XZ backdoor works]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967192/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967192/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T20:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Versions 5.6.0 and 5.6.1 of the
XZ
compression utility and library
were shipped with a backdoor that targeted
OpenSSH.
Andres Freund

discovered the backdoor by
noticing that failed SSH logins were taking a lot of
CPU time while doing some
micro-benchmarking, and tracking down the backdoor from there. It was introduced
by XZ co-maintainer "Jia Tan" — a probable alias for person or persons unknown.
The backdoor is a sophisticated attack with multiple parts, from the build
system, to link time, to run time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Infineon and Green Hills combine MCU and RTOS for EVs and SDVs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481826</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/infineon-and-green-hills-combine-mcu-and-rtos-for-evs-and-sdvs/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T17:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Platform is designed to provide OEMs and Tier 1s with a safe, secure processing platform to develop domain and zonal controllers as well as drivetrains for electric vehicles for next-generation software-defined vehicle architectures.
The post Infineon and Green Hills combine MCU and RTOS for EVs and SDVs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Free software's not-so-eXZellent adventure]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967866/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967866/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T16:22:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common theme in early-days anti-Linux FUD was that, since anybody can
contribute to the code, it cannot be trusted.  Over two decades later, one
rarely hears that line anymore; experience has shown that free-software
communities are not prone to shipping overtly hostile code.  But, as the backdooring of XZ has reminded us, the
embedding of malicious code is, unfortunately, not limited to the
proprietary realm.  Our community will be busy analyzing this incident for
some time to come, but clear conclusions may be hard to come by.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조선일보, 박은정에 집중 포화: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 (3월 넷째 주)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106379</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106379"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T15:22:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요약 주요 이슈 1. 박은정 후보 등 야권 후보 의혹 제기 본격화 2. 용산 촉발 의대 2천명 증원 논란 지속 3. 야, 지도부 유세… 여, 한동훈 개인 유세 4. 조국혁신당, 검찰 ‘디지털 캐비닛’ 국정조사 이슈화 5. 여야 총선 공약 보도량 증가 ① 공약 이슈, 보도량 5위 ② 논란 일으킨 공약 이슈는 급소멸 6. 판세-여론조사 보도...
The post 조선일보, 박은정에 집중 포화: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 (3월 넷째 주) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customize AWS cloud images with RHEL image builder and Packit]]></title>
        <id>9b61fb1e-9012-4216-9fc3-b1bf45d85f07</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/02/customize-aws-cloud-images-rhel-image-builder-and-packit"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to bring your pull request changes in a cloud image easily?
Curious about how easy it can be? With Packit, it can be just a matter of commenting on your pull request with the following command:
/packit vm-image-build
With the above command, Packit automates all the manual steps needed to create an RPM package with your pull request changes and asks the Red Hat Enterprise Linux image builder (RHEL image builder) to install it inside a brand new cloud image.
Let's have a look at the prerequisites for this.
Join the Red Hat Developer program
If you don't already have a business account, you can create a Red Hat Developer account at no cost.
You need a subscription in order to use the RHEL image builder service and launch the builded images in the Amazon Web Services (AWS)…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maja Massarini</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncovering Seams in a Mainframe's external interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/uncovering-mainframe-seams.html#InternalInterfaces</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/uncovering-mainframe-seams.html#InternalInterfaces"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alessio Ferri and Tom Coggrave move
       on to analyzing the internal seams of the application by treating
       the database as a coarse-grained seam. They describe how they introduced
       seams into the database readers and writers.
       
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967959/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967959/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:41:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (kernel and webkitgtk), Mageia (unixODBC and w3m), and SUSE (libvirt, netty, netty-tcnative, and perl-DBD-SQLite).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded world: Synzen brings first free-to download OS IoT design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481821</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-world-synzen-brings-first-free-to-download-os-iot-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The solution includes full Altium design files and all required software and firmware, along with an environmental sensor measuring temperature, humidity, air quality, and air pressure.
The post embedded world: Synzen brings first free-to download OS IoT design appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HighTec and Doulos offer Rust training including use with legacy C/C++ code]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481814</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/hightec-and-doulos-offer-rust-training-including-use-with-legacy-c-c-code/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T12:31:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The “Rust Fundamentals” course serves as a general introduction to Rust programming for building embedded systems and can be delivered in four days of in-person training or five interactive sessions of six hours each of live online training.
The post HighTec and Doulos offer Rust training including use with legacy C/C++ code appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded world: Microchip adds 2 Mb and 4 Mb serial SRAM devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481808</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-world-microchip-adds-2-mb-and-4-mb-serial-sram-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T11:19:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microchip said its new 2Mb and 4 Mb serial SRAM devices are intended to replace expensive parallel SRAM with an easy and cost-effective alternative.
The post embedded world: Microchip adds 2 Mb and 4 Mb serial SRAM devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded world: Advantech to show new OSM modules targeting edge AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481800</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-world-advantech-to-show-new-osm-modules-targeting-edge-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T10:52:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Among its x86/ARM portfolio for emerging markets such as EV charging and AI-integrated robotics, Advantech will be launching new OSM modules based on Qualcomm and NXP.
The post embedded world: Advantech to show new OSM modules targeting edge AI appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The xz attack shell script]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/xz-script</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/xz-script"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed walkthrough of the xz attack shell script.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[번역] 프로그래머를 위한 카테고리 이론 - 8. 펑터의 특성]]></title>
        <id>20240402-category-theory-for-programmers-8-functoriality</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/04/02/category-theory-for-programmers-8-functoriality/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T05:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이제 펑터가 무엇인지 알았으니, 작은 펑터로부터 큰 펑터를 구축해나가는 방법에 대해서 살펴보도록 하겠다. 여기서 특히 흥미로운 부분은 카테고리 내 대상 간의 매핑에 대당하는 타입의 생성자가 확장되어 사상 간의 매핑을 포함하는 펑터가 되는 과정을 볼 수 있다는 것이다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timeline of the xz open source attack]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/xz-timeline</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/xz-timeline"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T03:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A detailed timeline of the xz open source attack, from 2021 to 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[논문리뷰] PAC it up (ARM Pointer Authentication)]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16559829</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16559829"/>
        <updated>2024-04-02T02:46:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아래 논문은 USENIX 2019에서 발표되었다.

Liljestrand, Hans, et al. "{PAC} it up: Towards pointer integrity using {ARM} pointer authentication." 28th USENIX Security Symposium (USENIX Security 19). 2019.

출처: https://www.usenix.org/conference/usenixsecurity19/presentation/liljestrand


Abstract:
C나 C++ 등 메모리 취약점으로부터 안전하지 않은 언어로 작성된 프로그램에 대한 런타임 공격이 컴퓨터 시스템을 위협하고 있다. 실제로 ROP 등의 공격이 발전하면서 프로세서 주요 제조사들은 이를 하드웨어적으로 방어할 수 있는 방법을 고안하고 있다. 특히 스마트폰과 같은 장치에서 흔히 사용되는 ARMv8-A 프로세서 아키텍처에 최근 추가된 포인터 인증(PA) 지원이 있다. PA는 메모리 취약점에 저항하기 위해 포인터를 인증하는 저비용 기술이다. 이는 반환 주소나 함수 포인터를 변조하는 메모리 취약점에 대한 실용적인 보호를 가능하게 한다. 글나 지금까지 PA를 활용한 구체적인 사례들이 많지는 않았다. 이에 본 논문에서는 ARM 환경에서 PA를 활용하여 보호를 강화하는 방법을 다루고, LLVM 컴파일러에 이를 통합하는 도구인 PARTS 를 제안하고자 한다. 실제 실험 결과 PARTS를 사용하면 기존의 유사 솔루션에 비해 합리적인 성능으로 보안성을 강화할 수 있었다.


1. 서론 및 본 연구의 목적:
이 연구에서는…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[자본주의가 가장 마지막에 줄여야 하는 비용은 이것]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79039</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/04/01/npsp_techlayoffs/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_techlayoffs"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T22:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[실리콘 밸리 테크 기업들이 코로나19 때 ‘재미를 본’ 대량 해고를 통한 단기적인 주가 극대화 전략을 계속해서 사용하고 있습니다. 주가가 올라 주주들에게 이익이 돌아가면 모두가 좋은 이상적인 상황처럼 보일 수 있지만, 이러한 과정에서 철저히 배제되는 집단을 생각하면 마냥 좋은 일이라고 부르기 어렵습니다. 그 대표적인 이해관계자가 회사를 위해 일하는 임금 노동자들입니다. 전문 번역: 인간을 ‘믹서기 속의 삶’으로 몰아넣는 테크업계의 또 다른 유행 해설: 자본주의가 가장 마지막에 줄여야 하는 비용은 이것]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국민의힘 의원들이 “멸종 예감하는 공룡들 심정”이라고 말한 이유: 슬로우레터 4월2일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106346</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106346"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T22:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“2000명은 그냥 나온 숫자가 아니다.” 꿈보다 해몽, 신문마다 포인트가 다르다. “의사들을 악마화했다.” 윤석열은 달라지지 않을 것이다. “날아오는 혜성 보며 멸종 예감하는 공룡들의 심정.” “쇠귀에 경읽기, 탈당해 달라.” “70 평생에 이렇게 못 하는 정부는 처음.” 쟁점과 현안. 양문석, “아파트 팔겠다.” 옷 색깔이 달라졌다. “제 책임이 아니지 않습니까.” 다르게 읽기. 아낌없이 주는 한동훈. 자영업자 육아휴직 가능할까. 더...
The post 국민의힘 의원들이 “멸종 예감하는 공룡들 심정”이라고 말한 이유: 슬로우레터 4월2일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synopsys SNUG: AI driven EDA momentum, new tools for multi-die]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481788</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/synopsys-snug-ai-driven-eda-momentum-new-tools-for-multi-die/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T20:05:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Synopsys highlighted momentum its ai suite which includes DSO.ai and VSO.ai, and introduced 3DSO.ai to enable 3D design space optimization for multi-die systems, plus new hardware-assisted verification solutions and access to a new cloud hybrid system.
The post Synopsys SNUG: AI driven EDA momentum, new tools for multi-die appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nvidia GTC: NIM microservices will drive more generative AI copilots]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481779</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nvidia-gtc-nim-microservices-will-drive-more-generative-ai-copilots/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T19:08:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NIMs enable users to create and deploy custom applications on their own platforms and retain full ownership of their IP. Built on top of CUDA, a catalog of cloud-native microservices is available Nvidia and its partners.
The post Nvidia GTC: NIM microservices will drive more generative AI copilots appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Improving performance with SCHED_EXT and IOCost]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966618/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966618/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At SCALE
this year Dan Schatzberg and Tejun Heo,
both from Meta, gave back-to-back talks about some
of the performance-engineering work that they do there. Schatzberg presented on
the extensible BPF scheduler, which has been
discussed extensively on the kernel mailing list.
Heo presented on IOCost — a control group (cgroup) I/O controller
optimized for solid-state disks (SSDs) — and the benchmark suite that is necessary to
make it work well on different models of disk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ambiq launches SoC for running AI/ML on batteries]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481772</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ambiq-launches-soc-for-running-ai-ml-on-batteries/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T17:42:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ambiq said combination of performance and efficiency enables its customers to deploy sophisticated speech, vision, health, and industrial AI models on battery-powered devices everywhere.
The post Ambiq launches SoC for running AI/ML on batteries appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The volatile keyword]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1650.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1650.php"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T16:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have often talked and written about my thoughts on programming languages. In particular, the fact that there really is no language that was designed with embedded programming specifically in mind. Historically, there was assembly language, but that is rarely used for large scale coding nowadays. Intel promoted PL/M many years ago, but that has long since fallen by the wayside.
C and C++ are...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NetBSD 10.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967856/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967856/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T14:28:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 10.0 of the NetBSD system has been released.


	The netbsd-10 release branch is more than a year old now, so it is
	high time the 10.0 release makes it to the front stage. This
	matches the long time it took for the development branch to get
	ready for branching, a lot of development went into this new
	release.

	This also caused the release announcement to be one of the longest
	we ever did.


As might be imagined, there are a lot of changes; see the
above-mentioned release announcement for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967851/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967851/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T14:10:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Arch Linux (xz), Debian (libvirt, mediawiki, util-linux, and xz-utils), Fedora (apache-commons-configuration, cockpit, ghc-base64, ghc-hakyll, ghc-isocline, ghc-toml-parser, gitit, gnutls, pandoc, pandoc-cli, patat, podman-tui, prometheus-podman-exporter, seamonkey, suricata, and xen), Gentoo (XZ utils), Mageia (aide & mhash, emacs, microcode, opensc, and squid), Red Hat (ruby:3.1), and SUSE (kanidm and qpid-proton).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.9-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967792/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967792/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9-rc2 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Neither snow nor rain nor heat nor gloom of night stays kernel rc releases.

Nor does Easter."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[거짓말에 관한 다섯 가지 이야기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106318</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106318"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T13:10:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 만우절. 거짓말 혹은 진실과 거짓에 관한 다섯 가지 이야기. 잔돈과 선행 거짓에 관한 첫 번째 기억은 초등학교 2학년이나 3학년 때의 일인 것 같다. 정확히 언제인지는 모르겠다. 아무튼 담임선생님이 불우이웃돕기인 걸까, 어떤 아름다운 목적으로 돈을 걷었다. 나에겐 십원짜리 몇 개와 백원짜리 한두 개 그리고 천원짜리 지폐가 한두 장 있었던 것 같다. 나는 마침 그 잔돈이...
The post 거짓말에 관한 다섯 가지 이야기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[40+20 작업법]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/40-20-method/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/40-20-method/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T11:01:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드: undefined</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure JBoss EAP apps with Microsoft Entra ID & OpenID Connect]]></title>
        <id>f152e694-10b2-45c8-8ee2-ca166ca5c93d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/04/01/secure-jboss-eap-apps-microsoft-entra-id-openid-connect"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recent release of Red Hat JBoss EAP 8.0 includes native support for OpenID Connect (OIDC) via the elytron-oidc-client subsystem. OIDC is an identity layer that enables clients, such as JBoss EAP, to verify a user’s identity based on authentication performed by an OpenID provider. For example, you can secure your JBoss EAP applications using the Red Hat build of Keycloak as the OpenID provider.
In this article, we will use the elytron-oidc-subsystem to secure a simple web application using Microsoft Entra ID (formerly Azure Active Directory) as the OpenID provider.
For more information about JBoss EAP 8.0's native OpenID Connect support, refer to the product documentation.
Prerequisites
A local installation of JBoss EAP 8.0. Download the installation manager from Red Hat Developer.
JBOS…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Hayes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[생존은 필수품, 꿈은 사치품: 가난한 아이들은 어떻게 어른이 되는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106306</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106306"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T06:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, [정부가 없다] 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기…오늘 달려갈 책은 ‘가난한 아이들은 어떻게 어른이 되는가?’ 가난한 아이들에 대한 기억이 별로 없다. 어릴 적 살던 은마아파트는 31평, 34평 다들 비슷비슷 고만고만한 중산층 동네였다. 대학 졸업 후 나는 분명 사회적 약자의 목소리를 대변해야 할 기자가 됐는데, 만나는 이는 대부분 사회의...
The post 생존은 필수품, 꿈은 사치품: 가난한 아이들은 어떻게 어른이 되는가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 1분기 테슬라 판매량은 예상보다 나을 수 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594254</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594254/1%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%eb%9f%89"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T06:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of reading: January - March 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/summary-of-reading-january-march-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/summary-of-reading-january-march-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T05:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<ul class="simple">
<li>&quot;Lessons in Chemistry: A Novel&quot; by Bonnie Garmus - a research chemist finds
her way in the world following multiple personal tragedies and facing extreme
gender discrimination. I have some mixed feelings about this book. On one hand
it's original, enternaining, well-written and thought provoking. On the
other hand it's full …</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chasing resets]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/04/01/chasing-resets.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/04/01/chasing-resets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-01T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A true story.


Some years ago, given a customer’s honest need and request, I proposed a
change to a client’s ASIC
IP.  Specifically, I wanted to add CRC
checking,
based upon a CRC
kept in an out-of-band memory
region, to verify the ability
to properly read memory regions error free.  I said the change shouldn’t take
more than about two weeks, and I’d clean up some other problems I was aware of
in the mean time.  This change solved an urgent problem, so he agreed
to it.
By the time I was done, my 80 hr proposal had turned into 270+ hrs of work.
Build it well
I’d like to start my discussion of what went wrong with a list of good
practices to follow.
Fig 1. Basic test bench components


Just as a background, a general test bench follows the format shown in Fig. 1,
on the right.  The “test be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[투표율 65%가 민주당의 ‘매직 넘버’? 과연 그럴까: 슬로우레터 4월1일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106276</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106276"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T22:16:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사전 투표하겠단 사람 3분의 2가 민주당. “이대로 가면 대한민국 망한다.” 윤석열 오늘 대국민 담화. 2000명 증원 찬성은 29%뿐. 쟁점과 현안. 양문석 리스크, 10석 날아간다? ‘작업 대출’ 맞나. 공영운도 부동산 리스크. “전관예우라면 160억 원은 벌었어야.” 더 깊게 읽기. 2년은 너무 길었다. 이재명은 ‘경제’를, 한동훈은 ‘범죄’를 말했다. 세 살 아기의 죽음. 보수 과표집 아니라 진보 과표집? 오늘의...
The post 투표율 65%가 민주당의 ‘매직 넘버’? 과연 그럴까: 슬로우레터 4월1일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Census of general purpose computers installed in the 1960s]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8670</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/03/31/census-of-general-purpose-computers-installed-in-the-1960s/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T22:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the 1960s a small number of computer manufacturers sold a relatively small number of general purpose computers (IBM dominated the market). Between 1962 and 1974 the magazine Computers and Automation published a monthly census listing the total number of installed, and unfilled orders for, general purpose computers. A pdf of all the scanned census […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When a Mongoose met a MicroPython]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1649.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1649.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-31T20:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mongooses and very small pythons can coexist, and even be friends.

This is more a framework than an actual application, with it you can integrate MicroPython and Cesanta's Mongoose. Mongoose runs when called by MicroPython and is able to run Python functions as callbacks for the events you decide in your event handler. The code is completely written in C, except for the example Python...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A few relevant quotes]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967420/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967420/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T14:18:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm on a holiday and only happened to look at my emails and it
	seems to be a major mess. 

— Lasse Collin


	The reality that we are struggling with is that the free software
	infrastructure on which much of computing runs is massively and
	painfully underfunded by society as a whole, and is almost entirely
	dependent on random people maintaining things in their free time
	because they find it fun, many of whom are close to burnout.  This
	is, in many ways, the true root cause of this entire event.

— Russ Allbery



	Incredible work from Andres.  The attackers made a serious
	strategic mistake: they made PostgreSQL slightly slower.

— Thomas
Munro



	There is no way to discuss this in public without turning a single
	malicious entity into 10 000 malicious entities once the
	information is widely known.

	Making sure the impact and mitigations are known before posting
	this publicly so that everyone knows what to do before the 10 000
	malicious entities start attacking is just common sense.

— Marc
Deslauriers



	Again the FOSS world has proven to be vigilant and proactive in
	finding bugs and backdoors, IMHO. The level of transparency is
	stellar, especially compared to proprietary software
	companies. What the FOSS world has accomplished in 24 hours after
	detection of the backdoor code in #xz deserves a moment of
	humbleness. Instead we have flamewars and armchair experts shouting
	that we must change everything NOW. Which would introduce even more
	risks. Progress is made iteratively. Learn, adapt, repeat.

— Jan Wildeboer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[쇼트] 짝사랑의 정신증적 기제에 관해서]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3550</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2024/fade-into-you/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-30T04:19:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[헤르만 슈미츠의 『사랑의 현상학』에서도, 파트너 간의 사랑을 다룬다는 것은 나에게 있어서 수치스럽기 까지 한 감정을 느끼게 만들지만 그래도 그의 논의에서 건질 점은 있다. 이른바 감정은 공간적이라는 것이다. 나는 그를 짝사랑한다. 이러한 감정은 나를 쓸쓸하게 만든다. 그와 나는 공간적으로 가까울 수 도 있지만 기본적으로는 무한히 멀리 떨어져 있다. 감정적으로든, 공간적으로든 둘다든. 또는 수 천 키로미터 바깥일 수도 있다. 하지만 우리는 가까이 있기도 하다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A backdoor in xz]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967180/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967180/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T17:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andres Freund has posted a
detailed investigation into a backdoor that was shipped with versions
5.6.0 and 5.6.1 of the xz compression utility.  It appears that the
malicious code may be aimed at allowing SSH authentication to be bypassed.


	I have not yet analyzed precisely what is being checked for in the
	injected code, to allow unauthorized access. Since this is running
	in a pre-authentication context, it seems likely to allow some form
	of access or other form of remote code execution.


The affected versions are not yet widely shipped, but checking systems for
the bad version would be a good idea.

Update: there are advisories out now from
Arch,
Debian,
Red
Hat, and
openSUSE.

A further
update from openSUSE:


	For our openSUSE Tumbleweed users where SSH is exposed to the
	internet we recommend installing fresh, as it’s unknown if the
	backdoor has been exploited. Due to the sophisticated nature of the
	backdoor an on-system detection of a breach is likely not
	possible. Also rotation of any credentials that could have been
	fetched from the system is highly recommended.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Radicle: peer-to-peer collaboration with Git]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966869/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966869/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T13:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Radicle is a new, peer-to-peer,
MIT/Apache-licensed collaboration platform written in Rust and built on top
of Git. It adds support for issues and pull requests (which Radicle calls
"patches") on top of core Git, which are stored in the Git repository
itself. Unlike GitHub, GitLab, and similar forges, Radicle is distributed;
it doesn't rely on having everyone use the same server. Instead, Radicle
instances form a network that synchronizes changes between nodes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967134/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967134/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T13:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (apache-commons-configuration, chromium, csmock, ofono, onnx, php-tcpdf, and podman-tui), Mageia (curl), Oracle (libreoffice), Slackware (coreutils, seamonkey, and util), SUSE (minidlna, PackageKit, and podman), and Ubuntu (linux-azure-6.5 and linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schaller: Fedora Workstation 40 – what are we working on]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/967107/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/967107/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T12:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christian Schaller writes
about the desktop-oriented work aimed at the upcoming Fedora 40
release.


	Another major feature landing in Fedora Workstation 40 that Jonas
	Ådahl and Ray Strode has spent a lot of effort on is finalizing the
	remote desktop support for GNOME on Wayland. So there has been
	support for remote connections for already logged in sessions
	already, but with these updates you can do the login remotely too
	and thus the session do not need to be started already on the
	remote machine. This work will also enable 3rd party solutions to
	do remote logins on Wayland systems, so while I am not at liberty
	to mention names, be on the lookout for more 3rd party Wayland
	remoting software becoming available this year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미래가 사라진 총선, 괜찮으십니까?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106237</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106237"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T04:09:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이 모든 지표에서 한국이 OECD 국가 중 1위 또는 최상위권이라고 한다. GDP 순위만으로 선진국이라는 자부심을 가지기에는 우리의 삶이 참 버겁다. 저출생과 지방소멸의 가시화는 한국의 미래를 더욱 암담하게 만든다. 일자리가 없는 지방의 청년들이 떠나면서 지방소멸은 가속도를 내고 있고, 저출생에도 불구하고 인구가 오히려 늘어나고 있는 수도권 거주자들의 삶은 더 팍팍해지고 있다. 겨우 일자리를 잡는다 해도 끝이 안...
The post 미래가 사라진 총선, 괜찮으십니까? appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부적격 후보는 유권자가 걸러내라? 그건 정당과 언론이 해야죠!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106226</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106226"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T03:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[제22대 국회의원 선거가 다가온다. 정치권에 대한 냉소가 하루 이틀 일은 아니지만 이쯤 되면 정말 정치권이 국민의 정치 혐오 정서를 부추겨 그들만의 왕국을 꾸려가고 있다는 음모론에 신뢰가 갈 지경이다. 기초적 검증도 제대로 하지 못해 제1야당이 후보 등록 이후 공천을 취소하고 후보를 제명한 일이 벌어졌다. 여야를 가리지 않고 후보로 확정된 인물들이 이런저런 과거의 부적절한 언행으로 공천이 취소되는...
The post 부적격 후보는 유권자가 걸러내라? 그건 정당과 언론이 해야죠! appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/29, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594241</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594241/3-29-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T00:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving into JTAG — BSDL (Part 4)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-4</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous article of this series, we briefly touched on how .bsd files
written in Boundary Scan Description Language (BSDL) describe the structure of
the boundary scan chain and the instruction set. In this article, we will
examine this language’s syntax more closely before seeing how .bsd files are leveraged
in JTAG testing in the next article.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rohde & Schwarz to show measurements on novel Bluetooth Channel Sounding signals]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481763</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/rohde-schwarz-to-show-measurements-on-novel-bluetooth-channel-sounding-signals/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T23:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Bluetooth Channel Sounding feature will enable unprecedented positioning accuracy for consumer and commercial applications. Rohde & Schwarz will demonstrate signal measurement capabilities to support chip and device development.
The post Rohde & Schwarz to show measurements on novel Bluetooth Channel Sounding signals appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[양심을 찌른 사건, 그들에게 채수근은 2등 시민이었다: 슬로우레터 3월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106176</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106176"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T21:59:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[출근길 대란, 퇴근길에 끝났다. 사전투표, 국민의힘에도 좋다? 쟁점과 현안. 의대 정원, 의-정 갈등에서 의-윤 갈등으로. “정치를 개같이 한다.” 민생 토론회에 세 가지가 없다. 다르게 읽기. 열흘 동안 판세가 바뀔 수도 있을까. 윤석열과 한동훈의 패착. ‘역내로남불’. 더 깊게 읽기. 금지팡이와 흙지팡이. 그들에게 채수근은 2등 시민이었다. 김앤장 네트워크. 재판받겠습니까. 오늘의 TMI. ‘노담’ 청소년 늘었다. 트럼프 500대 부자...
The post 양심을 찌른 사건, 그들에게 채수근은 2등 시민이었다: 슬로우레터 3월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The race to replace Redis]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966631/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966631/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T20:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On March 21, Redis Ltd. announced that the Redis "in-memory data store" project would now be
released under non-free, source-available licenses, starting with Redis 7.4. The
news is unwelcome, but not entirely unexpected. What is unusual with this situation is
the number of Redis alternatives to choose from; there are at least
four options to choose as a replacement for those who wish to stay
with free software, including a pre-existing fork called KeyDB and the Linux Foundation's newly-announced Valkey project. The question now is which one(s)
Linux distributions, users, and providers will choose to take its place.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Joining LinkedIn]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-joining-linkedin.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-joining-linkedin.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the enmuskification of Twitter continues, I’ve increasingly heard that more people are using LinkedIn to keep up with new professional material. So, a couple of weeks ago, I set up my LinkedIn account, so people can follow me on that platform.
I’ve always avoided LinkedIn - I’ve found the whole vibe of connections rather off-putting. I get too much spam from people wanting to connect as it is. But LinkedIn has added a “creator mode”, which encourages people to follow someone for posts rather than the bi-directional connection.  It seems to be working reasonably well so far, so I’ve decided that I shall post all updates here to that account too. However I’m still avoiding connections, so please don’t send me a connection request unless we’ve done some substantial work together.
I’m still posting to X (Twitter), but as it steadily deteriorates, it gets less of my attention. If you follow me there, I recommend switching to one of my other feeds if you can.
I don’t particularly like LinkedIn for its feed, as I have little control over it. I never like the site suggestions, preferring as simple feeds of people. Sadly, LinkedIn doesn’t have lists, and pushes everything someone likes into the single connection feed. This leads to Too Many Posts which means I don’t pay attention to much.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Declarative partitioning in PostgreSQL]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965508/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965508/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T15:34:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keith Fiske gave a talk
(with 
slides) about the state of partitioning — splitting a large
table into smaller tables for performance reasons — in
PostgreSQL at
SCALE
this year. He spoke about the existing support for partitioning, what work still
needs to be done, and what place existing partitioning tools, like his own

pg_partman, still have as PostgreSQL gains more built-in features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Samba 4.20.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966996/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966996/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T14:19:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.20.0 of the Samba Windows interoperability suite has been
released.  Changes include better support for group-managed service
accounts, an experimental Windows search protocol client, support for
conditional access control entries, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Packet capture using Network Observability eBPF Agent]]></title>
        <id>1436d8ea-2740-42a2-ae76-77d9e38bb08f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/28/packet-capture-using-network-observability-ebpf-agent"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network observability is the ability to easily identify and answer questions about your network in real-time, and use the information to make informed decisions to manage and optimize network resources. To facilitate and dig deeper with more insights into an ongoing network flow in real-time, we present Packet Capture Agent (PCA), an extension to the Network Observability eBPF Agent (netobserv-agent).
Historically, network observability data constituted of flow logs. A flow log record captures network flow, essentially layer 4 and 5 data. While this is useful and is extensively used for making network decisions, the question we ask is: can we do better? Is there still information hiding that we have not been able to collect/use for observability?
We argue that significant additional networ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shachee Mishra Gupta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966961/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966961/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T13:54:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (perl-Data-UUID, python-pygments, and thunderbird), Mageia (clojure, grub2, kernel,kmod-xtables-addons,kmod-virtualbox, kernel-linus, nss firefox, nss, python3, python, tcpreplay, and thunderbird), Oracle (nodejs:18), Red Hat (.NET 6.0 and dnsmasq), SUSE (avahi and python39), and Ubuntu (curl, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, unixodbc, and util-linux).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With CUDA C on an Nvidia Jetson: GPU Architecture]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1648.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1648.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T10:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview
In the previous blog post (Getting Started With CUDA C on Jetson Nvidia: Hello CUDA World!) I showed how to develop applications targeted at a GPU on a Nvidia Jetson Nano. As we observed in that blog post, performing a calculation on a 1-D array on a GPU had no performance benefit compared to a traditional CPU implementation, even on an array with many elements. In this blog post,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[갑작스러운 버스 파업이요? 실은 총선에 밀려 구석에 처박혔죠]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106172</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106172"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T09:22:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 아침 갑작스러운(?) 서울 시내버스 파업으로 많은 시민이 당혹함 속에서 어려움을 겪었습니다. 어떻게 파업이 하룻밤 새에 실행될 수 있을까요? 언론의 환경감시 기능 부실 혐의가 짙습니다. 이미 노조는 협상 결렬 후 파업을 예고했고 어젯밤이 마지막 협상이었다고 하지요. 그런데 언론들은 시민들이 어떻게 해야 하는지 미리 알려주는 것은 언감생심이고 실제적인 파업 가능성 자체를 인지하기 어렵게 했습니다. 그리고 아침이...
The post 갑작스러운 버스 파업이요? 실은 총선에 밀려 구석에 처박혔죠 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>강형철</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI 개발자 Devin 소개를 보고 느낀 점]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=13359</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2024/03/28/devins/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T03:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[※ 아직 써보진 않았습니다. 써보면 의견이 어떻게 달라질지 모르겠네요. 작년 : “ChatGPT야, Java Spring 코드 만들어 줘”올해 : “Devin, 이런 거 이렇게 짜 줘” Cognition labs 라는 회사에서 세계 최초의 AI 개발자 “Devin”을 만들었습니다.Engineer 와 Developer는 다른데 그냥 “개발자”라고 의역을 하겠습니다. 회사 홈페이지를 가보았습니다. “왜 만들었나…” 궁금하더라고요.달랑 두 개의 블로그 글만 올라와 있습니다. 회사 이야기... Continue Reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 28, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966118/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966118/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T00:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 28, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 이것은 “혁신의 탈을 쓴 불평등”인가 아닌가]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78667</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/27/npsp_gigworkers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_gigworkers"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T22:59:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 2월 7일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 긱(gig)이란 영어 단어의 첫 번째 뜻은 크지 않은 규모로, 때론 즉흥적으로 진행하는 음악 연주나 코미디 공연입니다. 이어 두 번째 뜻이 일 또는 직장인데, 정규직보다는 임시로, 부정기적으로 하는 계약직 일자리나 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Renesas launches first general-purpose 32-bit RISC-V based MCUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481758</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/renesas-launches-first-general-purpose-32-bit-risc-v-based-mcus/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T22:54:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While many MCU providers have recently joined investment alliances to advance the development of RISC-V products, Renesas said it has already designed and tested a new RISC-V core independently.
The post Renesas launches first general-purpose 32-bit RISC-V based MCUs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[보수 진영의 때늦은 후회, 완전 연동형이라면 어땠을까: 슬로우레터 3월28일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106126</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106126"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T22:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[8일 동안의 전쟁. 윤석열의 급식 봉사. 혐오 vs. 혐오. 국회를 세종으로. 쟁점과 현안. “대통령이 우리한테 쓴 약 먹여도.” 비동의 강간죄, 공약집에 넣었다 뺐다. 2000명=윤석열의 불통. 더 깊게 읽기. 한동훈의 화법. 삼성 노조 와해, 항소 포기. 다르게 읽기. 수업 시간 몰래 녹음, 크게 늘었다. 독점의 개념을 다시 써야 한다. 소선거구제의 모순, 보수의 자승자박. 해법과 대안. ‘더...
The post 보수 진영의 때늦은 후회, 완전 연동형이라면 어땠을까: 슬로우레터 3월28일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Farewell, John Kordyback]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/kordyback-tribute.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/kordyback-tribute.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Kordyback, a treasured colleague and friend, died last week, aged 64.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The PostgreSQL community mourns Simon Riggs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966868/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966868/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T15:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PostgreSQL community is dealing with the loss of Simon Riggs, who
passed away on March 26:


	Simon was responsible for many of the enterprise features we find
	in PostgreSQL today, including point in time recovery, hot standby,
	and synchronous replication. He was the founder of 2ndQuadrant
	which employed many of the PostgreSQL developers, later becoming
	part of EDB where he worked as a Postgres Fellow until his
	retirement. He was responsible for the UK PostgreSQL conferences
	for many years until he passed that responsibility to PostgreSQL
	Europe last year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] High-performance computing with Ubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965516/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965516/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T15:36:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jason Nucciarone and Felipe Reyes gave back-to-back talks
about high-performance computing (HPC) using Ubuntu at
SCALE this
year. Nucciarone talked about ongoing work packaging

Open OnDemand — a web-based HPC cluster interface —
to make high-performance-computing clusters
more user friendly. Reyes presented on using
OpenStack — a cloud-computing platform
— to pass the performance benefits of one's hardware through
to virtual machines (VMs) running on a cluster.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncovering Seams in a Mainframe's external interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/uncovering-mainframe-seams.html#Seams</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/uncovering-mainframe-seams.html#Seams"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alessio Ferri and Tom Coggrave start
       detailing the seams they explored with two areas of external interfaces.
       Batch input of files are copied to new implementations while comparing the output of the
       processing pipelines. API access points can be covered with a proxy and
       traffic gradually directed to the new implementation.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966835/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966835/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T13:18:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (composer and nodejs), Fedora (w3m), Mageia (tomcat), Oracle (expat, firefox, go-toolset:ol8, grafana, grafana-pcp, nodejs:18, and thunderbird), Red Hat (dnsmasq, expat, kernel, kernel-rt, libreoffice, and squid), and SUSE (firefox, krb5, libvirt, and shadow).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘런종섭’이 지배한 한 주: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 (3월 셋째 주)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106105</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106105"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T11:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요약 주요 이슈 1. ‘이종섭 호주 대사 논란’ 보도건수‧노출시간이 모두 1위 2. 윤석열-한동훈 갈등이 주요 이슈로 부상 3. 더불어민주당 강북을 공천 논란, 국민의힘 비례공천 논란 보도 압도 4. 한동훈 위원장 지원 유세 발언, 이재명 대표보다 많아 5. 판세-여론조사 보도 본격화 6. 공약-의제 이슈 10위권 밖 7. 조국혁신당 지속 보도 언론사별 주요 이슈 1. KBS 이종섭...
The post ‘런종섭’이 지배한 한 주: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 (3월 셋째 주) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한국에서 여성으로 노동한다는 것: 비혼과 저출산이라는 개인적 합리성과 사회적 실패]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105650</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105650"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T08:25:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)이 전하는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기… 지난 3월 8일은 세계 여성의 날. 연례행사처럼 발표된 유리천장 지수는 12년째 꼴찌, 성별 임금 격차는 OECD 1위. 꼴찌와 1등: 유리천장 지수 꼴찌, 성별 임금 격차 1등 지난 3월 8일은 세계 여성의 날이었다. 이코노미스트가 유리천장 지수를 발표했다. 한국은 12년째 꼴찌다. 이제는 익숙한 연례행사. 거기에...
The post 한국에서 여성으로 노동한다는 것: 비혼과 저출산이라는 개인적 합리성과 사회적 실패 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrating from Red Hat Fuse to Red Hat build of Apache Camel]]></title>
        <id>10be0b9c-46f7-4bec-a02e-978e75e1450a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/27/migrating-red-hat-fuse-red-hat-build-apache-camel"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article proposes a simplified migration path for Red Hat build of Apache Camel that aims to drastically decrease your migration effort using a template-based solution pattern.
Migrating from Red Hat Fuse to Red Hat build of Apache Camel
Modernization is about more than just adopting the latest technologies; we should do it in a way that is both reliable and cost-effective to ensure that the investments we make today will preserve their impact and utility well into the future. Therefore, we choose vendor-neutral solutions that offer longevity, scalability, and flexibility. By utilizing integration best practices and patterns, developer teams can focus on high-value tasks.
Red Hat Fuse is the Red Hat solution for integrating applications based on Apache Camel version 2. Red Hat build of…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Thirion, Ivo Bek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중국이 ‘서구의 대안’? 아니라는 게 확실해지고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79011</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/27/npsp_chinaandthewest/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_chinaandthewest"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T04:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[올해 들어 프랑스 도서 베스트셀러 상위권을 꾸준히 지켜오고 있는 역사학자 엠마누엘 토드의 신간 “서구의 몰락(La Défaite de l’Occident)”은 실패 끝에 추락하고 있는 미국의 리더십을 다룬 책입니다. 21세기 들어 미국 중심의 세계 질서에 회의가 들 때마다, 문제가 지적될 때마다 중국은 대안으로 꼽히는 나라 중 하나였습니다. 과연 지금도 그렇다고 할 수 있을까요? 엠마누엘 토드의 통찰을 분석한 크리스토퍼 콜드웰의 칼럼을 번역하고 싱가포르 난양공대의 중국 정치 전문가 이종혁 교수가 해설을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 예언마다 적중시켰던 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/27, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594227</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594227/3-27-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T02:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966755/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966755/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sasha Levin has announced the release of the 6.8.2, 6.7.11,
6.6.23, 6.1.83, 5.15.153, 5.10.214, 5.4.273, and 4.19.311 stable kernels.  Each contains a long
list of important fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PCIe Gen6 CXL3.0 retimer: a small chip for big next-gen AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481742</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/new-pcie-gen6-cxl3-0-retimer-a-small-chip-for-big-next-gen-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T22:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next generation of AI clusters will require more GPUs and more machines which will require either optical interconnects or PCIe active electrical cables. We dive into the details of Astera Labs new Aries 6 PCIe Gen6 retimers that support the CXL 3.x protocol.
The post New PCIe Gen6 CXL3.0 retimer: a small chip for big next-gen AI appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Shilov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘대파 게이트’, 윤석열의 고집이 논란을 키우고 있다: 슬로우레터 3월27일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106060</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106060"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T22:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“총선 이후가 두렵다.” “대파는 문재인 때 더 비쌌다.” 한 단이냐 한 뿌리냐. ‘대파 게이트’, 국민의힘도 화들짝. 쟁점과 현안. 꼬이는 의정 갈등. 2000명 고집하지 말자는데. 조국 펀드, 1시간도 안 돼 200억 원 모았다. 더 깊게 읽기. 범야권 200석 불가능하지 않다. 결국 투표율이 변수. 다르게 읽기. 압수수색은 다 들고 가라는 치트키가 아니다. 해법과 대안. 다문화 학생 늘어나는데....
The post ‘대파 게이트’, 윤석열의 고집이 논란을 키우고 있다: 슬로우레터 3월27일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting up static analysis for Unreal Engine project]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1110/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1110/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PVS-Studio analyzer's been supporting the analysis of the Unreal Engine projects for a long time. Since the last post on the topic, we've hammered away at this mode. That's why we'd like to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] GNOME 46 puts Flatpaks front and center]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966187/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966187/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T16:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNOME project announced
GNOME 46 (code-named "Kathmandu") on March 20. The release has quite a few updates and improvements
across user applications, developer tools, and under the hood. One
thing stood out while looking over this release—a major emphasis on
Flatpaks as the way to acquire and update GNOME software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Rust: where are we today?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481737</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-rust-where-are-we-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T16:02:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust makes a lot of sense for general application development, but does it really make sense for embedded software teams? Have you heard about Rust?...
The post Embedded Rust: where are we today? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitigating MITRE CWE threats in IoT devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481731</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mitigating-mitre-cwe-threats-in-iot-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T15:43:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Of the MITRE Common Weakness Enumeration (CWE) Top 25 security weaknesses, 18 are commonly found in IoT devices. MITRE ATT&CK, which stands for Adversarial Tactics,...
The post Mitigating MITRE CWE threats in IoT devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilad David Maayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966678/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966678/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T14:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (kernel), Debian (firefox-esr), Fedora (webkitgtk), Mageia (curaengine & blender and gnutls), Red Hat (firefox, grafana, grafana-pcp, libreoffice, nodejs:18, and thunderbird), SUSE (glade), and Ubuntu (crmsh, debian-goodies, linux-aws, linux-aws-6.5, linux-aws-hwe, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-oracle, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15, pam, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: assertions and Design by Contract]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481726</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-assertions-and-design-by-contract/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T13:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Assertions and Design by Contract (DBC) are the most valuable and effective best practices for delivering high-quality software. Assertions and Design by Contract (DBC) [1]...
The post Programming embedded systems: assertions and Design by Contract appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Uncovering the seams in Mainframes for Incremental Modernisation]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/uncovering-mainframe-seams.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/uncovering-mainframe-seams.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mainframe systems continue to run much of the world's computing workload,
       but it's often difficult to add new features to support growing business
       needs. Furthermore the architectural challenges that make them slow to
       enhance also make them hard to replace. To reduce the risk involved, we
       use an incremental approach to legacy displacement, gradually replacing
       legacy capabilities with implementations in modern technology. This
       strategy requires us to introduce seams into the mainframe system: points
       in which we could divert logic flow into newer services. In a recent
       project Alessio Ferri and Tom Coggrave
       investigated several approaches to introduce these seams into a
       long-lived mainframe system.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오펜하이머, 2024년 S&P 500 전망을 5500으로 상향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594222</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594222/%ec%98%a4%ed%8e%9c%ed%95%98%ec%9d%b4%eb%a8%b8-sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T13:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Microchip 8-bit PIC Configuration]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1624.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1624.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T13:05:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understaning PIC Configuration
This second in a series of five blog posts continues exploring getting started with Microchip’s 8-bit PIC family of
microcontrollers by delving into basic processor memory organization and how this family of microcontrollers initialize, specifically:


	
PIC Memory & Registers

	
PIC Configuration Sources
Revisiting MPLAB X Project...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[로이터, 엔비디아 인공지능 지배력에 도전하는 테크 기업들]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594220</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594220/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%9d%b8%ea%b3%b5%ec%a7%80%eb%8a%a5-%ec%a7%80%eb%b0%b0%eb%a0%a5-%eb%8f%84%ec%a0%84-%ea%b8%b0%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T12:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“나는 방관자였습니다”: 드라마 ‘피라미드 게임’으로 보는 학폭의 해법.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=106025</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/106025"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T08:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[학교판 ‘오징어 게임’이라고 불렸던 ‘피라미드 게임’이 끝났다. 같은 이름의 네이버 웹툰을 원작으로 스트리밍 서비스 티빙에서 만든 드라마다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 피라미드 게임의 구조. 오징어 게임과 피라미드 게임은 다르다. 명자은과 성수지의 전혀 다른 해법. 핵심은. 못 본 척하는 친구가 문제 해결의 핵심이다. 결론.
The post “나는 방관자였습니다”: 드라마 ‘피라미드 게임’으로 보는 학폭의 해법. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Canary deployment strategy with OpenShift Service Mesh]]></title>
        <id>a7ad6a5c-040a-4a72-ae30-c08f0e516c73</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/26/canary-deployment-strategy-openshift-service-mesh"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we reviewed in my previous articles about blue/green deployment, a critical topic in cloud-native computing is the microservice architecture. We are no longer dealing with one monolithic application. We have several applications that have dependencies on each other and also have other dependencies like brokers or databases.
Applications have their own life cycle, so we should be able to execute independent canary deployment. All the applications and dependencies will not change their version at the same time.
Another important topic in the cloud-native space is continuous delivery. If we are going to have several applications doing canary deployment independently, we have to automate it. We will use Helm, Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh, Red Hat OpenShift GitOps, and (of course) Red Hat …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Severiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 마이크론 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594218</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594218/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T00:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/26, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594210</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594210/3-26-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T00:21:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조국과 조선일보가 같은 이야기를 한 날: 슬로우레터 3월26일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105987</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105987"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T22:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“하야도 방법일 수 있다.” “이름뿐인 대통령 자리에 앉아있을 수 없다.” 탄핵 저지선도 위태롭다. 낙동강 벨트 분위기가 심상치 않다. 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈 효과, 하루도 안 갔다. 책으로 정치 배웠나, 중앙일보의 불만. 아이 셋 낳으면 ‘대학 무료’ vs. ‘1억 원’. 더 깊게 읽기. 20대 투표율이 관건이다. 60대 이상이 20+30대보다 더 많다. 구호를 읽어보자. 다르게 읽기. ‘경비견’ 조중동이...
The post 조국과 조선일보가 같은 이야기를 한 날: 슬로우레터 3월26일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Nix at SCALE]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965631/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965631/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T17:35:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first-ever NixCon
in North America was co-located with
SCALE this year. The
event drew a mix of experienced
Nix users
and people new to the project.
I attended talks that covered using Nix to build Docker images, upcoming changes
to how NixOS performs early booting, and ideas for making the set of services
provided in nixpkgs
more useful for self hosting. (LWN covered the relationship between
Nix, NixOS, and nixpkgs in a
recent article.)
Near the end of the
conference, a collection of Nix contributors gave a "State of the Union"
about the growth of the project and highlighting areas of concern.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.9 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965541/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965541/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T16:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9-rc1
kernel prepatch was released on March 24, closing the merge window for
this development cycle. By that time, 12,435 non-merge changesets had been
merged into the mainline, making for a less-busy merge window than the last
couple of kernel releases (but similar to the 12,492 seen for 6.5).  Well
over 7,000 of those changes were merged after the first-half merge-window summary was
written, meaning that the latter part of the merge window brought many more
interesting changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966611/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966611/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T15:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (cacti, firefox-esr, freeipa, gross, libnet-cidr-lite-perl, python2.7, python3.7, samba, and thunderbird), Fedora (amavis, chromium, clojure, firefox, gnutls, kubernetes, and tcpreplay), Mageia (freeimage, libreswan, nodejs-hawk, and python, python3), Oracle (golang, nodejs, nodejs:16, and postgresql-jdbc), Slackware (emacs and mozilla), SUSE (dav1d, ghostscript, go1.22, indent, kernel, openvswitch, PackageKit, python-uamqp, rubygem-rack-1_4, shadow, ucode-intel, xen, and zziplib), and Ubuntu (firefox, graphviz, libnet-cidr-lite-perl, and qpdf).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테크크런치 엔비디아 전망, 엔비디아는 차세대 AWS가 될 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594205</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594205/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-2"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T13:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs 29.3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966547/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966547/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T11:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 29.3 of the
Emacs editor has been released:


	Emacs 29.3 is an emergency bugfix release; it includes no new
	features except a small number of changes intended to resolve
	security vulnerabilities uncovered in Emacs 29.2.


Those vulnerabilities mostly have to do with executing untrusted Lisp code;
see the
NEWS file for a bit more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[웨드부시, 구글의 AI 전쟁 승리 가능성으로  알파벳 주가 15% 상승 제시]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594199</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594199/%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80%ec%9d%98-ai-%ec%a0%84%ec%9f%81-%ec%8a%b9%eb%a6%ac-%ea%b0%80%eb%8a%a5%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T10:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선방심의위, [신장식의 뉴스하이킥]에 8번째 법정제재]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105970</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105970"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T08:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024년 3월 21일 제22대 국회의원선거 제11차 선거방송심의위원회 회의가 열렸습니다. 이날 안건은 총 18건으로 의견진술 2건, 의결보류 후 이번 회차로 넘어온 안건 8건, 일반 안건 5건, 재심청구 3건이었습니다. 이미나 위원(한국미디어정책학회 추천)이 불참하여 8명이 의결에 참여했고 이번 회의부터 권재홍 위원(공정언론국민연대 추천)이 부위원장으로 참여하게 되었습니다. 심의한 18건 대상과 결과는 아래 표와 같습니다. MBC라디오 [신장식의 뉴스하이킥]이 낸 3건의 재심청구는...
The post 선방심의위, [신장식의 뉴스하이킥]에 8번째 법정제재 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to navigate API evolution with versioning]]></title>
        <id>36f335d3-2ccb-4038-bcb4-e4835f82cc3a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/25/how-navigate-api-evolution-versioning"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[APIs and API management form critical pieces of an enterprise’s technology landscape. A typical API starts with identification of the need for an API and progresses through various lifecycle stages, including design, implementation, testing, deployment, and ongoing management.
With the evolution of business needs and the enterprise and technology landscape, changes to APIs become inevitable. The only constant is change, and APIs are no exception. Therefore it is important how well enterprises are adapted to change when it occurs—because it is bound to occur.
To better manage changes to APIs, the API management artifacts will need to be versioned just like any other software. Such artifacts which include OpenAPI specifications and the API management platform configurations should be version…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jaya Christina Baskaran</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[분노와 증오의 정치 사이클 반복: 윤석열과 이재명은 원인이 아니라 현상이다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105965</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105965"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T06:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국 민주주의 진로에 중요한 변곡점이 될 제22대 국회의원 선거가 이제 곧 치러진다. 두루 알듯이 민주주의 체제는 주권자인 시민이 선거를 통해서 선출한 대표자에게 주권을 일정 기간(대통령 5년, 국회의원 4년) 위임하여 실현하는 체제다. 주권자인 시민과 대리인인 대표자 사이에는 주인과 대리인의 문제가 내재하고 있다. 정보의 비대칭성(information asymmetry)으로 인해서 선거에서 최적의 대리인을 선택하지 못하는 경우가 종종 발생한다. 윤석열 정부...
The post 분노와 증오의 정치 사이클 반복: 윤석열과 이재명은 원인이 아니라 현상이다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024 총선, 대통령으로부터 민주주의를 구하는 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105958</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105958"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T05:17:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[각 정당이 공천을 마무리하고 본격적인 정책 발표와 선거운동에 나서고 있다. 그러나 여야 정치권은 여전히 한국 사회 앞에 놓인 복합 위기에 대한 대책과 미래에 대한 진지한 토론보다는 총선용 개발 공약, 선심성 공약, 재원 마련 계획도 불투명한 공약을 쏟아내는 중이다. 이에 더해 윤석열 대통령은 선거를 100여 일 앞둔 지난 1월부터 전국을 순회하면서 21차례에 걸쳐 부처별 업무보고를 대신한...
The post 2024 총선, 대통령으로부터 민주주의를 구하는 방법 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[잠시 찾아왔다가 금방 사라진 ‘복지국가’ 미국, 그리고 지금은?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78996</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/24/npsp_ussocialsafety/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_ussocialsafety"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T03:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[경제 지표만 보면 미국 경제는 분명 호황인데, 미국 사람들이 느끼는 체감 경기는 왜 이렇게 나쁜 걸까? 지난해 말부터 이 질문에 대한 직·간접적인 답을 찾는 칼럼과 해설만 벌써 여러 번 소개해 드렸습니다. 그런데 뉴욕타임스에 코로나19 팬데믹 때 미국 정부가 미국 역사에선 근래에 유례를 찾기 어려운 수준의 강력한 사회보장제도를 구축했다가 팬데믹이 끝나자 언제 그랬냐는 듯이 안전망을 걷어내 버려서 사람들이 계속해서 불안해한다는 주장을 담은 칼럼이 실렸습니다. 복지국가 미국은 어떻게 신기루처럼 왔다 사라졌는지, 선거를 앞두고 다시 제도가 마련될 가능성은 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A paper to forget about]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8663</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/03/24/a-paper-to-forget-about/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T23:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Papers describing vacuous research results get published all the time. Sometimes they get accepted at premier conferences, such as ICSE, and sometimes they even win a distinguished paper award, such as this one appearing at ICSE 2024. If the paper Breaking the Flow: A Study of Interruptions During Software Engineering Activities had been produced by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.9-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966525/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966525/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T23:10:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9-rc1 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  Linus Torvalds described some rather large updates to the core
kernel code that are coming for 6.9:


The timer subsystem had a fairly big rewrite, to have per-cpu timer
wheels to improve performance of timers, which can be a big deal
particularly for networking. The other fairly notable core update is
to the workqueue subsystem, where one notable addition is for BH
workqueue support. That's notable mainly because it means we finally
have a way away from tasklets. The tasklet interface has basically
been deprecated for a long while, but we've never really had any good
alternatives (with threaded interrupt handlers being one suggested
use-case, but not realistic in many cases).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“윤석열이 드러나고 말았다”, ‘멘붕’에 빠진 조중동: 슬로우레터 3월25일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105927</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105927"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T21:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[벌써 졌나, ‘멘붕’에 빠진 조중동. “윤석열이 결단해야 한다.” “다시 대통령이 드러나고 말았다.” 쟁점과 현안. 뚜껑 열면 다르다? 전문가들도 전망 뒤집는다. 한강 벨트도 민주당 강세. “한국의 X세대는 변종”, 조선일보의 깊은 좌절. “그냥 셰셰하면 된다.” 더 깊게 읽기. D-16, 윤석열의 카드는? 다르게 읽기. 20대 조국혁신당 지지율 논란. 20대 무당층이 크게 늘었다. 한동훈 유학설도 나온다. “자기 장사만 한다.”...
The post “윤석열이 드러나고 말았다”, ‘멘붕’에 빠진 조중동: 슬로우레터 3월25일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C to C++: Templates and Generics – Supercharging Type Flexibility]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1647.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1647.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T11:53:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While beneficial to embedded developers, the C programming language can be inflexible. For example, have you ever had a function that had to manage multiple types? How did you solve that problem?

I bet you either duplicated that function, which led to confusing code or used a complex series of macros. Neither of those is terribly helpful because it creates code that is difficult to maintain...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing Home Assistant RAM usage]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-03-24:/reducing-home-assistant-ram-usage.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/reducing-home-assistant-ram-usage.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I tried running Home Assistant with zigbee2mqtt on an A20 OLinuXino board that has only 1 GB of RAM.
Startup and initial operation was okay but after a random while (days)
the system locked up and become unreachable over the network. Without Home Assistant the board was running okay for weeks so I guessed that it must have been RAM usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using (Apache) NuttX Buttons Subsystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1646.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1646.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-23T00:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously in the EmbeddedRelated article (https://embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1633.php)
 we saw how to use LEDs Subsystem on NuttX testing on RaspberryPi Pico. In the same way we avoided using GPIO Subsystem to control LEDs we can avoid using GPIO Subsystem to read Buttons inputs. That is right, NuttX has an Input Device Subsystem like Linux and today we will learn how to use...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966415/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966415/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T12:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr, pillow, and thunderbird), Fedora (apptainer, chromium, ovn, and webkitgtk), Mageia (apache-mod_auth_openidc, ffmpeg, fontforge, libuv, and nodejs-tough-cookie), Oracle (kernel, libreoffice, postgresql-jdbc, ruby:3.1, squid, and squid:4), Red Hat (go-toolset:rhel8 and libreoffice), SUSE (firefox, jbcrypt, trilead-ssh2, jsch-agent-proxy, kernel, tiff, and zziplib), and Ubuntu (linux-aws and openssl1.0).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TV조선의 막말 보도: 정봉주 50분 vs 장예찬 6분]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105903</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105903"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T03:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[3월 둘째 주 종합편성채널 시사대담프로그램은 국민의힘과 더불어민주당 공천 후보들의 ‘막말 논란’이 주요 이슈였습니다. 국민의힘 도태우·장예찬·조수연 후보와 더불어민주당 정봉주·양문석 후보의 과거 망언이 알려지자 종편 시사대담은 자극적 막말을 다루는데 시간을 할애했습니다. TV조선, 정봉주 50분 vs 장예찬 6분 TV조선 [시사쇼 정치다] (3월 14일)는 첫 주제로 더불어민주당 정봉주(강북을) 후보의 설화를 다뤘습니다. 정봉주 후보는 2017년 유튜브 [정봉주의 전국구]에서 발목 지뢰를...
The post TV조선의 막말 보도: 정봉주 50분 vs 장예찬 6분 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving into JTAG — Debugging (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-3</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-3"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the third installment of this JTAG deep dive series, we will talk in-depth
about JTAG Boundary-Scan, a method used to test interconnects on PCBs and
internal IC sub-blocks. It is defined in the IEEE 1149.1 standard. I recommend
reading Part 1 &
Part 2 of the
series to get a good background on debugging with JTAG before jumping into this
one!
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 포퓰리즘 시대 전쟁이 된 선거, 결국 그들 손에 달렸다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78643</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/21/npsp_swatting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_swatting"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T22:59:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 1월 31일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난해 12월 30일, 사우스캐롤라이나주의 부촌 키아와 아일랜드 지역 경찰에 다급한 신고 전화가 접수됐습니다. 전 주 UN 미국 대사이자, 그에 앞서 사우스캐롤라이나 주지사를 두 번 지냈으며, 현재 공화당 경선에 참여하고 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[보수 유튜버들이 한동훈 손절을 요구하고 있다: 슬로우레터 3월22일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105867</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105867"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T22:09:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“민주개혁세력 200석도 가능.” “국민의힘 100석도 힘들다.” 보수 유튜버들의 한동훈 손절. 윤석열은 술래잡기 중. 윤석열의 손을 떠났다. “탄핵 불가능하지 않다.” 쟁점과 현안. 이종섭은 수사받으러 온 게 아니었다. 부르면 ‘맹탕’, 늦추자니 ‘맹공’. 조수진 사퇴. 이런 것도 변호인가. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘손해 연금’을 선택하는 이유. 선거에 노동 의제가 없다. 다르게 읽기. 하청 직원 정규직으로 뽑았더니 100억 원. 해법과...
The post 보수 유튜버들이 한동훈 손절을 요구하고 있다: 슬로우레터 3월22일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Hardening the kernel against heap-spraying attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965837/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965837/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T15:07:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While a programming error in the kernel may be subject to direct
exploitation, usually a more roundabout approach is required to take
advantage of a security bug.  One popular approach for those wishing to
take advantage of vulnerabilities  is heap spraying, and
it has often been employed to compromise the kernel.  In the future,
though, heap-spraying attacks may be a bit harder to pull off, thanks to the
"dedicated bucket allocator" proposed by Kees Cook.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966246/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966246/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T14:57:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (pdns-recursor and php-dompdf-svg-lib), Fedora (grub2, libreswan, rubygem-yard, and thunderbird), Mageia (libtiff and python-scipy), Red Hat (golang, nodejs, and nodejs:16), Slackware (python3), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde,
 linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gkeop,
 linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-kvm,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-6.5, linux-hwe-6.5,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-oem-6.5, linux-oracle,
 linux-oracle-6.5, linux-raspi, linux-starfive, linux-starfive-6.5, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4,
 linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-kvm, linux-laptop, linux-oem-6.1, and linux-raspi).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.77.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966205/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966205/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T13:48:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.77.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Changes include support
for NUL-terminated C-string literals, the ability for async
functions to call themselves recursively, the stabilization of the
offset_of!() macro, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Perl 5.39.9 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966181/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966181/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T11:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Verson 5.39.9 of the Perl language has been released.  Changes this time
include a new "medium-precedence" logical exclusive-or operator, a number
of updated modules, and more; see this
page for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[내 글은 절대 악플이 아니야: 리듬체조 선수 명예훼손 댓글 기소유예 취소 사건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105850</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105850"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T08:40:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[참여연대 사법감시센터 ‘광장에 나온 판결’] 손연재 선수 명예훼손 댓글 단 혐의로 기소유예처분을 받은 신 모 씨에 대해서, 헌법재판소가 기소유예처분 취소를 결정했습니다! 언론과 대중의 관심을 받는 것은 늘 자극적인 사건들이다. 충격적인 범죄, 대대적인 압수·수색, 피의자의 구속, 유무죄 판결들. 우리가 접하는 형사사건은 대부분 이렇게 다가온다. 복잡한 사회, 바쁜 일상 속에 평범한 사람의 속상한 이야기 정도는 주목을 끌기...
The post 내 글은 절대 악플이 아니야: 리듬체조 선수 명예훼손 댓글 기소유예 취소 사건 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redis is no longer free software]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966133/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966133/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T07:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Redis in-memory database system has had
its license changed to either the Redis Source Available
License or the Server Side
Public License (covered here in 2018);
neither license qualifies as free software.


	Under the new license, cloud service providers hosting Redis
	offerings will no longer be permitted to use the source code of
	Redis free of charge. For example, cloud service providers will be
	able to deliver Redis 7.4 only after agreeing to licensing terms
	with Redis, the maintainers of the Redis code.


Distributors like Fedora are already looking
at removing Redis as a consequence.  (Thanks to  Emmanuel Seyman).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The "Nova" driver for NVIDIA chipsets]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966129/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966129/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T07:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Danilo Krummrich has announced the
existence of the "Nova" project within Red Hat.


	We just started to work on Nova, a Rust-based GSP-only driver for
	Nvidia GPUs. Nova, in the long term, is intended to serve as the
	successor of Nouveau for GSP-firmware-based GPUs.

	With Nova we see the chance to significantly decrease the
	complexity of the driver compared to Nouveau for mainly two
	reasons. First, Nouveau's historic architecture, especially around
	nvif/nvkm, is rather complicated and inflexible and requires major
	rework to solve certain problems (such as locking hierarchy in VMM
	/ MMU code for VM_BIND currently being solved with a workaround)
	and second, with a GSP-only driver there is no need to maintain
	compatibility with pre-GSP code.

	Besides that, we also want to take the chance to contribute to the
	Rust efforts in the kernel and benefit from from more memory safety
	offered by the Rust programming language.


Given that the effort has just begun, it will be a while before this driver
shows up in a distribution release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Benchmark Cyclone DDS in CentOS Stream 9 VMs for low latency]]></title>
        <id>393c0a78-a4d0-423e-ad01-f704b54d989e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/21/benchmark-cyclone-dds-centos-stream-9-vms-low-latency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When users have to choose a middleware technology to communicate different software components, they often pick Robot Operating System 2 (ROS 2) due to its features like efficiency and reliability. These components can be deployed locally (i.e., same host, or remotely, different hosts), and they communicate by following a service-oriented pattern.
For example, a software component that reads data from a sensor would publish the sensor values whereas another software component that processes that data would subscribe to it. ROS 2 takes care of sending the data between the components and ensures that data arrives on time. ROS 2 relies on a DDS as its middleware, which is a specification that is implemented by different vendors, e.g., Eclipse Cyclone DDS, OpenDDS. DDS is used in a wide variet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matias Ezequiel Vara Larsen, Alexander Lougovski, Marcelo Tosatti</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement Source-to-Image builds in an Azure DevOps pipeline]]></title>
        <id>06c32f8b-1ca8-484a-bfb7-e06f2af8285c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/21/implement-source-image-builds-azure-devops-pipeline"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The advent of cloud technologies brings many benefits to the enterprise, such as provisioning at scale and a cloud-native DevOps approach. However, it also brings new challenges for developers and infrastructure engineers who wish to migrate from their datacenter to the public cloud. Among those challenges are integrating existing development methodologies with tool sets provided by the cloud provider as on-premise and cloud environments can each differ greatly. In this article, we explore a real-world implementation of a complete CI/CD pipeline using Source-to-Image builds deployed in Microsoft Azure Red Hat OpenShift with Azure tooling (see Figure 1).


        Figure 1: This logical workflow highlights the pipeline that will be built in this article.
The tools that will be leveraged in …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Chung, Amr Abualrub</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조수진의 직업윤리는 틀렸다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105825</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105825"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T06:32:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[조수진은 자신의 성범죄자 변호 이력이 논란이 되자 말도 안 되는 해명을 내놓았다. MBC 라디오에 출연해서는 “변호사로서 직업윤리와 법에 근거해 변론했다”면서 “공직자에게 바라는 국민 눈높이가 다르다는 걸 느꼈다”고 한다. 기자들에게 보낸 메시지에서는 “성범죄자 변론을 맡은 것과 블로그를 통해 이런 사실을 홍보한 것은 변호사로서 윤리 규범을 준수해 이뤄진 활동”이었다면서 앞으로 “국민 눈높이를 가치의 척도로 삼겠다”고 밝혔다. 즉,...
The post 조수진의 직업윤리는 틀렸다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 21, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965368/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965368/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T00:50:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 21, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“다 해결됐다”던 한동훈이 “내가 관둘게요”했던 이유: 슬로우레터 3월21일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105801</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105801"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T22:04:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[황상무 사퇴와 이종섭 귀국, 예상보다 빨랐다. 다 해결된 것 맞나. 쟁점과 현안. 의대 2000명 증원 강행. 지역 의료 강화 맞나. 조국혁신당 지지율 30%도 넘었다. “길에서 배지 주웠다.” 이재명의 자신감. 친윤-친한, 건널 수 없는 강을 건넜다. ‘한동훈의 시간’이 다시 올까. 다르게 읽기. 삼성이 삼성 같지 않다. “한국에서 RE100 하기 어렵다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 행동대장 윤석열, 게도...
The post “다 해결됐다”던 한동훈이 “내가 관둘게요”했던 이유: 슬로우레터 3월21일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME 46 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966096/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966096/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T21:07:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 46 of the GNOME desktop
has been released.  "GNOME 46 is code-named 'Kathmandu', in recognition
of the amazing work done by the organizers of GNOME.Asia 2023."
Significant changes include a new global search feature, enhancements to
the Files app, improved remote login support, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Invincible null: digging into nopCommerce source code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1109/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1109/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The nopCommerce project is a free open-source platform on ASP.NET Core to create online stores. Today we'll find out what ambiguities lurk in its code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Managing Linux servers with Cockpit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965434/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965434/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T17:53:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cockpit is an interesting
project for web-based Linux administration that has received
relatively little attention over the years. Part of that may be due to
the project's strategy of minor releases roughly every two weeks,
rather than larger releases with many new features. While the strategy
has done little to garner headlines, it has delivered a useful and
extensible tool to observe, manage, and troubleshoot Linux servers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[영어 아닌 외국어 사용이 문제라고? ‘효율적 소통’ 이면에도 문제가 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78954</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/20/npsp_englishofficial/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_englishofficial"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T17:30:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[통상 ‘미국의 언어’라고 하면 영어가 떠오르지만, 놀랍게도 미국에는 정부가 지정한 공용어가 없습니다. 가장 널리 쓰이는 건 영어지만, ‘이민자의 나라’ 답게 다양한 언어가 존재합니다. 일각에선 “효율적인 소통을 위해 영어만 사용하자”는 주장도 나오지만, 미국 사회에서 언어의 문제는 다른 모든 사안과 마찬가지로 인종 문제, 소수자와 이민자에 대한 차별과 맞닿아 있으므로 쉽게 결정할 수 없는 일입니다. 언어의 다양성에 관해선 올해 대선에 나설 두 후보의 생각도 꽤 달라 보입니다. 멸종위기 언어 연합 소속 활동가 로스 펄린이 쓴 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python announces first security releases since becoming a CNA]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966056/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966056/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T16:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python project has announced three security releases, 3.10.14,
3.9.19,
and 3.8.19.
In addition to the security fixes, these releases are notable for two reasons;
they are the first to make use of GitHub Actions to perform
public builds instead of building artifacts "on a local computer of one
of the release managers", and the first since Python became a
CVE Numbering Authority (CNA).
Python release team member Łukasz Langa said
that being a CNA means Python is able to "ensure the quality of the vulnerability
reports is high, and that the severity estimates are accurate." It also
allows Python to coordinate CVE announcements with the patched versions of
Python, as it has with two CVEs addressed in these releases. CVE-2023-6597 
describes a flaw in CPython's zipfile module that made it vulnerable to a zip-bomb exploit. CVE-2024-0450 is an
issue with Python's tempfile.TemporaryDirectory class which could be
exploited to modify permissions of files referenced by symbolic links. 
Users of affected versions should upgrade soon.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/966053/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/966053/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T12:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (fontforge and imagemagick), Fedora (firefox), Mageia (cherrytree, python-django, qpdf, and sqlite3), Red Hat (bind, cups, emacs, fwupd, gmp, kernel, libreoffice, libX11, nodejs, opencryptoki, postgresql-jdbc, postgresql:10, postgresql:13, and ruby:3.1), Slackware (gnutls and mozilla), and Ubuntu (firefox, linux, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm,
 linux-ibm-5.4, linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-aws, linux-aws-6.5, and linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 techniques to improve low-power design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481675</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3-techniques-to-improve-low-power-design/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T12:48:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We explore several low-power design techniques that I often see overlooked but that can make a big difference. Designing an embedded system for battery life...
The post 3 techniques to improve low-power design appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How IoT offers a transformative solution to water management]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481672</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-iot-offers-a-transformative-solution-to-water-management/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T12:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By optimizing water distribution, leveraging real-time data, and preventing structural damage, IoT stands as a transformative force in ensuring a sustainable and efficient water future....
The post How IoT offers a transformative solution to water management appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Neil Bosworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[망언은 공천 취소를 남기고…: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 분석 (3월 둘째 주)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105789</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105789"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T08:13:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요약 주요 이슈 1. 공천 윤곽 드러나자 공천취소 후보자 ‘막말’ 보도 급증 ① 국힘 역사왜곡 발언 잇딴 논란 ② 민주당 ‘목발 경품’ 정봉주 발언 이슈 2. ‘런종섭 사태’ 총선 주요 이슈로 급부상 3. ‘막말, 비리, 일탈’ 등 자극적 뉴스 급증 4. ‘민주당 공천+조국혁신당’ 보도량 1위 ① 불변의 ‘이재명+공천논란’ 프레임 ② 조국혁신당 보도량 2위 5. 정당...
The post 망언은 공천 취소를 남기고…: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 분석 (3월 둘째 주) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Network Observability 1.5]]></title>
        <id>1edc2259-2997-4963-89d7-11658ec714a8</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/20/whats-new-network-observability-15"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network Observability 1.5 is the new version of the operator from Red Hat that focuses on providing insights into networking. There's an upstream version that runs on plain Kubernetes, but this article will focus on using Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform (RHOCP) and the OpenShift web console for the user interface.
I will highlight the most important new features of this release, so if you want a summary of all the changes including bug fixes, check out the release notes. If you want some background of this product, read the OpenShift documentation and various Red Hat blogs on this topic, including my blog on the previous 1.4 release.
To get started, you should have an OpenShift cluster. You will need to log in with a cluster-admin role. Follow the documentation steps to install Networ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Steven Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Kuadrant Gateway API policies with Gatekeeper policies]]></title>
        <id>752edb9f-3db0-4abc-afc2-777c857ff4ef</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/20/using-kuadrant-gateway-api-policies-gatekeeper-policies"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the enterprise Kubernetes world, many developers use Kubernetes as a platform for designing, building, and deploying applications. The platform needs to be managed and provide a range of features, integrations, and checks and balances for developers. The role of the platform engineer is important in that regard. Policies are at the heart of what a platform engineer has to be define and enforce in their platform. Two technologies that aim to make defining and enforcing policies easier are Gatekeeper and Gateway API.
In this article, we'll talk about how these two policy-focused technologies can work together to solve platform engineer and application developer concerns.
What are Gatekeeper policies?
Gatekeeper is a policy controller for Kubernetes. Its main focus is to allow users to enf…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Martin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[파묘], 진짜 쇠말뚝은 다른 곳에 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105782</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105782"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T06:50:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[파묘] (2024) 제작진은 [건국전쟁] 김덕영 감독에게 명절마다 한우선물세트를 보내야 한다. 그가 좌파 어쩌고저쩌고 흰소리한 덕분에 수많은 사람이 [파묘]에 더 관심을 품게 됐다. 권좌에서 쫓겨난다고 외국으로 도망간 한민족 역사상 전무후무한 최고 권력자였던 이승만을 ‘오구오구’ 하는 뇌 구조를 가진 분이 비난하는 영화라면 틀림없이 괜찮은 영화일 테니까. 그런 연유로 우리 가족도 오랜만에 주말에 극장에 갔다. 이 자리를 빌려...
The post [파묘], 진짜 쇠말뚝은 다른 곳에 있다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>자작나무</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이강인 탁구 스캔들과 이슈 쏠림: 어젠다 세팅에서 어젠다 키핑으로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105041</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105041"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T03:15:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. 오늘 케이스는 이강인 탁구 스캔들과 이슈 쏠림. ‘나는 무엇을 해야 하는가’라는 질문에 답하려면, ‘내가 어떤 이야기의 일부라고 생각하는가’라는 선행 질문에 답할 수 있어야만 한다. 제프리 R. 핼버슨, H.L. 구달 주니어. & 스티븐 R. 코먼., ‘마스터 내러티브란 무엇인가’, 마스터 내러티브와 이슬람 극단주의. 2011. “부처의 눈에는...
The post 이강인 탁구 스캔들과 이슈 쏠림: 어젠다 세팅에서 어젠다 키핑으로 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.10.14, 3.9.19, and 3.8.19 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/03/python-31014-3919-and-3819-is-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/03/python-31014-3919-and-3819-is-now.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T00:29:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howdy!
Python 3.10.14
Get it here: Python Release Python 3.10.14
26 commits since the last release.

Python 3.9.19
Get it here: Python Release Python 3.9.19
26 commits since the last release. 

Python 3.8.19
Get it here: Python Release Python 3.8.19
28 commits since the last release.

Security content in this release
gh-115399 & gh-115398: bundled libexpat was updated to 2.6.0 to address CVE-2023-52425,
 and control of the new reparse deferral functionality was exposed with 
new APIs. Thanks to Sebastian Pipping, the maintainer of libexpat, who 
worked with us directly on incorporating those fixes!
gh-109858: zipfile is now protected from the “quoted-overlap” zipbomb to address CVE-2024-0450. It now raises BadZipFile when attempting to read an entry that overlaps with another entry or cent…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“남은 3년 동안 뭐할 건가”, 조선일보의 깊은 탄식: 슬로우레터 3월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105738</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105738"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T22:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈의 고백? 조선일보가 1면에 끌어올린 이유. 윤-한 갈등의 본질은 총선 주도권. 한동훈 ‘마이웨이’ 누가 말리겠나. “수도권 15석도 못 건질 판”, 국민의힘 후보들 아우성. 윤석열이 물러설까. 쟁점과 현안. 대통령 오는 날 대파 가격이 내려갔다. 박용진의 두 번째 좌절. 비슷한 공약에 재원은 ‘묻지 마’. 다르게 읽기. 대안도 없이 불쑥 던질 일인가. “이종섭 직권 남용 아니다”, 조선일보의 반격....
The post “남은 3년 동안 뭐할 건가”, 조선일보의 깊은 탄식: 슬로우레터 3월20일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] "Real" anonymous functions for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964839/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964839/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T21:18:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a number of different language-enhancement ideas that crop up
with some 
regularity in 
the Python community; many of them have been debated and shot down multiple
times over the years.  When one inevitably arises anew, it can sometimes be
difficult to tamp it down, even if it is unlikely that the idea will go
any further than the last N times it cropped up.  A recent discussion about
"real" anonymous functions follows a somewhat predictable path, but there
are still reasons to participate in vetting these "new" ideas, despite the
tiresome, repetitive 
nature of the exercise—examples of 
recurring feature ideas that were eventually adopted definitely exist.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 124.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965959/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965959/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T16:57:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
124.0 of the Firefox browser is out.  Changes include support for
"caret browsing mode" in the PDF viewer and the ability to control the
sorting of tabs in the Firefox View screen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965958/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965958/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T16:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (cacti, postgresql-11, and zfs-linux), Fedora (freeimage, mingw-expat, and mingw-freeimage), Mageia (apache-mod_security-crs, expat, and multipath-tools), Oracle (.NET 7.0 and kernel), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, and kpatch-patch), and Ubuntu (bash, kernel, linux, linux-aws, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, and vim).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Man Yue Mo: Gaining kernel code execution on an MTE-enabled Pixel 8]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965926/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965926/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:39:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Man Yue Mo explains
how to compromise a Pixel 8 phone even when the Arm memory-tagging extension is in use, by taking
advantage of the Mali GPU.


	So, by using the GPU to access physical addresses directly, I'm
	able to completely bypass the protection that MTE
	offers. Ultimately, there is no memory safe code in the code that
	manages memory accesses. At some point, physical addresses will
	have to be used directly to access memory.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to capture qualitative metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/measuring-developer-productivity-humans.html#HowToCaptureQualitativeMetrics</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/measuring-developer-productivity-humans.html#HowToCaptureQualitativeMetrics"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abi Noda and Tim Cochran complete
        their article on qualitative metrics by outlining how to capture them
        effectively. They discuss the mental steps that people go through as
        they respond to a survey and provide a template to get started when assessing
        developer experience. A final section looks at how qualitative and
        quantitative work together: often by starting with qualitative metrics to
        establish baselines and determine where to focus, followed with
        quantitative metrics to drill deeper into specific areas.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new for developers in Red Hat OpenShift 4.15]]></title>
        <id>c67496be-1af3-4507-b845-8d7ae904be28</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/19/whats-new-developers-red-hat-openshift-415"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift 4.15, based on Kubernetes 1.28 and CRI-O 1.28, is now generally available. This article highlights notable updates in this release for developers with OpenShift.
Pipelines, Developer Hub, and more
The Developer Perspective in the OpenShift console includes four new capabilities:
A new dynamic plug-in-based dashboard for Red Hat OpenShift Pipelines;
Access to additional information in OpenShift Pipelines for Red Hat Trusted Software Supply Chain;
Build strategy enhancements;
The ability to create serverless functions.
The PipelineRun Details page in the Developer or Administrator perspective of the web console provides an enhanced visual representation of PipelineRuns within a Project.
Discover Red Hat Developer Hub in the web console with new quick starts that provide ste…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Donna Smalls</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[번역] 프로그래머를 위한 카테고리 이론 - 7. 펑터]]></title>
        <id>20240315-category-theory-for-programmers-7-functors</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/03/15/category-theory-for-programmers-7-functors/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이번 챕터에서는 펑터(Functor)에 대해서 이야기를 해보려고 한다. 펑터는 간단하지만 매우 강력한 개념이며 카테고리 이론은 이처럼 간단하지만 강력한 아이디어로 가득 차있다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Quay/Clair: Database profiling results]]></title>
        <id>aa656170-d0af-49ce-8f3c-6b8174c2d317</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/19/optimizing-quayclair-database-profiling-results"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the second part of our exploration. In this continuation from our previous article, we will delve deeper into the results of our database profiling efforts and discuss strategies for further optimizing overall application performance.
Profiling results before optimization for Clair database
To gain insights into the inner workings of the Clair database, we conducted profiling using the pgBadger tool, specifically designed for PostgreSQL. This tool extracts information from the database logs and generates a comprehensive HTML report for result analysis. Through profiling, we identified that the recurrent spikes are attributed to bulk updates executed on the database, specifically around 10,000 updates by the updater, a sub-component of Clair that is responsible for maintaining an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vishnu Challa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing Quay/Clair: Profiling, performance, and efficiency]]></title>
        <id>843cca29-b59f-4fdf-915d-231506503a3a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/19/optimizing-quayclair-profiling-performance-and-efficiency"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Quay (also offered as a service via Quay.io) is a cloud-based container registry service that allows users to store, manage, and distribute container images. It provides a platform for hosting, sharing, and securing container images across multiple environments, including on-premise data centers, public cloud platforms, and hybrid cloud deployments.
As a complementary subproduct, Clair is an application specifically designed for parsing image contents and delivering reports on vulnerabilities that may impact these contents. Noteworthy is that this analysis is conducted through static analysis rather than at runtime. Clair excels in supporting the extraction of contents and the identification of vulnerabilities, enhancing the overall security and reliability of containerized applica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vishnu Challa</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선거방송심의위, 초현실적인 막장드라마]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105703</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105703"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T02:45:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[억지 설정과 무리한 전개를 거듭하면 ‘막장드라마’가 된다. 과장된 캐릭터, 비약과 궤변, 황당한 결말이 반복되면 사람들은 ‘개연성 없는 막장드라마’라며 손가락질한다. 자극적이고 퇴폐적인 막장드라마의 단 하나 장점을 꼽는다면 그래도 결말은 권선징악이란 점이다. 그런데 2024년 현재, 서울시 목동 방송회관에서 매주 라이브로 펼쳐지는 장면들은 그 단 하나의 장점조차 갖추지 못했다. 제22대 총선을 앞두고 구성된 선거방송심의위원회(이하 선방심의위)는 1997년 선방심의위가 법정기구로...
The post 선거방송심의위, 초현실적인 막장드라마 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주4일제, 이름만큼 혁신적인 논의 아니다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=104532</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/104532"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T01:16:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)이 전하는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기. ‘노동시간’ 본격 썰 3탄. 주4일제, 이름만큼 혁신적인가? 제오시 ‘노동시간’ 특집 현실성 있는 논의인가? 현재는 개별 기업과 노조 중심의 논의에 머물고 있다. 그것도 일부 대기업에 한정되는 주제다. 정부가 고민할 단계로 보기엔 시기상조다. 우선순위에서는 한참 후순위일 것으로 보이고, 현재 동력도 없으며, 동력을 만들어내기도 쉽지 않을...
The post 주4일제, 이름만큼 혁신적인 논의 아니다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/19, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594174</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594174/3-19-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T23:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘장바구니 물가 상승’이나 ‘손실 회피 성향’이라고만 넘길 수 없는 것들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78631</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/18/npsp_inflationsnickers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_inflationsnickers"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 1월 29일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 아직 280일도 더 남은 미국 대선 열기가 벌써부터 뜨겁게 달아오르고 있습니다. 공식 선거운동 기간이 따로 없는 미국에선 대선이 있는 해는 일 년 내내 선거 뉴스가 끊이지 않습니다. 지난 23일 뉴햄프셔 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“대통령이 이상하다”는 조선일보와 세상 평화로운 윤석열: 슬로우레터 3월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105670</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105670"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T22:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열-한동훈의 2차 충돌. 8년 전 ‘옥새 파동’의 기시감. “대통령이 이상하다”, 조선일보의 불만. 박력만큼 넘치지 않는 정교함. 이러고도 선거 이기겠나. 한동훈도 지쳤나. 쟁점과 현안. ‘마사중’으로 가는 이준석. 조국혁신당 박은정이 1번. 조국혁신당 인기 이유는. 국민의미래 비례 두고 부글부글. 더 깊게 읽기. 윤석열은 요즘. 2000명 증원 변함없다. 푸틴 87% 득표로 5선. 다르게 읽기. 통계 조작, 검찰은 못 본...
The post “대통령이 이상하다”는 조선일보와 세상 평화로운 윤석열: 슬로우레터 3월19일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아를 이기지 않아도 AMD는 AI 전쟁의 승자가 될 수 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594172</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594172/ai-%ec%a0%84%ec%9f%81%ec%9d%98-%ec%8a%b9%ec%9e%90%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-amd"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T17:47:01.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Toward a real "too small to fail" rule]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964793/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964793/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T15:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel developers have long been told that any attempt to allocate memory
might fail, so their code must be prepared for memory to be unavailable.
Informally, though, the kernel's memory-management subsystem implements a
policy whereby requests below a certain size will not fail (in process
context, at least), regardless of
how tight memory may be.  A recent discussion on the linux-mm list has
looked at the idea of making the "too small to
fail" rule a policy that developers can rely on.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965829/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965829/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T14:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (curl, spip, and unadf), Fedora (chromium, iwd, opensc, openvswitch, python3.6, shim, shim-unsigned-aarch64, and shim-unsigned-x64), Mageia (batik, imagemagick, irssi, jackson-databind, jupyter-notebook, ncurses, and yajl), Oracle (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, and dnsmasq), Red Hat (postgresql:10), SUSE (chromium, kernel, openvswitch, python-rpyc, and tiff), and Ubuntu (openjdk-8).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Trusted Profile Analyzer is now in tech preview]]></title>
        <id>dcf2cfd6-d435-491b-a4fc-b5a076f3571e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/18/red-hat-trusted-profile-analyzer-now-tech-preview"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security around building and deploying applications is more critical than ever. As such, it is also just as important to understand what comprises the applications your developers are building and where they are coming from. This is the mentality behind a trusted software supply chain. The ability to code, build, and monitor your applications through proven platforms, and get artifacts from trusted sources are imperative to building safer, and more reliable applications. One of the important aspects of this is the Software Bill of Materials (SBOM).
What is an SBOM?
A Software Bill of Materials functions as an inventory with layers, containing a comprehensive collection of elements that make up software components. This information can be used to ensure the elements used to build an applica…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sean Rickerd</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence and Arm launch ADAS chiplet development platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481668</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/cadence-and-arm-launch-adas-chiplet-development-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T11:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence and Arm join forces to provide ADAS chiplet reference design and software development platform based on the latest Automotive Enhanced technologies from Arm.
The post Cadence and Arm launch ADAS chiplet development platform appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PICMG releases version 2.2 of COM-HPC Mini design guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481665</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/picmg-releases-version-2-2-of-com-hpc-mini-design-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T11:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Revision 2.2 of PICMG carrier design guide introduces new diagrams, figures, and design notes for COM-HPC Mini, and contains technical materials such as interface schematics and practical guidance on design rules.
The post PICMG releases version 2.2 of COM-HPC Mini design guide appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IVT sensor provides precise battery state of charge measurement]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481659</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ivt-sensor-provides-precise-battery-state-of-charge-measurement/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T10:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Latest ams OSRAM sensor provides accurate current, voltage and temperature measurement for industrial applications, as part of its portfolio of high-precision sensors for battery management systems.
The post IVT sensor provides precise battery state of charge measurement appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to manage a fleet of heterogeneous OpenShift clusters]]></title>
        <id>824ee847-33ff-496c-b309-28101352aa8c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/18/how-manage-fleet-heterogeneous-openshift-clusters"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining a fleet of thousands of Red Hat OpenShift clusters, as is typical in network far edge deployments, requires a disciplined and consistent approach to managing configuration. In an ideal world all of the clusters would be running the same versions of software from the OpenShift Container Platform through application workload. In reality, however, the fleet of clusters will contain a mix of software versions due to phased rollouts, regional differences, or other operational requirements that may pin a set of clusters to an older release.
Addressing the complexity of multiple versions can be achieved by building on top of a couple of very powerful tools. Red Hat’s GitOps (Argo CD) operator allows for single-source of truth definitions of clusters and their configuration and Red Hat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sabbir Hasan, Ian Miller</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finding reports and papers on the web]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8651</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/03/17/finding-reports-and-papers-on-the-web/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T23:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is the best way to locate a freely downloadable copy of a report or paper on the web? The process I follow is outlined below (if you are new to this, you should first ask yourself whether reading a scientific paper will produce the result you are expecting): Google search. For the last 20 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[여긴 굶주리고 저긴 식량 남고…이 또한 ‘정치의 실패’다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78909</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/17/npsp_famine/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_famine"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T22:20:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인류는 이미 80억 명 가까운 전체 인구가 먹고도 남을 만한 식량을 생산하고 있습니다. 통계에 따라 다르지만, 100억 명이 먹을 수 있는 식량을 생산하고 있다는 통계도 있습니다. 실제로 생산하는 식량이 그 정도이고, 잠재적인 생산력을 고려하면 생산량은 얼마든지 더 늘릴 수도 있습니다. 그런데도 여전히 인류는 기아와 기근을 해결하지 못하고 있습니다. 8년 전 곧 인류가 기근을 해결할 수 있을 거란 낙관적인 전망을 내놓았던 사람이 자신의 예측이 틀렸다며 뉴욕타임스에 칼럼을 썼습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 능력이 있는데도 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[다시 한동훈-윤석열 대결 구도, 조중동의 초조함이 느껴진다: 슬로우레터 3월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105595</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105595"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T22:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[판이 기울었다. 윤석열 싫지만 지지 정당 없는 20%. ‘의-정’ 갈등 한 달, 여론이 식고 있다. 쟁점과 현안. 도태우-정봉주-장예찬-양문석. “임금 욕도 하는데.” 현역 물갈이, 민주당은 늘고 국민의힘은 줄었다. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘부르면 귀국’ 말고 ‘당장 귀국’해야 한다. 한동훈도 화들짝. 누가 먼저 움직일까. 윤석열은 왜 그랬을까. SWOT로 본 선거 판도. 다르게 읽기. 빛났던 민주당 영입 인재들. 하우스...
The post 다시 한동훈-윤석열 대결 구도, 조중동의 초조함이 느껴진다: 슬로우레터 3월18일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NXP MCU-Link for Rust with probe-rs]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40282</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/03/17/nxp-mcu-link-for-rust-with-probe-rs/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-17T15:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rust programming language gains popularity in embedded systems, and tools like probe-rs make it easier. The NXP MCU-Link debug probe, affordable at $15, is compatible with Rust and Visual Studio Code for debugging. With simple installation and usage, it offers a versatile and cost-effective solution for Rust applications. Links: probe-rs, MCU-Link debug probe. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 몰려드는 이민자들, 미국 정치권이 해결할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78582</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/16/npsp_2024electionimmigration/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_2024electionimmigration"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T22:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 1월 24일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. “미국은 이민자의 나라”라는 말은 식상하지만, 엄연한 사실이기도 합니다. ‘원래 미국인’이란 표현은 아메리카 원주민이 아닌 한 성립하지 않습니다. 당장 조 바이든 대통령이 아일랜드계 가톨릭 집안에서 태어났고, 도널드 트럼프 전 대통령도 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[신방과 교수 경력 33년 걸고 ‘MBC 미세먼지 1’ 비판한 백선기 선방심의위원장]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105585</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105585"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T03:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024년 3월 14일 제22대 국회의원선거 제10차 선거방송심의위원회 회의가 열렸습니다. 이날 안건은 총 15건으로 의견진술 4건, 의결보류 후 이번 회차로 넘어온 안건 1건, 일반 안건 10건이었습니다. 일반 안건은 3건만 심의하고 7건은 다음 회차로 미뤘습니다. 일신상 이유로 사퇴를 표명한 최창근 부위원장(한국방송기자클럽 추천) 후임 보궐로 위촉된 김문환(성신여대 미디어커뮤니케이션학과 초빙교수, 전 SBS 기자) 위원이 이날 참여했습니다. 김문환 위원이 세...
The post 신방과 교수 경력 33년 걸고 ‘MBC 미세먼지 1’ 비판한 백선기 선방심의위원장 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/16, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594155</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594155/3-16-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T02:07:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How web bloat impacts users with slow devices]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/slow-device/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/slow-device/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2017, we looked at how web bloat affects users with slow connections. Even in the U.S., many users didn't have broadband speeds, making much of the web difficult to use. It's still the case that many users don't have broadband speeds, both inside and outside of the U.S. and that much of the modern web isn't usable for people with slow internet, but the exponential increase in bandwidth (Nielsen suggests this is 50% per year for high-end connections) has outpaced web bloat for typical sites, making this less of a problem than it was in 2017, although it's still a serious problem for people with poor connections.
CPU performance for web apps hasn't scaled nearly as quickly as bandwidth so, while more of the web is becoming accessible to people with low-end connections, more of the web is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Cranelift code generation comes to Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964735/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964735/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T20:05:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cranelift is an Apache-2.0-licensed
code-generation backend being developed as part
of the Wasmtime runtime for
WebAssembly.
In October 2023, the Rust project made Cranelift available as an optional
component in its nightly toolchain.
Users can now use Cranelift as the code-generation backend for debug builds of
projects written in Rust,
making it an opportune time to look at what makes Cranelift different.
Cranelift is designed to compete with existing compilers by generating
code more quickly than they can, thanks to a stripped-down design that prioritizes
only the most important optimizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell: Today we launched Flox 1.0]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965584/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965584/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T19:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zach Mitchell has announced the 1.0 release of Flox, a tool that lets its users install packages from nixpkgs inside portable virtual environments, and share those virtual environments with others as an alternative to Docker-style containers. Flox is based on Nix but allows users to skip learning how to work with the Nix language:
install, uninstall, etc, but we also provide an entire new suite of functionality with the ability to share environments via flox push, flox pull, and flox activate --remote.


Flox is GPLv2-licensed, and releases are available as RPMs and Debian packages for x86_64 and arm64 systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Eight stable kernel updates for the weekend]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965603/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965603/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T19:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sasha Levin has announced the release of the 6.8.1,
6.7.10, 6.6.22,
6.1.82, 5.15.152,
5.10.213, 5.4.272,
and 4.19.310 stable kernels. As always, they contain important fixes throughout the tree. Users of those kernels should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code samples for the opening chapter of Refactoring]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-refactoring-code-samples.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-refactoring-code-samples.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T15:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From time to time people ask me for a copy of the code I used in the
       opening chapter of Refactoring, so
       they can follow along themselves. I had Reasons for not providing this code,
       specifically laziness. Fortunately Emily Bache is more dedicated, and she
       has set up a github repository - the Theatrical
       Players Refactoring Kata - with the code, and enough tests to make it
       reasonable to do the refactoring.
The repository goes further than this, however, in that it includes similar
       sample code in a dozen languages, including C, Java, Rust, and Python.
She has recently posted a video to her YouTube
       channel, which outlines why she encourages folks to use this code while
       they are reading that chapter. Her channel includes a lot of videos on good
       code technique, and she has a Patreon for readers to support
       her work.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965576/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965576/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T13:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (composer and node-xml2js), Fedora (baresip), Mageia (fonttools, libgit2, mplayer, open-vm-tools, and packages), Red Hat (dnsmasq, gimp:2.8, and kernel-rt), and SUSE (389-ds, gdb, kernel, python-Django, python3, python36-pip, spectre-meltdown-checker, sudo, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[유동적 저널리즘: 보도 건수를 넘어 보도 시간이 중요하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105581</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105581"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T11:12:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[중앙일보가 3월 첫째 주 포털 네이버 메인뉴스(6개)를 통해 가장 오래 보도한 선거, 정당 관련 기사는 무엇일까? 민언련 총선보도 모니터링 데이터에 따르면, [전여옥 “김신영, 문재인 시계 자랑해서 잘렸다? 황당”] (3월 6일 정시내 기자)가 가장 오래 보도되었다. 전여옥 전 새누리당 의원이 방송 관련 사안에 대해 좌파 커뮤니티 활동을 비판한 내용이다. 언론사는 중요한 뉴스일수록 해당 기사를 중요한 위치에...
The post 유동적 저널리즘: 보도 건수를 넘어 보도 시간이 중요하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈의 어린시절! 하하 너무 귀여워!! 한동훈과 사랑에 빠진 채널A]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105574</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105574"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T10:41:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[종합편성채널 시사대담프로그램에는 국민의힘과 더불어민주당의 선거유세 현장이 자주 등장합니다. 지원유세 보도량과 화면구성에서도 차이가 드러나지만, 보도 논조도 다른데요. 국민의힘의 경우 한동훈 비대위원장 지원유세 일정을 따라가며 현장의 긍정적인 분위기를 전하는 데 열심이지만, 더불어민주당에 대해서는 이재명대표 지원유세보다는 논란을 전하는 데 시간을 할애합니다. 특히 일부 종편엔 한동훈 비대위원장의 유년시절 사진까지 등장하며 ‘한동훈 띄우기’에 집중하고 있는데요. 여야 선거유세 현장을 전하는 종편...
The post 한동훈의 어린시절! 하하 너무 귀여워!! 한동훈과 사랑에 빠진 채널A appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[정문태, 골든 트라이앵글의 고독한 취재기자]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105428</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105428"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T09:31:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[정호재의 아시안 퍼스펙티브] 가깝도고 먼 ‘동남아시아’를 통해 한국을 바라보고 아시아 시대를 꿈꿉니다. 한겨레 지금은 한국의 언론사에 규모의 차이만 남았지만, 1990년대 대학을 다닌 사람들에게 ‘한겨레’는 더 특별했고, 한겨레에 관한 애정과 심적 부채감이 상당했다. 그러니까 창간 직후 ‘한겨레 신문’이라는 건, 일종의 민주주의 운동 혹은 언론 운동의 개념이었고, 그것을 인지한 대학생들은 없는 쌈짓돈을 털어서, 적어도 학회실에서라도 한겨레를 구독해...
The post 정문태, 골든 트라이앵글의 고독한 취재기자 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정호재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[요술 방망이는 없다: ‘외국인 노동자 차등적 최저임금’으로 돌봄노동 해결은 불가능하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105454</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105454"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T07:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)이 전하는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기. 오늘은 한국은행 ‘돌봄노동’ 해법에 관한 이상헌 박사의 칼럼. 외국인 노동자 X 차등적 최저임금 문제 슬로우뉴스는 노동과 경제의 세계에서 개인과 공동체가 공존하는 조화로운 방법론을 고민하는 이상헌 박사(ILO 고용정책국장)와 ‘제네바 오전 8시(제오시)’ 연재를 진행하고 있습니다. 그런데 오늘은 좀 특별하게 인터뷰가 아닌 칼럼입니다. (^^) 주제는 이상헌...
The post 요술 방망이는 없다: ‘외국인 노동자 차등적 최저임금’으로 돌봄노동 해결은 불가능하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이상헌</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Empower conversational AI at scale with KServe]]></title>
        <id>76e84722-e0b5-4c43-8ab1-12524eaa73ce</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/15/empower-conversational-ai-scale-kserve"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KServe is a standard Model Inference Platform on Kubernetes built for highly scalable use cases. It is a popular open source platform available as a community project, as well as a core component of Red Hat OpenShift AI. It provides a Kubernetes custom resource definition (CRD) for serving machine learning (ML) models on arbitrary frameworks. It aims to solve production model serving use cases by providing performant, high abstraction interfaces for common ML frameworks and model formats like TensorFlow, PyTorch, XGBoost, Scikit-learn, and ONNX.
It simplifies the deployment process by abstracting the complexities associated with serving machine learning models at scale in production. KServe is framework-agnostic, supporting various machine learning frameworks, and it leverages Kubernetes' …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Saurabh Agarwal, Yuan Tang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KBS 이별법: 이별에도 예의가 있다는데…]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105185</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105185"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T02:08:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[박미숙의 새 필드] 한국학이 활발한 영국 셰필드에서 대중문화를 공부한 박미숙 박사와 함께 미디어에 비친 우리 자신의 모습을 이야기합니다. 오늘 추가할 새 필드는 KBS에서 사라진 여자들. [뉴스9], [역사저널 그날], [홍김동전], [옥탑방의 문제아들], [전국노래자랑]. 여성이 단독으로 혹은 주도적으로 진행했던 프로그램들이다. 그리고 지금은 폐지되거나 남성으로 진행자가 교체된 프로그램들이다. 사라진 여성들은 다음과 같다. 물론 사라지거나 교체된 프로그램이 이것들만 있는...
The post KBS 이별법: 이별에도 예의가 있다는데… appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>박미숙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Very simple stack overflow detection for Cortex-M and RISC-V]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-03-15:/stack-overflow-detection-cortex-m-and-risc-v.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/stack-overflow-detection-cortex-m-and-risc-v.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many ways of detecting and dealing
with stack overflow in embedded systems. Here is a very, very easy stack canary with minimal
overhead that can be used on Cortex-M and RISC-V with GNU and LLVM toolchains.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/15, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594138</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594138/3-15-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T22:54:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[그러다 칼 맞는다? 황상무 “MBC 잘 들어” 발언의 의미는: 슬로우레터 3월15일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105504</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105504"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T22:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[도태우와 정봉주 둘 다 공천 취소. 그래도 박용진은 안 된다? 막말 퍼레이드. 쟁점과 현안. “MBC는 잘 들어.” 이종섭 리스크, 한동훈이 나설까. 색깔론에 휘둘리는 민주당. 다르게 읽기. “인권 외쳐왔던 민주당 맞나.” 의대 증원 80% 지역에 배분한다. 더 깊게 읽기. 부동산 통계 조작, 재판까지 간다. 선거제 개편, 국회에 맡겨서는 안 된다. 해법과 대안. 어촌계 진입 장벽 낮추자...
The post 그러다 칼 맞는다? 황상무 “MBC 잘 들어” 발언의 의미는: 슬로우레터 3월15일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don't fix anything — cultivate acceptance instead: bugs in games that have become features]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1108/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1108/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many psychologists recommend cultivating acceptance. That is, accepting one's mistakes, for example. Some game developers have taken this quite seriously. They decided, "Why not?" and made errors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tune in for Google I/O on May 14]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/google-io-2024-save-the-date.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/google-io-2024-save-the-date.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeanine Banks – VP & General Manager, Developer X, and Head of Developer Relations






Google I/O is arriving this year on May 14th and you’re invited to join us online! I/O offers something for everyone, whether you are developing a new application, modernizing an existing one, or transforming it into a business.
The Gemini era unlocks new possibilities for developers to build creative and productive AI-enabled applications. I/O is where you’ll hear how you can get from idea to production AI applications faster. We’re  excited to share what’s new for mobile, web, and multiplatform development, and how to scale your applications in the cloud. You will be able to dive deeper into topics that interest you with over 100 sessions, workshops, codelabs, and demos.
 

Visit the Google I/O site and register to stay informed about I/O and other related events coming soon. The livestreamed keynotes start May 14 at 10am PT, so mark your calendar.
If you haven’t already, go try out our newest Google I/O puzzle and head to @googlefordevs on Instagram if you need a hint.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The first half of the 6.9 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965141/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965141/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T15:00:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of this writing, just over 4,900 non-merge changesets have been pulled
into the mainline for the 6.9 release.  This work includes the usual array
of changes all over the kernel tree; read on for a summary of the most
significant work merged during the first part of the 6.9 merge window.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965470/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965470/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T14:06:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and openvswitch), Fedora (chromium, python-multipart, thunderbird, and xen), Mageia (java-17-openjdk and screen), Red Hat (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, postgresql:13, and postgresql:15), Slackware (expat), SUSE (glibc, python-Django, python-Django1, sudo, and vim), and Ubuntu (expat, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-lowlatency, linux-raspi, python-cryptography, texlive-bin, and xorg-server).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선거의 경제학: 우리는 왜 계급을 배반하는 투표를 하는가.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105451</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105451"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T08:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[선거가 한 달도 남지 않았다. 오늘은 선거와 경제를 주제로 이야기해 보자. 한국은 원래 지역 구도가 강하다고 하지 않나. 이번 선거는 다를 거라고 보나. 지역 구도가 확고하다면 결국 수도권이 변수가 될 텐데, 지난 총선에서는 민주당이 압승하지 않았나. 서울과 경기도의 정치적 성향 차이를 뭐라고 봐야 하나. 한강벨트의 최대 현안은 결국 부동산이라고 봐야 하는 건가. 종부세 내는 사람들이...
The post 선거의 경제학: 우리는 왜 계급을 배반하는 투표를 하는가. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simple C++ State Machine Engine]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1628.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1628.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T08:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When the going gets tough, the tough get going. So, if you are going to deal with a problem slightly harder than switching a lightbulb on and off, you may want something better in your toolbox than what I described in my previous post on State Machines.

In this post, I'll start from the basic ad-hoc implementation presented in my last post and will decouple the state handling (the state...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[능력주의를 넘어서: 나를 대변해 주는 정당이 아니라 내가 함께하는 정당]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105432</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105432"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T07:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[노동당 비례후보를 알리고자 지지 당부 글을 썼다. 두 가지 비판이 있었다. 그 비판에 답한다. 당장의 승패보다 더 중요한 것 첫 번째 비판 취지를 요약하면 다음과 같다: 내 글이 상당 정도 패배주의적이라는 데 동의한다. 원래 내가 강한 이상주의적 지향과 강한 현실주의적 판단을 동시에 지닌 좀 모순적인 사람이다. 하긴 사람은 누구나 일정 부분 모순적이니까 이게 나만 무슨...
The post 능력주의를 넘어서: 나를 대변해 주는 정당이 아니라 내가 함께하는 정당 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이장규</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Standardization and innovation: Enemies or partners in crime?]]></title>
        <id>0f384911-a9e7-474c-8d1f-871c3f778e7d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/14/standardization-and-innovation-enemies-or-partners-crime"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I aim to share personal insights gained over the past year, rather than presenting factual or technological certainties. It is important for readers to recognize that the perspectives I offer are shaped by my own experiences and reflections.
To provide some background: approximately one year ago, I transitioned from a career in software development to a role as a Solution Architect at Red Hat, with a continued focus on application development. At that time, I identified as a full-stack developer and a DevOps engineer. However, I soon came to understand that the concept of a "full-stack developer" is somewhat misleading; in reality, my strengths lay in back-end development, with a keen interest in front-end technologies. While I was capable of initiating projects using Angu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maarten Vandeperre</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Java container awareness in OpenShift 4]]></title>
        <id>4ff7241c-f709-4f2d-9a9e-addf632b85f2</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/14/how-use-java-container-awareness-openshift-4"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A brief foray into containerized Java, this article describes the usage and implications of container-aware Java application deployments, and how to use it to your advantage of fully containerized deployments. We also cover the risks of decoupling the heap (off-heap) from the container limits. Finally, we will explain Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform limit settings and specific container-aware troubleshooting tools.
Java is container-aware
When deploying Java inside a container, sometimes we see questions such as:
Should the user set max heap (Xmx)? What about the initial heap (Xms)? What about MaxRAM?
Should we set MaxRAM to contain the full size of the memory?
The answer for most of those questions is no—for most use cases. The reason is that Java is container-aware.
This is a great …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 14, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964623/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964623/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T00:17:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 14, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LLVM Google Summer of Code 2024 & 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2024-02-26-gsoc/</id>
        <link href="https://blog.llvm.org/posts/2024-02-26-gsoc/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LLVM organization was accepted to participate in Google Summer of Code in 2024. Soon, prospective participants will begin submitting their project proposals, and mentors will review them to select those who will spend a significant amount of time this year contributing to various parts of LLVM.
But first, let’s look back and see what we had in 2023. The Google Summer of Code 2023 was very successful for the LLVM project. Overall, we received 54 proposals for 24 open projects. Out of this set of proposals, 20 projects were successfully completed and covered many different aspects of LLVM and its subprojects.

ExtractAPI while building by Ankur Saini, mentored by Daniel Grumberg
WebAssembly Support for clang-repl by Anubhab Ghosh, mentored by Vassil Vassilev and Alexander Penev
Modules B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The LLVM Project Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘런종섭’ 논란과 박근혜 탄핵의 공통점, 범죄 전문가 윤석열이 간과한 사실: 슬로우레터 3월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105400</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105400"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T22:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“이종섭 임명 철회해 달라.” 이종섭은 윤석열 전화를 받았을까. 범죄 전문가 윤석열이 몰랐을까. 쟁점과 현안. 병역 기피냐 양심적 병역 거부냐. ‘수박 척결’ 양문석도 공천 안착. 또 시작된 의원 꿔주기 꼼수. 한동훈 한계론. 더 깊게 읽기. 시스템 공천에 숨은 ‘악마의 디테일’. 윤석열의 포퓰리즘 901조 원. 다르게 읽기. 도제식 의사 교육, 이대로 좋은가. 대형 병원의 박리다매식 경영. 해법과...
The post ‘런종섭’ 논란과 박근혜 탄핵의 공통점, 범죄 전문가 윤석열이 간과한 사실: 슬로우레터 3월14일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDE Women’s History Month Feature: Gema Parreño Piqueras, AI/ML GDE]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/gde-womens-history-month-feature-gema-parreno-piqueras.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/gde-womens-history-month-feature-gema-parreno-piqueras.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Justyna Politanska-Pyszko – Program Manager, Google Developer Experts 







For Women's History Month, we're shining a spotlight on Gema Parreño Piqueras, an AI/ML Google Developer Expert (GDE) from Madrid, Spain. GDEs are recognized by Google for their outstanding technical expertise and passion for sharing knowledge.



Gema Parreño Piqueras, AI/ML GDE, Madrid, Spain 



Gema's dedication to the GDE program makes her a true leader within the Google Developers community, and her work in Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning pushes the boundaries of Google's technological capabilities.
Gema is a force to be reckoned with in the world of data science. As a data scientist at Izertis and a GDE, she's not only making significant contributions to the field of AI/ML but also b…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to make sure no floating point code is used]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40242</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/03/13/how-to-make-sure-no-floating-point-code-is-used/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T18:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The article explains ways to avoid float and double data types in embedded applications to prevent precision, code size, and performance issues. It introduces using pragma to 'poison' these data types and setting options for software floating point runtime routines, as well as catching them in libraries through linker options. These methods ensure no floating point operations are used, providing greater control over the application. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Questions about machine-learning models for Fedora]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964739/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964739/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T18:08:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kaitlyn Abdo of Fedora's AI/ML
SIG opened an issue with the
Fedora Engineering Steering Committee (FESCo) recently that carried a few tricky
questions about packaging machine-learning (ML) models for Fedora. 
Specifically, the SIG is looking for guidance on whether pre-trained weights for
PyTorch constitute code or content. And, if the models are released under a
license approved by the
Open Source Initiative (OSI),
does it matter what data the models were trained on? The issue was quickly
tossed over to Fedora's legal
mailing list and sparked an interesting discussion about how to
handle these items, and a temporary path forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Benefits of Qualitative Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/measuring-developer-productivity-humans.html#TheTwoTypesOfQualitativeMetrics</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/measuring-developer-productivity-humans.html#TheTwoTypesOfQualitativeMetrics"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Abi Noda and Tim Cochran continue their
       discussion on using qualitative metrics to assess the productivity of
       development teams. In this installment they classify qualitative metrics into
       attitudinal and behavioral metrics. We also see that qualitative metrics
       allow you to measure things that are otherwise unmeasurable, provide missing
       visibility, and supply necessary context for quantitative data.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With CUDA C on an Nvidia Jetson: Hello CUDA World!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1641.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1641.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T14:26:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
Sales of Graphics Processing Units (GPU) have exploded over the past few years due to the rising popularity of machine learning applications. However, GPUs were originally architected and designed for gaming applications. Their native architecture naturally translated into use in machine learning due to the similar operations performed. Nvidia is one of the most...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[곧 닥칠 ‘고령 사회’, 우리가 던져야 할 질문은 따로 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78864</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/13/npsp_agingsociety/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_agingsociety"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T14:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국 사회의 출산율은 매번 최저치를 경신하고, 평균 수명은 꾸준히 늘어나고 있습니다. 이는 곧 (초)고령 사회의 도래를 피할 수 없다는 말이기도 합니다. 특히 66세 이상 은퇴 연령층의 상대적 빈곤율은 40.4%로 OECD 국가 가운데 가장 높은 수준이고, 노령층의 경제적 양극화도 갈수록 심화하고 있으며, 부실한 연금 제도 때문에 나이가 들수록 빈곤율이 높아지는 특징도 보입니다. 우리 사회는 급격히 바뀔 인구구조에 얼마나 대비하고 있을까요? 우리보다는 조금 사정이 나아 보이는 미국에서도 제대로 된 고령 사회 담론이 부족하다는 지적이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민주당 ‘편애’하는 종편: 공천 논란 보도량, 국힘보다  4.5배 많았다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105388</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105388"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T13:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[종합편성채널 시사대담프로그램은 더불어민주당 ‘공천 논란’에 대해 적극 보도하고 있습니다. 3월 첫째 주에는 권향엽(순천·광양·곡성·구례을) 후보 사천 논란과 더불어민주당 중진 의원들의 컷오프와 탈당 소식이 주요하게 다뤄졌는데요. 반면, 국민의힘의 유영하(대구 달서갑) 후보 공천논란을 비롯해 시스템 공천이 아니라고 비판하며 컷오프에 반발한 국민의힘 의원들의 소식은 짧게 전하는 수준에 그쳤습니다. 민주당 253분 vs 국힘 56분 조용한 공천이라 평가받던 국민의힘에서도 공천에서 탈락한...
The post 민주당 ‘편애’하는 종편: 공천 논란 보도량, 국힘보다  4.5배 많았다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965278/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965278/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T12:54:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (edk2, freeipa, kernel, and liblas), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (docker, edk2, kernel, kernel-rt, and kpatch-patch), SUSE (axis, fontforge, gnutls, java-1_8_0-openjdk, kernel, python3, sudo, and zabbix), and Ubuntu (dotnet7, dotnet8, libgoogle-gson-java, openssl, and ovn).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leveraging space system software best practices for edge IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481655</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/leveraging-space-system-software-best-practices-for-edge-iot/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T12:38:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers of embedded and edge IoT devices, it’s time to start learning the lessons of robust software development engrained in teams working on high-reliability...
The post Leveraging space system software best practices for edge IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: software tracing with binary protocols]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481652</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-software-tracing-with-binary-protocols/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T12:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video tutorial, we explain the general principles of software tracing based on a binary protocol, which is far less intrusive than using printf()....
The post Programming embedded systems: software tracing with binary protocols appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes for IoT: a practical guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481643</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/kubernetes-for-iot-a-practical-guide/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T12:11:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes offers a powerful, scalable platform for managing IoT workloads, with KubeEdge extending these capabilities to the edge. Kubernetes is an open-source platform designed to...
The post Kubernetes for IoT: a practical guide appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilad David Maayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[수입 부처만 있나? 우리나라 토종 부처도 있다!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105191</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105191"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T11:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[김훤주의 지역에서 본 세상] 베테랑 기자 김훤주가 잘 드러나지 않은 세상 이야기를 따뜻하고 담백한 시선으로 전합니다. 우리가 절에 가면 수많은 부처님을 만날 수 있다. 가장 손쉽게 볼 수 있는 것은 2500년 전에 룸비니에서 태어난 고타마 싯다르타 석가모니불(Gautama Buddha)이다. 부처님은 이 밖에도 많지만 보통 사람들에게 익숙한 것만 해도 미륵불·비로자나불·아미타불·약사여래불 등 여럿이 있다. 그런데 이들 부처님을 보면...
The post 수입 부처만 있나? 우리나라 토종 부처도 있다! appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘조국혁신당 누구?’ 악플보다 무서운 KBS의 무플: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 분석(3월 첫째 주)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105361</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105361"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T09:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요약 주요 이슈 1. 민주당 “비명횡사” VS 국힘 “조용한 공천” 2. 조국혁신당 돌풍 주목 3. 조중동, 성일종 친일발언·정우택 금품수수 의혹 외면 “(이토 히로부미에 관해) 한반도에 끔찍한 사태를 불러온 인물이고 그만큼 우리에게 불행한 역사이지만, (일본이) 우리보다 먼저 인재를 키웠던 선례” 성일종, 2024년 3월 3일 서산장학재단 장학금 전달식. 4. 공천확정 선거구 중심으로 ‘선거지역, 인물’ 부상 5. 선거운동...
The post ‘조국혁신당 누구?’ 악플보다 무서운 KBS의 무플: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 분석(3월 첫째 주) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A new filesystem for pidfds]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/963749/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/963749/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The pidfd abstraction is a Linux-specific
way of referring to processes that avoids the race conditions inherent in
Unix process ID numbers.  Since a pidfd is a file descriptor, it needs a
filesystem to implement the usual operations performed on files.  As the
use of pidfds has grown, they have stressed the limits of the simple
filesystem that was created for them.  Christian Brauner has created
a new filesystem for pidfds that seems likely to debut in the 6.9
kernel, but it ran into a little bump along the way, demonstrating that
things you cannot see can still hurt you.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Save memory with OpenShift Virtualization using Free Page Reporting]]></title>
        <id>9b1f4ce8-c323-4119-8eb5-046d2a61366b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/13/save-memory-openshift-virtualization-using-free-page-reporting"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenShift Virtualization, a feature of Red Hat OpenShift, allows running virtual machines (VMs) alongside containers on the same platform, simplifying management. It allows using VMs in containerized environments by running VMs the same way as any other pod, so that organizations with significant investment in virtualization or who desire the greater isolation provided by VMs with legacy workloads can use them in an orchestrated containerized environment.
While VMs offer important advantages in this regard, they do consume additional memory. There are several reasons why, but one of them is that while VMs can expand their memory use up to the limit of the defined size, but until now they cannot shrink their memory footprint. In this post, I will present a technology, Free Page Reporting (F…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Krawitz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kafka tiered storage deep dive]]></title>
        <id>cb1323a4-598b-4dbc-935d-8eebaad1e5f9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/13/kafka-tiered-storage-deep-dive"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tiered storage is a new early access feature available as of Apache Kafka 3.6.0 that allows you to scale compute and storage resources independently, provides better client isolation, and allows faster maintenance of your Kafka cluster. Let's dive into this new feature to see the motivations, design, and implementation details. In this post, we will focus on Tiered storage implementation, so it is assumed a good understanding of the Kafka architecture and main components. If you are looking for a tutorial or example, we recommend reading Getting started with tiered storage in Apache Kafka.
Tiering
The idea of tiering is not new in the software industry. The three-tier is a well-established software application architecture that organizes applications into three logical and physical computi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Federico Valeri, Luke Chen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 alpha 5 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/03/python-3130-alpha-5-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/03/python-3130-alpha-5-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T00:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 alpha 5 is now available:


  
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130a5/




This is an early developer preview of Python 3.13
Major new features of the 3.13 series, compared to 3.12
Python 3.13 is still in development. This release, 3.13.0a5, is the fifth of six planned alpha releases.
Alpha releases are intended to make it easier to test the current 
state of new features and bug fixes and to test the release process.
During the alpha phase, features may be added up until the start of 
the beta phase (2024-05-07) and, if necessary, may be modified or 
deleted up until the release candidate phase (2024-07-30). Please keep 
in mind that this is a preview release and its use is not recommended for production environments.
Many new features for Python 3.13 are sti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Differences Between ELF-32 and ELF-64]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/elf-format-differences</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/elf-format-differences"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ELF object file format is one of the most commonly used today. Most build
systems provide an output to this format, and ELF is commonly used to output
coredumps. The format varies in subtle ways for 32-bit and 64-bit targets
though, which can present problems for tools supporting both. This post will
highlight the main differences and is intended as a quick reference for these
differences.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/13, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594135</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594135/3-13-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T23:58:11.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘트럼프 대세론’ 굳혀줄 부통령 후보는 누구일까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78566</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/12/npsp_trumpveep/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_trumpveep"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T22:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 1월 22일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. *** 아이오와 코커스에서 낙승한 뒤 쓴 칼럼에서 예상했듯이 트럼프는 결국, 공화당 후보로 사실상 낙점됐습니다. 글에서 꼽은 후보 가운데 지난주까지 경선에서 물러나지 않고, 트럼프와 경쟁했던 니키 헤일리 후보는 절대로 부통령 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한 달은 길다, 국민의힘에 쏟아지는 악재: 슬로우뉴스 3월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105337</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105337"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T22:03:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한 놈만 팬다, 조국혁신당의 바람몰이. 조국이 ‘샤이 진보’를 불러낸다고? 쟁점과 현안. 5.18 망언 도태우를 안고 간다. 종북 논란 전지예‧정영이는 사퇴. 조국혁신당 비례 후보에 101명 몰렸다. 민주당은 비명횡사 넘어 비명궤멸로. 민주당 위성정당 비례 후보 확정. 더 깊게 읽기. 10대 공약 살펴보니. 의료 대란의 역습. 보수 언론의 경고. 의대 교수들도 합류한다. 의료 붕괴의 현장, 울산을 보라. 다르게...
The post 한 달은 길다, 국민의힘에 쏟아지는 악재: 슬로우뉴스 3월13일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Today's hardware vulnerability: register file data sampling]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965167/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965167/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T20:38:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mainline kernel has just received a set of commits addressing the
"register file data sampling" hardware vulnerability.


	RFDS may allow a malicious actor to infer data values previously
	used in floating point registers, vector registers, or integer
	registers. RFDS does not provide the ability to choose which data
	is inferred


Only Atom cores are affected, but those cores can be found inside a number
of processors.  See this documentation
commit for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Herb Sutter on increasing safety in C++]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965147/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965147/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T19:21:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Herb Sutter, chair of the ISO C++ standards committee,

writes about the current problems with writing secure C++,
and his personal opinion on next steps to address this while maintaining
backward compatibility.



If there were 90-98% fewer C++ type/bounds/initialization/lifetime
vulnerabilities we wouldn't be having this discussion. All languages have CVEs,
C++ just has more (and C still more); so far in 2024,

Rust has 6 CVEs, and

C and C++ combined have 61 CVEs. So zero isn't the goal; something like a 90%
reduction is necessary, and a 98% reduction is sufficient, to achieve security
parity with the levels of language safety provided by MSLs [memory-safe languages]… and has the strong
benefit that I believe it can be achieved with perfect backward link
compatibility (i.e., without changing C++'s object model, and its lifetime
model which does not depend on universal tracing garbage collection and is not
limited to tree-based data structures) which is essential to our being able to
adopt the improvements in existing C++ projects as easily as we can adopt other
new editions of C++. — After that, we can pursue additional improvements to
other buckets, such as thread safety and overflow safety.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A "Perspectival" Mirror of the Elephant]]></title>
        <id>3649303</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3649303"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T16:35:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software Drift]]></title>
        <id>3649297</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3649297"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T16:22:34.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google for Games is coming to GDC 2024]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/google-for-games-is-coming-to-gdc-2024.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/google-for-games-is-coming-to-gdc-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Aurash Mahbod – General Manager, Games on Google Play






Google for Games is coming to GDC in San Francisco! Join us on March 19 for the Game Developers Conference (GDC) at the Moscone Center, where game developers from across the world will gather to learn, network, problem-solve, and help shape the future of the industry. From March 18 to March 22, experience our comprehensive suite of multi-platform game development tools and explore the new features from Play Pass at the West Hall, Level 2 Lobby.
This year, we’re proud to host eight sessions for developers, designers, business and marketing teams, and everyone else in the gaming community with an interest to grow their game business. Take a look at this year’s sessions below and if you’re interested in learning more about …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Insecurity and Python pickles]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964392/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964392/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T15:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Serialization is the process of transforming Python objects into a sequence of
bytes which can be used to recreate a copy of the object later — or on another
machine.

pickle is Python's native serialization module. It can store complex Python
objects,
making it an appealing prospect for moving data without having to write
custom serialization code. For example, pickle is an integral component of
several file
formats used for machine learning. However, using pickle to deserialize
untrusted files is a major security risk, because doing so can invoke arbitrary
Python functions. Consequently, the machine-learning community is working to address the
security issues caused by widespread use of pickle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965113/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965113/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T14:50:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (qemu), Mageia (libtiff and thunderbird), Red Hat (kernel, kpatch-patch, postgresql, and rhc-worker-script), SUSE (compat-openssl098, openssl, openssl1, python-Django, python-Django1, and wpa_supplicant), and Ubuntu (accountsservice, libxml2, linux-bluefield, linux-raspi-5.4, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux-oem-6.1, openvswitch, postgresql-9.5, and ruby-rack).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring Developer Productivity via Humans]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/measuring-developer-productivity-humans.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/measuring-developer-productivity-humans.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Measuring developer productivity is a difficult challenge.
       Conventional metrics focused on development cycle time and throughput are
       limited, and there aren't obvious answers for where else to turn.
       Qualitative metrics offer a powerful way to measure and understand
       developer productivity using data derived from developers themselves.
       Abi Noda and Tim Cochran begin their
       discussion by explaining what a qualitative metric is and
       why we shouldn't reject them for being subjective or unreliable. 
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huston: KeyTrap!]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965067/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965067/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T08:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Geoff Huston digs into the
details of the KeyTrap DNS vulnerability, which was disclosed in February.


	It's by no means "[devastating]" for the DNS, and the fix is much the
	same as the previous fix. As well as limiting the number of queries
	that a resolver can generate to resolve a queried name, a careful
	resolver will limit both the elapsed time and perhaps the amount of
	the resolver's processing resources that are used to resolve any
	single query name.

	It's also not a novel discovery by the ATHENE folk. The
	vulnerability was described five years ago by a student at the
	University of Twente. I guess the issue was that the student failed
	to use a sufficient number of hysterical adjectives in describing
	this DNS vulnerability in the paper!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding Templates in Stakater's Multi Tenancy Operator]]></title>
        <id>0824d6b5-31bf-409a-b757-a9441b94b703</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/12/understanding-templates-stakaters-multi-tenancy-operator"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a Technology Partner within the Red Hat OpenShift ecosystem, Stakater's Multi Tenant Operator has been officially certified by Red Hat since March 2022, with the latest release certified in November 2023. With Red Hat OpenShift Certified Operators, customers can benefit from validated, verified, mature and supported Operators from Red Hat and partner ISVs in their hybrid cloud environments.
Learn more about Red Hat OpenShift Operator certification here. To learn more about becoming a Red Hat Partner see this link.
This is the third part in a series featuring the exploration of Multi Tenant Operator (MTO) by Stakater, an operator designed to streamline and secure multi-tenancy in OpenShift and Kubernetes environments. In our two previous blogs (1) (2), we described MTO fundamentals. In t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivien Wang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieve more with less using Red Hat Developer Hub's self-service features]]></title>
        <id>721f8a8a-c6e1-4104-b201-c0a229e5aeb4</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/12/achieve-more-less-using-red-hat-developer-hubs-self-service-features"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A client company’s Red Hat OpenShift team was facing a common issue: engineering teams had to allocate time to handle repetitive and manual tasks, such as addressing a high volume of service desk tickets. Many of these tickets stemmed from misconfigurations and unclear documentation, which not only consume valuable time and effort from the engineering team but also hinder the productivity and satisfaction of end-users.
The client wanted to improve the developer experience by introducing more self-service and automation. To achieve this, the client tested out Red Hat Developer Hub as a unified access point to tools and resources.
Background
Toil, as defined by Google’s site reliability engineering (SRE) framework, is work that doesn’t drive long-term value. In this case, answering recurring…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josephine Pfeiffer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Z세대 가치관에 문제 있다? 그런데 부모인 X세대가 더 문제다?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78860</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/12/npsp_gendergapgeneration/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_gendergapgeneration"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T04:00:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[현재 성인 가운데 가장 젊은이들은 Z세대에 속합니다. 최근 미국 Z세대 안에서 남녀 간에, 성별에 따라 정치적인 성향 차이가 두드러진다는 조사 결과가 있었습니다. 성별에 따라 어려서부터 경험하는 것이 달라서 가치관에도 차이가 벌어진 데는 부모들의 교육 방침이 적잖은 영향을 미쳤다고 할 수 있습니다. 이에 관해 Z세대의 부모들인 X세대의 과보호를 지적한 칼럼이 뉴욕타임스에 올라왔습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 단지 성향 차이를 넘어 젠더 갈등 양상까지 보이고 있는 한국 사회에 주는 함의가 무엇인지 짚어봤습니다. 전문 번역: 점점 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 저들을 이길 수 있다면 민주주의쯤이야? … 공동체 망치는 ‘정서적 양극화’]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105292</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105292"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T03:17:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[최근 우리 사회의 정치적 진영 대립과 갈등 정도가 이만저만이 아니다. 정파적 대립과 양극화는 비단 정치 영역에만 국한된 것이 아니라 경계를 넘어 비정치적 영역의 일상까지도 파고들고 있다. 양극 정치 갈등…대한민국 역시나 1등 한국 사회의 이념 대립과 정치 양극화가 심각하다는 사실은 일반 국민의 인식 속에서도 잘 드러나고 있다. 지난 2022년에 미국의 대표적 조사기관인 퓨리서치 센터(Pew Research Center)가...
The post 우리가 저들을 이길 수 있다면 민주주의쯤이야? … 공동체 망치는 ‘정서적 양극화’ appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/12, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594121</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594121/3-12-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T00:06:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling Gate Drive Diodes]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1640.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1640.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T23:08:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a short article about how to analyze the diode in some gate drive circuits when figuring out turn-off characteristics — specifically, determining the relationship between gate drive current and gate voltage during turn-off of a power transistor.

Here’s the diode I’m talking about; it’s the one labeled D1:



Just as an example, I’m going to use the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모건스탠리, 테슬라 주가 하락 4가지 요인]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594119</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594119/%eb%aa%a8%ea%b1%b4%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%a0%eb%a6%ac-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ed%95%98%eb%9d%bd-4%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80-%ec%9a%94%ec%9d%b8"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T22:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[제로섬 게임일까, 반윤 결집일까, 조국 돌풍에 조선일보가 긴장하는 이유: 슬로우레터 3월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105268</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105268"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T22:04:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[조국혁신당 돌풍, 조선일보의 불안. 사이다에 목말랐던 민주당 지지층이 흔들린다. 반윤 포위 구도. 박용진의 좌절. 쟁점과 현안. 종북횡재? 이재명의 선택은? 서울대 의대 교수들도 18일 사직 예고. 다르게 읽기. 공보의 차출하면 농어촌은 어떻게 하나. 69cm 잘라냈는데 다른 3647개 건물은? 더 깊게 읽기. “이해했다고 말하세요.” 해법과 대안. 폐지 줍는 노인 수입은 월 15만 원. 집 한 채에 1유로....
The post 제로섬 게임일까, 반윤 결집일까, 조국 돌풍에 조선일보가 긴장하는 이유: 슬로우레터 3월12일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Development statistics for 6.8]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964106/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964106/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.8 kernel was released on March 10
after a typical, nine-week development cycle.  Over this time, 1,938
developers contributed 14,405 non-merge changesets, making 6.8 into a
slower cycle than 6.7 (but busier than 6.6), with the lowest number of
developers participating since the 6.5 release.  Still, there was
a lot going on during this cycle; read on for some of the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started with the Microchip PIC® Microcontroller]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1622.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1622.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T15:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the first of five posts focusing on getting started with Microchip's 8-bit PIC® microcontrollers. The series of posts introduce successive topics culminating in a final project implementing a simple 4-bit counter with a "UI" of four external LEDs connected to GPIO pins counting up at a one second interval via an internal timer.

This post introduces the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/965032/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/965032/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T14:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libuv1, nss, squid, tar, tiff, and wordpress), Fedora (chromium, exercism, grub2, qpdf, and wpa_supplicant), Oracle (edk2 and opencryptoki), and SUSE (cpio, openssl-1_0_0, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, sudo, tomcat, and xen).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Challenges in Adopting and Sustaining Microservice-based Software Development]]></title>
        <id>3649402</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3649402"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T12:26:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free and Open Source Software - and Other Market Failures]]></title>
        <id>3649298</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3649298"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T12:09:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이 정도면 되었다: 욕먹을 줄 알면서 [파묘] 칼럼 쓴 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105193</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105193"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T03:49:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘나는 영화 파묘가 불편했다’(슬로우뉴스 제목 ‘쇠말뚝은 없다’)는 글을 개인 소셜미디어에 올리고 나서 욕을 많이 먹었다. 물론 공감과 격려도 조금은 있었다. 이쪽저쪽 모두에게 고맙다는 말씀을 올린다. 돌이켜보니 좀더 정확하게 쓸 수도 있었는데 마음이 급하다 보니 그렇게 하지 못한 구석도 있었다. 다 내 잘못이고 내 탓이다. 반성(反省)이라는 말뜻 그대로 많이 돌아보며 살펴보고 있다. 731부대는? 기록 없는 지배는...
The post 이 정도면 되었다: 욕먹을 줄 알면서 [파묘] 칼럼 쓴 이유 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sendbird is hiring Interns for AI Business Strategy team]]></title>
        <id>https://kimchihill.com/?p=2761</id>
        <link href="https://kimchihill.com/2024/03/11/sendbird-is-hiring-interns-for-ai-business-strategy-team/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=sendbird-is-hiring-interns-for-ai-business-strategy-team"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T02:51:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Silicon Valley unicorn startup Sendbird is looking for 2 positions: 1) short-term (3 month) part-time intern and 2) full-time (3 month) intern, for its AI Business Strategy. This is an opportunity to experience firsthand how a global unicorn captures and executes opportunities in the Gen AI trend. What You Will Do Who You Are Bonus PointsContinue reading "Sendbird is hiring Interns for AI Business Strategy team"
Sendbird is hiring Interns for AI Business Strategy team appeared first on Kimchi hill.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>kimchihill</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“이태원 특별법? 나는 핼러윈 특별법이라고 말할 것” 손형기 선거방송심의위원(TV조선 추천)의 뚝심?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105234</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105234"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T02:50:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024년 3월 7일 제22대 국회의원선거 제9차 선거방송심의위원회 회의가 열렸습니다. 이날 안건은 총 9건으로 별도 의견진술, 재심청구 등은 없었습니다. 일신상 이유로 사퇴를 표명한 최창근 부위원장(한국방송기자클럽 추천)은 제8차 회의와 마찬가지로 불참하여 이날도 8명이 의결에 참여했습니다. 심의한 9건 대상과 결과는 아래 표와 같습니다. 9건 중 1건(대전MBC)은 의결보류, 2건은 법정제재를 전제로 한 ‘의견진술’이 결정되었습니다. 나머지 6건 중 각 3건씩...
The post “이태원 특별법? 나는 핼러윈 특별법이라고 말할 것” 손형기 선거방송심의위원(TV조선 추천)의 뚝심? appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is known about software effort estimation in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8636</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/03/10/what-is-known-about-software-effort-estimation-in-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T23:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s three years since my 2021 post summarizing what I knew about estimating software tasks. While no major new public datasets have appeared (there have been smaller finds), I have talked to lots of developers/managers about the findings from the 2019/2021 data avalanche, and some data dots have been connected. A common response from managers, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“박근혜 이전 수준, 한국의 민주주의가 후퇴하고 있다”: 슬로우레터 3월11일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105210</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105210"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T22:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한 달 전 여론조사 잘 안 맞는 이유는? 보수 과표집 논란, 어떻게 볼까. 서울과 경기도는 달랐다. 언더독이 승부 가른다. ‘스윙보터’의 전쟁이다. 쟁점과 현안. 세 가지가 없는 선거. 민주당 위성정당 시민사회 비례 확정. 민주당 선대위는 이재명+이해찬+김부겸. 권은희의 양보. 다르게 읽기. 0명과 2000명 사이. 수가 타령으로 신뢰 얻겠나. 더 깊게 읽기. “한국의 민주주의가 후퇴하고 있다.” 피의자 이종섭...
The post “박근혜 이전 수준, 한국의 민주주의가 후퇴하고 있다”: 슬로우레터 3월11일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.8 kernel has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964784/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964784/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T21:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released the 6.8 kernel.


	So it took a bit longer for the commit counts to come down this
	release than I tend to prefer, but a lot of that seemed to be about
	various selftest updates (networking in particular) rather than any
	actual real sign of problems. And the last two weeks have been
	pretty quiet, so I feel there's no real reason to delay 6.8.


Significant changes in this release include
the deadline servers scheduling feature,
support for memory-management
auto-tuning in DAMON,
the large anonymous folios feature,
the kernel
samepage merging advisor,
the ability to prevent writes to block
devices containing mounted filesystems,
the listmount() and
statmount() system calls,
the first
device driver written in Rust,
the removal
of the (never finished) bpfilter
packet-filtering system,
three new system calls for managing Linux
security modules,
the BPF token mechanism for fine-grained
control over BPF permissions,
support for data-type profiling in the
perf tool,
guest-first memory for KVM virtualization,
the Intel Xe graphics driver,
and a lot more.  See the LWN merge-window summaries
(part 1,
part 2) for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chiplets are the latest buzz, but many challenges lie ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481613</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/chiplets-are-the-latest-buzz-but-many-challenges-lie-ahead/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T18:52:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With lots of hype on chiplets, we look at the state of play through interviews with several players in the ecosystem: Synopsys, Anysys, Intel, Samsung, and Bosch, to understand the opportunities, the status and the challenges ahead.
The post Chiplets are the latest buzz, but many challenges lie ahead appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Huang: IRIS (Infra-Red, in situ) Project Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964956/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964956/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-10T10:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrew 'bunnie' Huang provides an update on
his IRIS infrared chip-scanning project as the starting point for a
detailed summary on how chip customers can detect forgeries and
modifications in general.


	The technique works because although silicon looks opaque at
	visible light, it is transparent starting at near-infrared
	wavelengths (roughly 1000 nm and longer). Today's commodity optics
	and CMOS cameras are actually capable of working with lights at
	this wavelength; thus, IRIS is a low-cost and effective technique
	for confirming the construction of chips down to block level. For
	example, IRIS can readily help determine if a chip has the correct
	amount of RAM, number of CPU cores, peripherals, bond pads,
	etc. This level of verification would be sufficient to deter most
	counterfeits or substitutions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/7, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594117</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594117/3-7-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T11:11:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4분기 크라우드스트라이크 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594115</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594115/4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%81%ac%eb%9d%bc%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ec%9d%84-%ec%9d%bd%eb%8a%94-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%9c%ec%84%a0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T11:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 장르가 된 범죄실화물, 어떻게 소비하는 게 정답일까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78547</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/08/npsp_truecrimestory/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_truecrimestory"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T22:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 1월 17일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 인간의 잔혹함과 끔찍한 범죄, 그 어두운 세상의 단면을 가까이서 자세히 들여다보고 싶은 욕망은 역사가 깊습니다. 사형 등 형벌을 집행하는 것이 서민들의 엔터테인먼트였던 먼 과거로 돌아가지 않더라도 범죄와 범죄자를 조명한 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Untangling the Open Collectives]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964402/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964402/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T20:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Name collisions aren't just a problem for software
development—organizations, projects, and software that have the
same or similar names can cause serious confusion. That was certainly
the case on February 28 when the Open Collective
Foundation (OCF) began to notify its hosted projects that it would
be shutting down by the end of 2024. The announcement surprised
projects hosted with OCF, as one might expect. It also worried and
confused users of the Open Collective software platform from Open Collective, Inc. (OCI), as
well as organizations hosted by the Open Source
Collective (OSC) and Open Collective
Europe (OC Europe). There is enough confusion about the names,
relationships between the organizations, and impact on projects like
Flatpak, Homebrew, and htop hosted by OCF, that a
deeper look is warranted.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Better linked-list traversal in BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964381/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964381/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:34:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before loading a BPF program, the kernel must verify that the program is
safe to run; among other things, that verification includes ensuring that
the program will terminate within a bounded time.  That requirement has
long made writing loops in BPF a challenging task.  The situation has
improved over the years for some types of loops, but others — including
linked-list traversal — are still awkward in BPF programs.  A new set of
BPF primitives aims to make life easier for this use case through the
installation of what can be seen as a sort of circuit breaker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964832/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964832/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (fontforge), Fedora (chromium, iwd, libell, and thunderbird), Oracle (buildah, kernel, skopeo, and tomcat), Red Hat (opencryptoki), Slackware (ghostscript), SUSE (go1.21, go1.22, google-oauth-java-client, jetty-minimal, openssl-1_0_0, python310, sudo, wpa_supplicant, and xmlgraphics-batik), and Ubuntu (libhtmlcleaner-java, linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde,
 linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke, linux-gkeop,
 linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux-azure, linux-azure-6.5, linux-hwe-6.5, mqtt-client, ncurses, and puma).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블로그 업데이트]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/blog-update-2024-mar/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/blog-update-2024-mar/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T08:26:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다보니 블로그 업데이트를 연례 행사처럼 치루고 있다.
그동안...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드: undefined</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘좋빠가’로 밀어붙이는 의대 정원 논란, 정부가 한 발 물러서야 한다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105171</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105171"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T05:51:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] ‘얼마나’보다 ‘어떻게’를 이야기해야 할 때, 총선 포퓰리즘으로 밀어붙일 일 아니다. 2월20일부터 전공의들 이탈이 시작됐다. 3주가 다 돼 가는데 해법을 찾지 못하고 있는 상황이다. 언론 보도를 보면 파업이라고 쓰지 않던데, 이게 무슨 차이인가. 의사들 반발이 거센데 강대강으로 치닫는 것 같다. 달리 대안이 없었을까. 의사 수가 부족한 건 맞지 않나. 여러가지 문제가 한꺼번에 터져나오고 있는 것...
The post ‘좋빠가’로 밀어붙이는 의대 정원 논란, 정부가 한 발 물러서야 한다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“80이 넘었잖아요” 박지원 나이 언급하며 ‘수도권 판세’ 운운한 TV조선 패널]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105153</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105153"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T02:29:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2월 22일부터 3월 1일까지 종합편성채널 시사대담프로그램의 주요 이슈는 더불어민주당 ‘공천 논란’이었습니다. 더불어민주당 공천에서 탈락한 의원들이 당적을 옮기거나 공개적인 비판에 나서고 있기는 하지만, 공천 대상자 하나하나를 호명하며 공천내용을 지적하는 방송은 ‘계파 갈등’을 부각하며 더불어민주당의 부정적 이미지를 강화하는 모습으로 비치기도 합니다. ‘비명’이라 탈락했다면서, ‘친명 중의 친명’? 채널A [뉴스 TOP10] (2월 22일)은 총 방송시간 91분 중 72분인 80%가량을...
The post “80이 넘었잖아요” 박지원 나이 언급하며 ‘수도권 판세’ 운운한 TV조선 패널 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘유리 천장’ 지수, 한국이 12년째 꼴찌인 이유: 슬로우레터 3월8일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105113</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105113"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T22:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여성의 유리 천장이 가장 낮은 곳은? 여성들에게는 일이 시민권이다. 성별 임금 격차 핵심은 경력 단절. 쟁점과 현안. 출발선으로 돌아갔다. “참으로 놀랄 일이다.” 홍영표와 설훈은 새로운미래로. 민주당 위성정당 시민사회 몫 12명 후보 압축. 출국 금지됐는데 호주 대사, 나갈 수는 있나. 박용진 살아 돌아올까. 다르게 읽기. 전국노래자랑 시청률 반토막. 김신영은 그냥 MC가 아니었다. 더 깊게 읽기. “피해자들이...
The post ‘유리 천장’ 지수, 한국이 12년째 꼴찌인 이유: 슬로우레터 3월8일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make Your Own MCU Boards (2023 Teardown Conference)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1635.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1635.php"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T20:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I just realized (probably very belatedly) that all (most?) of the talks from last year's Teardown Conference in Portland, Oregon, are now freely available online! This includes a talk I gave about designing your own breakout board or development board for a microcontroller, which is embedded below. Enjoy!


References:

	
Presentation...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Vale: enforcing style guidelines for text]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964075/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964075/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While programmers are used to having tools to check their code for
stylistic problems, writers often limit automatic checks of their texts to
spelling and, sometimes, grammar, because there are not a lot of options
for further checking. If that is the case, Vale, an 
open-source, command-line tool to enforce editorial-style guidelines, would
make a
useful addition to their toolbox. The recent release of
Vale 3.0 
warrants a look at this versatile tool, which assists writers by
identifying common errors and helping them maintain a consistent voice in their
prose.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964725/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964725/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T15:05:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and yard), Fedora (cpp-jwt, golang-github-tdewolff-argp, golang-github-tdewolff-minify, golang-github-tdewolff-parse, and suricata), Mageia (wpa_supplicant), Oracle (curl, edk2, golang, haproxy, keylime, mysql, openssh, and rear), Red Hat (kernel and postgresql:12), SUSE (containerd, giflib, go1.21, gstreamer-plugins-bad, java-1_8_0-openjdk, python3, python311, python39, sudo, and vim), and Ubuntu (frr, linux, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-iot,
 linux-kvm, linux-raspi, and linux, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-6.5, linux-laptop, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-oem-6.5, linux-oracle, linux-raspi,
 linux-starfive, linux-starfive-6.5).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Give Your Project a Name]]></title>
        <id>3649296</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3649296"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T14:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Large Language Models On-Device with MediaPipe and TensorFlow Lite]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/running-large-language-models-on-device-with-mediapipe-andtensorflow-lite.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/03/running-large-language-models-on-device-with-mediapipe-andtensorflow-lite.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Mark Sherwood – Senior Product Manager and Juhyun Lee – Staff Software Engineer






TensorFlow Lite has been a powerful tool for on-device machine learning since its release in 2017, and MediaPipe further extended that power in 2019 by supporting complete ML pipelines. While these tools initially focused on smaller on-device models, today marks a dramatic shift with the experimental MediaPipe LLM Inference API.
 

This new release enables Large Language Models (LLMs) to run fully on-device across platforms. This new capability is particularly transformative considering the memory and compute demands of LLMs, which are over a hundred times larger than traditional on-device models. Optimizations across the on-device stack make this possible, including new ops, quantization, cachi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[js 템플릿 리터럴을 이용한 템플릿 함수 만들기]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/template-function-using-template-literals-in-js/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/template-function-using-template-literals-in-js/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T11:40:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[블로그를 변경하면서 간단한 템플릿 엔진이 필요했다. 템플릿 엔진을 사용하려고
살펴보니 새 문법을 배우는 것도 번거롭고 정말 작은 부분 때문...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드: undefined</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[북리뷰] 러스트 프로그래밍 공식 가이드(제2판)]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16411090</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16411090"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[서론(러스트를 써야하는 이유)
나는 기본적으로 다양한 프로그래밍 언어에 대해 열려있는 편이다. 대학에서 처음 접한 언어는 C언어였고 2학년때는 C++ 객체지향 프로그래밍을 배웠다. 교양(?) 과목으로 기계과 포트란 프로그래밍도 들었다. 학부를 졸업하고 군에서는 주로 C 및 Java 프로그래밍을 했고, 웹개발(php, javascript)도 병행했다. 군 전역 후에는 보안 분야로 뛰어들면서 주로 파이썬을 사용한 도구 개발을 업무로 하고 있다. 파이썬은 편리함 때문에 여전히 가장 많이 사용하고 있지만, 솔직히 우아한(?) 언어라고는 생각되지 않는다. 나는 개인적으로 컴파일 언어를 더 선호하는 것 같다. 
다른 언어를 더 배우고 싶은 욕심에 2022년에는 Golang을 공부하면서 관련 도서도 번역을 했다. 2023년에는 회사 업무로 iOS 관련 도구를 만들기 위해 Swift를 사용했으나 솔직히 완전한 적응이 어려웠다. 스위프트는 아무래도 앱개발을 주된 목적으로 하기 때문에 내가 하는 시스템 프로그래밍이나 보안 분석 도구 개발에서는 적합한 느낌이 아니었다. 
그러던 중 최근 아래와 같은 기사가 나오고 있다.
https://www.ciokorea.com/news/327256
요약하면, 미국 백악관 국가사이버책임자실(ONCD)은 소프트웨어 개발자들이 C와 C++와 같은 취약한 프로그래밍 언어의 사용을 중단하고, 대신 메모리 안전 프로그래밍 언어(memory-safe programming languages )를 사용하라는 권고를 내린 것이다. 실제로 C/C++ 언어는 언어 설계적으로 해킹에 취약할 수밖에 없는데, 레거시 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 7, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964042/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964042/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T00:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for March 7, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in February (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/february-2024-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/february-2024-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
February.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대통령의 선거 개입, 노무현은 탄핵까지 당했다: 슬로우레터 3월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105066</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105066"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T21:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[박광온과 윤영찬, ‘친명 자객’에 당했다. 감점이 갈랐다. 쟁점과 현안. 국민의힘 공천은 문제 없나. 친윤의 98%가 공천, 보이지 않는 손 있다. 다르게 읽기. 4명 지키던 응급실, 교수 혼자 지킨다. 총선용 의료 대란. 의사들을 굴복시켜서 얻는 게 뭔가. 해법과 대안. 출구전략을 찾아보자. 제주도는 일회용 컵 보증금제 안 버린다. 레지던스를 집이라 해주세요. 더 깊게 읽기. 니키 헤일리 경선...
The post 대통령의 선거 개입, 노무현은 탄핵까지 당했다: 슬로우레터 3월7일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] MySQL and MariaDB changes coming in Fedora 40]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960630/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960630/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T21:02:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fedora Project switched
to MariaDB as the default implementation of MySQL in Fedora 19 in 2013. Once a drop-in
replacement for MySQL, MariaDB has diverged enough that this is no longer
the case—and, despite concerns about Oracle
and optimism that MariaDB would supplant MySQL, the reality is that MySQL
and MariaDB seem to be here to stay. With that in mind, Fedora developer
Michal Schorm
proposed that the project revise the way MySQL and MariaDB
are packaged in Fedora starting with Fedora 40.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parable of null pointer for indolent C programmers]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1107/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1107/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I agree that a memory allocation error with malloc is quite rare case, and after such an error it's most likely that the program can't fully function. But I'm bewildered how programmers persistently...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding systemd to postmarketOS]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964574/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964574/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T20:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The postmarketOS project, which produces
a Linux distribution for phones and mobile devices,
has announced
that it is in the early stages of adding systemd to make it easier to support GNOME and KDE.
Users who prefer the OpenRC
init system are assured they will still have that option when building their own
images "as long as OpenRC is in Alpine Linux (on which postmarketOS is 
based)":
 


As with text editors, some people are really passionate about their favorite init
systems. When discussing this announcement, please keep a friendly tone. Remember
that we all share the love for free and open source software, and that our
communities work best if we focus on shared values instead of fighting over what
implementations to use.


Proof-of-concept images
are available now for a limited set of devices. Users are warned these images are "buggy, 
unreliable, and NOT suitable for use on a device you rely on". Those interested
in helping with testing and development are encouraged to follow along and report
bugs on the systemd
issue at GitLab.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Not so quickly extending QUIC]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964377/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964377/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T18:30:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[QUIC is a UDP-based transport protocol that forms the foundation of
HTTP/3.
It was initially developed at Google in 2012, and became an
IETF standard in
2021. Work on the protocol did not stop with its standardization, however. The
QUIC working group
published several follow-up standards. Now, it is working on
four more extensions to QUIC intended to patch over various shortcomings in the
current protocol — although progress has not been quick.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wednesday's stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964567/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964567/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T17:44:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced another round of stable kernel updates:
6.7.9, 6.6.21,
6.1.81, 5.15.151,
5.10.212, 5.4.271,
and 4.19.309 have all been
released. Each contains a set of important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What if we rotate pairs every day?]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/rotate-pairs-experiment.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/rotate-pairs-experiment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When pair programming, it's important to rotate the pairs frequently, 
       but many organizations that do pair programming are reluctant to do that.
       Gabriel Robaina and Kieran Murphy ask
       the question: “What if we rotate pairs every day?” and worked with three
       teams through an exercise of daily pair rotation. They developed a
       lightweight methodology to help teams reflect on the benefits and
       challenges of pairing and how to solve them. Initial fears were overcome
       and teams discovered the benefits of frequently rotating pairs. They
       learned that pair swapping frequently greatly enhances the benefits of
       pairing. Their article shares the methodology they
       developed, their observations, and some common fears and insights shared
       by the participating team members.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering motor control: synchronization, timing, and software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481606</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mastering-motor-control-synchronization-timing-and-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this next installment of our motor control series, we examine synchronization, timing, RTOS, and motor control software architecture in motor control design. Synchronization and...
The post Mastering motor control: synchronization, timing, and software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Radonic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to monetize the IoT]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481601</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-monetize-the-iot/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T14:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To find your place in the rapidly growing IoT market, it’s important to take a fresh look at traditional IoT business models, as well as...
The post How to monetize the IoT appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Julia Seredovich</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964559/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964559/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T13:49:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libapache2-mod-auth-openidc, libuv1, php-phpseclib, and phpseclib), Red Hat (buildah, cups, curl, device-mapper-multipath, emacs, fence-agents, frr, fwupd, gmp, gnutls, golang, haproxy, keylime, libfastjson, libmicrohttpd, linux-firmware, mysql, openssh, rear, skopeo, sqlite, squid, systemd, and tomcat), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (kernel-firmware-nvidia-gspx-G06, nvidia-open- driver-G06-signed, postgresql-jdbc, python, python-cryptography, rubygem-rack, wpa_supplicant, and xmlgraphics-batik), and Ubuntu (c-ares, firefox, libde265, libgit2, and ruby-image-processing).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[경합지 잡긴 잡아야 하는데… 바이든의 딜레마, 돌파구 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78823</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/03/06/npsp_michiganevchina/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_michiganevchina"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T13:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미시건주는 올해 대선에서 가장 치열한 경합주가 될 것으로 꼽히고 있습니다. 본선에 앞서 각 당의 후보를 뽑는 경선을 미시건주는 지난달 2월 27일 치렀는데, 미시건에 모여 사는 아랍계 유권자들이 조 바이든 대통령에 대한 불만을 표로 표출해 주목을 받기도 했습니다. 그런데 또 다른 변수가 있습니다. 바로 양산 체제에 돌입해 곧 미국에도 수출될 것으로 보이는 중국산 전기자동차 BYD입니다. 가성비 측면에서 미국산 전기차와 비교할 수 없을 만큼 뛰어난 중국산 전기차가 시장을 장악하면 전미자동차노조(UAW)의 핵심 거점이라 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The life of an Ollama prompt]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/the-life-of-an-ollama-prompt/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/the-life-of-an-ollama-prompt/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T13:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In <a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/gemma-ollama-and-langchaingo/">a previous post</a>
I've described how - thanks to standardized tooling - we
could use a locally-running <a class="reference external" href="https://blog.google/technology/developers/gemma-open-models/">Gemma model</a>
from a Go program within hours from its public release.</p>
<p>This post dives into the internals of <a class="reference external" href="https://ollama.com/">Ollama</a> -
a popular and extremely convenient open-source Go project that makes such
workflows possible.</p>
<img alt="Mechanical llama being taken apart" class="align-center" src="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/images/2024/mllama.png" />
<div class="section" id="http-request-to-ollama">
<h2>HTTP …</h2></div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Numerous vulnerabilities in Xunlei Accelerator application]]></title>
        <id>https://palant.info/2024/03/06/numerous-vulnerabilities-in-xunlei-accelerator-application/</id>
        <link href="https://palant.info/2024/03/06/numerous-vulnerabilities-in-xunlei-accelerator-application/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T13:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Xunlei Accelerator (迅雷客户端) a.k.a. Xunlei Thunder by the China-based Xunlei Ltd. is a wildly popular application. According to the company’s annual report 51.1 million active users were counted in December 2022. The company’s Google Chrome extension 迅雷下载支持, while not mandatory for using the application, had 28 million users at the time of writing.


I’ve found this application to expose a massive attack surface. This attack surface is largely accessible to arbitrary websites that an application user happens to be visiting. Some of it can also be accessed from other computers in the same network or by attackers with the ability to intercept user’s network connections (Man-in-the-Middle attack).
It does not appear like security concerns were considered in the design of this application. Exten…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Almost Secure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Open Access to Guarded Trust]]></title>
        <id>3649305</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3649305"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T10:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한국 사법의 흑역사 추가요! 바이든/날리면 1심 판결]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105050</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105050"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[참여연대 사법감시센터 ‘광장에 나온 판결’] ‘바이든/날리면’ 정정보도 사건. 당사자 대통령 대신 외교부 앞장세워 언론사 상대 소송? 판결까지 상식 밖! 대통령의 2022년 바이든/날리면 막말 논란 이후, 외교부가 MBC 보도에 대해서 정정보도를 청구하였고, 그 취지는 MBC가 해당 보도영상에 “바이든은 쪽팔려서 어떡하나?”라고 자막을 기재한 부분이 허위라는 것이었다. 약 14개월 만에 나온 1심 판결은 매우 놀랍게도(!!) 원고 외교부의 정정보도를...
The post 한국 사법의 흑역사 추가요! 바이든/날리면 1심 판결 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Helm charts to deploy Data Grid on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>943a04bc-c495-44d4-8d18-f5a5117198d6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/03/06/how-use-helm-charts-deploy-data-grid-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Red Hat OpenShift 4.x, the Operator framework became a fundamental part of the daily cluster operations, and we explain the Data Grid Operator in this Data Grid Operator installation article.
The Data Grid Operator provides an easy and straightforward method for deploying a Red Hat Data Grid server. Once the Data Grid is deployed it can include features such as cross-site and JVM settings, which are set via the Custom Resources (CRs) consumed by the Data Grid Operator to build the Data Grid server.
[ Learning path: Cross site and cross applications with Red Hat OpenShift and Red Hat Data Grid ]
Another supported approach for deploying Data Grid in Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform (RHOCP) 4 is via the use of Helm charts, where the user installs the charts and passes a value YAML file…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior, Alexander Barbosa Ayala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민주당 ‘공천’ 보도 국힘보다 2.5배 많았다: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 분석 (2월 넷째 주)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105028</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105028"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T02:34:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요약 주요 이슈 1. 총선보도 3건 중 1건은 민주당 공천 논란 2. 민주당 공천보도, 노출시간 보도건수 앞질러 3. 민주당 ‘공천 파동’ 프레임 4. 국민의힘 공천 결과 단순중계 방식 ※재명당: 한동훈 비대위원장이 이재명 더불어민주당 대표의 이름을 빌려 ‘재명당’으로 언급하자 언론이 이를 받아쓰기하면서 이슈로 부상함. 5. 윤석열 대통령 총선용 활동 부각 6. 기타 언론사별 주요 이슈 1....
The post 민주당 ‘공천’ 보도 국힘보다 2.5배 많았다: 2024 총선 포털뉴스 분석 (2월 넷째 주) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스,차트로 살펴본 23년 4분기 실적 시즌 결산]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594098</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594098/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%8b%9c%ec%a6%8c-%ea%b2%b0%ec%82%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T01:36:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3/6, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594093</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594093/3-6-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T00:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[건생구팽, 김건희 특검법 끝나자 컷오프가 시작됐다: 슬로우레터 3월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=105001</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/105001"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T21:53:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[건생구팽, 김건희 특검법 끝나자 컷오프가 시작됐다. 조국혁신당 돌풍, 10석 이상도 가능하다. 이재명과 조국의 선거연대. 위성정당 비례만 두 번째, 용혜인 논란. 쟁점과 현안. 의대 증원 신청 3401명. 청년도 여성도 없었다. 다르게 읽기. “내 측근 누가 공천을 받았나.” 수도권과 충청이 스윙 보터. 민주당 호남 민심 이탈도 심상찮다. 더 깊게 읽기. 30대 그룹 사외이사 10명 중 4명이 전관....
The post 건생구팽, 김건희 특검법 끝나자 컷오프가 시작됐다: 슬로우레터 3월6일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patterns of Legacy Displacement: Event Interception]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-legacy-displacement/event-interception.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/patterns-legacy-displacement/event-interception.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When we gradually replace a legacy system, we have plenty of cases
       where the legacy system and its replacement need to interact. Since these
       legacy systems are often difficult, and costly, to change, we need a
       mechanism that can integrate elements of the replacement while minimizing
       the impact to the legacy system. Ian Cartwright, Rob Horn, and
       James Lewis explain how we can use Event Interception on
       state-changing events, allowing us to forward them to the
       replacement.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Formalizing policy zones for memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964239/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964239/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T12:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's memory-management subsystem is built on the concept of
"zones", which were initially added to describe the physical
characteristics of the memory pages contained within them.  Over time,
zones have taken on more of a policy-related role as well.  With a patch
set called THP
allocator optimizations, Yu Zhao has set out to better define the role
of policy-related zones on the path toward adding two more of them, with
the ultimate purpose of improving the kernel's support for transparent huge
pages (THPs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/964450/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/964450/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T12:48:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (yard), Oracle (buildah and kernel), Red Hat (389-ds:1.4, edk2, frr, gnutls, haproxy, libfastjson, libX11, postgresql:12, sqlite, squid, squid:4, tcpdump, and tomcat), SUSE (apache2-mod_auth_openidc and glibc), and Ubuntu (linux-gke, python-cryptography, and python-django).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[바클레이즈, AMD가 엔비디아를 추격하면서 인공지능 칩 매출이 크게 증가 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594088</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594088/amd-%ec%9d%b8%ea%b3%b5%ec%a7%80%eb%8a%a5-%ec%b9%a9-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T12:03:16.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>