<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-08-04T20:14:41.967Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 아마존 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595820</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595820/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T00:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enum class improvements for C++17, C++20 and C++23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/enum-improvements/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/enum-improvements/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The evolution of the C++ language continues to bring powerful features that enhance code safety, readability, and maintainability. Among these improvements, we got changes and additions to enum class functionalities across C++17, C++20, and C++23. In this blog post, we’ll explore these advancements, focusing on initialization improvements in C++17, the introduction of the using enum keyword in C++20, and the std::to_underlying utility in C++23.
Let’s go.



     
    


Before diving into the enhancements, let’s briefly recap what enum class is. An enum class (scoped enumeration) provides a type-safe way of defining a set of named constants. Unlike traditional (unscoped) enums, enum class does not implicitly convert to integers or other types, preventing accidental misuse. Here’s a basic e…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three stable kernel updates for Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984448/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984448/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T13:41:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10.3, 6.6.44, and 6.1.103 stable kernel updates have all been released. As usual, they
contain important fixes throughout the tree. Users of those kernels
should upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 미국이 자칫하면 ‘한국 꼴’ 될 수 있다고? 달갑지 않은 최신 ‘K-트렌드’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79498</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/02/npsp_birthrategendernorm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_birthrategendernorm"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T22:59:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 10일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 일찌감치 산업화를 달성한 서구의 많은 나라와 소위 선진국에서 사람들이 아이를 낳지 않아 인구가 정체되는 건 새로운 현상이 아닙니다. 미국의 사정도 다르지 않습니다. 미국 질병통제예방센터는 지난 4월 2023년 출산 통계를 발표하며, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Divvi Up: privacy-respecting telemetry aggregation]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983843/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983843/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T13:13:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is ongoing discussion about the ethics and effectiveness of
telemetry following some recent LWN articles that touched on

Thunderbird's use of opt-out
telemetry and planned metrics in Fedora. The

Internet Security Research Group (ISRG), the nonprofit behind

Let's Encrypt, has a potential solution to the problem of how to collect and
aggregate telemetry without violating users' privacy. The scheme is based on a
draft
protocol being standardized with the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF),
and has an
open-source implementation
available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984370/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984370/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T13:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium), SUSE (docker and patch), and Ubuntu (bind9, gross, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, and tomcat8, tomcat9).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이진숙 ‘2인 체제’ 방송 장악 속도전, 엄호 나선 조선∙경제지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113321</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113321"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T01:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 대통령은 7월 31일 이진숙 방송통신위원장 임명을 강행했습니다. 국회 인사청문회 과정에서 부적절한 법인카드 유용과 극우·편향적 발언, 노조탄압, 사회적 참사 공감능력 결여 등 공직자 후보로서 부적격한 사유가 차고 넘쳤음에도 윤 대통령은 보고서 채택이 불발된 후보자를 방송통신위원장으로 임명했는데요. 이진숙 방송통신위원장은 대통령실 임명발표가 나기도 전에 통상적인 임명장 수여식과 현충원 참배도 생략한 채 정부과천청사로 출근했습니다. 이후 같은 날 임명된...
The post 이진숙 ‘2인 체제’ 방송 장악 속도전, 엄호 나선 조선∙경제지 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지금 민주당과 해리스의 최우선 과제?… “두 마리 토끼 쫓는 셈”]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79766</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/08/01/npsp_harrisvtrump/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_harrisvtrump"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T01:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[바이든 대통령이 재선에 도전하지 않기로 하면서 카멀라 해리스 부통령 지지를 선언했고, 해리스는 바이든 캠페인을 이어받아 빠르게 민주당 내 지지를 규합하고 트럼프 전 대통령과의 일전을 준비하고 있습니다. 해리스의 등판 이후 부진을 면치 못하던 민주당은 빠르게 지지율을 회복했습니다. 바이든을 상대하는 한 선거에서 대승을 거둘 수도 있다고 본 공화당 일각의 기대는 물거품이 됐습니다. 참패가 예상되던 선거를 다시 박빙, 접전으로 돌려놓긴 했지만, 해리스는 과연 트럼프를 넘어설 수 있을까요? 이에 대해 책 “정의란 무엇인가”로 한국에는 특히 잘 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동아일보의 경고, “윤석열, 가장 무능한 대통령으로 남을 수도”: 슬로우레터 8월2일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113290</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113290"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T22:19:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이진숙의 3일 방통위. 쟁점과 현안. 25만 원 민생 지원금법도 필리버스터 돌입. “분열 막기 위해 그만둔다.” 세금을 안 걷나, 못 걷나, 예측을 잘못했나. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘킹 달러’의 퇴장, 9월 금리 인하 가능성. 한국도 10월 인하? 가계 빚이 변수다. 환율 착시 효과. 미국 금리는 트럼프가 변수. ‘슈퍼 엔저’가 끝났나. 이란 보복 공격 카운트 다운. 다르게 읽기....
The post 동아일보의 경고, “윤석열, 가장 무능한 대통령으로 남을 수도”: 슬로우레터 8월2일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[.NET Digest #2]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1148/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1148/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to our second news and event digest for the .NET world! The first digest resonated with you, so the PVS-Studio C# team has gathered the most awesome and handy insights for you again. Let's...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write Better Code with Block Diagrams and Flowcharts]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1685.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1685.php"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:33:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Contents

	
Introduction

	
Software block diagrams
	

		
What is it?

		
How do I draw one?

		
Implementing a block diagram in code

		
Ready for a small challenge?

	

	
Flowcharts
	

		
What is it?

		
How do I draw one?

		
Implementing a flowchart in...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use GNU Coverage (gcov) in a Freestanding Environment for Embedded Systems]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40990</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/08/01/how-to-use-gnu-coverage-gcov-in-a-freestanding-environment-for-embedded-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T18:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNU Coverage (gcov) tool is a part of the GNU gcc suite and is commonly used in hosted environments like Linux or Windows. However, it can also be utilized in embedded systems without a debugger, semihosting, or file I/O. This article provides a detailed guide on setting up a freestanding environment to collect gcov data, improving performance and enabling flexible data collection. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sovereign Tech Fund introduces fellowship pilot program]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984266/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984266/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T15:31:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Sovereign Tech Fund (STF) has announced
a fellowship program to support "the dedicated individuals who keep
our digital infrastructure running":
According to the fellowship
page the STF plans to fund five fellowships, beginning in the
fourth quarter of this year, for a period of 12 months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Maximal min() and max()]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983965/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983965/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:28:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like many projects written in C, the kernel makes extensive use of the C
preprocessor; indeed, the kernel's use is rather more extensive than most.
The preprocessor famously has a number of sharp edges associated with it.
One might not normally think of increased compilation time as one of them,
though.  It turns out that some changes to a couple of conceptually simple
preprocessor macros — min() and max() — led to some truly
pathological, but hidden, behavior where those macros were used.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mel Chua RIP]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984213/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984213/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:39:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have received the
sad news that Dr. Mel Chua has passed away. Mel was probably best
known in the free-software community as a contributor to the Fedora
Project in its early days. The Fedora Community blog honored
Mel recently after she had moved to hospice care with tributes
from several Fedorans. Stephen Jacobs wrote:
Mel will be greatly missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984212/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984212/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (kernel, obs-cef, and xen), Mageia (emacs), Oracle (freeradius, freeradius:3.0, and kernel), Red Hat (emacs, httpd, and kpatch-patch-4_18_0-305_120_1), Slackware (curl), SUSE (apache2, cockpit-wicked, glibc, gnutls, gvfs, less, nghttp2, opensc, python-idna, python-requests, qemu, rpm, tpm2-0-tss, tpm2.0-tools, and unbound), and Ubuntu (clickhouse, exim4, libcommons-collections3-java, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, mysql-8.0, openssl, php-cas, prometheus-alertmanager, and snapd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Command — Response Framework in ESP RainMaker]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/5e8273db7d22</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/command-response-framework-in-esp-rainmaker-5e8273db7d22?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T10:19:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 release candidate 1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/08/python-3130-release-candidate-1-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/08/python-3130-release-candidate-1-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T09:30:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.13 release candidate 1.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130rc1/
 
This is the first release candidate of Python 3.13.0
This release, 3.13.0rc1, is the penultimate release 
preview. Entering the release candidate phase, only reviewed code 
changes which are clear bug fixes are allowed between this release 
candidate and the final release. The second candidate (and the last 
planned release preview) is scheduled for Tuesday, 2024-09-03, while the
 official release of 3.13.0 is scheduled for Tuesday, 2024-10-01.
There will be no ABI changes from this point forward in the 3.13 series, and the goal is that there will be as few code changes as possible.
Call to action
We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open source AI coding assistance with the Granite models]]></title>
        <id>ae9ecad3-fa26-4c36-b0c7-13f072dfbb10</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/01/open-source-ai-coding-assistance-granite-models"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As developers, we're always looking for ways to be more productive and write higher-quality code. While tools like GitHub Copilot have gained popularity as AI pair programmers, the downside is they run on closed models and you might have to pay a subscription to use them. Imagine instead being able to use state-of-the-art free AI coding assistants right on your local machine using powerful open source models, with auto-completions and confidence that your data stays private! 
Let’s take a look at how to integrate an AI code assistant into your IDE using a combination of open source tools, including Continue (an extension for VS Code and JetBrains), Ollama or InstructLab as a local model server, and the Granite family of code models to supercharge your development workflow without any cost …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Clyburn</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrustyAI Detoxify: Guardrailing LLMs during training]]></title>
        <id>4b523a23-28b5-4e53-bd32-45d5e56a8702</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/01/trustyai-detoxify-guardrailing-llms-during-training"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Detoxifying or preventing toxic content generation from large language models (LLMs) is challenging. Data used to train these models is usually scraped from the internet which often contains toxic content. Without proper guardrails, a model can learn undesirable properties and in turn, generate toxic text. Removing toxic samples from training data can be expensive as it usually requires data annotators to manually identify samples that align with human values. Inherent bias in the annotators themselves can also affect the data labeling process in a negative way. By using the open source project TrustyAI Detoxify in conjunction with Hugging Face's SFTTrainer (Supervised Fine-Tuning Trainer) on Red Hat OpenShift AI, we can help lower the costs of detoxifying LLMs during training. 
In this ar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christina Xu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Minimize downtime when migrating from VMware to OpenShift Virtualization]]></title>
        <id>8f690152-28e1-42b3-9eb4-d084ae1e9055</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/08/01/minimize-downtime-when-migrating-vmware-openshift-virtualization"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Gartner, despite the growing trend towards cloud migration and container adoption, a significant portion of datacenter x86 workloads will remain hypervisor-based virtualization through 2027, albeit reduced from previous years. See this e-book for more information on this topic. Managing a hybrid infrastructure that includes both hypervisor-based virtual machines and Kubernetes clusters can be a daunting task.
For platform teams, the challenge lies in efficiently managing diverse environments while optimizing existing investments. Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization offers a compelling solution by allowing organizations to run both virtual machines (VMs) and containers on a single, unified platform. This enables them to have a platform that addresses their current needs while also…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vamsi Ravula</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 1, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983267/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983267/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T04:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for August 1, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8/1, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595812</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595812/8-1-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T02:16:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions for STM32CubeIDE]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/github-actions-for-stm32cubeide</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/github-actions-for-stm32cubeide"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will explore how to use GitHub Actions to automate building
STM32CubeIDE projects. Eclipse-based IDEs like STM32CubeIDE are often used for
developing embedded systems but can be a little tricky to build in a headless
environment.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving _Generic in C2y]]></title>
        <id>https://thephd.dev/improving-_generic-in-c2y</id>
        <link href="https://thephd.dev/improving-_generic-in-c2y"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The first two meetings of C after C23 was finalized are over, and we have started working on C2y. We decided that this cycle we’re not going to do that “Bugfix” followed by “Release” stuff, because that proved to be a REALLY bad idea that killed a ton of momentum and active contributors during the C11 to C17 timeframe. So, this time, we’re hitting both bugfixes AND features so we can make sure we don’t lose valuable contributions and fixes by stalling for 5 to 6 years again. So, with that…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Pasture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“한동훈 나오면 이재명이 된다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 8월1일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113206</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113206"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T22:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이스마일 하니야 암살. 김문수가 돌아왔다. 취임 첫날 이진숙이 한 일. 탄핵과 사퇴 무한 반복. 이동관이 돌아온다고? 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈의 ‘마이웨이.’ 정점식을 갈아치우려 하는 이유. 윤석열-한동훈 미팅 뒷이야기. 더 깊게 읽기. 한동훈은 퇴로가 없다. 민주당이 한동훈 제안을 받는다면? “한동훈 나오면 이재명이 된다.” 다르게 읽기. 티메프가 드러낸 그림자 금융. 스타벅스 선불 충전금 3000억 원. 3일 정산, 네이버는...
The post “한동훈 나오면 이재명이 된다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 8월1일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A deprecation timeline for older Arm CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984143/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984143/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arnd Bergmann has posted a
detailed timeline for the deprecation of support for old Arm CPUs in
both the kernel and the compiler toolchain.  Anybody who is working with
that hardware will likely want to review this list and let the relevant
developers know if any of that support is still needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro and 1.5 Flash GA, 1.5 Flash tuning support, higher rate limits, and more API updates]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:14:19.665Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re incredibly excited to see what you build with these new models. Get started with Gemini 1.5 Flash and 1.5 Pro free of charge in Google AI Studio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smaller, Safer, More Transparent: Advancing Responsible AI with Gemma]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/smaller-safer-more-transparent-advancing-responsible-ai-with-gemma/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/smaller-safer-more-transparent-advancing-responsible-ai-with-gemma/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:14:19.664Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ShieldGemma is a suite of safety content classifiers models built upon Gemma2 designed to keep users safe. GemmaScope is a new model interpretability tool that offers unparalleled insight into our models' inner workings.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Refresh of the PoEAA catalog page]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-eaa-catalog-refresh.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-eaa-catalog-refresh.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T20:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From time to time I take a look at my site analytics to see how much traffic various bits of this site get. When doing this I saw that I continue to get a lot of traffic to the Catalog of Patterns of Enterprise Application Architecture. I put this together not long after writing the book, and it’s rather minimal. Since it still gets traffic I felt it was time for some sprucing up. The content is the same, summaries of the patterns in the book. I’ve changed the main catalog page to include the pattern intents. I’ve also added deep links to the book on oreilly.com, so if you have a subscription to that, it will jump directly to that text. Hopefully these changes will make the catalog page a bit more useful.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2022-2023 Quarterly Discussion Panel Archives]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=42412</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2024/07/31/2022-2023-quarterly-discussion-panel-archives/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T19:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[31 July 2024 by Phillip JohnstonDuring 2022-2023, Embedded Artistry and Memfault teamed up to run a series of embedded-focused discussion panels. These discussion panels were rich with insight and advice for embedded teams. Even if you missed the live broadcasts, we hope you will take time to watch the recordings. Building Embedded Systems at Scale … 
Continue reading "2022-2023 Quarterly Discussion Panel Archives"
The post 2022-2023 Quarterly Discussion Panel Archives appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deep list copy: More than meets the eye]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/07/31/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/07/31/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T18:49:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently came across a take-home C programming test which had more depth
and complexity than I suspect the interviewer intended. While considering
it, I also came up with a novel, or at least unconventional, solution. The
problem is to deep copy a linked list where each node references a random
list element in addition to usual linkage — similar to LeetCode problem
138. This reference is one of identity rather than value, which has
murky consequences.

typedef struct node node;
struct node {
    node *next;
    node *ref;   // arbitrary node in the list, or null
};

node *deepcopy(node *);


In the copy, nodes have individual lifetimes allocated using malloc
which the caller is responsible for freeing. While thickheaded, this
is conventional, and I cannot blame the test’s designer for st…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vanilla OS 2 "Orchid" released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984117/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984117/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T18:13:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.0 of the Vanilla OS image-based Linux distribution has
been released. Dubbed
"Orchid", Vanilla OS is now based on Debian Sid (prior versions were Ubuntu-based),
allows creation
of customized Linux environments, support for running Android
applications using Waydroid, and many other improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Showing up for Python in GNOME]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983897/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983897/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few years ago, PyGObject—the Python
package that provides bindings for GTK and GNOME applications—was not
faring particularly well. Several maintainers had left the project and its
development was not keeping pace with changes in GTK. At this year's
GUADEC, Dan Yeaw presented a talk
about the project's decline, improvements in the last year, and his
experience getting involved in an undermaintained project.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Poor roads, money, and cybercriminals: why sci-fi cars are not here yet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490505</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/poor-roads-money-and-cybercriminals-why-sci-fi-cars-are-not-here-yet/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T17:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The flying taxis with smart assistants from the Fifth Element, a stunning Audi RSQ, custom built by Audi for I, Robot, and the Lexus 2054 with advanced biometric systems and automatic driving mode from Minority Report: it seems automakers from around the world are racing to be the first to make these dreams come true. While such advanced hi-tech vehicles have […]
The post Poor roads, money, and cybercriminals: why sci-fi cars are not here yet appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Forgejo v8.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984116/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984116/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T15:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.0 of the Forgejo
software-development platform has been released. Notable
changes include the removal
of non-free software found in the codebase, improved stability, and a
reduction
in "seemingly random User Interface changes":
See the release
notes for a full list of changes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배롱나무 명소, 물놀이 계곡을 즐기기 좋은 밀양 표충사 베롱나무]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595796</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595796/%eb%b0%80%ec%96%91-%ed%91%9c%ec%b6%a9%ec%82%ac-%eb%b0%b0%eb%a1%b1%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Pulling Linux up by its bootstraps]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983340/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983340/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T13:18:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 
bootstrappable build is one that builds existing
software from scratch — for example, building GCC without relying on an existing
copy of GCC. In 2023, the Guix project
announced that the project had reduced the size
of the binary bootstrap seed needed to build its operating system to just 357-bytes —
not counting the Linux kernel required to run the build process. Now, the
live-bootstrap project
has gone a step further and removed the need for an existing kernel at all.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/984080/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/984080/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T13:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (xdg-desktop-portal-hyprland), Red Hat (freeradius, freeradius:3.0, git-lfs, httpd, kernel, openssh, and varnish:6), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, cont, git, gtk2, gtk3, kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-exportproxy-container, virt-exportserver-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-t, orc, postgresql14, python-dnspython, python-urllib3, shadow, and xen), and Ubuntu (openjdk-17, openjdk-21, openjdk-8, openjdk-lts, and python3.10, python3.8).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A software-connected approach to automated post-silicon device validation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490486</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/a-software-connected-approach-to-automated-post-silicon-device-validation/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T12:50:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amidst the many disruptions faced by the global semiconductor industry, the relentless pursuit of higher performance silicon to power the ever-evolving landscape of modern technology has only increased. While Covid-19 underscored the vulnerability of the semiconductor supply chain, the demand for innovative silicon remains steadfast, driving continual advancements in product development . For semiconductor organizations […]
The post A software-connected approach to automated post-silicon device validation appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alphawave Semi launches 3nm UCIe IP for chiplet ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490482</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/alphawave-semi-launches-3nm-ucie-ip-for-chiplet-ecosystem/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T11:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alphawave Semi said it has launched the industry’s first successful silicon bring-up of Universal Chiplet Interconnect Express (UCIe) die-to-die (D2D) IP with TSMC’s 3nm chip-on-wafer-on-substrate (CoWoS) advanced packaging technology. The complete PHY and controller subsystem was developed in collaboration with TSMC and targets applications such as hyperscaler, high-performance computing (HPC) and artificial intelligence (AI). Using […]
The post Alphawave Semi launches 3nm UCIe IP for chiplet ecosystem appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debian derivative eLxr addresses simplifies and enhance edge-to-cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490476</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/debian-derivative-elxr-addresses-simplifies-and-enhance-edge-to-cloud/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new community-driven open source project based on a derivative of Debian and designed to deliver enterprise-grade Linux for edge-to-cloud deployments has launched its first release. The eLxr project, spearheaded by Wind River and supported by AWS, Intel, Supermicro, SAIC, and Capgemini, is an enterprise-grade Linux distribution that addresses the challenges of near-edge networks and […]
The post Debian derivative eLxr addresses simplifies and enhance edge-to-cloud appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily expanding Red Hat OpenShift clusters]]></title>
        <id>e6d51a6d-803f-45f4-bfec-27f5d25a97bb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/31/easily-expanding-red-hat-openshift-clusters"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding nodes to Red Hat OpenShift clusters on-premises is a laborious and sometimes complex endeavor. With various methods available, each with different levels of automation, users often find themselves navigating through complex and even unsupported solutions, leading to a less-than-ideal user experience. 
A new feature is now available as a Developer Preview in OpenShift 4.16, that makes cluster expansions faster, simpler, and more user-friendly than ever before.
This new method leverages the Agent Based Installer technology under the hood, but doesn’t need the cluster to have been installed by it, it will work on any cluster where its nodes can be installed from an ISO image.
It first gets information of the cluster to be expanded, then it provides a bootable ISO image, and after booti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ramon Acedo Rodriguez</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation for developers and data scientists]]></title>
        <id>11ed32d2-2b95-4194-aa59-1f3bb41441b5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/31/red-hat-openshift-data-foundation-developers-and-data-scientists"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you develop applications with a cloud-first mindset, you probably use (or plan to use) object storage with the S3 API from Amazon Web Services (AWS). Even if you do not use AWS, all large and smaller public cloud providers offer object storage compatible with the S3 API.
If you plan to work with artificial intelligence (AI), most AI tools require S3 storage to store data from models, training, and tuning, besides the raw data on which AI models make inferences and the results of such inferences.
But, if you have to work on premises, or have to create applications which must work both on premises and on cloud, you require something that provides an S3-compatible API outside of cloud providers. Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation is a nice alternative proven to support large scale deploymen…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Fernando Lozano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[강릉여행, 활래정과 둘레길이 아름다웟던 강릉 선교장 방문기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595782</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595782/%ea%b0%95%eb%a6%89%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89-%ed%99%9c%eb%9e%98%ec%a0%95%ea%b3%bc-%eb%91%98%eb%a0%88%ea%b8%b8%ec%9d%b4-%ec%95%84%eb%a6%84%eb%8b%a4%ec%9b%9f%eb%8d%98-%ea%b0%95%eb%a6%89-%ec%84%a0%ea%b5%90"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T06:18:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/31, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595784</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595784/7-31-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T06:04:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘억만장자들만의 세상’, 이제는 대놓고 펼쳐진다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79483</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/30/npsp_buylongerlife/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_buylongerlife"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T22:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 5일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 불로초를 찾으려 했던 진시황의 이야기는 다들 잘 아실 겁니다. 굳이 진시황이 아니라도 인류 역사에 이름을 남긴 권력자 가운데는 다시 젊어지려고 애쓴 사람이 많습니다. 그게 어렵다면 늙지 않는 비결을 찾아 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“용산이 괘씸하게 보고 있다”, 마약 수사 외압 사건 또 터진다: 슬로우레터 7월31일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113137</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113137"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T22:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[디올 백 알고도 신고 안 했다. 김건희 벙커? 제2부속실로 생색내기. 쟁점과 현안. 800억 원밖에 없다. 공정위는 몰랐다. 얼마가 부족한지도 몰랐다. 더 깊게 읽기. 5박6일 필리버스터 종료, 방송4법 국회 통과. 이진숙 프로젝트 속도전. 필리버스터+거부권+재의결 부결 3종 세트. “용산이 괘씸하게 보고 있다.” 다르게 읽기. 도청‧미행 당할 거 몰랐나. 댐 만들어 기후 대응한다고? 골칫덩어리 영주댐 잊었나. 해법과 대안....
The post “용산이 괘씸하게 보고 있다”, 마약 수사 외압 사건 또 터진다: 슬로우레터 7월31일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building static binaries with Go on Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/building-static-binaries-with-go-on-linux/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/building-static-binaries-with-go-on-linux/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>One of Go's advantages is being able to produce statically-linked
binaries <a class="footnote-reference" href="#footnote-1" id="footnote-reference-1">[1]</a>. This doesn't mean that Go always produces such binaries by default,
however; in some scenarios it requires extra work to make this happen.
Specifics here are OS-dependent; here we focus on Unix systems.</p>
<div class="section" id="basics-hello-world">
<h2>Basics - hello world</h2>
<p>This post …</p></div>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Famfs: a filesystem interface to shareable memory]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983105/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983105/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the 2024 Linux
Storage, Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, John Groves led
a session on famfs, which is a filesystem he has developed that uses the
kernel's direct-access (DAX)
mechanism to access memory that is shareable between hosts.  The discussion
was aimed at whether a different approach should be taken and, in
particular, whether FUSE should be used instead of implementing as an
in-kernel filesystem.  As noted in the thread about his
proposal for an LSFMM+BPF session, and the mailing-list discussions on the first and second
version of his patch set, there is some skepticism that a new in-kernel
filesystem is warranted for the use case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Search query for bugs in Apache Solr]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1147/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1147/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, we're checking the Apache product. This time we chose Solr, an open-source search server platform. Solr enables you quickly and efficiently search for information in databases and online...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API for Custom LLMs on Device]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:13:36.471Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API enables developers to bring powerful new capabilities on-device, such as summarization, content generation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Google Pay at I/O 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T20:13:36.471Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re adding new features to Google Pay so you can offer richer and more accessible payment experiences for your customers, and improved APIs to simplify your payments integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Funtoo Linux is being discontinued]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983977/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983977/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T17:10:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Daniel Robbins, founder of the Gentoo Linux distribution and its
spinoff Funtoo Linux, has
announced
that he has decided to end the Funtoo project:
Funtoo
container, it will continue to be online through the end of August
so you have time to find another hosting solution if you need one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing Ansible plug-ins for Red Hat Developer Hub]]></title>
        <id>1ef09165-659e-4bc1-81e6-09ab9d398e39</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/30/announcing-ansible-plug-ins-red-hat-developer-hub"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T16:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Developer Hub is an enterprise-grade internal developer portal (IDP). It allows platform engineering teams to offer software templates based on your best practices to maximize developer skills, ease onboarding, increase development productivity, and focus on writing great code by reducing friction and frustration for development teams.
Red Hat is constantly curating a set of plug-ins and ensuring the best experience on Red Hat Developer Hub. Red Hat supported and validated  plug-ins let you extend the Red Hat Developer Hub environment with confidence, eliminating compatibility and operational issues.
As part of these efforts, we are pleased to announce Technology Preview of Ansible plug-ins for Red Hat Developer Hub. With Ansible plug-ins, organizations using Red Hat Developer Hub …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Himanshu Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of restricting AI and algorithms, make them explainable]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-restrict-algorithm.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-restrict-algorithm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The steady increase in deployment of AI tools has led a lot of people concerned about how software makes decisions that affect our lives. In one example, its about “algorithmic” feeds in social media that promote posts that drive engagement. A more serious impact can come from business decisions, such as how much premium to charge in car insurance. This can extend to affecting legal decisions, such as suggesting sentencing guidelines to judges.
Faced with these concerns, there is often a movement to restrict the use of algorithms, such as a recent activity in New York to restrict how social media networks generate feeds for children. Should we draw up more laws to fence in the rampaging algorithms?
In my view, the restricting the use of algorithms and AI here isn’t the right target. A regu…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Report from the annual general meeting at GUADEC]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983203/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983203/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At GUADEC
in Denver, Colorado on July 21, the GNOME Foundation held its annual
general meeting (AGM) to provide updates from the foundation's board and committees.
Topics included work accomplished in the past year, challenges
facing the GNOME Foundation–including fundraising and finding a new
executive director–and some insight into plans for the next year. And
last, but not least, the awarding of the Pants of Thanks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983935/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983935/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (curl), Mageia (virtualbox), Oracle (squid), Red Hat (kernel), SUSE (apache2, bind, cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, devscripts, espeak-ng, freerdp, ghostscript, gnome-shell, gtk2, gtk3, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, kubevirt, libgit2, openssl-3, orc, p7zip, python-dnspython, and shadow), and Ubuntu (kernel, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-ibm, linux-nvidia, linux-oem-6.8, linux-raspi, linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-raspi, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-aws-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-raspi, linux-gcp-5.15, and linux-lowlatency).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secure boot with auto-signing in ESP RainMaker OTA]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/d1a2e1161059</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/secure-boot-with-auto-signing-in-esp-rainmaker-ota-d1a2e1161059?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Piyush Shah</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How multi-sensory data enhances advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4490453</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-multi-sensory-data-enhances-advanced-driver-assistance-systems-adas/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T09:37:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cars have become intelligent, manufacturers have focused on implementing certain smart features at the expense of others. Sensors tied to rear view cameras and blind spot warnings are now nearly ubiquitous, but other safety tools have lagged behind. This is delaying the progress of advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS), a suite of technologies that […]
The post How multi-sensory data enhances advanced driver assistance systems (ADAS) appeared first on Embedded.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8월 여행 추천, 아름다운 배롱나무 명소 추천]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595747</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595747/8%ec%9b%94-%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89-%eb%b0%b0%eb%a1%b1%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4-%eb%aa%85%ec%86%8c-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T08:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조인트 까면서 좌파 대청소, 뭐가 달라졌나.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113098</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113098"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T07:37:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 한상진이 “차라리 김우룡이 그립다”고 말하는 이유. 이진숙(방송통신위원회 위원장 후보)의 청문회를 지켜보면서 많은 사람들이 불쾌한 기시감을 느끼고 있다. 이동관(전 방통위원장)이 가고 김홍일(전 방통위원장)이 가니 이진숙이 왔다. 지금까지 그랬듯이 청문보고서가 채택되거나 말거나 윤석열(대통령)은 이진숙을 임명할 거고, 이진숙이 가면 비슷한 누군가가 올 가능성이 크다. 이명박 정부 3년차인 2010년의 일이다. ‘방통대군’이라고 불렸던 최시중(당시 방통위원장)이 방통위를 장악하고 있었다. 최시중은...
The post 조인트 까면서 좌파 대청소, 뭐가 달라졌나. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Set up a streams for Apache Kafka cluster with Ansible]]></title>
        <id>d924849e-4059-4a9a-8620-3258d7dfdbd9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/30/set-streams-apache-kafka-cluster-ansible"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Based on the project Apache Kafka, streams for Apache Kafka is a powerful, innovative distributed event streaming platform. Using a fully distributed architecture, a streams for Apache Kafka cluster requires you to setup and deploy numerous services, ensure they are all properly configured and, even more importantly, that each component is functional and can communicate with each other. 
For all these reasons, applying an automation solution such as Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform to deploy and manage streams for Apache Kafka makes a lot of sense, especially as Ansible now has a collection dedicated for the product.
Overview
As mentioned, a typical implementation of streams for Apache Kafka includes several components, each deployed on numerous target systems. Depending on the organiza…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romain Pelisse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지리산 정상석 역사와 소회]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595740</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595740/%ec%a7%80%eb%a6%ac%ec%82%b0-%ec%a0%95%ec%83%81%ec%84%9d-%ec%97%ad%ec%82%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T06:13:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전기차 충전요금 인상 대응안]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595736</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595736/%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%b6%a9%ec%a0%84%ec%9a%94%ea%b8%88-%ec%9d%b8%ec%83%81"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T06:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[티메프 사태, 핵심은 금융과 비금융의 분리다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113075</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113075"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:53:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“…약간만 도와주시면은 다시 정상화시키고, 해결하고, 반드시 피해복구를 완전히 할 수 있다는 확신을 갖고 있습니다.” 구영배(큐텐그룹 대표), 국회정무위원회 티몬·위메프 미정산 사태 현안질의, 2024.07.30. 티몬과 위메프를 합쳐서 티메프, 인터파크까지 합쳐서 티메파크라고 부른다. 정부가 어제 긴급 자금 5600억 원을 투입하기로 했다. 사재를 털어 보상한다는 말이 나오더니 갑자기 법정 관리를 신청해서 피해자들이 분노하고 있는 상황이다. 이번 사건을 어떻게 보나....
The post 티메프 사태, 핵심은 금융과 비금융의 분리다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이진숙 청문회의 네 가지 문제: 2012년 MBC 총파업 해직기자의 출석 후기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=113053</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/113053"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T05:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 잘못된 프레임 지난주 이진숙 방통위원장 후보자 인사청문회 사흘 중 첫날과 이튿날 참고인으로 다녀왔습니다. 다들 보셨겠지만 첫날은 이진숙 검증이 아닌 MBC 청문회처럼 흘러갔죠. 전 MBC사장인 국민의힘 김장겸 의원이 후임 사장인 최승호 선배를 불러세워놓고 추궁하는 장면은 아찔했습니다. 김장겸 전 사장에 관해서는 서울고등법원이 ‘방송의 공정성·공익성 훼손, 보도 신뢰도 및 사회적 영향력 하락, 부당노동행위, 조직관리 및 운영 능력...
The post 이진숙 청문회의 네 가지 문제: 2012년 MBC 총파업 해직기자의 출석 후기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>박성호</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘영어 울렁증’ 사라지는데도 외국어 공부는 왜 해야 하냐 묻는다면]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79736</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/29/npsp_foreignlanguage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_foreignlanguage"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T03:10:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인공지능 기술이 얼마나 발전했는지 절감할 수 있는 분야 중 하나가 번역과 통역일 겁니다. 스마트폰의 번역기 앱을 이용하면 현지어를 한마디도 못 하는 곳에 가서도 여행하는 데 필요한 대화를 어느 정도 할 수 있을 정도입니다. 그러나 번역기가 많은 걸 해주는 세상에서도 번역기가 해줄 수 없는 것이 여전히 있기 때문에 외국어를 배울 이유와 의미는 충분히 많습니다. 비행기 조종사이자 작가인 마크 바노에네커의 칼럼을 번역하고, 해설을 덧붙였습니다. 전문 번역: 번역기가 다 번역해주는데… 외국어 공부는 이제 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/30, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595724</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595724/7-30-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T02:57:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[티메파크 사태, 경쟁의 룰을 다시 짜야 한다: 슬로우레터 7월30일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112999</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112999"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T22:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[정치 진공상태. 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈, 왜 말이 달라졌나. 결국 제2부속실 만든다. “김민석 표가 왜 이렇게 안 나오나.” 더 깊게 읽기. 빅5 병원, 전공의 지원 0명. 이진숙 청문보고서 불발. 피해 금액 1조 원? ‘티메프’ 회생신청. 민간 기업의 실패를 왜 정부가 지원하나. 구영배의 야망. 다르게 읽기. 티메파크 사태, 공정위는 뭐했나. 트럼프의 밴스 리스크. 해법과 대안. 인구가 늘었다....
The post 티메파크 사태, 경쟁의 룰을 다시 짜야 한다: 슬로우레터 7월30일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Git 2.46.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983850/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983850/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T17:20:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.46.0 of the Git
source-code management system has been released.  This release seems to
consist of a long list of interface and performance improvements rather
than big new features; see the announcement for the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an AI-powered service for detecting fraudulent card transactions]]></title>
        <id>8d98dd31-6c94-44f2-a54f-26d1452b6962</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/29/creating-ai-powered-service-detecting-fraudulent-card-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T14:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI and machine learning become integral to modern applications, developers need robust platforms that simplify the development and deployment process. Red Hat OpenShift AI offers a powerful and flexible environment tailored for these needs, making it easier for AI engineers and DevOps teams to collaborate and deliver high-quality AI solutions. In this blog post, we’ll explore how to set up a fraud detection system using Red Hat OpenShift AI, complete with a practical example and a demo API.
Developer experience with OpenShift
OpenShift AI simplifies the journey for teams working on AI applications. Utilizing OpenShift AI and Red Hat OpenShift, developers can enjoy a streamlined and efficient workflow. Let's take a look at an overview of the process:




  

Access Jupyter Notebook: Begi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating an AI powered service for detecting fraudulant card transactions]]></title>
        <id>8d98dd31-6c94-44f2-a54f-26d1452b6962</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/29/creating-ai-powered-service-detecting-fraudulant-card-transactions"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T14:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI and machine learning become integral to modern applications, developers need robust platforms that simplify the development and deployment process. Red Hat OpenShift AI offers a powerful and flexible environment tailored for these needs, making it easier for AI engineers and DevOps teams to collaborate and deliver high-quality AI solutions. In this blog post, we’ll explore how to set up a fraud detection system using Red Hat OpenShift AI, complete with a practical example and a demo API.
Developer Experience with OpenShift
OpenShift AI simplifies the journey for teams working on AI applications. Utilising OpenShift AI and Red Hat OpenShift, developers can enjoy a streamlined and efficient workflow. Let's take a look  overview of the process:




  

Access Jupyter Notebook: Begin by …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.11 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982605/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982605/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:54:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The release of 6.11-rc1
marked the end of the 6.11 merge window on July 28.  By that time,
12,102 non-merge changesets had been pulled into the mainline repository;
about 8,000 of those came in after the
first-half summary was written.  Quite a few significant changes were
to be found in those changesets; there is also one big change that did not
make it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983816/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983816/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (java-11-openjdk), Debian (bind9), Fedora (darkhttpd, mod_http2, and python-scrapy), Red Hat (python3.11, rhc-worker-script, and thunderbird), SUSE (assimp, gh, opera, python-Django, and python-nltk), and Ubuntu (edk2, linux, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux-oracle, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-nvidia-6.5, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, and lua5.4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[두산중공업에 녹색을! 기후위기 스프레이 액션은 무죄]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112977</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112977"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기후활동가들이 베트남 붕앙에 석탄화력발전소를 건설하기로 결정한 두산중공업(현 두산에너빌리티)의 행위를 고발하기 위한 ‘기후불복종’ 운동의 일환으로 조형물에 녹색 스프레이를 뿌리고 현수막을 펼쳤습니다. 1, 2심은 이 같은 직접행동에 책임을 물으며 벌금형을 선고했지만 대법원은 파기환송 했습니다. 이에 상현 기후활동가가 직접행동을 위축시키는 ‘과도한 벌금’에 대해 경고한 대법원의 선고의 의미를 비평했습니다. 기후정의를 위해 기후위기 시대, 우리 사회가 보호해야 할 가장 중요한...
The post 두산중공업에 녹색을! 기후위기 스프레이 액션은 무죄 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to classify Red Hat OpenShift audit logs]]></title>
        <id>8d7ad87c-7f2b-422c-a01d-dad505820806</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/29/how-classify-red-hat-openshift-audit-logs"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Audit logs are a crucial component of any robust IT infrastructure, providing a detailed record of activities and changes within a system. In the context of Red Hat OpenShift, a comprehensive and highly scalable container platform, audit logs play a vital role in ensuring security, compliance, and operational transparency.
OpenShift audit logs track a wide range of actions performed by users and services. These logs capture data such as who accessed the system, what actions were taken, and when these actions occurred. By maintaining a detailed and chronological record of these activities, audit logs help administrators monitor the system for unauthorized access, detect potential security breaches, and ensure compliance with organizational and regulatory requirements.
Why use OpenShift audi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Filice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지리산 운해 시기와 운해 장소]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595720</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595720/%ec%a7%80%eb%a6%ac%ec%82%b0-%ec%9a%b4%ed%95%b4-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b8%b0%ec%99%80-%ec%9e%a5%ec%86%8c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T02:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] AI와 같이 살아도 ‘외로움’을 느낄 수밖에 없는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79462</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/28/npsp_aillmloneliness/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aillmloneliness"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 6월 3일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 제가 정의하는 ‘연결’은 에너지입니다. 누군가가 나를 진심으로 봐주고, 들어주고, 가치 있게 여긴다고 느낄 때, 두 사람이 서로 아무런 가치판단 없이 무언가를 주고받을 수 있을 때, 그리고 그들이 그 관계에서 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rukahs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.11-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983760/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983760/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds has released 6.11-rc1 and closed the
merge window for this development cycle.  "The merge window felt pretty
normal, and the stats all look pretty normal too. I was expecting things to
be quieter because of summer vacations, but that (still) doesn't actually
seem to have been the case."

Note that the  extensible scheduler class
("sched_ext") was not merged, even though Torvalds had said he would back in June.  Sched_ext, it
seems, will need another development cycle out of tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘강제노동’ 빠졌는데 찬성? 어느 나라 정부냐는 말이 나온다: 슬로우레터 7월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112941</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112941"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[방통위가 ‘빵통위’가 됐다. 야당 추천은 왜 안 하나. 이진숙 법카 월 420만 원. “바보들의 행진 멈춰라.” 쟁점과 현안. 김건희가 장관 인사에 개입했나. “돌려주라” 했다더니 “맘에 안 드셨나요?” 의사 국가고시 11%만 접수. 윤석열 지지율 반등? 더 깊게 읽기. “저도 요새 거의 야당이라서요.” 국민의힘이 ‘배신자’를 선택한 이유. 상속세 인하, 민주당 동의가 관건. 다르게 읽기. 사도광산이 세계 유산?...
The post ‘강제노동’ 빠졌는데 찬성? 어느 나라 정부냐는 말이 나온다: 슬로우레터 7월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 update to my desktop system]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9248</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/07/28/the-2024-update-to-my-desktop-system/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T22:14:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have just upgraded my desktop system. As you can see from the picture below, it is a bespoke system; the third system built using the same chassis. The 11 drive bays on the right are configured for six 5.25-inch and five 3.5-inch disks/CD/DVD/tape drives, there is a drive cage that fits above the power […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning Gemma 2 with Keras - and an update from Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/fine-tuning-gemma-2-with-keras-hugging-face-update/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/fine-tuning-gemma-2-with-keras-hugging-face-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T20:14:21.277Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next generation of Gemma models is now available in KerasNLP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing the I/O magic to Berlin]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/bringing-the-io-magic-to-berlin/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/bringing-the-io-magic-to-berlin/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T20:14:16.687Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are some highlights from what we announced both on stage in Berlin and elsewhere in the world in celebration of this event!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro 2M context window, code execution capabilities, and Gemma 2 are available today]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/new-features-for-the-gemini-api-and-google-ai-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/new-features-for-the-gemini-api-and-google-ai-studio/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T20:14:16.669Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers will now be able to give Gemini 1.5 Flash a set of pre-trained data of their own and tune it to improve model performance significantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[태백여행, 바위굴로 흐르는 강물이 신비한 태백 구문소]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595706</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595706/%ed%83%9c%eb%b0%b1%ec%97%ac%ed%96%89-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c-%ed%83%9c%eb%b0%b1-%ea%b5%ac%eb%ac%b8%ec%86%8c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-28T11:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왜 저 나라가 스포츠 강국이냐… 올림픽 메달 개수보다 조금 더 ‘공정’한 방법은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79723</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/27/npsp_olympicmedalcounts/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_olympicmedalcounts"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T21:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[파리 올림픽이 개막했습니다. 올림픽을 즐기는 법은 여러 가지가 있겠지만, 언젠가부터 우리는 선수들의 국적을 기준으로 메달을 집계해 어느 나라가 메달을 많이 땄는지 순위를 매기는 경쟁에 몰두하고 있습니다. 국가주의와 상업주의가 결합한 올림픽에서 어쩔 수 없는 일이긴 해도 올림픽 정신, 스포츠 정신과는 다소 동떨어진 세태라서 아쉽기도 합니다. 뉴욕타임스 칼럼니스트 피터 코이가 기왕 메달 집계를 가지고 순위를 매길 거면 좀 더 공정하게 순위를 매기는 방법이 없을지 짚은 칼럼을 썼습니다. 칼럼을 번역하고, 올림픽을 맞아 올림픽 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Built It: The I/O Crossword]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-we-built-the-io-crossword/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-we-built-the-io-crossword/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T20:13:40.529Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a helpful twist to a classic crossword puzzle with the power of Flutter, Firebase, and the Gemini API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Explorer: Simplifying ML models for Edge devices]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/model-explorer-simplifying-ml-models-for-edge-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/model-explorer-simplifying-ml-models-for-edge-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T20:13:40.529Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Model Explorer, a new graph visualization tool from Google AI Edge, enables developers to overcome the complexities of optimizing models for edge devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel updates for Saturday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983652/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983652/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T14:35:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.10.2,
6.9.12,
6.6.43,
6.1.102,
5.15.164,
5.10.223,
5.4.281, and
4.19.319
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains a relatively
small set of important fixes, at
least one of which appears to close a minor security hole.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[태백 바람의언덕 차박, 매봉산 풍력발전단지 차박기록]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595686</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595686/%ed%83%9c%eb%b0%b1-%eb%b0%94%eb%9e%8c%ec%9d%98%ec%96%b8%eb%8d%95-%ec%b0%a8%eb%b0%95"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T04:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] May the FOLL_FORCE not be with you]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983169/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983169/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T14:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the simplest hardening concepts to understand is that memory should
never be both writable and executable, otherwise an attacker can use it to
load and run arbitrary code.  That rule is generally followed in Linux
systems, but there is a glaring loophole that is exploitable from user
space to inject code into a running process.  Attackers have duly exploited
it.  A new effort to close the hole ran into trouble early in the merge
window, but a solution may yet be found in time for the 6.11 kernel
release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983523/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983523/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T13:47:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (linux-firmware and squid), Debian (bind9), Fedora (kubernetes, thunderbird, and tinyproxy), Oracle (containernetworking-plugins, cups, edk2, httpd, httpd:2.4, kernel, kernel-container, libreoffice, libuv, libvirt, python3, and runc), Red Hat (freeradius:3.0, httpd, and squid), and SUSE (giflib and python-dnspython).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한국에도 분자요리가 있다: 여름 감자전 2.0]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112792</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112792"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T02:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[여름이다. 감자가 맛있는 계절이다. 감자는 세상에서 가장 소중한 식재료 중 하나다. 영양 섭취의 관점에서 옥수수와 함께 대표적인 구황작물로 인류를 기아에서 구원했다는 점에서 훌륭하다. 그러나 못 먹어서 아픈 자만큼, 많이 먹어 아픈 자 또한 넘쳐나는 슬픈 오늘날 여전히 감자는 미식의 영역에서 그 가치를 한껏 빛내고 있다. 감자로 서양 미식사에 획을 그은 메뉴들이 있다. 대표적으로는 프랑스 조엘...
The post 한국에도 분자요리가 있다: 여름 감자전 2.0 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최명진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 81조 원 감세, 이게 전부가 아니다: 슬로우레터 7월26일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112882</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112882"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T22:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[국민의힘 이탈표 3표. 한동훈은 생각이 달라졌나. 쟁점과 현안. 방송 전쟁, 방통위 부위원장도 탄핵 간다. 4박5일 필리버스터 돌입. “윤석열은 몰랐다.” 김건희가 새벽 3시에 최재영에게 보낸 메시지. 20억 원 물려줘도 0원. 더 깊게 읽기. 지금이 감세할 때인가. 500억 원 이상 ‘초부자’들 평균 62억 원 혜택. 다르게 읽기. 어차피 민주당이 결정한다. 이재명은 “종부세 완화”. 윤석열 3년 동안 81조...
The post 윤석열 81조 원 감세, 이게 전부가 아니다: 슬로우레터 7월26일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging bugs in x64dbg debugger. No debugger]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1146/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1146/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can't develop programs without debugging. Modern IDEs have a built-in debugger, but there are cases when using IDE for debugging is superfluous or impossible. So, standalone debuggers come to the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google @ KotlinConf 2024: A Look Inside Multiplatform Development with KMP and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T20:14:41.678Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KotlinConf 2024 reveals Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) for sharing business logic across mobile, web, server, and desktop platforms, and in Google Workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] What became of getrandom() in the vDSO]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983186/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983186/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T16:19:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous episode of the
vgetrandom() story, Jason Donenfeld had put together a version of
the getrandom()
system call that ran in user space, significantly improving performance for
applications that need a lot of random data while retaining all of the
guarantees provided by the system call.  At that time, it seemed that a
consensus had built around the implementation and that it was headed toward
the mainline in that form.  A few milliseconds after that article was
posted, though, a Linus-Torvalds-shaped obstacle appeared in its path.
That obstacle has been overcome and this work has now been merged for the
6.11 kernel, but its form has changed somewhat.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] More informative kernel panics for Fedora]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982398/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982398/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T15:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On July 12, Jocelyn Falempe

proposed a change to the configuration options that Fedora sets for its
kernels, in order to make kernel panics easier to report.
Falempe would like to enable the kernel's recently added
DRM-panic feature, which adds
a graphical crash screen that is reminiscent of the infamous
Windows "blue screen of death" for kernel panics. The feature introduces a few
tradeoffs, including currently limited driver support, so the proposal spawned a
good deal of discussion.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.80.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983265/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983265/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T14:59:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.80.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Changes include the new
LazyCell and LazyLock types (which delay data
initialization until the first access), the stabilization of the
exclusive-range syntax for match patterns, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983331/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983331/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T14:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9.11, 6.6.42, and 6.1.101 stable kernels have been released.  As
usual, they contain important fixes throughout the tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983328/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983328/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T14:03:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (containernetworking-plugins, cups, edk2, httpd, httpd:2.4, libreoffice, libuv, libvirt, python3, and runc), Fedora (exim, python-zipp, xdg-desktop-portal-hyprland, and xmedcon), Red Hat (cups, fence-agents, freeradius, freeradius:3.0, httpd:2.4, kernel, kernel-rt, nodejs:18, podman, and resource-agents), Slackware (htdig and libxml2), SUSE (exim), and Ubuntu (ocsinventory-server, php-cas, and poppler).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint 22 "Wilma" released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983301/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983301/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T13:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint has announced version 22 of
the distribution in three editions: Cinnamon, MATE, and Xfce. Mint 22
is based on Ubuntu 24.04 and uses kernel version 6.8.0:
LWN covered the
Linux Mint 22 beta in early July. See the new
features page and release notes for
more information on this release.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[방송4법 팩트체크: “파우치 그 조그마한 백” 이런 방송 계속 보고 싶습니까?]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112874</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112874"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T08:24:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[방송4법 취지와 개요 7월 17일 우원식 국회의장은 여야에 “범국민협의체를 구성해 합리적인 공영방송 제도 마련에 나서자”며 정부‧여당엔 ‘공영방송 이사선임 중단’, 야당엔 ‘방송4법 입법강행 중단·법안 원점 재검토’를 요청했습니다. 여당은 우원식 의장 중재안에 거부의사를 밝혔으며, 야당은 7월 25일 본회의에서 방송4법을 일정대로 처리할 것이라 발표했습니다. 방송4법(방송법·방송문화진흥회법·한국교육공사법·방송통신위원회설치법 개정안)은 정권의 전리품이 아니라 국민의 품으로 공영방송을 돌려주고자 방송 독립성과 공공성을 보장하자는 법안인데요. 정치...
The post 방송4법 팩트체크: “파우치 그 조그마한 백” 이런 방송 계속 보고 싶습니까? appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Memory Mapped I/O in C]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1683.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1683.php"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T07:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A considerable part of my job as embedded developer entails brokering interactions between whichever processor my code happens to be running on and the underlying hardware peripherals.Save for older architectures this often means managing memory mapped registers.When a device employs this strategy a portion of the main memory space is not actually memory but a bus connection to a peripheral...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Easily upgrade hosted OpenShift Virtualization clusters on hosted control planes]]></title>
        <id>08c1710c-1784-4569-9d74-a7351f5c711b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/25/easily-upgrade-hosted-openshift-virtualization-clusters-hosted-control-planes"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the greatest benefits to OpenShift hosted control planes (HCP) is that it makes Red Hat OpenShift operational management easier through reduced upgrade complexity and downtime. For example, in a traditional situation you’d be upgrading both the control plane and the workers. With HCP, you’re just upgrading the workers in most cases, thus reducing the risk and turnaround time normally associated with standalone installations. For a visual representation of the difference between a standalone setup and HCP, see Figure 1.



  
        



  

Figure 1: Standalone control plane vs. hosted control plane.

In this article I’m going to run through upgrading a decoupled worker/node cluster (or NodePool in this case) hosted on HCP and point out some of the current caveats and things to look…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nicholas Schuetz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Managing Sensitive Assets Within Image Mode for Red Hat Enterprise Linux]]></title>
        <id>ac3ee416-5652-46a1-a3fc-bc35b1abc389</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/25/managing-sensitive-assets-within-image-mode-red-hat-enterprise-linux"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T05:28:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aside from naming and versioning, managing sensitive assets, like credentials, is one of the more challenging aspects in technology. So, why is it so difficult? Well, to start off. What may be considered a sensitive asset to one individual or organization may not be the same as another. Also, given that there are so many different ways that sensitive assets can be managed, there is no universally accepted method available.
The challenges that encompass how sensitive assets are handled also apply to image mode, a new method that enables building and deploying Operating Systems using similar tools and approaches as any other traditional container. In this article, we will discuss the types of sensitive assets that apply to image mode for RHEL specifically and how to design appropriate workfl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 알파벳 실적(구글 실적)을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595653</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595653/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%8c%ed%8c%8c%eb%b2%b3-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T04:33:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 테슬라 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595649</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595649/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T04:23:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[카멀라 해리스가 대선 캠페인 천재가 된 비결]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112856</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112856"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T04:02:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[바이든 대통령이 용퇴를 결심하고 카멀라 해리스 부통령을 지지한 지 이틀 만에 여론조사에서 약간이나마 해리스가 트럼프를 앞선다는 조사가 나왔다. 이게 무슨 일일까? 해리스가 이틀 만에 캠페인 천재만재라도 된 건가?? 4년 전을 돌아보자. 2020년 조 바이든이 선거에서 이긴 이유 중 하나는 바이든이 고령임에도 불구하고 1020세대에 어필했기 때문이었다. 테일러 스위프트가 바이든을 지지한 건 그 정점에 있었다. 바이든은 민주당의...
The post 카멀라 해리스가 대선 캠페인 천재가 된 비결 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>평범엄마</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 25, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982336/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982336/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T02:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 25, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 전례 없는 흥행 돌풍의 벌써 ‘레전드’…그런데 프로 되니까 수익 증발했다?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79434</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/24/npsp_caitlinclark/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_caitlinclark"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T22:59:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 29일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 미국은 다들 아시다시피 프로 스포츠의 천국입니다. 스포츠 산업의 규모는 다른 나라와 비교가 안 될 만큼 압도적으로 크고, 주요 종목에서 최고의 선수들이 소속된 구단은 대개 미국 리그에 있습니다. 재밌는 건 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[조선일보의 한동훈 평가, “1점도 안 깎이려는 앞뒤 꽉막힌 범생이”: 슬로우레터 7월25일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112811</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112811"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T22:09:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열과 한동훈의 러브샷. 더 이상 지시-복종 관계가 아니다. 쟁점과 현안. “앞뒤 꽉 막힌 범생이의 조급증.” 김건희를 ‘읽씹’할 수 있는 유일한 사람. 조중동의 불안. 입증된 결과 아니고 검증받을 차례. 이진숙의 맷집. 채 상병 특검법과 방송 4법. 꼬리 내린 이원석. 더 깊게 읽기. 월별 출생아 두 달 연속 반등. ‘티메프’ 1조 원 지급 불능 사태. “차라리 떠나게...
The post 조선일보의 한동훈 평가, “1점도 안 깎이려는 앞뒤 꽉막힌 범생이”: 슬로우레터 7월25일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel update 6.10.1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983153/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983153/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T17:02:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released the 6.10.1 stable kernel update. This release
contains a small number of seemingly urgent regression fixes. Users of
this kernel series are advised to upgrade.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenMandriva ROME 24.07 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983133/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983133/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T16:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Updated installation images for the OpenMandriva ROME rolling release Linux distribution are now available. Notable features in the
24.07 snapshot include KDE Plasma 6 as the default desktop, the addition of Proton and Proton
experimental packages for playing Windows games on Linux, as well as 
GNOME 46.3 and LXQt 2.0.0 spins.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSL announces new governance structure]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983120/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983120/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T15:58:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSL has announced
that it has adopted a new governance framework:
The OpenSSL Management Committee (OMC) has been dissolved, and two
boards of directors have been elected for the Foundation and the Corporation. Each
organization has ten voting members. These boards share all the
responsibilities and authorities of the former OMC co-equally.
To further engage our communities, we are establishing two advisory
committees for each entity: a Business Advisory Committee (BAC) and a
Technical Advisory Committee (TAC). The communities will elect the
members of the BACs and TACs, creating a direct channel for community
input in roadmap development and reflecting the diverse perspectives
of OpenSSL's communities.
OpenSSL has also announced that two projects have adopted the OpenSSL Mission
and become OpenSSL
projects: Bouncy Castle, which provides
cryptographic APIs for Java and C#, and the cryptlib security
software development toolkit. See the announcement for full details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Large folios, swap, and FS-Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982887/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982887/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T15:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Howells wanted to discuss swap handling in light of multi-page folios
in a combined storage, filesystem, and memory-management session at
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  Swapping has always been
done with a one-to-one mapping of memory pages to swap slots, he said, but
swapping multi-page folios breaks that assumption.  He wondered if it would
make sense to use filesystem techniques to track swapped-out folios.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Lessons from the death and rebirth of Thunderbird]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982610/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982610/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T14:38:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ryan Sipes told the audience during his keynote at
GUADEC 2024 in Denver, Colorado that the Thunderbird mail client 
"probably shouldn't still be alive". Thunderbird, however, is not only
alive—it is arguably in better shape than ever
before. According to Sipes, the project's turnaround is a result of
governance, storytelling, and learning to be comfortable asking users
for money. He would also like it quite a bit if Linux distributions stopped
turning off telemetry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Encrypt plans to drop support for OCSP]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982965/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982965/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T13:19:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's Encrypt has
announced
that it intends to end support "as soon as possible" for the 

Online Certificate Status Protocol (OCSP) over privacy concerns. OCSP was developed as a
lighter-weight alternative to

Certificate Revocation Lists (CRLs) that did not involve downloading
the entire CRL in order to check whether a certificate was valid. Let's Encrypt will continue
supporting OCSP as long as it is a requirement for Microsoft's

Trusted Root Program, but hopes to discontinue it soon:



We plan to end support for OCSP primarily because it represents a considerable risk to privacy on the Internet. When someone visits a website using a browser or other software that checks for certificate revocation via OCSP, the Certificate Authority (CA) operating the OCSP responder immediately becomes aware of which website is being visited from that visitor's particular IP address. Even when a CA intentionally does not retain this information, as is the case with Let's Encrypt, CAs could be legally compelled to collect it. CRLs do not have this issue.



People using Let's Encrypt as their CA should, for the most part, not need to change their setups.
All modern browsers support CRLs, so end-users shouldn't notice an impact either.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/983083/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/983083/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T12:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (ghostscript and xmedcon), Gentoo (Dmidecode, ExifTool, and Freenet), Red Hat (containernetworking-plugins, cups, edk2, httpd, httpd:2.4, kernel, kernel-rt, krb5, libreoffice, libuv, libvirt, linux-firmware, nghttp2, nodejs, openssh, python3, runc, thunderbird, and tpm2-tss), Slackware (aaa_glibc, bind, and mozilla), SUSE (postgresql14, python-sentry-sdk, and shadow), and Ubuntu (activemq, bind9, haproxy, nova, provd, python-zipp, squid, squid3, and tomcat).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New features in Cryostat 3.0 for monitoring Java applications on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>83141155-8d9c-45f5-8fa1-65df103952d1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/24/new-features-cryostat-30-monitoring-java-applications-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryostat has been at the forefront of providing advanced monitoring and management tools for Java applications on Red Hat OpenShift. With the release of Red Hat build of Cryostat 3.0, a list of new features and enhancements are now available, designed to streamline operations, enhance security, and improve overall functionality. Here’s an in-depth look at what’s new and how these updates can benefit users.
Cryostat database (DB)
One of the most significant additions in Cryostat 3.0 is the introduction of the Cryostat database (DB) container image (cryostat-db). This container, which is deployed automatically when you install Cryostat via the Cryostat Operator or a Helm chart, provides a customized Postgres database. Centralizing data storage in a robust Postgres database enhances data inte…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Syed M Shaaf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[자동차로 정상까지, 자동차 등산이 가능한 풍경 맛집을 알아보자]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595628</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595628/%ec%9e%90%eb%8f%99%ec%b0%a8-%eb%93%b1%ec%82%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T06:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[체코 원전, 확정 아닌가요? KBS와 TV조선의 호들갑]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112776</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112776"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T06:07:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국수력원자력(한수원)이 7월 17일 체코 원전 건설 우선협상자로 선정됐습니다. 성태윤 대통령실 정책실장은 “윤석열 대통령은 ‘팀코리아 정신으로 최종계약을 위해 최선을 다해달라’고 당부했다”, “2009년 아랍에미리트(UAE) 바라카 원전 수주 이후 15년 만의 쾌거”, “상업용 원자로를 최초로 건설한 원전의 본산 유럽에 수출하는 교두보가 마련됐다”고 기쁨을 표했습니다. 윤석열 대통령이 “최종계약을 위해 최선을 다해달라”고 당부했듯 한국수력원자력은 체코 신규원전 건설사업 우선협상대상자로 선정된 것으로...
The post 체코 원전, 확정 아닌가요? KBS와 TV조선의 호들갑 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/24, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595631</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595631/7-24-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T02:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on Taylor and Maclaurin series]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/notes-on-taylor-and-maclaurin-series/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/notes-on-taylor-and-maclaurin-series/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T01:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A Maclaurin series is a power series - a polynomial with carefully selected
coefficients and an infinite number of terms - used to approximate arbitrary
functions with some conditions (e.g. differentiability). The Maclaurin series
does this for input values close to 0, and is a special case of the Taylor
series …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Considerations when Building Embedded Databases]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/choosing-or-building-an-embedded-db</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/choosing-or-building-an-embedded-db"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Persisting to flash is a necessary evil for many embedded devices. Let’s take a
look at some of the pitfalls and how they may be avoided.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[달라진 권력과 위상, 폴더 인사도 어퍼컷 세리머니도 없었다: 슬로우레터 7월24일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112713</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112713"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T22:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈 당 대표가 의미하는 것. ‘윤심’이 안 통했다. 당심과 민심의 미묘한 격차. 다시 8표에 달렸다. 쟁점과 현안. 이창수의 반격, “나만 조사하라”. 4년째 수사 배제, 이게 말이 되나. “양주는 폐기했다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 문 걸어 잠그고 류희림 연임. 다르게 읽기. 사교육 카르텔? 때릴수록 더 커졌다. 주 1시간도 취업? 고용률 63.5%의 비밀. 해법과 대안. 목 졸린 적...
The post 달라진 권력과 위상, 폴더 인사도 어퍼컷 세리머니도 없었다: 슬로우레터 7월24일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fixing bugs in your AI: let's analyze bugs in OpenVINO]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1145/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1145/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fellow developers, we invite you to continue our exciting journey through the depths of Intel OpenVINO code! Equipped with a static analyzer, just like detectives, we'll uncover the most insidious...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Imitation, not artificial, intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982289/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982289/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T20:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Willison, co-creator of the popular Django web framework for Python,
gave a keynote presentation at PyCon 2024 on a topic that is
unrelated to that work: large language models (LLMs).
The topic grew out of some other work that he is doing on Datasette, which is a Python-based
"tool for exploring and publishing data".  The talk was a look
beyond the hype to try to discover what useful things you can actually do
today using these models.  Unsurprisingly, there were some
cautionary notes from Willison, as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improvements to the PSF Grants program]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982967/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982967/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T19:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Software Foundation (PSF) board has announced
improvements to its grants program that have been enacted as a
response to "concerns and frustrations" with the program:
open letter from the pan-African delegation
seriously, and we began to draft a plan to address everything in the
letter. We also set up improved two-way communications so that we can
continue the conversation with the community. The writers of the open
letter have now met several times with members of the PSF board. We
are thankful for their insight and guidance on how we can work
together and be thoroughly and consistently supportive of the
pan-African Python community.


So far the PSF has set up office
hours to improve communications, published
a retrospective on the DjangoCon Africa review, and put out a transparency
report on grants from the past two years. The PSF board has also
voted to "use the same criteria for all grant requests, no matter
their country of origin".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zuckerberg: Open Source AI Is the Path Forward]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982954/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982954/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T16:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg has posted
an article announcing some new releases of the Llama large language
model and going on at length about why open-source models are important:


	AI has more potential than any other modern technology to increase
	human productivity, creativity, and quality of life – and to
	accelerate economic growth while unlocking progress in medical and
	scientific research. Open source will ensure that more people
	around the world have access to the benefits and opportunities of
	AI, that power isn't concentrated in the hands of a small number of
	companies, and that the technology can be deployed more evenly and
	safely across society.

	There is an ongoing debate about the safety of open source AI
	models, and my view is that open source AI will be safer than the
	alternatives. I think governments will conclude it's in their
	interest to support open source because it will make the world more
	prosperous and safer.


Of course, whether Llama is truly open source is debatable at best, but it
is more open than many of the alternatives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some Embedded System Software Design Resources]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1680.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1680.php"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T15:54:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently received a message from an embedded systems engineer in England asking about a good resource for embedded system software design and easing debugging difficulties.

That's challenging because embedded systems cover such a wide range. There are many possible run-time environments and architectures.

Thus there's no single resource that covers all ground. However, the resources...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A look inside the BPF verifier]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982077/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982077/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T14:57:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LWN has covered BPF

since its initial introduction to Linux, usually through the lens of the newest
developments; this can make it hard to view the whole picture. BPF provides
a way to extend a running kernel, without having to recompile and reboot.
It does this in a safe way, so that malicious BPF
programs cannot crash a running kernel, thanks to the BPF verifier. So how does
the verifier actually work, what are its limits, and how has it changed since
the early days of BPF?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU C Library 2.40 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982940/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982940/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T13:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.40 of the GNU C
Library has been released.  Changes include partial support for the ISO C23
standard, a new tunable for the testing of setuid programs, improved 64-bit
Arm vector support, and a handful of security fixes.  See the release notes
for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982939/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982939/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T13:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (gtk3 and jpegxl), Red Hat (kpatch-patch and thunderbird), SUSE (apache2, git, gnome-shell, java-11-openjdk, java-21-openjdk, kernel, kernel-firmware, kernel-firmware-nvidia-gspx-G06, libgit2, mozilla-nss, nodejs20, python-Django, and python312), and Ubuntu (linux-aws, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-iot, linux-aws-5.15, pymongo, and ruby-rack).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[플랫폼 노동: 카카오와 배민의 독점본색]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111922</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111922"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T07:47:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[→ 이 글은 ‘플랫폼 노동: 문제는 기술이 아니라 독점이다’에서 이어집니다. 인트로: 독점본색 카카오T와 배달의민족. 택시 호출과 음식 배달 분야의 대표적 플랫폼이다. 이슈의 흐름을 간단히 짚어보자. 주요 등장인물 공정위, 카카오T에 257억 과징금 부과 (2023.02) 카카오모빌리티가 자회사 가맹 택시인 ‘카카오T블루’ 기사들에게 부당하게 승객 호출(콜)을 몰아줘 독과점 지위를 확대·강화했다고 공정위가 판단했다. 택시 앱 호출 시장에서 카카오T가 차지하는 점유율은...
The post 플랫폼 노동: 카카오와 배민의 독점본색 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get Red Hat OpenShift operators' information without oc-mirror plug-in]]></title>
        <id>fd69a741-455e-4a98-8137-6b99ac06e2a9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/23/how-get-red-hat-openshift-operators-information-without-oc-mirror-plug"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying a Red Hat OpenShift operator in an online environment is a breeze! OpenShift will simply pull the required images from public registries, and voila, we're good to use it without any hassle.
However, the game changes when we're working in a disconnected environment. For most customers, keeping their servers off the internet is a top priority due to security concerns. Suddenly, deploying an OpenShift operator becomes more intricate and we can't rely on public registries anymore. Instead, we need to gather all the necessary container images and make sure they're available within our disconnected environment. Only then can we successfully deploy an operator on OpenShift. 
Using oc-mirror in a typical environment
When deploying the OpenShift operators in a disconnected environment, on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eric Beaudoin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“구국의 결단” 바이든 그 이후… 절대 놓치면 안 되는 것들이 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79699</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/22/npsp_bidenharristrumpvance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_bidenharristrumpvance"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T03:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 21일, 조 바이든 대통령이 대선을 100일 남짓 앞두고 현직 대통령으로서 재선에 도전하지 않겠다고 발표했습니다. 그러면서 바이든 대통령은 카말라 해리스 부통령을 지지한다고 밝혔습니다. 해리스 부통령은 빠르게 민주당 내부의 지지를 모으며 대통령 후보로 굳어지고 있습니다. 해리스가 바이든보다 잘해줄 거란 기대도 없지 않지만, 트럼프 전 대통령의 기세가 만만치 않습니다. 특히 8년 전만 해도 큰 주목을 받지 못하던 “마가(MAGA)”는 이제 엄연한 정치 사조가 됐습니다. 민주당이 “마가”를 뛰어넘으려면 어떻게 해야 할지 데이비드 브룩스가 바이든 대통령이 재선에 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/23, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595613</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595613/7-23-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T00:00:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[검찰이 부른 게 아니라 김건희가 검찰을 불렀다: 슬로우레터 7월23일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112665</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112665"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T22:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[권력과 맞서는 방법. 검찰 출석? 김건희가 검찰을 불렀다. 김건희의 요구. ‘패싱’ 당한 이원석. 추미애가 박탈한 도이치모터스 수사지휘권. 2특검 4국조 간다. 쟁점과 현안. 바이든이 선택한 X. ‘상왕’ 오바마의 선택. 다르게 읽기. ‘힐빌리의 노래’를 읽는 방법. 더 깊게 읽기. 국민의힘 전당대회 흥행 실패. 누가 되든 미국은 4년 더 보호무역. 해법과 대안. 일 넘겨받은 동료에게 ‘응원 수당’. 비싼...
The post 검찰이 부른 게 아니라 김건희가 검찰을 불렀다: 슬로우레터 7월23일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[캔커드, 2분기 테슬라 실적 주목 요소, FSD와 로보택시]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595601</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595601/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%a3%bc%eb%aa%a9-%ec%9a%94%ec%86%8c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T15:21:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] "Opt-in" metrics planned for Fedora Workstation 42]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/980598/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/980598/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T13:54:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat, through members of the Fedora
Workstation Working Group, has taken another
swing at persuading the Fedora Project to allow metrics related to
the real-world use of the Workstation edition to be collected. The first
proposal, aimed for Fedora 40, was withdrawn to be reworked
based on feedback. This time around, the proponents have shifted from
asking for opt-out telemetry to opt-in metrics, with more detail about
what would be collected and the policies that would govern data collection. The
change seems to be on its way to approval by the Fedora Engineering
Steering Council (FESCo) and is set to take effect for
Fedora 42.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982845/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982845/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T13:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (botan2, chromium, ffmpeg, fluent-bit, gtk3, httpd, suricata, tcpreplay, and thunderbird), Mageia (apache, chromium-browser-stable, libfm & libfm-qt, and thunderbird), Oracle (firefox, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, java-21-openjdk, kernel, libndp, qt5-qtbase, ruby, skopeo, thunderbird, and virt:ol and virt-devel:rhel), Red Hat (containernetworking-plugins, firefox, libndp, qt5-qtbase, and thunderbird), SUSE (caddy, chromium, emacs, global, mockito, snakeyaml, testng, and opera), and Ubuntu (thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2분기 넷플릭스 실적을 읽는월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595597</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595597/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ec%9d%84-%ec%9d%bd%eb%8a%94%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ec%8b%9c%ec%84%a0"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T11:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 myths about platform engineering, debunked]]></title>
        <id>18d2295f-0feb-47c7-9803-7fe8d2e50ebd</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/22/5-myths-about-platform-engineering-debunked"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Myths and misconceptions tend to run rampant in the fast-moving software development space, and with the growing popularity of platform engineering, it's no surprise that there's confusion around the concept. Is platform engineering a developer's dream come true, a magical land of streamlined processes and rapid innovation? Or is it a productivity-sucking plague, a bureaucratic nightmare that slows everything down? 
Buckle up, because we're strapping on our myth-busting goggles and diving deep into the world of platform engineering. We'll separate fact from fiction, explore common myths, and ultimately reveal whether platform engineering is a blessing or a burden for your development workflow.
Myth #1: Platform engineering slows down development
In the high-octane world of software develop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Eisele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[​​Try OpenShift AI and integrate with Apache Camel]]></title>
        <id>cfe0e3c3-aabd-4405-b9b2-c7e7fbf8ae24</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/22/try-openshift-ai-and-integrate-apache-camel"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access the Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift to learn with guidance the basics of powering applications with AI. The sandbox is a free-to-use environment that includes OpenShift AI, where you can create and deploy models and connect services using Apache Camel as our integration Swiss Army knife to build AI-enabled APIs.
This is not your usual, read-fast-retain-little article. We want to make a difference by welcoming you to experience first-hand how to train a model with your own data set, make it consumable, and show you how to create applications that expose and enrich the capability.
You’ll need no local environment to set up and no preparation time or effort. It all happens in our Developer Sandbox which automatically provisions the tutorial on demand. The learning guide is desi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bruno Meseguer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A quick look at large language models with Node.js, Podman desktop, and the Granite model]]></title>
        <id>3bd2f3da-0e9a-4bf5-ae71-b7aed915921b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/22/quick-look-large-language-models-nodejs-podman-desktop-and-granite-model"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve been learning a lot about large language models (LLMs) and how they can be used with Node.js and JavaScript. If you want to follow what we’ve learned, you can check out this learning path that we put together on our journey so far: How to get started with large language models and Node.js.
In our initial learning we followed the most common path by using one of the most popular models from Hugging Face and using tools like ollama and node-llama-cpp to run the models. However, not all models are created equal, and there are a number of aspects that should be considered when choosing a model. The article "Why trust open source AI" is a good introduction to a number of them.
In that context we wanted to try out the Granite model and see what if any differences there were from using the …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protecting your models made easy with Authorino]]></title>
        <id>32294db6-bb5f-4801-ace0-bb4ebcbac75b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/22/protecting-your-models-made-easy-authorino"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my previous article, we explored how easy is to deploy KServe on Red Hat OpenShift using Open Data Hub. Now that we have KServe installed, it's time to deploy a model. In this post, we will register the popular SKlearn runtime as a custom ServingRuntime and deploy the iris model.
While KServe makes it very easy to deploy models, it doesn't mean that everyone should have access to these models. Restricting access to certain individuals helps conserve resources. In this example, the runtime is CPU-based, but if you're using a GPU-based runtime, this resource issue becomes even more significant. Open Data Hub (ODH) and Red Hat OpenShift AI have made it simpler than ever with the integration of Authorino into the model serving components from ODH 2.10 and OpenShift AI 2.9.
Authorino is a po…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JooHo Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/22, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595587</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595587/7-22-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T04:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “정의 구현” 대 “마녀사냥”, 프레임 전쟁의 승자와 패자는]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79414</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/21/npsp_trumptrialelection/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_trumptrialelection"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T22:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 27일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난 13일 뉴욕타임스가 시에나대학교와 올해 미국 대선의 승패를 가를 경합주 6곳에서 진행한 여론조사 결과를 발표했습니다. 미국 대통령 선거는 유권자의 전체 득표를 집계하지 않고, 주별로 할당된 선거인단의 표를 더해 당락을 가르죠. 그래서 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new NASA software dataset from the 1970s]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9238</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/07/21/a-new-nasa-software-dataset-from-the-1970s/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T22:29:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When modeling the process of software development, to optimise the creation of new projects, the best measurement data to use are those relating to whatever developers are doing today. Unfortunately, measurement data for software engineering processes is very hard to find; few development groups record anything about what they do, and even when they do […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 포토라인 피하려, 검찰총장도 패싱했다: 슬로우레터 7월22일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112551</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112551"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T22:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[조 바이든 사퇴. 카멀라 해리스가 민주당 후보가 되려면. 대타 해리스의 지지율은? 60 vs. 78. 쟁점과 현안. 김건희 비공개 조사. 검찰총장도 몰랐다. 핵심은 김건희 청문회 출석. 민주당 최고위원 1위는 정봉주. “3일도 너무 길다”, 전투력 높아진 조국. 더 깊게 읽기. 블루스크린 공포, 연결된 세상의 재앙. 낡은 시스템의 역설. 엔저가 끝나간다. 원화 가치 바닥 친다. 다르게 읽기. 손석희가...
The post 김건희 포토라인 피하려, 검찰총장도 패싱했다: 슬로우레터 7월22일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Years of Innovation: Student developers solving real-world problems using Google tech]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-21T20:15:42.466Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Developer Student Clubs globally are tackling the United Nations' Sustainable Development Goals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SMD Cut Tape Organization with Transparent Containers]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40495</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/07/20/smd-cut-tape-organization-with-transparent-containers/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-20T17:41:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The author describes a storage system for SMD cut-tape components using inexpensive transparent containers, 3D-printed trays, and customized labels for easy organization and accessibility. This method allows for quick part identification and selection based on the PCB's Bill of Material, enhancing efficiency in PCB assembly. Additionally, the author encourages sharing alternative storage methods. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[종부세는 잘못이 없다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112516</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112516"/>
        <updated>2024-07-20T07:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[기고] 원칙이 흔들리면 누구나 불만을 품게 된다… 종부세 하나로 가야 하는 이유. 종합부동산세를 없애거나 줄여야 한다는 주장이 이제 민주당 내에서도 힘을 얻는 국면이다. 노무현 정부와 문재인 정부에서 부동산 정책이 실패했다고 보는 사람들도 여기에 말을 얹고 있다. 종부세는 과연 옳은 세금인가, 또는 거두기 좋은 세금인가에 대한 질문을 하는 사람은 없을까. 종부세를 없애느니 축소하느니 주장을 하려면, 이...
The post 종부세는 잘못이 없다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Everon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How It’s Made: AI Roadtrip, a Pixel Campaign Powered by Generative AI and Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-ai-roadtrip-a-pixel-campaign-powered-by-generative-ai-and-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-ai-roadtrip-a-pixel-campaign-powered-by-generative-ai-and-fans/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T20:15:53.264Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Phones Forever: AI Roadtrip is our first experiment in using generative AI to put fans in the driver's seat and bring characters to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NGI project may lose funding]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982585/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982585/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T17:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Generation Internet
(NGI) project, an initiative of the EU's European Commission (EC),
provides funding in the form of grants for a wide variety of
open-source software,
including
Redox,
Briar,
SourceHut, and many more.
But the NGI project is not among those that would be funded under the current draft budget for 2025,

as The Register reports. More than 60 organizations have signed on to an open letter asking the
EC to reconsider:



We find this transformation incomprehensible, moreover when NGI has proven efficient and economical to support free software as a whole, from the smallest to the most established initiatives. This ecosystem diversity backs the strength of European technological innovation, and maintaining the NGI initiative to provide structural support to software projects at the heart of worldwide innovation is key to enforce the sovereignty of a European infrastructure.
Contrary to common perception, technical innovations often originate from European rather than North American programming communities, and are mostly initiated by small-scaled organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A new major version of NumPy]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981663/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981663/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T16:41:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 
NumPy project 
released version 2.0.0 on
June 16, the first major release of the widely
used Python-based numeric-computing library since 2006. The release has been planned for some
time, as an opportunity to clean up NumPy's API. As with most NumPy updates,
there are performance improvements to several individual functions. There are only a few new
features, but several backward-incompatible changes, including a change to
NumPy's numeric-promotion rules. Changes to the Python API require relatively minor changes to
Python code using the library, but the changes to the C API may be more
difficult to adapt to. In
both cases, the official

migration guide describes what needs to be adapted to the new version.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Restricting execution of scripts — the third approach]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982085/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982085/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T14:05:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel will not consent to execute just any file that happens to be
sitting in a filesystem; there are formalities, such as the checking of
execute permission and consulting security policies, to get through first.
On some systems, security policies have been established to limit execution
to specifically approved programs.  But there are files that are not
executed directly by the kernel; these include scripts fed to language
interpreters like Python, Perl, or a shell.  An attacker who is able to get
an interpreter to execute a file may be able to bypass a system's security
policies.  Mickaël Salaün has been working on closing this hole for years;
the latest
attempt takes the form of a new flag to the execveat()
system call.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982559/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982559/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T13:19:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (firefox, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, java-21-openjdk, libndp, openssh, qt5-qtbase, ruby, skopeo, and thunderbird), Debian (thunderbird), Fedora (dotnet6.0, httpd, python-django, python-django4.2, qt6-qtbase, rapidjson, and ruby), Red Hat (389-ds-base, firefox, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, libndp, qt5-qtbase, and thunderbird), Slackware (httpd), SUSE (apache2, chromium, and kernel), and Ubuntu (apache2, linux-aws, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-aws-6.5, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-oracle-6.5, linux-starfive-6.5, and linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Virtual Machinations: Using Large Language Models as Neural Computers]]></title>
        <id>3676287</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3676287"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing quantum computers with energy-efficiency in mind]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482844</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/designing-quantum-computers-with-energy-efficiency-in-mind/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:45:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We can build quantum computers in a way that can help tackle climate change-related problems without releasing excessive additional CO2 into the atmosphere. Any other...
The post Designing quantum computers with energy-efficiency in mind appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Ghibaudi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[봄쑥 봉골레 파스타]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112468</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112468"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T08:36:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[육수를 먼저 만들도록 하자. 아니 파스타 말건데 웬 국물이냐고? 세상에 존재하는 모든 육수는 졸이면 소스가 된다. 그게 맛이 좋냐, 나쁘냐의 문제일 뿐이다. 토마토나 크림파스타의 맛이 소스 맛이듯, 봉골레나 알리오 올리오 같은 오일 베이스 파스타의 경우도 맛을 결정짓는 것은 소스다. 아무도 그렇게 부르지 않지만, 알리오 올리오를 만들기 위해 넉넉한 올리브 오일에 마늘과 페퍼론치노와 파슬리를 넣고 나중에...
The post 봄쑥 봉골레 파스타 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최명진</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Metaspace setting and tuning in JDK 8+ Applications (in and outside containers)]]></title>
        <id>3b7cde7e-16cd-4bea-ac57-0d2cfed15d76</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/19/metaspace-setting-and-tuning-jdk-8-applications-and-outside-containers"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since JDK 8, including upper versions, Metaspace has been set apart from the main heap section of memory and set via MetaspaceSize and MaxMetaspace flags. Objectively, this means metadata of loading classes in Java are set in the non-heap region also known as the native region of the memory (again, not inside the heap).
This Metaspace region is a change from previous versions, which had Java Metaspace as part of the heap in the so-called "Permanent Generation" and was set using the Java Virtual Machine (JVM) flag: PermSize and MaxPermSize. 
Although this discussion is very well settled, this article aims to review Metaspace, its tuning, and the consequences for container and non-container usage. It also adds troubleshooting steps in case those are needed.
Metaspace explanation
As briefly m…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트럼프의 픽은 ‘리틀 트럼프’… 그가 그리는 더 큰 그림은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79679</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/18/npsp_jdvance/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_jdvance"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T02:15:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[공화당 전당대회가 성황리에 열리고 있습니다. 잠시 후 도널드 트럼프 전 대통령이 정식으로 당의 후보 지명을 수락하고 연설할 예정입니다. 전당대회 첫 날에서야 공개된 트럼프의 러닝메이트는 초선 상원의원인 J.D. 밴스(오하이오)였습니다. 밴스 의원의 이력과 트럼프가 그를 선택한 이유를 분석한 칼럼을 번역하고, 추가로 트럼프가 그리는 큰그림은 무엇일지 짚어봤습니다. 전문 번역: 39살의 ‘흙수저 신인’이 트럼프의 부통령 후보로 지명된 이유는 해설: 트럼프의 픽은 ‘리틀 트럼프’… 그가 그리는 더 큰 그림은]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 딜레마, 배신자일수록 배신을 두려워한다: 슬로우레터 7월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112405</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112405"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T22:09:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대법원이 동성 부부를 인정했다. “사랑이 이겼다.” 쟁점과 현안. 채 상병 1주기. “신중하지 못했다.” 주워 담을 수 있겠나. 25만 원 민생지원법 행안위 통과. 더 깊게 읽기. “모두 문재인 정권에서 일어난 일.” 결국 상속세도 손댄다. 상속세 부담 OECD 최고라는 착각. 부동산 서울 쏠림. 다르게 읽기. 체코 원전 덤핑? 9조 원 더 받았다. “국가 경사, 두 신문만 1면에...
The post 윤석열 딜레마, 배신자일수록 배신을 두려워한다: 슬로우레터 7월19일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Peter de Schrijver RIP]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982470/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982470/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T21:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sad news that Peter de Schrijver has passed away has just reached us.  An obituary in Dutch relates that he passed in a Helsinki hospital on July 12.  Mind Software Consulting, which he founded, has a message of condolences as well.
De Schrijver was a Debian Developer and a Linux kernel contributor; he will be missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to train your cat to code: bizarre learning approaches]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1144/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1144/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Has your little hamster forgotten how to write C# code? Is it trying to get back into programming, but time has flown by so fast that C# 12 has already come out? Or maybe your kitty can't plan an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google URL Shortener links will no longer be available]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-url-shortener-links-will-no-longer-be-available/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-url-shortener-links-will-no-longer-be-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T20:14:33.175Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand how you will be impacted by our decision to turn off the serving portion of Google URL Shortener.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Evolving the ASF Brand (Apache Software Foundation blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982392/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982392/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T16:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Apache Software Foundation (ASF)
has announced
that it will be changing its logo to remove the feather that has been part
of its brand since 1997.  ASF members will have input on the rebranding process and be
able to vote on the new logo, which will be unveiled at the Community Over Code conference in October.


The feather is a well-loved and iconic part of the ASF brand. We know of community members who have ASF feather tattoos. People love taking photos with the feather at our flagship event each year. 

So why would we change it? As a non-Indigenous entity, we acknowledge that it is inappropriate for the Foundation to use Indigenous themes or language. We thank Natives in Tech and other members of the broader open source community for bringing this issue to the forefront. Today we are announcing we will be retiring the feather icon and logo and replacing it with a new logo that embodies the Foundation's rich history of providing software for the public good.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A bunch of new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982379/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982379/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T15:07:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released seven new stable kernels: 6.9.10, 6.6.41, 6.1.100, 5.15.163, 5.10.222, 5.4.280, and 4.19.318.  As usual, each contains important
fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Filesystem testing for stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982099/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982099/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T14:39:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leah Rumancik led a filesystem-track session at
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit on the testing needed to
qualify 
XFS patches for the stable kernels.  At last year's summit,
Rumancik, Amir Goldstein, and Chandan Babu Rajendra presented on their efforts to test and
backport fixes for the XFS filesystem to three separate stable kernels.
There has been some longstanding unhappiness in
the XFS-development community
with the stable-kernel process, which led to
backports ceasing for that filesystem until Goldstein started working on XFS testing for the stable
trees a few years ago.  In this year's session, Rumancik updated
attendees on how things had gone over the last year and wanted to discuss some
remaining pain points for the process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The first half of the 6.11 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982034/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982034/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T14:31:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The merge window for the 6.11 kernel release opened on July 14; as of
this writing, 4,072 non-merge changesets have been pulled into the mainline
repository since then.  This merge window, in other words, is just now
beginning.  Still, there has been enough time for a number of interesting
changes to land for the next kernel release; read on for a summary of what
has been merged so far.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982378/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982378/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T14:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (freeradius), Red Hat (firefox, java-1.8.0-openjdk, and java-17-openjdk), Slackware (openssl), SUSE (ghostscript, gnutls, podman, and python-Django), and Ubuntu (linux-hwe-6.5, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-oracle-5.15, linux-oracle, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, and stunnel).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hash-Based Bisect Debugging in Compilers and Runtimes]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/bisect</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/bisect"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T14:18:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Binary search over program code or execution to find why a new library or compiler causes a failure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 beta 4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/07/python-3130-beta-4-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/07/python-3130-beta-4-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T14:16:00.003Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.13 beta 4.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130b4/
 
This is a beta preview of Python 3.13
Python 3.13 is still in development.  This release, 3.13.0b4, is the final beta release preview of 3.13.
Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the 
opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their 
projects to support the new feature release.
We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects to test with 3.13 during the beta phase and report issues found to the Python bug tracker
 as soon as possible.  While the release is planned to be feature 
complete entering the beta phase, it is possible that features may be 
modified or, in rare cases, deleted up until the start of the rel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accessing Red Hat Data Grid in Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform 4]]></title>
        <id>9317d845-0592-43a8-9e20-87ddf3af6bf6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/18/accessing-red-hat-data-grid-red-hat-openshift-container-platform-4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Data Grid is a stable product for in-memory distributing caching solutions. In Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform, Data Grid can be installed via Data Grid Operator or Helm Charts can be used to deploy Data Grid 8 and have containers deployed running Data Grid. Those pods can then join together in a cluster—therefore having clustering capabilities.
Given the deployment of the Data Grid cluster as described above and with the pods deployed, the next step is to access the Data Grid cluster. 
When accessing the clustering within the OpenShift Container Platform cluster—i.e., when the application access is done inside OpenShift Container Platform—the communication can be via internal service. However, if the application is outside OpenShift Container Platform, Data Grid must expose a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[왕년의 종군 기자, 이진숙은 왜 민주주의와 싸우는가.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112357</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112357"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T06:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열(대통령)이 이진숙(전 대전MBC 사장)을 방송통신위원회 위원장 후보로 지명했다. 청문회에서 격렬한 비판이 쏟아지겠지만 임명을 강행할 가능성이 크다. 민주당은 이진숙이 안건을 하나라도 의결하면 곧바로 탄핵을 밀어붙인다는 계획이다. ‘런동관’에 이어 ‘런홍일’, ‘런진숙’의 해프닝이 계속될 전망이다. 이진숙이라는 카드. MBC 시절 잘 나가던 종군 기자 아니었나. 방통위원장 자리가 이렇게 뜨거운 이유가 뭔가. 이동관은 석 달, 김홍일은 반년 조금 넘게 버텼다....
The post 왕년의 종군 기자, 이진숙은 왜 민주주의와 싸우는가. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 18, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981628/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981628/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T00:01:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 18, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Schematic Review Checklist for Firmware Engineers]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/schematic-review-checklist</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/schematic-review-checklist"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Schematic reviews are a part of the hardware development cycle in many if not
most, hardware development companies. Typically led by the electrical
engineering team, it is easy to overlook design issues that will be important to
the firmware team. This post tells of a few stories of design misses that I have
made and puts some common lessons learned into a checklist for other firmware
engineers. It is not meant to be an exhaustive list, but rather a starting point
for a firmware engineer to build their own checklist with the goal of helping
teams catch software/hardware interaction bugs earlier in the design cycle when
they’re cheaper to fix.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 둘이 같은 목소리 낼 때도 있네? ‘두 번째 차이나 쇼크’ 어떻게 될까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79391</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/17/npsp_chinashock/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_chinashock"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:59:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 22일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 2016년, 도널드 트럼프가 공화당 대통령 후보가 됐을 때 미국 언론은 트럼프가 깬 여러 가지 금기나 관행에 주목했습니다. 그 가운데 하나가 자유무역에 대한 생각이었습니다. 미국이란 나라가 건국되고 다른 나라와 무역을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열이 읽어야 할 새치기를 잘 하는 방법: 슬로우레터 7월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112320</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112320"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T22:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“멈춰야 한다”, 우원식의 제안. 쟁점과 현안. 김용현의 통화, ‘빼박’ 증거가 나왔다. “이러다 다 죽는다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 탈탈 털었다, 민주당만. 30조 원 원전 수주, 덤핑 논란. 미저리 비율. 트럼프 총격 이후 윤석열 메시지까지 7시간. 다르게 읽기. 미국 검찰에 탈탈 털린 국정원의 스파이. 종부세 폐지? 4가지를 생각해 보자. 해법과 대안. 언론이 여성을 이야기하는 방법. 오송 지하차도...
The post 윤석열이 읽어야 할 새치기를 잘 하는 방법: 슬로우레터 7월18일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Genkit for Go: Build scalable AI-powered apps in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-genkit-for-go-build-scalable-ai-powered-apps-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-genkit-for-go-build-scalable-ai-powered-apps-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T20:14:29.703Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Genkit for Go is an open source framework for building AI-powered applications in Go. It leverages Go's simplicity, scalability, and security, and is currently in alpha.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The I/O journey continues in Bengaluru]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/the-io-journey-continues-in-bengaluru/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/the-io-journey-continues-in-bengaluru/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T20:14:29.703Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's I/O Connect event in Bengaluru highlighted India's contributions to AI and introduced new tools for app development, including AI agents for coding and testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome India to the Google Wallet API]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T20:14:29.703Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To all developers in India: Welcome to the Google Wallet API! Now you can create digital assets like boarding passes, event tickets, gift cards, loyalty cards, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about Google Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T20:14:29.703Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the new features and enhancements Google Wallet announced at I/O this year, focused on security, wearables, push notifications, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reality AI Explorer provides sandbox for AI/ML development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482839</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/reality-ai-explorer-provides-sandbox-for-ai-ml-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T20:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New Reality AI Explorer Tier provides users with free access to a comprehensive, self-guided evaluation sandbox.
The post Reality AI Explorer provides sandbox for AI/ML development appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NXP receives Car Connectivity Consortium digital key certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482835</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nxp-receives-car-connectivity-consortium-digital-key-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T19:45:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NXP's system solution encompasses the full digital car key ecosystem across Ultra-Wideband (UWB), NFC chips and Bluetooth Low Energy (LE). 
The post NXP receives Car Connectivity Consortium digital key certification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Design services more prominent as system complexity grows]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482797</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/design-services-more-prominent-as-system-complexity-grows/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T17:36:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Growth in design services reflects more general growth in the need for more design capability to address massively increasing system design complexity, driven by the need for more compute and AI-driven applications.
The post Design services more prominent as system complexity grows appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blender 4.2 LTS released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982286/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982286/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T15:38:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
4.2 LTS of the Blender
open-source 3D creation suite has been released. Major improvements
include a rewrite of the EEVEE
render engine, faster rendering, and much more. See the showcase
reel for examples of work created by the Blender community with
this release.
See the text release
notes for even more about 4.2 LTS, which will be maintained until
July 2026.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Changing the filesystem-maintenance model]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981854/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981854/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T14:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintenance of the kernel is a difficult, often thankless, task; how it is
being handled, the role of maintainers, burnout, and so on are recurring
topics at kernel-related conferences.  At
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Josef Bacik and
Christian Brauner led a session to discuss possible changes to the way
filesystems are maintained, though Bacik took the lead role (and the podium).  There are a number of interrelated topics,
including merging new filesystems, removing old ones, making and testing changes
throughout the filesystem tree, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[digiKam 8.4.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982276/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982276/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T14:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.4.0 of the digiKam photo editing and management
application has been released. This
release includes an update of the LibRaw RAW decoder which
brings support for many new cameras, a new version of the LensFun
toolkit, a feature for automatic translation of image tags, GMIC-Qt 3.4.0, and many
bug fixes. See the announcement for full details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silva:  How to use the new counted_by attribute in C (and Linux)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982275/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982275/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T14:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gustavo A. R. Silva describes
the path to safer flexible arrays in the kernel, thanks to the
counted_by attribute supported by Clang 18 and GCC 15.


	There are a number of requirements to properly use the
	counted_by attribute. One crucial requirement is that the
	counter must be initialized before the first reference to the
	flexible-array member. Another requirement is that the array must
	always contain at least as many elements as indicated by the
	counter.


See also: this article from 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982270/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982270/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T13:14:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel), Fedora (golang and krb5), Red Hat (cups, firefox, git, java-21-openjdk, kernel, linux-firmware, nghttp2, nodejs, and podman), SUSE (libndp, nodejs18, nodejs20, tomcat, and xen), and Ubuntu (gtk+2.0, gtk+3.0 and linux-hwe-5.4, linux-oracle-5.4).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서울 경기 여름 물놀이 계곡 추천]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595532</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595532/%ec%97%ac%eb%a6%84-%eb%ac%bc%eb%86%80%ec%9d%b4-%ea%b3%84%ea%b3%a1-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T12:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panasonic offers Matter certification service for smart home deployments]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482789</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/panasonic-offers-matter-certification-service-for-smart-home-deployments/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:47:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Launched as a three-tier service, the baseline PAN-MaX silver service delivers X.509 certificate injection from Panasonic managed PKI infrastructure into compatible Panasonic wireless modules.
The post Panasonic offers Matter certification service for smart home deployments appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing USB in embedded systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482783</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/implementing-usb-in-embedded-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:04:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[USB can be easily added into a design using an ASIC at the cost of a larger BOM or, alternatively, using a microcontroller with USB...
The post Implementing USB in embedded systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Robert Perkel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How customer support and engineering teams can work better together]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482774</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-customer-support-and-engineering-teams-can-work-better-together/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T10:28:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the years I’ve talked to so many support teams that see engineering as where bug reports go to die, while engineers complain that support...
The post How customer support and engineering teams can work better together appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coleman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[플랫폼 노동: 문제는 기술이 아니라 독점이다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111480</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111480"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:01:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인트로: 플랫폼 노동의 현실 본론으로 들어가기 전에 독자의 이해를 돕기 위해 몇 가지 용어와 사례를 소개한다. 더불어 ‘라이더, 혁신의 노예'(오마이뉴스, 2022) 기획 연재 기사를 추천한다. 두 가지 플랫폼 플랫폼 노동에는 이슈가 꽤 많다. 노동자성(근로자성, 근로기준법 적용 여부를 가르는 기준)을 따지는 게 중요하긴 한데, 우선은 플랫폼의 두 가지 종류를 구별하는 게 중요하다. 우선, 온라인 플랫폼(Web-based Platform)이...
The post 플랫폼 노동: 문제는 기술이 아니라 독점이다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MCUXpresso IDE v11.10: Easy MCU-Link Firmware Update with Eclipse]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40907</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/07/17/mcuxpresso-ide-v11-10-easy-mcu-link-firmware-update-with-eclipse/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T07:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new NXP MCUXpresso IDE v11.10 offers an improved firmware update mechanism for MCU-Link (LinkServer) debug probes. With this update, the process becomes jumper-less and can be triggered directly from the Eclipse IDE. This enhancement makes firmware updates easier and more efficient, providing both a user interface and command line option for future modifications. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A brief introduction to Apps and Stacks Container Images]]></title>
        <id>363a6d62-d58b-496b-b070-7742c85a713a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/17/brief-introduction-apps-and-stacks-container-images"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article aims to describe Apps and Stacks container images from two perspectives: user’s and developer's.
Apps and Stacks container images can be divided into two groups: 

Source-to-Image (S2I) images 
No Source-to-Image (NoS2I) images

Source-to-Image (S2I) is a toolkit and workflow for building reproducible container images from source code.
S2I images are:

S2i-nodejs-container
S2i-php-container
S2i-ruby-container
S2i-python-container
Nginx-container
httpd-container

NoS2I images are:

Postgresql-container
Mysql-container
mariadb-container
Redis-container
varnish-container

Apps and Stacks container images support several operating systems like Fedora, CentOS Stream 8 (C8S), CentOS Stream 9 (C9S), Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8, and RHEL 9, and soon also RHEL 10. CentOS7 and RHE…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Petr Hracek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[넷플릭스 실적을 기다리는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595527</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595527/2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T03:01:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/17, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595518</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595518/7-17-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T02:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘넘사벽’ 이진숙, 여기서 끝이 아닐 수도 있다: 슬로우레터 7월17일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112231</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112231"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T22:17:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[차원이 다른 이진숙. 지금이 민주당 정권이라고 가정해 보자. 쟁점과 현안. 힐빌리의 노래, 속편. 트럼프는 한마디도 하지 않았다. 더 깊게 읽기. 디올 백 돌려주라 했다면 국고 횡령. 반란표 8표 나올 수도. 다르게 읽기. 검사도 울고 가족들도 울고. 엑시트 코리아. 해법과 대안. 첫 직장 잡기까지 11.5개월. 20대 81%가 캥거루족. 정치만 있고 정책은 없는 이유. 필리핀 가사 도우미,...
The post ‘넘사벽’ 이진숙, 여기서 끝이 아닐 수도 있다: 슬로우레터 7월17일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Firebase Genkit helped add AI to our Compass app]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T20:13:42.515Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We used Firebase Genkit – Firebase’s open source framework for building powerful AI features into your apps with familiar patterns and paradigms – to add AI to an existing application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] SUSE asks openSUSE to consider name change]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981018/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981018/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T16:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SUSE has, in a somewhat clumsy
fashion, asked openSUSE
to consider rebranding to clear up confusion over the
relationship between SUSE the company and openSUSE as a community
project. That, in turn, has opened conversations about revising
openSUSE governance and more. So far, there is no concrete proposal to
consider, no timeline, or even a process for the community and company
to follow to make any decisions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Hierarchical storage management, fanotify, FUSE, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981392/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981392/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T14:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amir Goldstein led a filesystem-track session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit on his project to build a
hierarchical
storage management (HSM) system using fanotify.
The idea is to monitor file access in order to determine when to retrieve
content from non-local storage (e.g. the cloud).  The session was a
follow-up to last year's introduction to the
project, which covered some of the problems he had encountered; this
year, he
was updating attendees on its status and progress, along with some other
problem areas that he wanted to discuss.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Redox to implement POSIX signals in user space]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982186/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982186/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T14:12:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redox has received a
grant to work on implementing POSIX-compatible signals. The

draft design calls for them to be implemented nearly completely in user space.



So far, the signals project has been going according to plan, and
hopefully, POSIX support for signals will be mostly complete by the
end of summer, with in-kernel improvements to process management.
After that, work on the userspace process manager will begin,
possibly including new kernel performance and/or functionality
improvements to facilitate this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory Utility for SQL Server (ADUTIL) now officially supported with RHEL 9]]></title>
        <id>ad812db3-40db-4a4f-9dbc-79990c80f560</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/16/active-directory-utility-sql-server-adutil-now-officially-supported-rhel-9"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of June 2024, Active Directory Utility for SQL Server (ADUTIL) is now officially supported with RHEL 9. SQL Server 2022 has as of July 2024 been officially certified with RHEL 9, and is now Generally Available on Red Hat Ecosystem Catalog.
The adutil tool is a command-line interface (CLI) utility for configuring and managing Windows Active Directory domains for SQL Server on Linux and containers, without switching between Windows and Linux machines to manage Active Directory. This tool was developed to ensure that users get the most out of authentication, user management, and keytab configuration in a more integrated setting.
Does this all sound good to you? Let's dive in and find out how exactly we can set up adutil on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 9. 
Prepping and installing
You wil…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivien Wang, Arne Arnold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying SQL Server on Linux using an Ansible playbook]]></title>
        <id>78b261d7-71f7-48bc-a468-395bf429e3b6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/16/deploying-sql-server-linux-using-ansible-playbook"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why deploy SQL Server on Linux using an Ansible playbook? The answer is that automation is a key aspect of modern IT operations, which is why we at Red Hat are delighted to announce that the deployment and configuration of Microsoft SQL Server on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) can be easily automated using Ansible and corresponding RHEL system roles for SQL Server. You can deploy high availability (HA) solutions, including configuring Always On availability groups. Ansible scripts can automate the entire deployment process, reducing manual intervention and minimizing errors.
SQL Server 2022 has as of July 2024 been officially certified with RHEL 9, and is now Generally Available on Red Hat Ecosystem Catalog.
Sounds good—what do I need to do?
First off, you’ll need an Azure subscription to…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivien Wang, Arne Arnold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982169/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982169/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T12:50:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel), Fedora (erlang-jose, mingw-python-certifi, and yt-dlp), Mageia (firefox, nss, libreoffice, sendmail, and tomcat), Red Hat (firefox, ghostscript, git-lfs, kernel, kernel-rt, ruby, and skopeo), SUSE (Botan, cockpit, kernel, nodejs18, p7zip, python3, and tomcat), and Ubuntu (ghostscript, linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gke, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-intel-iotg, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-nvidia, linux-oracle, linux-azure-6.5, linux-gcp-6.5, and linux-gke, linux-nvidia).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using dynamic power control to reduce heat in IDACs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482757</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/using-dynamic-power-control-to-reduce-heat-in-idacs/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T11:43:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic power control reduces on-chip power dissipation on a current output DAC (IDAC) and lowers the total power consumed while not impacting the load operation....
The post Using dynamic power control to reduce heat in IDACs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suraj Pai and Vikash Sethia</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Toolbx]]></title>
        <id>2a27bc4d-5450-47b0-a330-5e08203ab04a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/16/introducing-toolbx"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) offers a development and troubleshooting tool called Toolbx. It was first added to RHEL as a technical preview, but was later blessed as production ready in versions 8.8 and 9.2. This article provides a high level introduction to Toolbx, describing how it supports modern development and troubleshooting workflows with pointers to some lower level details.
What is Toolbx?
Toolbx is a tool for Linux, which allows the use of interactive command line environments for software development and troubleshooting the host operating system, without having to install software on the host. It is built on top of Podman and other standard container technologies from Open Container Initiative (OCI).
Every additional piece of software that’s installed on a production machine …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sumantro Mukherjee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved Right Sizing experience in Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes (RHACM)]]></title>
        <id>809162bf-d0de-47b0-8d73-03c09dd7f709</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/16/improved-right-sizing-experience-red-hat-advanced-cluster-management-kubernetes"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine having a feature that gives you—as a Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes (RHACM) Cluster Admin—the option to gather feedback on how efficiently developers use namespaces across all your clusters. This information would empower you to adjust resource controls settings and even enforce best practices if needed. In the long term, this would contribute to large cost savings in your organization. That is where RHACM Right Sizing capabilities becomes an asset and helps you achieve this scenario. 
RHACM Right Sizing complements other Red Hat features in Insights Advisor and Insights Cost Management that recommend your developers to follow best practices when deploying their workloads in the most efficient way. This way, you will be able to monitor whether the best practices…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vanessa Martini, Christian Stark</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘조지 클루니, 너마저…’ 바이든의 속내가 어떻든 지금은 ‘트럼프의 시간’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79657</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/15/npsp_rnctrump/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_rnctrump"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T02:00:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 토요일, 트럼프 전 대통령이 유세 현장에서 총격을 받았지만 다행히 목숨을 건지는 사건이 발생하면서 미국 대선 구도는 완전히 바뀌었습니다. 트럼프의 승리가 따놓은 당상이나 다름없어졌다는 분석이 나오는 가운데 공화당은 현지시각 오늘(15일)부터 나흘간 전당대회를 엽니다. 전당대회 첫날 트럼프는 J.D. 밴스 상원의원(오하이오)을 부통령 후보로 지명했습니다. 오늘 스프에 소개한 칼럼은 트럼프가 피습되기 전, 그러니까 민주당 내에서 바이든 대통령의 재선 출마를 만류하는 목소리가 한창 높아지던 때 배우 조지 클루니가 쓴 칼럼입니다. 끔찍한 참사가 될 뻔한 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/16, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595516</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595516/7-16-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T01:09:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역사적 장면? 우리가 트럼프 사진을 다시 봐야 하는 이유: 슬로우레터 7월16일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112184</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112184"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T22:22:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[총을 맞으면 사람이 달라진다. 다르게 읽기. 역사적인 장면이라고? 바이든 교체론도 잠잠. ‘트럼플레이션’이 온다. 쟁점과 현안. “김건희는 가방을 만진 적도 없다.” “일반 사건이면 각하됐을 것.” 수습이 안 된다. “배신자 꺼져라.” “입장들이야 다양할 수 있다.” 전공의들은 돌아오지 않았다. 더 깊게 읽기. 금융 시장의 네 가지 리스크. 부동산 ‘패닉 바잉’ 올 수도 있다. 서울 아파트 분양가 평당 4190만...
The post 역사적 장면? 우리가 트럼프 사진을 다시 봐야 하는 이유: 슬로우레터 7월16일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A hash table by any other name]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/972580/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/972580/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T17:27:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 25, Matthew Wilcox posted

a second version of a patch set
introducing a new
data structure called rosebush, which
"is a resizing, scalable, cache-aware, RCU optimised hash
table." The kernel already has generic hash tables, though, including
rhashtable. Wilcox believes that the design of
rhashtable is not the best choice for performance, and has written rosebush as
an alternative for use in the

directory-entry cache (dcache) — the filesystem cache used to speed up
file-name lookup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Development statistics for the 6.10 kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981559/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981559/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:52:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10 kernel was released
on July 14 after a nine-week development cycle.  This time around,
13,312 non-merge changesets were pulled into the mainline repository — the
lowest changeset count since 5.17 in early 2022.  Longstanding tradition
says that it is time for LWN to gather some statistics on where the new
code for 6.10 came from and how it got to the mainline; read on for the
details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 6.6.40 and 6.1.99]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982049/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982049/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T15:41:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has released the 6.6.40
and 6.1.99 stable kernels.  Both contain a
fix for the USB subsystem; anyone who uses those kernel series and "the XHCI
USB host controller driver (i.e. USB 3) must upgrade".]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/982029/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/982029/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T14:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (cups, krb5, pgadmin4, python3.6, and yarnpkg), Mageia (freeradius, kernel, kmod-xtables-addons, kmod-virtualbox, and dwarves, kernel-linus, and squid), Red Hat (ghostscript, kernel, and less), SUSE (avahi, c-ares, cairo, cups, fdo-client, gdk-pixbuf, git, libarchive, openvswitch3, podman, polkit, python-black, python-Jinja2, python-urllib3, skopeo, squashfs, tiff, traceroute, and wget), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How insecure is Avast Secure Browser?]]></title>
        <id>https://palant.info/2024/07/15/how-insecure-is-avast-secure-browser/</id>
        <link href="https://palant.info/2024/07/15/how-insecure-is-avast-secure-browser/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T12:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago I already looked into Avast Secure Browser. Back then it didn’t end well for Avast: I found critical vulnerabilities allowing arbitrary websites to infect user’s computer. Worse yet: much of it was due to neglect of secure coding practices, existing security mechanisms were disabled for no good reason. I didn’t finish that investigation because I discovered that the browser was essentially spyware, collecting your browsing history and selling it via Avast’s Jumpshot subsidiary.
But that was almost five years ago. After an initial phase of denial, Avast decided to apologize and to wind down Jumpshot. It was certainly a mere coincidence that Avast was subsequently sold to NortonLifeLock, called Gen Digital today. Yes, Avast is truly reformed and paying for their crimes in Europe …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Almost Secure</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-driven SRAM demand needs integrated repair and security]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482750</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ai-driven-sram-demand-needs-integrated-repair-and-security/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T12:24:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Increasing popularity of AI applications and DPU architecture has led to growing demand for higher SRAM densities, in turn placing challenges on SRAM yield and reliability.
The post AI-driven SRAM demand needs integrated repair and security appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Meng-Yi Wu</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서학개미 트렌드를 추종하는 ETF, ACE 미국주식베스트셀러]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595508</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595508/ace-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d%eb%b2%a0%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%ec%85%80%eb%9f%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T10:56:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[24년 2분기 스마트폰 성장율 및 스마트폰 점유율, 삼성 스마트폰 점유율 18.9%로 1위 차지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595506</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595506/24%eb%85%84-2%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%8a%a4%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8%ed%8f%b0-%ec%84%b1%ec%9e%a5%ec%9c%a8-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%8a%a4%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8%ed%8f%b0-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T07:52:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating and deploying an OVF Template to support image mode for RHEL at scale]]></title>
        <id>5f3c78b1-8af0-40d6-90f1-ca5c8c5e752b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/15/creating-and-deploying-ovf-template-support-image-mode-rhel-scale"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T07:11:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Repeatability and consistency -- These are tenants of cloud native infrastructure and just some of the many benefits that are inherently found within container images which led to the rapid adoption of the technology. Image mode for RHEL extends many of the benefits of running containers and applies them to building, deploying and managing traditional Operating System environments.
In the preceding articles (Creating a VMDK using image mode for RHEL and Integrating an image mode for RHEL produced VMDK into vSphere), we described the process for producing a VMDK file with image mode for RHEL, publishing the resulting file to a VMware vSphere environment, and creating a new Virtual Machine using the VMDK as the primary disk drive for the machine. These steps illustrated just how easy it can …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ansible Collection for Red Hat Runtimes]]></title>
        <id>4586f01f-de4c-42ea-aa58-e998b4a36963</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/15/ansible-collection-red-hat-runtimes"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several of the key products of the Red Hat Runtimes portfolio (Red Hat JBoss Enterprise Application Platform (EAP), Red Hat JBoss Web Server, Red Hat AMQ including streams for Apache Kafka and AMQ Broker, Red Hat build of Keycloak, etc.) now offer an integration within Ansible. Following the open source model of Red Hat, those extensions for Ansible have both a community version and a productized version. To help users better understand the philosophy behind this approach, this article explains in detail the differences between each option and how they can be used.
Many, if not all, Red Hat products have origins in open source or free software communities and are developed by both contributors of the project and employees of the company. A few famous examples include Red Hat Enterprise Lin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romain Pelisse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Integrating a VMDK produced with image mode for RHEL into vSphere]]></title>
        <id>7fb1c838-c6ea-40a0-95ac-56dc21056dcb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/15/integrating-vmdk-produced-image-mode-rhel-vsphere"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T06:55:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Change can be hard. This is especially true when applying a new set of technologies or approaches. Fortunately, image mode for RHEL takes many of the benefits that are found in container technologies, including a simplified build process and portability across a variety of environments, and applies them to traditional Virtual Machine workflows. In the prior post, Creating a VMDK using image mode for RHEL, a VMDK-formatted disk image was produced as an output from a bootc image.  
While the VMDK format is open source, they are traditionally used within the VMware family of solutions, such as VMware Workstation and VMware vSphere. In this post, we will describe how the previously created VMDK disk can be used as the basis for a virtual machine hosted in a VMware vSphere environment.
Read mor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘살아 있는 전설’ 학전 김민기에 관한 뒤늦은, 그래도 고마운 3부작 다큐멘터리]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112156</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112156"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T06:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[그것이 알고 싶다]에서 끈질기게 미제사건 실마리를 추적해온 이동원 PD, [TV동물농장]에서 가수 이효리와 반려견 순심의 이별 이야기로 반려인들의 마음을 어루만진 고혜린 PD, [집사부일체]에서 다양한 분야 사부들을 통해 깨달음을 선사한 김명정 작가. SBS를 대표하는 시사, 교양, 예능프로그램 PD와 작가가 정통 다큐멘터리 [SBS스페셜]로 뭉쳤다. 33년 만에 문을 닫는 학전과 학전을 탄생시킨 김민기를 조명하기 위해서였다. 이동원 PD와 고혜린 PD는...
The post ‘살아 있는 전설’ 학전 김민기에 관한 뒤늦은, 그래도 고마운 3부작 다큐멘터리 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만삭스, 테슬라 실적 긍정적이나 수요 우려는 여전해 테슬라 주가 상승 여력은 제한적 평가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595502</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595502/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9-%ec%97%ac%eb%a0%a5"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T06:32:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating a VMDK using image mode for Red Hat Enterprise Linux]]></title>
        <id>5ff9f741-a02c-47b7-9952-5cffade58ebe</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/15/creating-vmdk-using-image-mode-red-hat-enterprise-linux"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T06:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image mode for Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) combines the benefits and methodologies of container technologies with the ability to operate within traditional virtual machine environments. By enabling a familiar container image assembly process that supports several popular output types, end users have the flexibility to choose where and how they want to operate.
One of the supported output formats is a Virtual Machine Disk (VMDK), which is commonly used within VMware’s supported virtualization platforms, like vSphere, but support is also available elsewhere, including VirtualBox. Bridging the gap between traditional operating environments and cloud-native technologies is one of the benefits that image mode provides. Over the course of this series, we will describe the process for creatin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Block</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/15, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595493</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595493/7-15-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T01:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10 kernel has been released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981961/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981961/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T23:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has
released
the 6.10 kernel.


	So the final week was perhaps not quite as quiet as the preceding
	ones, which I don't love - but it also wasn't noisy enough to
	warrant an extra rc.



Changes in 6.10 include
the removal of support for some ancient Alpha CPUs,
shadow-stack support for the x32 sub-architecture,
Rust-language support on RISC-V systems,
support for some Windows NT synchronization
primitives (though it is marked "broken" in 6.10),
the mseal() system call,
fsverity
support in the FUSE filesystem subsystem,
ioctl() support in the Landlock security
module,
the memory-allocation profiling subsystem,
and more.


See the LWN merge-window summaries (part 1, part 2) and the KernelNewbies 6.10 page
for more details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모든 것이 정치다, 트럼프 총격 사건이 말하는 것: 슬로우레터 7월15일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112092</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112092"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T22:21:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[유력 대통령 후보가 죽을 뻔했다. 트럼프 당선 확률 69%. 주먹 불끈 트럼프. 800달러짜리 총. 가자지구에서는 100여 명 사망. 쟁점과 현안. 김용현도 임성근 배후였다. “VIP는 김건희”, 이종호의 말 바꾸기. 특검 거부권? 상설 특검으로 간다. 한동훈 댓글팀, 2년 동안 댓글 6만 개. “대선 때 있던 애들 좀 써야 되는 거 아닙니까.” 오늘 전공의 사직 처리 마감일. 친명일색...
The post 모든 것이 정치다, 트럼프 총격 사건이 말하는 것: 슬로우레터 7월15일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Program fault reports are caused by its users]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=9222</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/07/14/program-fault-reports-are-caused-by-its-users/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T22:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faults are generated by users of the software; no users, no fault reports. Fault reports will be generated for software that is free of coding mistakes; one study found that 42.6% of fault reports were misclassified as either requests for an enhancement, changes to documentation, or a refactoring request, or not requiring changes to the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cursed fire, or magic of C preprocessor]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1143/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1143/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered if you could fully write code using only the #define directive in C? It's well-known that the C++ templates are Turing-complete—developers write ray tracers that do all...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“억장이 무너진다”, 민주당의 감세 딜레마.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=112035</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/112035"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T07:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 종부세 폐지를 이야기하는 이재명의 ‘먹사니즘’ 손익 전망. “‘먹사니즘’이 유일한 이데올로기여야 한다.” 이재명(민주당 전 대표)이 당 대표 출마 선언을 하면서 한 말이 심상치 않다. “종합부동산세를 근본적으로 검토할 때가 됐다”고 한 걸 두고 동아일보는 “대권 주자로서 차별화된 면모를 강조했다”고 평가했다. 그동안 민주당에서 종부세 완화를 이야기한 의원들이 몇 있었지만 이재명이 직접 종부세를 언급한 건 처음이다. 이게 왜...
The post “억장이 무너진다”, 민주당의 감세 딜레마. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[22 Common Filesystem Tasks in C++20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/common-filesystem-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/common-filesystem-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-14T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with the filesystem can be a daunting task, but it doesn’t have to be. In this post, I’ll walk you through some of the most common filesystem operations using the powerful features introduced in C++17, as well as some new enhancements in C++20/23. Whether you’re creating directories, copying files, or managing permissions, these examples will help you understand and efficiently utilize the std::filesystem library.
Let’s start.



     
    



1. Creating Directories 
  




     
    


Creating directories is a basic yet essential operation. The std::filesystem library makes this straightforward with the create_directory function.
#include <filesystem>
#include <iostream>

int main() {
    std::filesystem::path dir = "example_directory";
    if (std::filesystem::create_directory(…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How it's Made: GenType Alphabet Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T20:14:18.744Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of our newest experiments in the series is GenType. This tool uses generative AI to create an alphabet out of anything you want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNOME Foundation Announces Transition of Executive Director]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981850/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981850/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T17:51:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNOME Foundation has announced
that executive director Holly Million is stepping down at the end of
July, and will be replaced by Richard Littauer as interim executive
director:
On behalf of the whole GNOME community, the Board of Directors
would like to give our utmost thanks to Holly for her achievements
during the past 10 months, including drafting a bold five-year
strategic plan for the Foundation, securing two important fiscal
sponsorship agreements with GIMP and Black Python Devs, writing our
first funding proposal that will now enable the Foundation to apply
for more grants, vastly improving our financial operations, and
implementing a break-even budget to preserve our financial
reserves.
The Foundation's Interim Executive Director, Richard Littauer,
brings years of open source leadership as part of his work as an
organizer of SustainOSS and CURIOSS, as a sustainability coordinator
at the Open Source Initiative, and as a community development manager
at Open Source Collective, and through open source contributions to
many projects, such as Node.js and IPFS. The Board appointed Richard
in June and is confident in his ability to guide the Foundation during
this transitional period.


Million says she is leaving to pursue a PhD in psychology. The
board plans to announce its search plan for a permanent executive
directory after GUADEC, which takes
place July 19 through 24.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Active Directory Utility for SQL Server (ADUTIL) now officially supported with RHEL 9]]></title>
        <id>ad812db3-40db-4a4f-9dbc-79990c80f560</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/12/active-directory-utility-sql-server-adutil-now-officially-supported-rhel-9"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As of June 2024, Active Directory Utility for SQL Server (ADUTIL) is now officially supported with RHEL 9. The adutil tool is a command-line interface (CLI) utility for configuring and managing Windows Active Directory domains for SQL Server on Linux and containers, without switching between Windows and Linux machines to manage Active Directory. This tool was developed to ensure that users get the most out of authentication, user management, and keytab configuration in a more integrated setting.
Does this all sound good to you? Let's dive in and find out how exactly we can set up adutil on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 9. 
Prepping and installing
You will need to join your host machine to the domain as a prerequisite—see Join SQL Server on Linux to Active Directory on how to get this all…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivien Wang, Arne Arnold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A look at Linux Mint 22]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981130/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981130/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T14:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Mint has released a beta of its
next long-term-support (LTS) release, Linux Mint 22 (code-named "Wilma"), based on Ubuntu 24.04. Aside from the standard
software updates that come with any major upgrade, some of Wilma's
largest selling points are what it doesn't have; namely snap
packages or GNOME applications that have broken theming on non-GNOME
desktops like Mint's Cinnamon desktop.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981813/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981813/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T13:06:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (apache2), Fedora (mingw-python3 and python-urllib3), Oracle (dotnet6.0, dotnet8.0, fence-agents, openssh, pki-core, and virt:ol and virt-devel:rhel), SUSE (apache2, firefox, libvpx, oniguruma, python-zipp, python310, thunderbird, and tomcat10), and Ubuntu (apache2, apport, linux, linux-azure, linux-gcp, linux-ibm, linux-intel, linux-lowlatency, linux-oem-6.8, linux-raspi, linux, linux-gcp, linux-nvidia-6.5, linux-raspi, linux-gke, and python-django).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세 가지 양파를 사용한 제육볶음]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111953</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111953"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T08:26:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[캐러멀라이즈 양파, 한식의 구원자 (연재 속 특집) 들어가며 여러 편에 걸쳐 한식과 설탕, 그리고 그 단맛의 대안으로써 양파를 위시한 야채의 활용을 입에 올렸으니 이제 실제 예시를 드는 것이 도리일 듯하다. 한식을 이야기하며 여태 비중 있게 다뤘던 부분 중 하나는 단연 ‘장’이었다. 그러니 장이 주인공의 역할을 하는 동시에 우리 모두에게 익숙한 일상의 메뉴로 배움을 시험해 보도록...
The post 세 가지 양파를 사용한 제육볶음 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>펜타클</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use of Cryostat and Java Flight Recording in Red Hat OpenShift 4]]></title>
        <id>2633d0c1-7f4a-4055-bcb7-e4dc04aba9e1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/12/use-cryostat-and-java-flight-recording-red-hat-openshift-4"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Collecting troubleshooting data, like creating a heap dump, can considerably impact the performance of an application, particularly critical ones. Creating a heap dump on production can (and most of the time will) directly impact the Java Virtual Machine's (JVM) performance for a few seconds of applications deployed. 
To reduce the overhead of usage (i.e., overhead on data capture), one alternative is to use a lower overhead capturing framework such as Java Flight Recording (JFR) data. This data can be later analyzed offline and used to track down memory usage, high CPU utilization, and thread inspection, for example. But it can be even more useful depending on the events it records. 
For Red Hat OpenShift deployments, you can collect data via the Red Hat build of Cryostat Operator, which …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쓰러졌다? 우선 의식과 호흡 체크, 긴가민가하면 심폐소생술! 망설이지 마!]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111935</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111935"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T04:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[새우를 반주 삼아 술잔이 깊어지던 어느 밤. 쿵 하는 소리가 들렸다. 맞은 편에서 소주를 들이켜던 형님이 반사적으로 뛰쳐나갔다. 등 뒤로 고개를 돌려보니 사람이 쓰러져 있었다. 형님은 특수구조대원이었고 나는 응급의학과 전문의였으니 우리 둘은 말하자면 사람 살리는 선수들이었다. 일하는 장소와 방식은 다르지만 도움이 필요한 곳에 나서는 걸 주저하지 않는 사람들이기도 하다. 그날도 우리의 술안주는 1년 전 네팔에서...
The post 쓰러졌다? 우선 의식과 호흡 체크, 긴가민가하면 심폐소생술! 망설이지 마! appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>조용수</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/12, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595491</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595491/7-12-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T02:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/11, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595472</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595472/7-11-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-%eb%b3%b4%ea%b3%a0%ec%84%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T01:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오펜하이머, 테슬라는 건전성 유지 전략을 성공적으로 수행중이나 FSD 수익화 가능성은 미확실]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595488</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595488/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5-sfd-%ec%88%98%ec%9d%b5%ed%99%94-%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T01:26:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/12, DataTrek, 테슬라 주가는 미래 기대감에 의지하고 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595485</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595485/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-2"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T01:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices in firmware]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-07-12:/best-practices-in-firmware.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/best-practices-in-firmware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Across the years spent writing firmware I have come across
techniques that have helped me with reliability, meeting delivery deadlines,
and overall "debug quality of life".
In this article I want to focus on developments practices and lifehacks
that apply uniquely to firmware 
and avoid the ones that apply to "big" desktop or server software.
This article will be updated as more ideas become crystallized
so please add my blog to your RSS reader. 🙂]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“삼부 내일 체크하고”, 두 달 뒤 주가가 네 배 뛰었다: 슬로우레터 7월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111881</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111881"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T22:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이종호가 말한 V1과 V2. “삼부 내일 체크하고.” 쟁점과 현안. “국방부 장관을 추천했는데 우리 것이 될 거야.” 국민의힘의 자폭. 더 깊게 읽기. 박근혜 정부가 왜 무너졌겠나. 김건희와 한동훈이 말하지 않은 것. 다르게 읽기. 성장이 고용을 만든다. 버텨라, 한은. “서울 집값 추세적 상승 아니다.” 해법과 대안. 대형 병원, 중환자 중심으로 돌린다. “불운과 불의의 사고는 없다.” 한국 종부세와...
The post “삼부 내일 체크하고”, 두 달 뒤 주가가 네 배 뛰었다: 슬로우레터 7월12일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authorization pitfalls: what does Keycloak cloak?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1142/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1142/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User authorization and registration are important parts of any application, not only for users but also for security. What pitfalls does the source code of a popular open-source identity management...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enabling more private generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/enabling-more-private-gen-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/enabling-more-private-gen-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T20:14:00.592Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has developed a number of technologies that you can use to start experimenting with and exploring the potential of generative AI to process data that needs to stay private.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Nix alternatives and spinoffs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981124/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981124/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T16:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the

disagreements that led to Eelco Dolstra

stepping down from the NixOS
Foundation board, there have been a number of projects forked from or inspired
by

Nix that have stepped up to compete with it. Two months on, some of these
projects are now well-established enough to look at what they have to offer and
how they compare to each other. Overall, users have a number of good options to
choose from, whether they're seeking a compatible replacement for Nix (the
configuration language and package manager) or NixOS (the Linux distribution),
or something that takes the same ideas in a different direction.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Reports from OSPM 2024, part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981371/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981371/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T14:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sixth edition of the Power Management and Scheduling
in the Linux Kernel (OSPM) Summit took place on May 30-31 2024, and was
graciously hosted by the Institut de
Recherche en Informatique de Toulouse (IRIT) in Toulouse, France.  This
is the first of a series of articles describing the discussions held at
OSPM 2024; topics covered include latency hints, energy-aware scheduling,
ChromeOS, and user-space schedulers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 6.9.9, 6.6.39, and 6.1.98]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981717/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981717/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T14:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9.9, 6.6.39, and 6.1.98 stable kernels have been released.  As
usual, they contain lots of important fixes throughout the tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981716/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981716/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T14:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (dotnet6.0, dotnet8.0, fence-agents, and virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel), Debian (exim4 and firefox-esr), Fedora (dotnet8.0, firefox, onnx, qt6-qtbase, squid, and wordpress), Mageia (golang, netatalk, php, and poppler), Red Hat (ghostscript, httpd, openssh, python3, and ruby), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (kernel and openssh), and Ubuntu (linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-ibm-5.15, and python3.5, python3.6, python3.7, python3.8, python3.9, python3.10,
 python3.11, python3.12).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An empirical study of Rust for Linux]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981635/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981635/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:33:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The research value of this
USENIX paper by Hongyu Li et al. is not entirely clear, but it does
show that the Rust-for-Linux project is gaining wider attention.


	Despite more novice developers being attracted by Rust to the
	kernel community, we have found their commits are mainly for
	constructing Rust-relevant toolchains as well as Rust crates alone;
	they do not, however, take part in kernel code development. By
	contrast, 5 out of 6 investigated drivers (as seen in Table 5) are
	mainly contributed by authors from the Linux community. This
	implies a disconnection be- tween the young and the seasoned
	developers, and that the bar of kernel programming is not lowered
	by Rust language.


As a bonus, it includes a ChatGPT analysis of LWN and Hacker News comments.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global shutter image sensor brings HDR technology to AR/VR/MR]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482745</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/global-shutter-image-sensor-brings-hdr-technology-to-ar-vr-mr/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T11:16:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Latest global shutter image sensor for AR/VR/MR from Omnivision features on-chip single-exposure DCG technology for ghost-free high dynamic range imaging.
The post Global shutter image sensor brings HDR technology to AR/VR/MR appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous observability for debugging RTOS-based firmware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482735</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/continuous-observability-for-debugging-rtos-based-firmware/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T10:33:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By adding software functionality for continuous observability in a device, diagnostic data can be provided over any I/O interfaces, such as a local UART connection in the test lab or a cloud connection in the field.
The post Continuous observability for debugging RTOS-based firmware appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Johan Kraft</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[시대착오적 후보자비방죄: 한계 드러낸 헌재, 팬클럽만 신경 쓰는 국회]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111812</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111812"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[흔히들 민주주의 꽃은 선거라고 표현합니다. 민주주의가 성장하기 위해서는 ‘선거’가 반드시 필요하고 또 그만큼 중요하다는 뜻이겠지요. 그런데 한국 공직선거법에 따르면 정작 선거 시기에 유권자 할 수 있는 일은 많지 않습니다. 아무것도 하지 말라는 공직선거법이 유독 강조하는 규정 중에는 후보자에 대한 비방을 처벌한다는 내용이 포함됩니다. 선거 시기에 후보자에 대한 비판과 검증이 없어도 괜찮은가요? 비방과 비판은 다른 걸까요?...
The post 시대착오적 후보자비방죄: 한계 드러낸 헌재, 팬클럽만 신경 쓰는 국회 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KBS는 장악했고 YTN은 팔았다 이제 MBC만 남았다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111789</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111789"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어떤 권력은 언론의 비판·감시·견제 기능을 불편해한다. 이들은 역으로 언론을 장악하고자 한다. 공영방송 장악을 시도했던 몇몇 정권이 보여온 모습이다. 이명박 정부가 들어서기 전 당시 한나라당은 한국방송(KBS), 문화방송(MBC) 보도에 끊임없이 불만을 드러냈다. 이후 이명박 정부에서는 공영방송 장악이 이뤄졌다. 구체적 모습에서 차이는 있지만 공영방송 장악 방식의 본질은 같다. 경영진을 강제로 교체하고, 이에 저항하는 구성원을 해고하는 등 인사조치하고, 보도나...
The post KBS는 장악했고 YTN은 팔았다 이제 MBC만 남았다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MySQL replication between VMs in OpenShift through external network]]></title>
        <id>e63a24a7-85e3-4545-b5fd-0f016e09312e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/11/mysql-replication-between-vms-openshift-through-external-network"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article explores setting up MySQL replication using an external network across virtual machines (VMs) in separate projects in a Red Hat OpenShift cluster. The fundamentals discussed here can be used to set up replication across VMs in geographically distinct OpenShift clusters. This configuration offers robust disaster recovery for business critical databases. See Figure 1.



  
        



  

Figure 1: OpenShift Cluster with two networks. One for Management and other for VM Traffic.

Set-up Details 
This blog post explores a unique OpenShift cluster architecture that enables replication across geographically separated clusters. The cluster consists of three master nodes and two worker nodes. Each worker node houses a virtual machine (VM) equipped with an external network interface …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kalyanaraman Narayanan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[당신을 취소합니다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111448</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111448"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T03:32:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사람을 취소할 수 있을까. 물건 구매를 취소하듯 혹은 계약을 취소하듯 사람을 취소한다고? 물론 이것은 비유다. 하지만 아주 강력한 비유다. 사람을 취소하다니, 그런 권력을 가진 사람이 있을까. 스스로 옳다고 믿는 일군의 디지털 유저는 그렇다고 생각하는 것 같다. 물론 이 과장된 비유는 자신의 권력을 과장하려는 허세일 수도 있다. 캔슬 컬처(이하 ‘취소 문화’와 혼용)는 무엇인가. 디지털 단두대는 또...
The post 당신을 취소합니다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 애플 주가 상승 요인은 AI투자가 아니다. 광고 진입을 고려해야]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595470</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595470/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9-%ec%9a%94%ec%9d%b8-2"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T02:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 11, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/980654/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/980654/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T00:49:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for July 11, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in June (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/june-2024-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/june-2024-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this June.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열을 상습적인 거짓말쟁이로 만든 건 질문 없는 언론: 슬로우레터 7월11일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111730</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111730"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T22:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[임성근 구명 로비 제보자는 김규현. 임성근은 “이종호 만난 적 없다.” VIP가 김건희였나. 쟁점과 현안. “댓글팀 사실이면 정권 문 닫을 일.” “일부러 졌나.” “먹사니즘이 유일한 이데올로기.” 띠 장마, 군산에 시간당 146mm 폭우. 더 깊게 읽기. 빌려줄 때 사자, 주담대 1년 동안 5배 늘었다. 한동훈의 세 가지 길. 해법과 대안. 택배 기사에게 작업 중지권을 주자. 현대차의 계속...
The post 윤석열을 상습적인 거짓말쟁이로 만든 건 질문 없는 언론: 슬로우레터 7월11일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 fun Gemma project ideas]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/3-fun-gemma-project-ideas/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/3-fun-gemma-project-ideas/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T20:14:05.637Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Gemma models to translate an old language, brainstorm game design ideas, and write a letter to Santa.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brown: Fixing a 6-year-old bug in Ubuntu MATE and Xubuntu]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981565/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981565/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T18:04:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doug Brown documents
the long journey to fixing a bug in the GDebi utility for
installing Debian packages. He first encountered the bug in
Ubuntu MATE 18.04: "at the time I just ignored this
issue. I didn't want to deal with it. I went off to the trusty Linux
terminal and installed Chrome that way instead".
Two and a half years ago, I committed to doing more open-source
contributions in my free time and was finally irritated enough about
this problem to look into it. I searched around for more info. Lo and
behold, lots
of people
were also
affected and there was already an
issue from 2019 on Ubuntu's bug tracker about it.
[...] As is commonly the case in software development, the difficult part of
this fix had nothing to do with the code itself. All of my effort was
spent figuring out Ubuntu's patch submission processes and advocating
for my merge request. Nobody else seemed to be interested in doing the
work to actually fix this bug that has been plaguing Ubuntu MATE and
Xubuntu, not to mention some Debian users, for over 6 years. After
dealing with the long process of getting my merge request approved, I
think I'm starting to understand why!


Brown notes that the fix is
now packaged for the upcoming Ubuntu 24.10 release, and should be
backported to 22.04 and 24.04 eventually.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix for Fedora Atomic Desktop and Fedora IoT boot failure]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981561/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981561/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T17:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Atomic Desktop
and Fedora IoT systems installed
before Fedora 40 may fail to boot after an update if secure boot
is enabled. Fedora Magazine has a
post by Timothée Ravier about the problem, how users can work
around it, and what the project is doing to avoid the similar problems
in the future:
On Fedora Atomic Desktops and Fedora IoT systems, the components
that are part of the boot chain (Shim, GRUB) are not (yet)
automatically updated alongside the rest of the system. Thus, if you
have installed a Fedora Atomic Desktop or a Fedora IoT system before
Fedora 40, it uses an old versions of the Shim and bootloader binaries
to boot your system.
When Secure Boot is enabled, the EFI firmware loads Shim
first. Shim is signed by the Microsoft Third Party Certificate
Authority so that it can be verified on most hardware out of the
box. The Shim binary includes the Fedora certificates used to verify
binaries signed by Fedora. Then Shim loads GRUB, which in turn loads
the Linux kernel. Both are signed by Fedora.
Until recently, the kernel binaries where signed two times, with an
older key and a newer one. With the 6.9 kernel update, the kernel is
no longer signed with the old key. If GRUB or Shim is old enough and
does not know about the new key, the signature verification fails.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Improving pseudo filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981155/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981155/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T15:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eventfs filesystem provides an interface to the tracepoints that are available
to be used by various Linux tracing tools (e.g. ftrace, perf, uprobes,
etc.); it is meant to be a version of the tracefs filesystem that
dynamically allocates its entries as needed.  The goal is to reduce the memory
required for multiple instances of tracefs, as Steven Rostedt described in
a session at the 2022
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  He returned to the 2024
edition of the summit to talk further about how to make pseudo (or virtual)
filesystems, such as tracefs/eventfs, more like regular Linux filesystems,
where the directory entries (dentries) and inodes are only created (and
cached) as needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Sxmo: a text-centric mobile user interface]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981320/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981320/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T14:54:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sxmo, short for "Simple X Mobile", is described on its web site as "a
minimalist environment for Linux mobile devices"; it offers a menu-driven
interface that is controlled with the phone's hardware buttons. Sxmo enables the user
to send SMS messages from a text editor and is entirely customizable with
shell scripts. This peculiar mobile user interface significantly differs
from the prevailing approach—but it works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981508/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981508/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:15:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (buildah, gvisor-tap-vsock, kernel-rt, libreswan, linux-firmware, pki-core, and podman), Fedora (firefox and jpegxl), Gentoo (Buildah, HarfBuzz, and LIVE555 Media Server), Oracle (buildah, gvisor-tap-vsock, kernel, libreswan, and podman), Red Hat (containernetworking-plugins, dotnet6.0, dotnet8.0, fence-agents, kernel, libreswan, libvirt, perl-HTTP-Tiny, python39:3.9, toolbox, and virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel modules), SUSE (firefox, freeradius-server, haproxy, jbigkit, kernel, kernel-firmware, pam, ppp, python3-cryptography, skopeo, and tar), and Ubuntu (dotnet6, dotnet8, exim4, firefox, golang-1.21, golang-1.22, openssh, and python-django).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Here Comes The Noise!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1674.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1674.php"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T11:58:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Noise. That wiggle or apparent fuzziness you see riding on top your pristine signal which you automatically turn a blind eye to until you enter the world of precision where that wiggle now causes supreme headaches/stress for your company at large.



Imagine you've found yourself embedded within a company (working as an embedded systems engineer if you'll pardon the terrible...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toward Effective AI Support for Developers]]></title>
        <id>3675416</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3675416"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T11:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the new Traces UI in the Red Hat OpenShift Web Console]]></title>
        <id>b13a3bfc-c066-4de8-8ede-539b128626a0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/10/introducing-new-traces-ui-red-hat-openshift-web-console"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the latest Cluster Observability Operator 0.3.0 release, you can deploy a brand new Traces UI plug-in as part of the Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform web console experience. This is a great step forward as we continue to work on our mission to provide Observability as one. After releasing a Metrics UI and Logs UI, we enhance the overall Observability journey for our OpenShift users by providing the opportunity to visualize the third pillar of Observability: distributed tracing. This is a Developer Preview feature, as additional enhancements are currently being worked on. 
The OpenShift distributed tracing platform is evolving. A few months back, we announced general availability of Tempo as part of the distributed tracing platform 3.0 release. While making this change, we decided …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vanessa Martini, Jose Gomez-Selles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improved observability signal correlation for Red Hat OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>ecff2cce-0242-4d44-a34f-12bd303cb80a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/10/improved-observability-signal-correlation-red-hat-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observability signal correlation for Red Hat OpenShift has exponentially evolved over the past few months. A developer preview was made available to OpenShift users in December 2023 as part of the Logging 5.8 release. But since then, our team has worked to provide you with a series of great new features!
Observability signal correlation for Red Hat OpenShift continues to be powered by Korrel8r—an open source observability project founded within Red Hat—aimed at providing a set of rules for easily correlating metrics, logs, alerts, and additional observability signals across different data stores. Key enhancements include 1) expanded signal support, as you can now correlate netflows, 2) brand new troubleshooting panel in the OpenShift web console that simplifies the overall observability si…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vanessa Martini, Alan Conway</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부산에 먼저 도착한 인구 소멸, 20대 여성이 탈출하는 이유를 봐야 한다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111636</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111636"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:02:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[부산이 광역시 가운데 처음으로 소멸 위험 단계에 진입했다. 부산에는 노인과 바다밖에 없다는 말이 나올 정도다. 부산은 서울 다음으로 큰 도시지만 가까운 미래에 인천에 따라잡힐 가능성이 크다. 지난해 기준으로 부산은 328만 명, 인천은 301만 명이다. 이게 왜 중요한가. ‘지역 소멸’의 개념 정의. ‘소멸 위험’은 광역시 가운데 처음. 합계 출산율 0.72. 부산이 특히 더 심각한 이유. 여성...
The post 부산에 먼저 도착한 인구 소멸, 20대 여성이 탈출하는 이유를 봐야 한다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Asking an LLM to build a simple web tool]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/asking-an-llm-to-build-a-simple-web-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/asking-an-llm-to-build-a-simple-web-tool/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T03:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I've been really enjoying following <a class="reference external" href="https://simonwillison.net/">Simon Willison's blog posts</a> recently. Simon shows other
programmers the way LLMs will be used for code assistance in the future, and
posts full interactions with LLMs to build small tools or parts of larger
applications.</p>
<p>A <a class="reference external" href="https://simonwillison.net/2024/Jul/8/box-shadow-css-generator/">recent post</a>
caught my attention; here Simon got …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열이 임성근을 싸고 돌았던 이유, 결국 김건희가 연결고리였다: 슬로우레터 7월10일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111594</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111594"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T22:11:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“VIP에게 내가 이야기하겠다.” 증거가 수두룩하다. 쟁점과 현안. 채 상병 특검법 또 거부권 행사. 거부권 행사로 끝 아니다. 김건희와 최은순, 국회 온다. “다 공개하면 정부가 위험해진다.” “둘 다 이해 안 된다.” “다 망했다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 문재인에게 있고 윤석열에게 없는 것. “지금 그럴 때가 아니다.” 가장 약한 곳을 때렸다. 다르게 읽기. 잘 해야 할 것과 하지...
The post 윤석열이 임성근을 싸고 돌았던 이유, 결국 김건희가 연결고리였다: 슬로우레터 7월10일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A new API for tree-in-dcache filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/980558/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/980558/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T21:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a number of kernel filesystems that store their directory entries
directly in the directory-entry cache (dcache) without having any permanent
storage for those objects. It started out as a "neat hack" for ramfs,
Al Viro said, at the start of his filesystem-track session at
the
2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  Unfortunately, as the use
of this technique has grown into other filesystems, there has been a lot of
scope creep that has gotten out of control.  He wanted to discuss some new
infrastructure that he is working on to try to clean some of that up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with Gemma on Ray on Vertex AI]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/get-started-with-gemma-on-ray-on-vertex-ai/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/get-started-with-gemma-on-ray-on-vertex-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T20:14:41.518Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Use Gemma Supervised tuning on Ray on Vertex AI to train and serve machine learning models efficiently and effectively.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 128.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981334/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981334/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:54:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
128.0 of the Firefox browser has been released.  Changes this time
include the ability to translate highlighted phrases from the context menu,
display of recent searches on opening the address bar (US/Canada only), a
streamlined dialog for clearing user data, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use LUTs to ease your development burden]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482729</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/use-luts-to-ease-your-development-burden/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:46:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you use look-up tables (LUTs) strategically, you’ll find that your code will be more configurable and scalable, which might help you write higher-quality software...
The post Use LUTs to ease your development burden appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging technologies address smart factory maintenance challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482726</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/emerging-technologies-address-smart-factory-maintenance-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T15:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Emerging embedded technologies can simplify how companies approach the maintenance of smart manufacturing systems. The implementation of autonomous systems across industries is taking shape, placing...
The post Emerging technologies address smart factory maintenance challenges appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sanjay Murthi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How rugged edge computing drives better transportation options]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482723</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-rugged-edge-computing-drives-better-transportation-options/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T14:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One multinational intelligent transport systems company is leveraging the potential of modular industrial edge computing to enhance multi-lane free-flow toll solutions essential for traffic safety....
The post How rugged edge computing drives better transportation options appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dustin Seetoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Offload-friendly network encryption in the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/980430/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/980430/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T14:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The

PSP security protocol (PSP) is a way to transparently encrypt packets by
efficiently offloading encryption and decryption to the network
interface cards (NICs) that Google uses for connections inside its data centers. The
protocol is similar to

IPsec, in that it allows for wrapping arbitrary traffic
in a layer of encryption. The difference is that PSP is encapsulated in UDP, and
designed from the beginning to reduce the amount of state that NICs
have to track in order to send and receive encrypted traffic, allowing for more
simultaneous connections. Jakub Kicinski

wants to add support for the protocol to the Linux kernel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Another OpenSSH remote code execution vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981287/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981287/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:36:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alexander "Solar Designer" Peslyak has disclosed another OpenSSH
vulnerability that can be exploited for remote code execution, but only
on distributions that have applied a patch to add auditing support.
Specifically, RHEL 9 and derivatives are affected, as are
Fedora 36 and 37 (but not later releases).


	The main difference from CVE-2024-6387 is that the race condition
	and RCE potential are triggered in the privsep child process, which
	runs with reduced privileges compared to the parent server process.
	So immediate impact is lower.  However, there may be differences in
	exploitability of these vulnerabilities in a particular scenario,
	which could make either one of these a more attractive choice for
	an attacker, and if only one of these is fixed or mitigated then
	the other becomes more relevant.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981285/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981285/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel), Fedora (ghostscript, golang, httpd, libnbd, netatalk, rust-sequoia-chameleon-gnupg, rust-sequoia-gpg-agent, rust-sequoia-keystore, rust-sequoia-openpgp, and rust-sequoia-sq), Mageia (apache), Red Hat (booth, buildah, edk2, fence-agents, git, gvisor-tap-vsock, kernel, kernel-rt, less, libreswan, linux-firmware, openssh, pki-core, podman, postgresql-jdbc, python3, tpm2-tss, virt:rhel, and virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel modules), SUSE (krb5, poppler, and python-docker), and Ubuntu (apache2, cinder, glance, nova, and Tomcat).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel update 6.6.38]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981256/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981256/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:58:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.6.38 stable kernel update has been
released, without the benefit of the usual review process.  It reverts some
BPF changes with patches that do not appear in the mainline (in this form,
at least).  "All powerpc and arm64 users of the 6.6 kernel series must
upgrade.  Everyone else probably should as well to be safe."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[뉴진스 하니 푸른산호초 그리고 러브레터]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595457</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595457/%eb%89%b4%ec%a7%84%ec%8a%a4-%ed%95%98%eb%8b%88-%ed%91%b8%eb%a5%b8%ec%82%b0%ed%98%b8%ec%b4%88%ec%99%80-%eb%9f%ac%eb%b8%8c%eb%a0%88%ed%84%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T08:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying SQL Server on Linux using an Ansible playbook]]></title>
        <id>78b261d7-71f7-48bc-a468-395bf429e3b6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/09/deploying-sql-server-linux-using-ansible-playbook"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Why deploy SQL Server on Linux using an Ansible playbook? The answer is that automation is a key aspect of modern IT operations, which is why we at Red Hat are delighted to announce that the deployment and configuration of Microsoft SQL Server on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) can be easily automated using Ansible and corresponding RHEL system roles for SQL Server. You can deploy high availability (HA) solutions, including configuring Always On availability groups. Ansible scripts can automate the entire deployment process, reducing manual intervention and minimizing errors.
Sounds good—what do I need to do?
First off, you’ll need an Azure subscription to get this set up. If you don't have an Azure subscription, you can easily create a free account here. You will also need to create a new…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Vivien Wang, Arne Arnold</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with the OpenShift Cluster Observability Operator]]></title>
        <id>61bd0b74-7f73-4d35-ace0-4ba4a0782e25</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/09/get-started-openshift-cluster-observability-operator"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are cases in which a Red Hat OpenShift team supporting a central monitoring stack can struggle to fulfill application teams' requests or demands for Prometheus metrics and configuration changes. For instance:

One department would like metrics retention for a period of 3 months whereas another department requested metrics retention for 6 months.
One department requested remote_writes to an external server for metrics matching one pattern and to a different server for metrics matching another pattern. This group changes their requirements every few weeks.
One department uses a Prometheus exporter to dump all their data to Prometheus for easy viewing in Grafana and is overloading the Prometheus server causing it to use many G-bytes of RAM which results in poor Prometheus query response…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Greenberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[파이퍼샌들러가 S&P 500 전망치 제시를 포기한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595451</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595451/%ed%8c%8c%ec%9d%b4%ed%8d%bc-%ec%83%8c%eb%93%a4%eb%9f%ac-sp-500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d%ec%b9%98"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T06:38:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Esfahbod: State of Text Rendering 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981178/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981178/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T03:48:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On his blog, Behdad Esfahbod has published a lengthy and detailed look at the state of open-source text rendering.  It looks at the libraries available, application support, future directions, and gives a summary analysis of the ecosystem. 


In broad strokes, OpenType added support for color fonts, variable fonts, and the Universal Shaping Engine. The Free & Open Source stack supports all of these advances at the lower level, but application UI support has been slower to arrive. The Open Source text stack also gained enormous market-share when Android and Google Chrome fully embraced it.

Looking forward, there is a Rust migration of the text stack underway, which will unify font compilation and consumption under a safe programming language. Incremental Font Transfer will enable streaming fonts to web browsers. And my proposed Wasm-fonts will enable more expressive fonts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아주가, AI 반도체 시장규모는 얼마나 큰가요?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595443</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595443/ai-%eb%b0%98%eb%8f%84%ec%b2%b4-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5%ea%b7%9c%eb%aa%a8"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T03:31:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/9, UBS, 엔비디아 블랙웰 수요 견조 → 목표주가 150달러로 상향 조정]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595435</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595435/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%eb%b8%94%eb%9e%99%ec%9b%b0-%ec%88%98%ec%9a%94-%ea%b2%ac%ec%a1%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T01:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/9, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595426</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595426/7-9-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T00:54:27.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[임성근 무혐의? 윤석열의 외압이란 본질은 달라진 게 없다: 슬로우레터 7월9일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111553</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111553"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T22:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 메시지가 공개됐다. 국민의힘이 빠진 ‘읽씹’ 함정. 윤석열이냐 한동훈이냐. 윤석열 탄핵 청원 청문회, 김건희도 부를까. 쟁점과 현안. 임성근 무혐의? 특검 가야 할 이유. 이첩은 잘못된 게 없다. 민주당 최고위원 후보는 모두 친명. 더 깊게 읽기. 선명성과 팬덤의 상관관계. 이재명 위증교사 재판 9월30일 결심. 다시 집값이 뛴다. 미복귀 전공의 처벌하지 않는다. 다르게 읽기. 이참에 파견법 완화하자고?...
The post 임성근 무혐의? 윤석열의 외압이란 본질은 달라진 게 없다: 슬로우레터 7월9일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Giving bootloaders the boot with nmbl]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979789/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979789/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T18:10:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At DevConf.cz 2024,
Marta Lewandowska gave a talk to discuss a
new approach for booting Linux systems, "No more boot
loader: Please use the kernel instead". The talk, available on
YouTube, introduced a new project called nmbl (for "no more bootloader",
pronounced "nimble"). The idea is to get rid of bootloaders (e.g., 
GNU GRUB) with a
Unified
Kernel Image (UKI) that removes the need for a separate bootloader
altogether. It is early days for nmbl, currently the project is only
being tested for use with virtual machines, but the idea is
compelling. If successful, nmbl could offer security, performance, and
maintenance benefits compared to GRUB and other separate bootloaders.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GDB 15.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981080/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981080/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T14:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 15.1 of the GNU debugger has been released.  Changes include a
number of enhancements to GDB's Python support, some Debugger Adapter
Protocol additions, some new GDBserver options, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981119/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981119/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T14:09:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (openssh), Debian (krb5), Fedora (yt-dlp), Gentoo (firefox, KDE Plasma Workspaces, Stellarium, thunderbird, and X.Org X11 library), Mageia (python-js2py and znc), Oracle (389-ds, c-ares, container-tools, cups, go-toolset, httpd:2.4/httpd, iperf3, kernel, less, libreoffice, libuv, nghttp2, openldap, openssh, python-idna, python-jinja2, python-pillow, python3, python3.11-PyMySQL, and xmlrpc-c), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, openssh, and virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel modules), and SUSE (go1.21, go1.22, krb5, kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-exportproxy-container, virt-exportserver-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-t, netty3, opera, and python-urllib3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don't Know Jack about Bandwidth]]></title>
        <id>3674953</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3674953"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T13:35:25.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplify access to your ROSA clusters using external OIDC]]></title>
        <id>8f2701d9-ae82-4487-a12d-0014664a24da</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/07/08/simplify-access-your-rosa-clusters-using-external-oidc"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article introduces a new feature for Red Hat OpenShift Service on AWS (ROSA) with hosted control planes that simplifies authentication and authorization workflows through direct integration with your existing OpenID Connect (OIDC) compliant identity providers (IdPs). Now you can seamlessly leverage your corporate identity tokens to access the Red Hat OpenShift and Kubernetes APIs on ROSA with hosted control planes (HCP).
Benefits you'll experience:

Simplified authentication: No need to manage separate credentials for ROSA. Just use your familiar corporate identity, making access easier and more secure.
Unified access control: Bring your existing user and group management policies into ROSA. Manage permissions consistently across your organization with a single, unified approach.
Stre…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adel Zaalouk, Anjali Telang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 테슬라 주가 상승을 견인하는 2가지 요소]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595421</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595421/%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9-%ec%9a%94%ec%95%88"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T04:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 엔비디아 투자의견 다운그레이드과 엔비디아 주가 전망]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595414</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595414/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%8b%a4%ec%9a%b4%ea%b7%b8%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b4%eb%93%9c%ec%99%80-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T04:32:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Street,  엔비디아 주가 전망 부정적,엔비디아 주가 상승여력 소진, 투자의견 다운그레이드]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595412</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595412/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-5"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T02:31:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc7]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/981020/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/981020/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T23:34:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10-rc7 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	Things remain calm, although I do suspect that part of it is that
	it's been the July 4th week in the US, and a lot of Europe is
	starting to go away on summer vacation.

	But hey, let's not look a gift horse too closely in the
	mouth. Maybe it's really just that 6.10 is shaping up well. Right?
	RIGHT?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 만악의 근원은 그놈이었네… “이미 늦었다”면 뭘 할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79376</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/07/07/npsp_pollenallergy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_pollenallergy"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 20일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 오늘은 좀 개인적인 이야기로 글을 시작하려 합니다. 지난해 뉴욕주에서 바로 옆에 있는 뉴저지주로 이사했는데, 한동안 잊고 지낸 봄철의 불청객 꽃가루 알레르기가 아주 심하게 도져 몇 년 만에 정말 고생했기 때문입니다. 연방제 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘읽씹’ 논란 핵심은 김건희의 분노와 윤석열 ‘패싱’: 슬로우레터 7월8일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111491</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111491"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T22:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘읽씹’ 논란이 사라지지 않는 이유. ‘읽씹’ 논란의 두 가지 쟁점. 한동훈의 해명. 쟁점과 현안. 김건희가 1월에 사과를 했다면? 김건희 부르나. 임성근 불송치. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘마통’ 땡겨쓰는 정부. 이동관 3개월에 김홍일 6개월. 6000억 달러짜리 질문. 철도를 깔면 기차가 다닌다는 믿음. 다르게 읽기. “회사가 전쟁터? 밖은 지옥이야.” “자폐 아이 두고 회사를 못 다닙니다.” 해법과 대안. 일본이...
The post ‘읽씹’ 논란 핵심은 김건희의 분노와 윤석열 ‘패싱’: 슬로우레터 7월8일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Confidence intervals: my one recommended practice]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8931</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/07/07/confidence-intervals-my-one-recommended-practice/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T21:42:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What recommended practices should developers/managers follow when analysing data they have collected/available? The scientific approach to data analysis mandates specifying a hypothesis before gathering the data, let alone analysing it. This approach has proven workable when researchers are familiar with an evidence-based body of knowledge. In this environment it’s acceptable, even required, to criticise anyone […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An insect is sitting in your compiler and doesn't want to leave for 13 years]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1141/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1141/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's imagine you have a perfect project. Tasks get done, your compiler compiles, static analyzers analyze, and releases get released. At some point, you decide to open an ancient file that nobody...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7/4, 로이터, 데이터센터 투자는 전력 인프라 수준에 죄우될 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595407</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595407/%eb%8d%b0%ec%9d%b4%ed%84%b0%ec%84%bc%ed%84%b0-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%99%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a0%a5-%ec%9d%b8%ed%94%84%eb%9d%bc"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T12:10:22.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My Personal Journey in Verification]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/formal/2024/07/06/verifjourney.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/formal/2024/07/06/verifjourney.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-06T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This week, I’ve been testing a CI/CD pipeline.  This has been my opportunity
to shake the screws and kick the tires on what should become a new verification
product shortly.
I thought that a good design to check might be my
SDIO project.  It has roughly all the
pieces in place, and so makes sense for an automated testing pipeline.
This weekend, the CI project engineer shared with me:
It’s literally the first time I get to know a good hardware project needs
such many verifications and testings!  There’s even a real SD card
simulation model and RW test…
After reminiscing about this for a bit, I thought it might be worth taking a
moment to tell how I got here.
Verification: The Goal
Perhaps the best way to explain the “goal” of verification is by way of an
old “war story”–as we used to call t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>