<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-01-05T20:13:21.125Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Kernel-text replication on NUMA systems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956900/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956900/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T15:41:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel developers often go out of their way to reduce the memory used by
the kernel itself; that memory is not available for the workloads that
people are actually interested in running on their systems.  Lower memory
usage also tends to lead to better performance overall.  But there are
times when the expenditure of some extra memory can make the system faster.
The replication of the kernel's text (executable code) and read-only data
across a NUMA system may be a case in point; patch sets have been posted
adding that capability to two architectures.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four stable kernels released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/957007/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/957007/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T14:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.6.10, 6.1.71, 5.15.146, and 5.10.206 stable kernels have been released.
They contain numerous important fixes, as usual.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/957005/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/957005/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T14:45:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (asterisk, chromium, exim4, netatalk, and tomcat9), Fedora (chromium), Gentoo (BlueZ, c-ares, CUPS filters, RDoc, and WebKitGTK+), Oracle (firefox, squid:4, thunderbird, and tigervnc), SUSE (python-aiohttp and python-paramiko), and Ubuntu (linux-intel-iotg).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enable fine-grained API authorization using Keycloak and 3scale]]></title>
        <id>bd3b4727-2870-448c-80e6-ed688af465af</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/05/enable-fine-grained-api-authorization-using-keycloak-and-3scale"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Applying fine-grained access control to APIs is a common enterprise requirement that can be challenging to implement. Encapsulating authorization decisions into the API gateway can quickly become difficult to manage in complex APIs with many resources and access control rules. However, you can externalize API authorization decisions from the API gateway and from your microservices by leveraging Keycloak Authorization Services as a centralized authorization component. Keycloak Authorization Services acts as a policy decision point integrated with 3scale API gateway, which is the central enforcement place to access your APIs. 
Integrating Keycloak Authorization Services into your API architecture has many benefits:
Centralized control with simplified administration: Organizations have a sing…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdelhamid Soliman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[觀光弗]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=84884</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/84884/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T05:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[먼저 다울링 대사가 환율의 현실화를 미국식의 접근방식으로 설명했고, 이어서 데커 장군이 한국에 와 있는 수많은 미국 장병들이 500대 1의 고정환율에 따라 봉급을 환화로 바꾸어 한국시장에서 물건을 사려고 하면, 실제로는 그 가치의 절반도 안되기 때문에 사령관의 입장으로서도 고충이 많다고 거듭 설명드렸다. 그 자리에서 李대통령은 해방 후 1달러당 15환부터 시작된 환율이 500환까지 치솟게 된 아픈 역사를 되새기고 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[체납 알림 카톡 열어본 사람 66%가 세금을 냈다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101948</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101948"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T02:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우데이터] 보도자료에서 숫자를 이야기하는 방법. 서울시가 지방세 체납을 카카오톡 메시지로 알려주는 서비스를 한 달 동안 테스트했는데 결과가 흥미롭다. TMI. ‘쓸고퀄’이지만 정확한 설명은 다음과 같다. 아쉬운 대목.
The post 체납 알림 카톡 열어본 사람 66%가 세금을 냈다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The return of None-aware operators for Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956862/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956862/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:24:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The saga of the  None-aware (or null-coalescing) operators for Python
continues.  We last looked in on the topic
a little over a year ago and noted that either adoption or a clear
rejection of the idea might help tamp down its regular recurrence.  That
has not happened, so, predictably, it was raised again—and does not look
any closer to resolution this time around.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Listing stuck Python threads]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-01-05:/listing-python-threads.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/listing-python-threads.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than once I have been in the situation where a multithreaded Python application (eventually 😁)
runs fine, all the threads cooperate nicely, but do not shut down cleanly.
This for example happens after closing GUI windows where the GUI goes away but
some worker threads do not. A Ctrl+C might help to shut down the stuck application only if the
main thread is stuck.
Still, every application should shut down cleanly so that it can be correctly monitored
and restarted by init / systemd / wrapper script etc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/5,  월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593280</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593280/1-5-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[전두환‘씨’ 말고 ‘전 대통령’이라고 불러라? 지금 KBS에서 벌어지고 있는 일: 슬로우레터 1월5일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101914</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101914"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T22:04:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘어느 쪽 사람인가’가 중요한가. 이슈 블랙홀. 이준석과 이낙연 신당, 각각 10%와 6%. “전두환 ‘씨’ 말고 ‘전 대통령’이라고 불러라.” 30가지 감세 선물? 더 깊게 읽기. 10년 불매 운동의 승리? 남양유업 ‘오너 경영’ 끝났다. 이 개가 그 개 맞나, 1억 원 들여 반려견 복제 논란. 다르게 읽기. 사실을 말했다는 이유로 유죄? 오늘의 TMI. 테트리스 끝까지 가봤다. 상장기업...
The post 전두환‘씨’ 말고 ‘전 대통령’이라고 불러라? 지금 KBS에서 벌어지고 있는 일: 슬로우레터 1월5일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 24년 애플 투자의견 다운그레이드로 애플 주가 폭락]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593275</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593275/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac%ea%b3%bc-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ed%8f%ad%eb%9d%bd"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T18:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computer science pioneer Niklaus Wirth passes away (ITWire)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956864/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956864/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:30:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ITWire covers
the passing of Niklaus Wirth.


	Wirth is well-remembered for his pioneering work in programming
	languages and algorithms. For these achievements, he received the
	ACM Turing Award in 1984, inducted as a Fellow of the ACM in 1994,
	and a Fellow of the Computer History Museum in 2004.

	They include, among many, being chief designer for the programming
	languages Euler (1965), PL360 (1966), ALGOL W (1968), Pascal
	(1970), Modula (1975), Modula-2 (1978), Oberon (1987), Oberon-2
	(1991), and Oberon-07 (2007).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956855/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956855/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T14:29:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Oracle (firefox, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, thunderbird, tigervnc, and xorg-x11-server), Red Hat (squid:4), SUSE (exim, libcryptopp, and proftpd), and Ubuntu (openssh and sqlite3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: Legacy Seam]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/LegacySeam.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/LegacySeam.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When working with a legacy system it is valuable to identify and create seams:
  places where we can alter the behavior of the system without editing
  source code. Once we've found a seam, we can use it to break dependencies to
  simplify testing, insert probes to gain observability, and redirect program
  flow to new modules as part of legacy displacement.
Micheal Feathers coined the term “seam” in the context of legacy systems in
  his book Working Effectively with Legacy Code. His definition: “a seam is a place
  where you can alter behavior in your program without editing in that place”.
Here's an example of where a seam would be handy. Imagine some code to
  calculate the price of an order.
// TypeScript
export async function calculatePrice(order:Order) {
  const itemPrices = order.i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[장애인의 지하철 투쟁이 징글징글한 당신에게: 데모꾼이 된 대학원생의 500일 기록]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101888</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101888"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T10:42:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 대학원생 연구로 시작해 어느새 데모꾼이 된 500일 체험의 기록… 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, ‘홍보가 아니라 소통입니다’ 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기. 오늘 ‘마냐의 북라이딩’이 소개하는 책은 [장애시민 불복종] 변재원 지음, 창비: 2023.입니다. 전장연(전국장애인차별철폐연대)의 투쟁은 많은 비장애인에게는 폭력적이고 낯설며 기이하게 느껴지기까지 합니다. 하지만 편하고 우아하고 보기 좋은 투쟁이라는 건 세상에...
The post 장애인의 지하철 투쟁이 징글징글한 당신에게: 데모꾼이 된 대학원생의 500일 기록 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering Kafka migration with MirrorMaker 2]]></title>
        <id>a8b59903-ea85-44ab-be14-0b3158d5b74e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/04/mastering-kafka-migration-mirrormaker-2"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our previous article, we discussed the basics of Apache Kafka MirrorMaker 2, and how it improves data replication between Kafka clusters. This article will focus more on the practical side of things. We'll dive into how to deploy MirrorMaker 2 when using Red Hat AMQ Streams and how to fine-tune MirrorMaker 2 settings for better performance, a crucial step for anyone using this tool. We will also focus on Kafka migration use-cases and describe how the consumer-first Kafka migration strategy can be beneficial in many scenarios.
Prerequisites
Red Hat AMQ Streams, which leverages the open source project Strimzi, provides a way to deploy Apache Kafka to Kubernetes using the operator pattern. The deployment of MirrorMaker 2 is supported with the creation of a custom resource of type KafkaMirr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Radu Domnu, Etienne Dubois</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An update on packet drop reasons in Linux]]></title>
        <id>20dc445e-b01b-4176-96bf-b23234aa78f3</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/04/update-packet-drop-reasons-linux"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since our first blog post on how to retrieve packet drop reasons in the Linux kernel, upstream development of the feature has continued and new additions have been made. Drop reasons can be retrieved manually, but they are also used by an increasing number of utilities such as the Network Observability operator for Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform, which can report packets being dropped with their reasons.
Let's see what happened recently in the drop reason space of the Linux kernel and how to avoid pitfalls, especially between kernel versions. It's worth noting tools designed on top of drop reasons, like the above operator, are already doing the right thing and do not need special care. But as we saw in the previous article, drop reasons can be retrieved manually when debugging networ…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Antoine Tenart</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Asimov Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1619.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1619.php"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T05:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the Internet is choke-full of explanations of basic data communication protocols, very little is said about the higher levels of packing, formatting, and exchanging information in a useful and practical way. This less-charted land is still fraught with strange problems, whose solutions may be found in strange places – in this example, a very short, 60 years old Science Fiction...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/4,  월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593264</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593264/1-4-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T03:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 4, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955921/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955921/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T01:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 4, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in December (2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/december-2023-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/december-2023-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🎉 Happy New Year! 🎉 Here’s to making 2024 the best year yet.
2023 was an exciting year for Interrupt, with 36 new articles, 13 new external contributors, 12 community Meetups, and a partridge in a pear tree. Thanks for being a part of it.
Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
December.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Smuggling email inside of email]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956533/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956533/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T22:42:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Normally, when a new vulnerability is discovered and releases are
coordinated with those affected, the announcement is done at
a convenient time—not generally right before the end-of-year holidays, for
example. The SMTP
Smuggling vulnerability has taken a different path, however, with its
announcement landing on December 18.  That may well have been
unpleasant for some administrators that had not yet updated, but it was
particularly problematic for 
some projects that had not been made aware of the vulnerability at
all—though it was known to affect several open-source mailers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“한동훈에게 총선 주연 넘겨라”, 조선일보의 조언: 슬로우레터 1월4일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101850</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101850"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T22:08:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[누가 음모론을 말하는가. 이재명 공격한 피의자는 미래통합당 당원 출신. 민주당의 이재명 구심력이 강해졌다. 증오정치와 분노투표, 이대로는 안 된다. 윤석열이 병문안을 가야 한다. 쟁점과 현안. 피할 수 있었던 논란. 기자회견 대신 민생 토론회? “류호정처럼 되지 말자.” 더 깊게 읽기. 윤세영의 눈물? 협박? 제2의 레고랜드 사태? 금투세 폐지하면 세수 1조3000억 원 증발. 한국의 중도는. 해법과 대안. 90초...
The post “한동훈에게 총선 주연 넘겨라”, 조선일보의 조언: 슬로우레터 1월4일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lenôtre: Maestro - Introduction]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956699/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956699/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T16:05:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On his blog, 
Luc Lenôtre introduces
Maestro, "a Unix-like kernel and operating system written from
scratch in Rust". Maestro is intended to be
"lightweight and compatible-enough with Linux to be usable in everyday
life".  The project began, in C, back in 2018, but switched over to
Rust after a year-and-a-half.  The current status:

Maestro is a monolithic kernel, supporting only the x86 (in 32 bits)
architecture for now. 

At the time of writing, 135 out of 437 Linux system calls
(roughly 31%) are 
more or less implemented. The project has 48 800 lines of code
across 615 
files (all repositories combined, counted using the cloc command). 


There is a Hacker
News discussion of the project as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NXP and MicroEJ use containers for software portability across MCUs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481186</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/nxp-and-microej-use-containers-for-software-portability-across-mcus/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:37:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NXP Platform Accelerator, co-developed with MicroEJ, leverages software containers with standard APIs to bring smartphone-like software design flexibility to the industrial and IoT edge.
The post NXP and MicroEJ use containers for software portability across MCUs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vim 9.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956696/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956696/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 9.1 of the
Vim editor has been released.  "This release is dedicated to Bram
Moolenaar, Vims lead developer for more than 30 years, who passed away half
a year ago. The Vim project wouldn't exist without his work".  Changes
include new support for classes and objects in the scripting language,
smooth scrolling support, an EditorConfig plugin, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956694/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956694/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T15:21:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kernel), Fedora (slurm), Oracle (kernel and postgresql:15), Red Hat (firefox, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, thunderbird, tigervnc, and xorg-x11-server), SUSE (polkit, postfix, putty, w3m, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (nodejs).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering motor control: motor control 101]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481178</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mastering-motor-control-motor-control-101/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T14:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The fundamental working principle of brush-type DC motors has largely remained consistent for decades, but there have been dramatic advancements in technology, materials, and design....
The post Mastering motor control: motor control 101 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Radonic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ceva releases Wi-Fi 7 IP]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481162</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/ceva-releases-wi-fi-7-ip/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T14:07:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RivieraWaves Wi-Fi 7 IP platform helps developers implement latest high throughput Wi-Fi 7 features in SoCs targeting high-end consumer and industrial applications.
The post Ceva releases Wi-Fi 7 IP appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사이시옷, 없애기보다 더 많이 쓰자]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101807</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101807"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T13:41:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사이시옷은 발음 문제다 사이시옷 문제는 알고 보면 발음 문제다. 사실 모든 표기 문제는 발음 문제다. 글자는 결국 말을 담는 그릇일 뿐이니까. 그래서 한글 맞춤법은 들머리 제1항부터 “한글 맞춤법은 표준어를 소리대로 적”는다고 밝히고 있는 것이다. 만약 어떤 말을 사람마다 제각기 달리 발음한다면, 적을 때도 제각기 달리 적게 될 것이다. 그러니 ‘소리’, 즉 표준 발음이 없으면 맞춤법은...
The post 사이시옷, 없애기보다 더 많이 쓰자 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>권영전</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: automatic code generation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481154</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-automatic-code-generation/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T13:25:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The automatically generated code tends to be the most solid part of the project, while the manually written parts are typically more problematic due to...
The post Programming embedded systems: automatic code generation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 애플 주가 하락, 애플 주가 상승 요인은 혁신에 달려 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593246</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593246/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9-%ec%9a%94%ec%9d%b8"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T12:52:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[슬기로운 은퇴생활, 연금 인출 팁]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593244</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593244/%ec%9d%80%ed%87%b4%ec%83%9d%ed%99%9c-%ec%97%b0%ea%b8%88-%ec%9d%b8%ec%b6%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T10:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSJ, 미국인들의 스트리밍 서비스 해지율이 급증하고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593233</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593233/%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%a6%ac%eb%b0%8d-%ec%84%9c%eb%b9%84%ec%8a%a4-%ed%95%b4%ec%a7%80%ec%9c%a8-%ec%a6%9d%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T10:13:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to the Node.js reference architecture: Wrapping up]]></title>
        <id>4649f433-4575-46da-84f9-76cc2af4688a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/03/introduction-nodejs-reference-architecture-wrapping"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to the Node.js reference architecture series. This post will serve as a wrap-up for the Node.js series and offer a look at what is coming next from our reference architecture team.
Catch up on the rest of the series:
Part 1: Overview of the Node.js reference architecture
Part 2: Logging in Node.js
Part 3: Code consistency in Node.js
Part 4: GraphQL in Node.js
Part 5: Building good containers
Part 6: Choosing web frameworks
Part 7: Code coverage
Part 8: TypeScript
Part 9: Securing Node.js applications
Part 10: Accessibility
Part 11: Typical development workflows
Part 12: npm development
Part 13: Problem determination
Part 14: Testing
Part 15: Transaction handling
Part 16: Load balancing, threading, and scaling
Part 17: CI/CD
Part 18: Wrap-up
Where we started
When we started thi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lucas Holmquist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대법원 면죄부보다 중요한 것, 김용균의 죽음으로 만든 법이 후퇴하고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101796</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101796"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T06:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[참여연대 사법감시센터 ‘광장에 나온 판결’] 김용균 5주기 코앞에 두고, 대법원 결국 김용균 원청업체 경영진 무죄 판결을 확정했다. 더 큰 문제는 김용균법(개정 산안법)과 중대재해처벌법(중처법)의 후퇴. 여기엔 민주당 책임도 작지 않다. 그날, 2018년 12월의 밤 그는 1994년에 태어났다. 외동아들이었다. 부모님의 속을 썩이는 일이 크게 없이 잘 자라서 군대까지 다녀오고, 대학 졸업 후에 서부발전이 운영하는 태안화력발전소(이하 ‘태안화력’)에 입사했다....
The post 대법원 면죄부보다 중요한 것, 김용균의 죽음으로 만든 법이 후퇴하고 있다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/3, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593218</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593218/1-3-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T03:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[메모리 취약점:과거, 현재, 미래 (8) Integer Overflow]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/9084973</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/9084973"/>
        <updated>2024-01-03T02:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2002년 12월 28일 발간된 Phrack 매거진 60호에서 Basic integer overflows 라는 제목으로 정수 오버플로우 취약점의 위험성 및 악용 가능성에 대해 언급되었다. 이 취약점은 2023 CWE Top 25에서 여전히 14위를 기록하고 있다(CWE-190: Integer Overflow or Wraparound). 이 취약점에 대해 CERT-C Secure coding 가이드에서도 아래와 같이 안내하고 있다.

CERT-C : INT30-C. Ensure that unsigned integer operations do not wrap
CERT-C : INT32-C. Ensure that operations on signed integers do not result in overflow

이 포스팅에서는 다음 논문의 내용을 기반으로 정리해본다.
Dietz, Will, et al. "Understanding integer overflow in C/C++." ACM Transactions on Software Engineering and Methodology (TOSEM) 25.1 (2015): 1-29.

1. 개요
이 논문의 취지는 C/C++ 언어로 작성된 프로그램에서 정수 오버플로우(Integer Overflow)는 치명적인 오류나 악용 가능한 취약점을 초래할 수 있으며, 이를 추적하는 것은 상당히 어렵다는 것을 강조한다.
이러한 버그를 자동으로 찾아주는 도구가 있다면 편리할 텐데, 모든 정수 오버플로우가 반드시 버그로 재현되는 것은 아니기 때문에 판정 기준을 만들 때 고려해야 할 사항이…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My favorite musical discoveries of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2023-music.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2023-music.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T23:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another year, another time to pick six favorite musical
     discoveries. 2023 includes ambient bluegrass, Afro-Andean funk, Northumbrian
     smallpipes, dancing kora, and Ukrainian folk jazz.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 어쩌면 세상에서 가장 어려운 ‘공통분모 찾기’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78458</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/02/npsp_discoursetoxic/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_discoursetoxic"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:59:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 11월 13일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 전쟁은 서로 생각과 의견이 다른 인류가 벌일 수 있는 가장 잔인한 집단 폭력 행위입니다. 이미 전쟁이 벌어진 상황에서 총칼을 거두는 휴전이나 평화를 논의하는 건 소용없는 일이 될 가능성이 커 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN's guide to 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954544/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954544/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:40:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The calendar has flipped over into 2024 — another year has begun.  Here at
LWN, we do not have a better idea of what this year will bring than anybody
else does, but that doesn't keep us from going out on a shaky limb and
making predictions anyway.  Here, for the curious, are a few things that we
think may be in store for 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[혐오의 정치를 혐오하면서 혐오를 부추기는 조선일보의 방식: 슬로우레터 1월3일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101762</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101762"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T22:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이재명 피습, 죽을 뻔 했다. 사고 5시간 만에 수술. 혐오의 정치를 혐오하는 방식. 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈은 또 대구로. 금융투자소득세 폐지, “조세 정의를 걷어찼다.” 90초만에 승객 379명 전원 탈출. 더 깊게 읽기. 태영건설과 SBS 가운데 고른다면? 태영건설 다음은 어딜까. 다르게 읽기. 출산 때문에 경제활동 참여 낮다는 건 거짓말. 노인들이 살기 좋은 세상을 만들어야 한다. 해법과 대안....
The post 혐오의 정치를 혐오하면서 혐오를 부추기는 조선일보의 방식: 슬로우레터 1월3일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Simplifying Git: choosing between Gitflow and Trunk-Based Development]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481150</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/simplifying-git-choosing-between-gitflow-and-trunk-based-development/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T17:33:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are somewhere around seven major Git strategies that teams use to manage their version control but Gitflow and TBD tend to be the most...
The post Simplifying Git: choosing between Gitflow and Trunk-Based Development appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 trends for 2024: AI drives more edge intelligence, RISC-V, & chiplets]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481139</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3-trends-for-2024-ai-drives-more-edge-intelligence-risc-v-chiplets/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T17:07:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the rise of AI, once “simple” devices are becoming increasingly intelligent, leading to more computing devices than ever before.
The post 3 trends for 2024: AI drives more edge intelligence, RISC-V, & chiplets appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956568/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956568/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T15:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Gentoo (Joblib), Red Hat (firefox and thunderbird), SUSE (gstreamer-plugins-bad, libssh2_org, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (firefox and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[’24년 고객 서비스 트렌드 & CX 트렌드  10가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593216</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593216/2024%eb%85%84-%ea%b3%a0%ea%b0%9d-%ec%84%9c%eb%b9%84%ec%8a%a4-%ed%8a%b8%eb%a0%8c%eb%93%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T10:56:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring x86-64-v3 for Red Hat Enterprise Linux 10]]></title>
        <id>22437bbb-f952-4417-b426-1e8d6c17164b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/02/exploring-x86-64-v3-red-hat-enterprise-linux-10"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 9, we upgraded the instruction set architecture (ISA) baseline to the x86-64-v2 microarchitecture level. For RHEL 10, we are exploring whether we can go a step further, to the x86-64-v3 level.
New CPU capabilities in x86-64-v3
The x86-64-v3 x86-64 microarchitecture level primarily benefits numerical applications (for data science, for example) which do not include specialized implementations for modern CPU microarchitectures. Overall, the x86-64-v3 change brings the following improvements:
The AVX and AVX2 instruction sets increase the width of the vector registers from 128 bits to 256 bits and add many new vector operations. 
The fused multiply-add (FMA) instruction is supported, combining multiplication and addition into a single operation that computes…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Florian Weimer</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How lazy debuginfo loading improves GDB and Valgrind]]></title>
        <id>2df095f0-07b1-42ad-9457-cf280b7769b9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/02/how-lazy-debuginfo-loading-improves-gdb-and-valgrind"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging information, a.k.a debuginfo, relates the machine instructions in an executable or shared library with human-readable information from the binary's source files. This information includes the names of functions and variables as well as the source file and line numbers where these symbols are declared and referenced. Debuggers such as GDB, the GNU debugger, and profilers such as Valgrind use debuginfo to provide developers with richly detailed views into the occurrence of memory errors in a running process or the exact cause of a crash recorded in a core file. To learn more about debuginfo, check out the following articles: Debuginfo is not just for debugging programs and The GDB developer’s GNU Debugger tutorial Part 2.
Debuginfod
Debuginfo is very useful for developers but it ca…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Aaron Merey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[골든걸스]의 미학: 솔리스트 디바의 성장, 공감, 어울림… 우리도 도전할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101692</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101692"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T04:56:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[박미숙의 새 필드] 한국학이 활발한 영국 셰필드에서 대중문화를 공부한 박미숙 박사와 함께 TV, 드라마, 영화 등을 이야기합니다. 오늘 추가할 새 필드는 ‘골든걸스’입니다. 텔레비전만큼 ‘지금, 여기’를 즉각적으로 반영하는 것은 없다. 텔레비전을 통해 웃고 울으며 몸과 마음을 튜닝한다. 한편 텔레비전은 항상 천덕꾸러기였다. 잉여와 시간 낭비의 상징이자 바보상자이며, 길티 플레저(guilty pleasure: 죄의식과 쾌락을 동시에 느끼는 심리)의 대상이다. 그런...
The post [골든걸스]의 미학: 솔리스트 디바의 성장, 공감, 어울림… 우리도 도전할 수 있을까 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>박미숙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한글 맞춤법 최대의 난제, 사이시옷을 없앨 때가 됐다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101699</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101699"/>
        <updated>2024-01-02T04:47:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사이시옷은 논쟁적인 맞춤법 규칙이다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 기본 원칙. 사이시옷의 두 가지 조건. 사이시옷이 붙지 않는 세 가지 경우. 한자어+한자어인데도 사이시옷을 붙이는 여섯 가지 예외. 발음에 따라 다르다. 헷갈리는 경우. ‘값’도 붙여쓴다. 문제는 원칙이 없다는 것. 생각해 볼 부분. 한글 표기법의 최대 난제, 대안은?
The post 한글 맞춤법 최대의 난제, 사이시옷을 없앨 때가 됐다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이념 패거리 카르텔? 윤석열은 지금 초조하다: 슬로우레터 1월2일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101670</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101670"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T22:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[국민의힘 33% Vs. 민주당 33%. 일본에서 진도 7.6 강진. 이번에는 이념 패거리 카르텔? 김건희 특검, 조선일보가 내놓은 출구 전략은. 신년 기자회견은 건너 뛰나. 쟁점과 현안. “두 개의 조선”. ‘동료 시민’과 ‘단결’. 더 깊게 읽기. 민주당 200석 만들면 12월 대선 가능할까. 젖은 나뭇가지? 혼돈의 부동산 시장. 해법과 대안. 인구 3만 단양군, 생활인구는 27만 명. 오늘의 TMI....
The post 이념 패거리 카르텔? 윤석열은 지금 초조하다: 슬로우레터 1월2일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023 in Review]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=39537</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2024/01/01/2023-in-review/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1 January 2024 by Phillip JohnstonThe end of one year (or the beginning of the next) is always a great time to check in. In review, 2023 was quite a productive one: Published a total of 123 new items on the website: 26 blog posts, 23 Glossary entries, 42 Field Atlas entries, and 32 lessons … 
Continue reading "2023 in Review"
The post 2023 in Review appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Phillip Johnston</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 6.6.9 and 6.1.70]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956524/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956524/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T16:16:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.6.9 and 6.1.70 stable kernels.  As usual, they contain
important fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The trouble with MAX_ORDER]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956321/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956321/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T16:14:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One might not think that much could be said about a simple macro defining a
constant integer value.  But the kernel is special, it seems.  A change to
the definition of MAX_ORDER has had a number of follow-on effects,
and the task of cleaning up after this change is not done yet.  So perhaps
a look at MAX_ORDER is in order.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scribus 1.6.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956522/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956522/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T15:46:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 1.6.0 of the Scribus
desktop-publishing application has been released.  The
list of new features is rather long and includes a user interface overhaul,
improvements for HiDPI screens, new scripting commands, lots of
typographical improvements and features, a new picture browser for
graphical asset management, support for more gradient types, and much more.


Scribus 1.6.0 is the long awaited release in the next stable series,
replacing 1.4.8 and development versions in the 1.5.x series. This version
has been in development for some years and contains thousands of
enhancements and fixes across all areas of the program. It has more
features, is faster, and is more stable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956521/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956521/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T15:30:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ansible, asterisk, cjson, firefox-esr, kernel, libde265, libreoffice, libspreadsheet-parseexcel-perl, php-guzzlehttp-psr7, thunderbird, tinyxml, and xerces-c), Fedora (podman-tui, proftpd, python-asyncssh, squid, and xerces-c), Mageia (libssh and proftpd), and SUSE (deepin-compressor, gnutls, gstreamer, libreoffice, opera, proftpd, and python-pip).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[레버리지 ETF 투자 유의점]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593213</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593213/%eb%a0%88%eb%b2%84%eb%a6%ac%ec%a7%80-etf-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T08:43:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[24년 ETF 투자 가이드, ETF 수익률,  ETF분배율 기준]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593201</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593201/24%eb%85%84-etf-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%b4%eb%93%9c-etf-%ec%88%98%ec%9d%b5%eb%a5%a0-etf%eb%b6%84%eb%b0%b0%ec%9c%a8"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T07:39:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of reading: October - December 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/summary-of-reading-october-december-2023/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/summary-of-reading-october-december-2023/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-01T05:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<ul class="simple">
<li>&quot;Nomadland: Surviving America in the Twenty-First Century&quot; by Jessica
Bruder - describes the lives of the modern van-dwellers, mostly of older
adults that travel around the country between seasonal jobs and live in
their RVs or cars. Interesting book that tells a good story and avoids being
preachy most of the …</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 미국의 소극적인 태도가 오히려 중국을 도발할 가능성이 높다 하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78158</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/31/npsp_uschinataiwan/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_uschinataiwan"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T22:59:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 11월 12일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 이종혁 교수의 양안 관계 분석은 아메리카노 전문가 인터뷰에서도 보실 수 있습니다. 오는 13일 대만 총통 선거 이후에 대만 선거를 둘러싼 중국과 미국의 셈법을 이종혁 교수와 함께 분석해볼 예정입니다. 미국 지도자들에게는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[새해 첫날 아침, 엇갈린 전망과 새로운 질문: 슬로우레터 1월1일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101646</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101646"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T22:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 투표를 한다면? 완전히 다른 결과. “김건희 특검법 거부권 옳지 않다”, 62%. “이준석‧이낙연 신당 나오면 지지정당 바꿀 수도”, 18%. 새해 첫날 신문 1면의 키워드는. 새해 달라지는 것들. “윤석열 신년 기자회견 해야 한다.” 쟁점과 현안. 명낙회동은 쇼잉? 한동훈 회동도 김건희가 빠졌다. 이낙연 1월4일 창당 선언. 윤석열은 박근혜를 또 만났다. 한동훈 비대위 출범 하루 만에 민경우 사퇴....
The post 새해 첫날 아침, 엇갈린 전망과 새로운 질문: 슬로우레터 1월1일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My 2023 in software engineering]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8485</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/12/31/my-2023-in-software-engineering/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T22:36:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a 2009 post, I predicted that Chinese and Indian developers would become a major influence in the next decade. This year, it was very noticeable that many of the authors of papers at major conferences had Asian names. I would say that, on average, papers with Asian author names were better than papers by […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.7-rc8]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956467/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956467/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T21:44:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.7-rc8 for testing.


	So as expected, pretty much nothing happened over the holiday week.
	We've got literally just 45 files changed, and almost a third of
	those files aren't even kernel code (ie things like selftests,
	scripting, Kconfig and maintainer file updates). And some of the
	rest is prep-work and cleanups for future (real) changes.

	But we do have a couple of real fixes in there, and I suspect we'll
	get a few more next week as people come back from their
	food-induced torpor.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Julia 1.10 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956456/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956456/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T21:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Julia programming language project has released Julia v1.10.  It is mainly a performance release, with only two new language features mentioned in the release notes: "JuliaSyntax.jl is now used as the default parser, providing better diagnostics and faster parsing." and the addition of two Unicode symbols for use as binary operators: "⥺ (U+297A, \leftarrowsubset) and ⥷ (U+2977, \leftarrowless)".  Package-loading time has been improved further and the mark phase of garbage collection has been parallelized, among other improvements.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gnuplot 6.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956454/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956454/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T19:47:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.0 of the Gnuplot plotting system
has been released.


	Gnuplot has been supported and under active development since 1986.
	This is the first new major version of gnuplot since the release of
	version 5 in January 2015.  It introduces extensions to the gnuplot
	command language, an expanded collection of special and
	complex-valued functions, additional 2D and 3D plotting styles, and
	support for new output protocols.


See the
release notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘Experience Energy’ at the Verkehrshaus: The ‘House of Energy’ Construction Kit]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39981</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/31/experience-energy-at-the-verkehrshaus-the-house-of-energy-construction-kit/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-31T18:35:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 'Swiss Museum of Transport' in Lucerne opened a new 'Experience Energy!' exhibition in April 2023. The project involved creating a sustainable construction kit to explore energy, featuring renewable energy, energy storage, and usage. The kit highlights energy concepts using customized hardware and software, promoting energy education. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Power Measurement with INA260 Sensor]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39953</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/30/power-measurement-with-ina260-sensor/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T17:59:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To measure voltage, current and power, I quickly had to write a software driver for the Texas Instruments INA260 power sensor, using the Adafruit INA260 breakout board for a research project at HSLU university. The driver, implemented with necessary functions and configurations, is available on GitHub. Its command-line interface and support for a single INA260 make it simple and efficient. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How bad are search results? Let's compare Google, Bing, Marginalia, Kagi, Mwmbl, and ChatGPT]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/seo-spam/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/seo-spam/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In The birth & death of search engine optimization, Xe suggests
Here's a fun experiment to try. Take an open source project such as yt-dlp and try to find it from a very generic term like "youtube downloader". You won't be able to find it because of all of the content farms that try to rank at the top for that term. Even though yt-dlp is probably actually what you want for a tool to download video from YouTube.
More generally, most tech folks I'm connected to seem to think that Google search results are significantly worse than they were ten years ago (Mastodon poll, Twitter poll, Threads poll). However, there's a sizable group of vocal folks who claim that search results are still great. E.g., a bluesky thought leader who gets high engagement says:
i think the rending of garments about ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gentoo in binary form]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956366/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956366/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T15:17:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gentoo Linux is the prototypical source-based distribution, but there is
now a
binary installation option available as well.


	To speed up working with slow hardware and for overall convenience,
	we’re now also offering binary packages for download and direct
	installation! For most architectures, this is limited to the core
	system and weekly updates - not so for amd64 and arm64
	however. There we’ve got a stunning >20 GByte of packages on our
	mirrors, from LibreOffice to KDE Plasma and from Gnome to Docker.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Core Symmetric Multi-Processing (SMP) with FreeRTOS]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39897</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/29/multi-core-symmetric-multi-processing-smp-with-freertos/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T10:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new FreeRTOS V11 has Symmetric Multi-Processing (SMP) integrated, simplifying its usage for single-core and multi-core applications. SMP support, previously available through dedicated forks, is now integrated into the mainline. Configuration options for SMP are available, and debugging for multi-core applications is also possible. However, some limitations with debugging support currently exist. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[번개탄, 유서, 언론의 조회수 장사는 끝나지 않았다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101622</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101622"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T08:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[배우 이선균 씨가 27일 자신의 차 안에서 숨진 채 발견됐습니다. 이 씨는 마약 투약 혐의로 경찰 수사를 받고 있었는데요. 유흥업소 실장의 진술에 의존해 3개월 넘게 이어진 수사에서 경찰은 이 씨를 소환조사마다 포토라인에 세웠고, 범죄 혐의가 확인되기도 전에 피의 사실을 언론에 흘렸습니다. 언론은 무분별한 경찰 발 받아쓰기에 이어 사생활까지 선정적으로 전했는데요. 이 씨 죽음의 책임에서 결코...
The post 번개탄, 유서, 언론의 조회수 장사는 끝나지 않았다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Autoscaling Kafka workloads with custom metrics autoscaler]]></title>
        <id>c60856e2-3066-4ce6-a992-9719d72ac457</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/29/autoscaling-kafka-workloads-custom-metrics-autoscaler"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Autoscaling plays an important role in cloud-native applications, ensuring both efficiency and reliability. It automatically adapts resource allocation in response to current demands, scaling up during peak periods to maintain stable performance and scaling back in quieter times to reduce costs. This flexibility is especially useful for handling unpredictable traffic, ensuring applications stay responsive without using more resources than necessary. Essentially, autoscaling helps manage cloud applications effectively and cost-efficiently.
The custom metrics autoscaler operator enhances Red Hat OpenShift scaling capabilities, particularly for event-driven applications. Unlike the standard Horizontal Pod Autoscaler (HPA), which primarily scales applications based on CPU and memory metrics, t…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Etienne Dubois</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베스트셀러로 돌아보는 2023년의 풍경]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101597</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101597"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T06:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] ‘외전’ 2023 베스트셀러 분석… 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, ‘홍보가 아니라 소통입니다’ 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기. 한해 베스트셀러 ‘시장’의 풍경을 정리해 봤다. 온라인서점 알라딘에서 월간 베스트셀러 리스트를 참고했고, 소설은 제외하고 봤는데, 그동안 내가 독서 팟캐스트에서 소개한 책들은 베스트셀러 트렌드에서 백만 광년 쯤 떨어진 딴 세상에 있었다. 조금 뻘쭘한 건...
The post 베스트셀러로 돌아보는 2023년의 풍경 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[알 권리? 물고 뜯고 즐기는… 잔인한 한국 사회]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101557</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101557"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T01:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어제 이선균 배우가 우리와 함께 살던 이 세상을 떠나갔다. 오후에 들어온 페이스북에는 애도로 가득했다. 큰 상실감, 분노, 한탄의 글을 읽노라니, 나 또한 마음이 착잡하여 일이 손에 잡히지 않을 지경이었다. 많은 이들이 피의사실 공표와 언론, 연예인(개인)의 사생활 폭로 문제를 짚으면서 정치권, 언론과 수사기관을 비난한다. 이 지점에서 생각해 볼 문제는 결국 세 가지다. 첫째는 피의사실 공표의 문제....
The post 알 권리? 물고 뜯고 즐기는… 잔인한 한국 사회 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정연순</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 인류 문명의 단계는 ‘온라인 쇼핑’에 이르렀다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78134</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/28/npsp_onlineshopping/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_onlineshopping"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T22:59:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 11월 8일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 인간의 생존을 위해서는 많은 것들이 필요합니다. 우리는 자신이 가진 것과 남이 가진 것을 교환함으로써 그 필요를 충족해 왔고, 이 교환의 효율은 문명의 발전 속도에 비례했습니다. 아니, 교환을 효율적으로 만드는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 특검 거부권 괜찮을까, 조중동의 우려와 경고: 슬로우레터 12월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101562</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101562"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T22:05:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 특검법이 통과됐다. 국민 여론은 압도적인 찬성. 거부권이 최선인가, 조중동의 질문. 정권 심판론 피로감, 한겨레의 우려. 검찰이 특검 불렀다. 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈 비대위, 3040 비정치인을 전면에. 정세균이 “벼랑 끝에서 손을 놓으라”고 말한 이유. 국방부 교재에 “독도는 분쟁 지역”이라고? 더 깊게 읽기. 국민의힘에 소장파 의원이 없는 이유. “한계가 너무 컸다.” 한국 사회에도 양극화 해소, 저출생·고령화, 기후변화,...
The post 김건희 특검 거부권 괜찮을까, 조중동의 우려와 경고: 슬로우레터 12월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.75.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956303/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956303/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T18:33:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.75.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Notable changes include
"async
fn and -> impl Trait in traits", a pointer byte-offset
API, some compiler performance improvements, and a number of stabilized APIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The Linux graphics stack in a nutshell, part 2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955708/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955708/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T14:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Displaying an application's graphical output onto the screen requires
compositing and 
mode setting that are correctly synchronized among the various pieces,
with low overhead.
In this second and final article in the series, we will look at
those pieces of the Linux graphics stack. In the  first installment, we 
followed the path of graphics from the application, through Mesa, while
using the 
memory-management features of the kernel's Direct
Rendering Manager (DRM) subsystem.
We ended up with an application's graphics data stored in an output buffer,
so now
it's time to display the image to the user.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956257/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956257/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T14:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (haproxy, libssh, and nodejs), Fedora (filezilla and minizip-ng), Gentoo (Git, libssh, and OpenSSH), and SUSE (gstreamer, postfix, webkit2gtk3, and zabbix).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아무도 미워하지 않았던 남자의 죽음: ‘박 부장’의 죽음을 애도하며]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101540</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101540"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T09:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우중충한 날씨 탓인가, 한 해를 보내는 착잡한 기분 때문일까, 유난히 기분이 침울했는데 27일 정오쯤에 들려온 뉴스는 다가올 새해의 작은 희망마저도 박살 내고 말았다. 마음이 뒤숭숭하니 일을 완전히 놓아 버렸다. 이 같은 비극적 뉴스 한두 번 겪어 본 나이가 아니기 때문에 담담해지려 애써도 보았다. 어차피 내 가족 일도 아닌데, 맘속으로 수십 번 욕하다 보면 ‘이 또한...
The post 아무도 미워하지 않았던 남자의 죽음: ‘박 부장’의 죽음을 애도하며 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정호재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operating OpenShift the SRE way]]></title>
        <id>cd4ad152-5a7e-4e49-9e79-e46ad98ad1f6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/28/operating-openshift-sre-way"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: The following is an excerpt from Operating OpenShift: An SRE Approach to Managing Infrastructure by Rick Racklow and Manuel Dewald (O'Reilly Media, September 2023). Download the e-book to learn best practices and tools that can help reduce the effort of deploying a Kubernetes platform.
Operating distributed software is a difficult task. It requires humans with a deep understanding of the system they maintain. No matter how much automation you create, it will never replace highly skilled operations personnel.
OpenShift is a platform, built to help software teams develop and deploy their distributed software. It comes with a large set of tools that are built in or can be deployed easily. While it can be of great help to its users and can eliminate a lot of traditionally manual operatio…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>clobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공개SW페스티벌 발표 후기]]></title>
        <id>https://taegon.kim/?p=10678</id>
        <link href="https://taegon.kim/archives/10678"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T06:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난 12월 1일 코엑스에서 과학기술정보통신부와 정보통신산업진흥원(NIPA) 주관으로 2023 공개SW 페스티벌이 열렸다. 나는 여기에서 '오늘 저녁부터 시작하는 오픈소스 기여'라는 제목으로 오픈소스에 기여하는 방법에 관한 발표를 했다. 사실 이 글을 쓸 생각이 있던 건 아니었는데 오늘 문득 "발표 자료 언제 공개하지" 싶어서 검색해봤다가 이미 발표 전날 공개가 되었던 것을 발견했다. 보통 발표하고 며칠 있다가 홈페이지에 업데이트되는 경우가 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>taggon</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[자녀에게 최고의 선물은… 좋은 어른이 되는 것]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101505</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101505"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T04:39:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 좋은 부모, 좋은 어른이 된다는 것… 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, ‘홍보가 아니라 소통입니다’ 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기. 오늘 읽을 책은 [어른을 키우는 어른을 위한 심리학] 하지현 지음, 은행나무: 2023. 입니다. 성인 자녀를 둔 부모를 위한 책으로 어른이 된 자녀를 흐뭇하게 바라보며 인생 후반기를 행복하게 보낼 수 있도록, 부모와...
The post 자녀에게 최고의 선물은… 좋은 어른이 되는 것 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘법치’와 ‘민주주의’ 기로에 선 미국?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78422</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/27/npsp_coloradotrump/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_coloradotrump"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T02:30:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[미국 콜로라도주 대법원이 지난주 놀랄 만한 판결을 내렸습니다. 트럼프 전 대통령이 1월 6일 의사당 테러를 방조하고 사실상 부추기며 반란 행위에 가담했으므로, 대선 투표용지에 이름을 올릴 자격이 없다고 판결한 겁니다. 수정헌법 14조 3항이 근거가 됐습니다. 트럼프 측이 즉각 항소한 데 이어 미시건주 대법원은 같은 사안에 대해 트럼프가 출마하는 데 문제가 없다고 판결해 공은 연방 대법원으로 넘어가게 됐습니다. 트럼프의 후보 자격을 사법부가 법치의 기준으로 판단하느냐, 아니면 유권자가 직접 심판하게 두는 게 맞느냐를 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/28, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593173</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593173/%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T22:54:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[연말에 돌아보는 윤석열의 아무말 대잔치: 슬로우레터 12월28일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101507</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101507"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T22:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이선균의 죽음, 언론이 만든 사회적 타살이다. 마약과의 전쟁이 놓친 것. 썰렁했던 이준석 탈당. 쟁점과 현안. 오늘 쌍특검법 처리 한다. 바닥을 드러낸 김홍일. 민주당 공관위원장은 임혁백이 유력. 총선에 ‘올인’, 차관과 비서관도 무더기 차출. 대장동 의혹 제보자는 남평오. 더 깊게 읽기. 태영건설 워크아웃 신청은 시작일 뿐? 한동훈 연설에 ‘윤석열’이 없었다. 해법과 대안. 간병비 대책, 이걸로 되겠나. 울산...
The post 연말에 돌아보는 윤석열의 아무말 대잔치: 슬로우레터 12월28일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded’s top 10 articles of 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481101</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embeddeds-top-10-articles-of-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post embedded’s top 10 articles of 2023 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Embedded staff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debian statement on the Cyber Resilience Act]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956187/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956187/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T18:35:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Debian project has completed a
general-resolution vote, adopting a statement expressing concern about
the Cyber Resilience Act (CRA) pending in the European Union.


	Even if only "commercial activities" are in the scope of CRA, the
	Free Software community - and as a consequence, everybody - will
	lose a lot of small projects. CRA will force many small enterprises
	and most probably all self employed developers out of business
	because they simply cannot fulfill the requirements imposed by
	CRA. Debian and other Linux distributions depend on their work. If
	accepted as it is, CRA will undermine not only an established
	community but also a thriving market. CRA needs an exemption for
	small businesses and, at the very least, solo-entrepreneurs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moving Pixel Clock Project]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39772</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/27/moving-pixel-clock-project/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T15:44:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article describes building a clock using moving pixels. The pixels are moved by tiny stepper motors, and addressable RGB LEDs illuminate the pixels from the back, creating a mesmerizing moving clock. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[슬기로운 은퇴생활, 연금과 종합과세 그리고 세금을 최소화하는 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593171</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593171/%ec%8a%ac%ea%b8%b0%eb%a1%9c%ec%9a%b4-%ec%9d%80%ed%87%b4%ec%83%9d%ed%99%9c-%ec%97%b0%ea%b8%88%ea%b3%bc-%ec%a2%85%ed%95%a9%ea%b3%bc%ec%84%b8-%ea%b7%b8%eb%a6%ac%ea%b3%a0-%ec%84%b8%ea%b8%88%ec%9d%84"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T12:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서울의 봄, 언론의 겨울]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101500</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101500"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T09:56:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[권력에 의한 노골적인 언론탄압의 해였던 지난 1년, 윤석열 정부의 언론정책-그것도 언론정책이라고 할 수 있다면-의 주요한 특징은 유신이나 전두환 독재정권에다 이명박 정권하의 언론탄압 양상을 합해 놓은 것을 넘어 새로운 차원을 보여주고 있다는 것이다. 언론에 대한 장악과 억압을 넘어서 언론기능 자체의 와해, 특히 공영언론의 해체를 의도하고 있다. 군사독재 정권이나 이른바 ‘보수’ 정권에서 공영언론의 친정권화를 시도하던 것과도 다른...
The post 서울의 봄, 언론의 겨울 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[위안부 판결, 다시 한번 일본의 국가면제 주장을 배제하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101489</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101489"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T08:29:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[참여연대 사법감시센터 ‘광장에 나온 판결’] 한국 법원, 다시 한 번 일본의 ‘국가면제’를 배제하다 2023년 11월 23일, 서울고등법원 제33민사부(구회근, 황성미, 허익수 판사)는 일본의 국가면제를 배제하고 일본군‘위안부’ 피해자들의 청구를 전면적으로 받아들이는 판결(이하 ‘구회근 판결’)을 선고했다. 2021년 1월 8일에 서울중앙지방법원 제34민사부(김정곤, 김경선, 전경세 판사)가 같은 취지의 판결(이하 김정곤 판결)을 선고한 데 이어 두 번째이다. 두 판결의 쟁점은 일본의...
The post 위안부 판결, 다시 한번 일본의 국가면제 주장을 배제하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Kafka Connect]]></title>
        <id>5ce15a20-8c95-4939-9928-94010cbeccd1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/27/introduction-kafka-connect"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Note: The following is an excerpt from Kafka Connect: Build and Run Data Pipelines by Mickael Maison and Kate Stanley (O'Reilly Media, September 2023). Download the e-book for practical advice to help you quickly adopt Kafka and build modern data pipelines.
Systems to handle data have existed since the early days of computers. However, the amount of data being generated and collected is growing at an exponential rate. In 2018, an estimated 2.5 quintillion bytes of data were being created each day, and the International Data Corporation (IDC) expects that the total size of all existing data will double between 2022 and 2025.
For organizations to handle these large volumes of data, now called “big data,” new classes of systems have been designed. There are now hundreds of different databases…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mickael Maison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이선균은 경찰의 피의사실 공표와 받아쓰기 언론의 희생자다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101455</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101455"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T04:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[배우 이선균이 숨진 상태로 발견됐다. 유서가 발견됐고 경찰은 자살로 추정하고 있다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 경찰이 흘린 사건이다. 언론의 여론 재판. 이상보 사건의 교훈. 의도적으로 흘렸나. 알권리라는 핑계. 좌표 찍기를 넘어. 해법은 없나.
The post 이선균은 경찰의 피의사실 공표와 받아쓰기 언론의 희생자다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2024년을 준비하라: 노인 – 노동시장 – 이주노동자 묶는 마스터플랜 필요하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101325</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101325"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T04:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 2024년 ‘블루’ 코리아의 가장 차가운 곳에 관하여. 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)이 전하는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기. 지방소멸이 아니다. 국가소멸이다. 다이내믹 코리아는 경제성장만큼 인구감소도 극적이다. 물론 호들갑 떨기보다는 차분하게 더 냉정하게 이미 늦었지만, 하나씩 준비해야 할 일이다. 인구감소를 피할 수 없다면 그 조건 속에서 함께 더불어 잘 사는 방법을 모색해야 한다. 물론 현실은...
The post 2024년을 준비하라: 노인 – 노동시장 – 이주노동자 묶는 마스터플랜 필요하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/27, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593169</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593169/12-27-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T02:56:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[너무 일찍 꺼낸 한동훈 카드, 보수 언론의 불안과 불만: 슬로우레터 12월27일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101410</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101410"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T22:08:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈이 내놓은 어젠다. 불출마? 당선 가능성 없으니 버리는 카드. 한동훈에게 김건희 물었더니. 다르게 읽기. 중앙일보의 기대에 못 미친 한동훈. 쟁점과 현안. 류희림 청부 민원 드러나자 신고자 고발. 또 언론사 대표 압수수색. 김홍일의 검사 시절 흑역사. 해법과 대안. 재활용 안 되는 중국산 배터리가 골치. 아파트에 불이 났을 때는. 반짝반짝 아이디어가 살린 지방정부 스타 정책. 바다 밑에...
The post 너무 일찍 꺼낸 한동훈 카드, 보수 언론의 불안과 불만: 슬로우레터 12월27일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956156/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956156/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T14:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (curl, openssh, osslsigncode, and putty), Fedora (chromium, filezilla, libfilezilla, mingw-gstreamer1, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-base, mingw-gstreamer1-plugins-good, opensc, thunderbird, unrealircd, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Gentoo (Ceph, FFmpeg, Flatpak, Gitea, and SABnzbd), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable), Slackware (kernel and postfix), and SUSE (cppcheck, distribution, gstreamer-plugins-bad, jbigkit, and ppp).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DJ-공간에서의 미적경험에 대해서 그리고 DJ덱의 영원회귀]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3237</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2023/djspace/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T12:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[. 울지 않으려면 우리는 잠깐 웃어넘겨야 한다. DJ-공간은 시대의 우울의 몽상이자 알레고리 인 것 이다. 그러나 명심해야 될 것은 디제잉 컨트롤러는 하나의 악기이며, 오케스트라를 지휘하도록 도와준다. 단지 반복될 그것을 위해서 말이다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[About the aesthetic experience in DJ-space and the eternal return of DJ decks]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3265</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2023/djspace-eng/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T12:42:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In order not to cry, we have to laugh a little. The DJ-space is a dream and an allegory of the melancholy of the era. However, we must keep in mind that the DJ controller is a musical instrument that helps conduct the orchestra. Only for it to be repeated.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3분기 마이크론 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 반도체 업사이클의 도래와 마이크로 목표주가 상향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593163</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593163/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80%ec%99%80-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T11:08:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/26, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593154</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593154/12-26-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T10:57:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[재생 에너지를 늘리면 전기요금이 낮아질까.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101392</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101392"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T06:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[결론부터 말하면 쉽지 않다. 당장 내일부터 엄청난 규모의 재생 에너지를 보급하더라도 여러 이유 때문에 10~20년 안에 전기요금이 낮아질 거라고 기대하기 어려운 상황이다. 재생 에너지 확대에 대한 대중의 지지를 확보하려면, 탄소 중립의 대의도 중요하지만 경제적 실익에 대한 비전을 제시해야 한다. ‘미래소년 코난’을 보고 자란 세대들은 아마도 재생 에너지는 연료비가 들지 않으니 거의 공짜에 가까운 깨끗한 전기가...
The post 재생 에너지를 늘리면 전기요금이 낮아질까. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>권효재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘격노’가 아니라 ‘불쾌’? 언론에 제목 고쳐달라 했나: 슬로우레터 12월26일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101375</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101375"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T22:03:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[예고된 충돌, 김건희 특검법 날리나. 격노 아니고 불쾌감, 제목 바꿔달라 했나. “정치 9단도 풀기 어려운 문제.” 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈 비대위는 ‘밑져야 본전’이다? 약속대련? 차기 권력의 숙명. ‘꿀 지역구’ 노리는 민주당 비례들. 병립형? 위성정당? 맘 못 정한 민주당. 이준석의 ‘이별 공식’이 꼬였다. 더 깊게 읽기. 뉴스타파 고발 쏟아졌는데 알고 보니 류희림 가족 민원. 문과 소멸. 다르게...
The post ‘격노’가 아니라 ‘불쾌’? 언론에 제목 고쳐달라 했나: 슬로우레터 12월26일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ruby 3.3.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956115/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956115/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T17:58:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As is the tradition for the Ruby programming language, December 25 is the date for new major releases; this year, Ruby 3.3.0 was released.  It comes with a new parser called "Prism" that is "both a C library that will be used internally by CRuby and a Ruby gem that can be used by any tooling which needs to parse Ruby code".  The release also has many performance improvements, especially in the YJIT (Yet another Ruby JIT) just-in-time compiler. Ruby 3.3 adds a new Ruby-based JIT, RJIT, that targets x86_64, which is available for experimental purposes.  There are lots of other improvements and new features described in the announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘역사적 승리’ 거둔 미국 자동차노조, 그들의 ‘Make America Great Again’은 이뤄질까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78119</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/24/npsp_uaw/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_uaw"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 11월 6일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 2023년 미국 경제를 관통하는 열쇳말 중 하나는 노동조합이 될 것으로 보입니다. ‘노동조합’ 하면 해묵은 구호나 한물간 투쟁 방식과 같은 부정적인 이미지를 떠올리는 분이 많을 텐데, 사실 미국에서도 노조의 이미지는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[산타는 어떻게 좁은 굴뚝으로 들어가나요: 슬로우레터 12월25일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101365</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101365"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T22:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[8년 만에 화이트크리스마스. 산타가 가짜라고? 오늘 베들레헴에서는. 다르게 읽기. 차라리 나무를 베자? 예수님은 기뻐하실까. 쟁점과 현안. 대통령실 크리스마스 행사에 김건희가 없었다. 한동훈의 세 가지 킬러 문항. 한나땡? 민주당의 한가한 총선 전략. 방통위 2명으로 안 된다. 더 깊게 읽기. 한국이 뒤처지는 이유. 공수처 엑소더스. 해법과 대안. K팝 행동주의, 나무 11만 그루 심었다. 애플이 AI 학습에 돈을...
The post 산타는 어떻게 좁은 굴뚝으로 들어가나요: 슬로우레터 12월25일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sample size needed to compare performance of two languages]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8466</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/12/24/sample-size-needed-to-compare-performance-of-two-languages/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T22:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A humungous organization wants to minimise one or more of: program development time/cost, coding mistakes made, maintenance time/cost, and have decided to use either of the existing languages X or Y. To make an informed decision, it is necessary to collect the required data on time/cost/mistakes by monitoring the development process, and recording the appropriate […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Little Algorithms, Part 7: Continued Fraction Approximation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1620.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1620.php"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T18:43:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a long time since my last Ten Little Algorithms post, and I need a break from long articles, so here is Part Seven, in which we show the use of continued fractions for the approximation of real numbers. 


Other articles in this series:



Part 1: Russian Peasant Multiplication

Part 2:...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Processor Expert Components: 24-Dec-2023 Release]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39768</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/24/processor-expert-components-24-dec-2023-release/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T11:58:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of the year 2023, time for a new Processor Expert component and library release. Enjoy and Happy New Year! Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.7-rc7]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956092/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956092/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T01:26:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.7-rc7 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	Anyway, rc7 itself looks fairly normal. It's actually a bit bigger
	than rc6 was, but not hugely so, and nothing in here looks at all
	strange. Please do give it a whirl if you have the time and the
	energy, but let's face it, I expect things to be very quiet and
	this to be one of those "nothing happens" weeks. Because even if
	you aren't celebrating this time of year, you might take advantage
	of the peace and quiet.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernel 5.15.145]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956082/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956082/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T22:16:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 5.15.145 stable kernel has been
released.  It consists mostly of fixes to the ksmbd subsystem, which has
been marked as broken due to (until now) a lack of support for the 5.15.x
kernels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(번역) 인공지능은 소프트웨어라는 개념을 완전히 바꿔버립니다.  – 빌 게이츠]]></title>
        <id>http://ebadak.news/?p=3756</id>
        <link href="https://ebadak.news/2023/12/23/ai-agent-will-change-everything/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T11:52:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인공지능 에이전트가 테크 산업을 완전히 바꿔버릴겁니다. 검색, 커머스, SNS, 광고 모두 지금과는 완전히 다른 형태의 비즈니스가 될거에요.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>에디</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Gemini models from Go]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/using-gemini-models-from-go/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/using-gemini-models-from-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-23T01:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Google has recently made their newest family of multimodal LLMs available
<a class="reference external" href="https://ai.google.dev/">via an API</a> with a generous free tier.
Google also released SDKs in several popular programming languages, including
Go.</p>
<p>This post is a quick overview of how to get started with the Go SDK to ask
the model questions …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darktable 4.6.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956017/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956017/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T17:24:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
4.6.0 of the darktable photo editor has been released.  Changes include
a new "rgb primaries" module that "can be used for delicate color
corrections as well as creative color grading", enhancements to the
sigmoid module, some performance improvements, and more.  (LWN looked at darktable in 2022).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/956012/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/956012/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bluez, chromium, gst-plugins-bad1.0, openssh, and thunderbird), Fedora (chromium, firefox, kernel, libssh, nss, opensc, and thunderbird), Gentoo (Arduino, Exiv2, LibRaw, libssh, NASM, and QtWebEngine), Mageia (gstreamer), and SUSE (gnutls, gstreamer-plugins-bad, libcryptopp, libqt5-qtbase, ppp, tinyxml, xorg-x11-server, and zbar).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대중 참여가 오히려 정치를 망친다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101273</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101273"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T06:38:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, ‘홍보가 아니라 소통입니다’ 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기. 오늘 ‘마냐의 북라이딩’에서는 논쟁적인 책, [책임 정당]을 함께 읽습니다. 이 책은 바람직한 민주주의의 상식처럼 받아들여지는 다수 시민의 적극적인 정당 참여가 오히려 역효과를 가져올 수 있음을 경고하고, 비례대표제도가 가지는 약점을 다양한 국제적인 사례를 통해 분석합니다. 많은 나라에서 이상적으로...
The post 대중 참여가 오히려 정치를 망친다 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[양극화한 세계, 가짜뉴스로 진영화하기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101190</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101190"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T04:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 2023년 미디어 이슈 결산 국내 편 ‘가짜뉴스’. ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수와 함께 2023년을 돌아봅니다. 캡콜드에게 2023년을 돌아볼 수 있는 키워드를 뽑아달라고 요청했다. 그는 챗GPT로 상징되는 생성형 AI와 정권 유지를 위한 억압적인 담론 전략으로서 ‘가짜뉴스’를 각각 가장 중요한 세계 이슈와 국내 이슈로 뽑았다. 그 두 개의 키워드를 중심으로 이야기했다. 이 글은 그 두 번째다. 참고로 캡콜드가...
The post 양극화한 세계, 가짜뉴스로 진영화하기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Developer’s New Year’s Resolution]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1618.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1618.php"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T02:05:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we reach the end of another year, while wrapping up this one, we also contemplate the year ahead. Though nothing major might change on the 1st of January, it’s nice to pause during the holidays to reflect on the past and plan for future improvements.
I like to plan my professional improvements, and I always include them in my New Year’s resolution. Here are some ideas that I’d like to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.7 kernel will be released on January 7]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955970/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955970/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T22:48:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unsurprisingly, Linus Torvalds has let
it be known that he will do a 6.7-rc8 release (rather than 6.7 final)
on December 31, thus avoiding opening the 6.8 merge window on New
Year's Day.


	Just FYI - my current plan is that -rc7 will happen this Saturday
	(because I still follow the Finnish customs of Christmas _Eve_
	being the important day, so Sunday I'll be off), and then if
	anything comes in that week - which it will do, even if networking
	might be offline - I'll do an rc8 the week after.

	Then, unless anything odd happens, the final 6.7 release will be Jan
	7th, and so the merge window for 6.8 will open Jan 8th.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공급중시 경제이론이 중시하는 것, 남자의 기 살려주기]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=84864</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/84864/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T22:17:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[남자들은 여자들에게 먹을 것을 갖다 주고 또 보호하는 과정에서 남성으로서의 만족감을 느낀다. 복지사회에서 이러한 역할을 할 수 없게 되면 결국 술집이나 거리에서 남자들끼리만 어울려 다니려 하게 된다. [중략] 남성과 여성간의 이 같은 차이만으로도 남자들이 가정 밖에서 열심히 일하고 관료적인 위계질서 속에서 승진기회를 얻기 위해 적극적인 경쟁을 벌리며 또 돈벌이를 인생의 주요목표 중의 하나로 삼으려 하는 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열과 이준석, 누가 군만두만 먹게 될까: 슬로우레터 12월22일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101282</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101282"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T21:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈 비대위의 두 가지 메시지. 구원 투수? 아니면 패전 처리 투수? “나를 밟고 가라 해야 한다.” “9회말 2아웃 2스트라이크 상황이다.” 쟁점과 현안. 강제동원 2차 소송도 손배 인정. “출마 자격 없다”는데 트럼프에 오히려 호재? 더 깊게 읽기. 대선 때만 같아라? 다르게 읽기. 은행 팔 비틀어 돈 푼다. 해법과 대안. 도로 열선 100m에 1억 원. 총선 앞두고...
The post 윤석열과 이준석, 누가 군만두만 먹게 될까: 슬로우레터 12월22일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bugs and suspicious places in .NET 8 source code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1095/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1095/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every year, Microsoft releases a new version of .NET. This annual event is a great chance to learn about the latest .NET enhancements as well as to explore the .NET source code. Let's take the bull...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Data-type profiling for perf]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955709/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955709/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tooling for profiling the effects of memory usage and layout has always
lagged behind that for profiling processor activity, so Namhyung Kim's patch set for data-type profiling
in perf is a welcome addition.  It provides aggregated breakdowns of
memory accesses by data type that can inform structure layout and access
pattern changes.  Existing tools have either, like heaptrack, focused on
profiling allocations, or, like perf mem, on accounting memory
accesses only at the address level.  This new work builds on the latter,
using DWARF debugging information to correlate memory operations with their
source-level types.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Programming series]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481095</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-systems-programming-series/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:06:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dr. Miro Samek brings his youtube series on embedded systems programming to embedded.com with original descriptions and summaries included with each video. Follow along in...
The post Embedded Systems Programming series appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Announcing `async fn` and return-position `impl Trait` in traits (Rust Blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955925/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955925/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:02:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust Blog announces
the stabilization of a couple of trait features aimed at improving support
for async code:


	Ever since the stabilization of RFC #1522 in Rust 1.26, Rust has
	allowed users to write impl Trait as the return type of
	functions (often called "RPIT"). This means that the function
	returns "some type that implements Trait". This is
	commonly used to return closures, iterators, and other types that
	are complex or impossible to write explicitly. [...]

	Starting in Rust 1.75, you can use return-position impl
	Trait in trait (RPITIT) definitions and in trait impls. For
	example, you could use this to write a trait method that returns an
	iterator: [...]

	So what does all of this have to do with async functions? Well,
	async functions are "just sugar" for functions that return
	-> impl Future. Since these are now permitted in
	traits, we also permit you to write traits that use async fn.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to combine UWB and BLE for secure entry systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481084</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-combine-uwb-and-ble-for-secure-entry-systems/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T14:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[UWB might seem the perfect solution for secure keyless entry, but UWB radios are relatively power hungry. Combining UWB with BLE offers a solution enable coin cell driven solutions for secure entry. This article explores how.
The post How to combine UWB and BLE for secure entry systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Wood</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955914/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955914/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T13:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr), Fedora (kernel), Mageia (bluez), Oracle (fence-agents, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, opensc, openssl, postgresql:10, and postgresql:12), Red Hat (postgresql:15 and tigervnc), Slackware (proftpd), and SUSE (docker, rootlesskit, firefox, go1.20-openssl, go1.21-openssl, gstreamer-plugins-bad, libreoffice, libssh2_org, poppler, putty, rabbitmq-server, wireshark, xen, xorg-x11-server, and xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remember Y2K?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1617.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1617.php"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T09:44:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even if you do not remember the “Millennium bug” or “Y2K problem” and I guess, for some younger readers, this would be considered ancient history, I am sure that you have heard about it. In the late 1990s we were all sure that chaos would occur as the year 2000 dawned. The problem was that any code written to process the date might have used just two digits to store the year and,...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with RHEL on WSL]]></title>
        <id>7825b3cc-a36e-46cf-ad19-38df9b2929e4</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/21/getting-started-rhel-windows-subsystem-linux"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) has opened up a new world for developers, allowing them to run Linux distributions alongside their Windows environment. The release of WSL 2 introduced support for more Linux distributions, including Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL). In this article, we'll explore the steps to get started with RHEL on WSL, enabling developers to work seamlessly with Windows and Linux environments.
Prerequisites
Before we begin, ensure that you have the following prerequisites in place:
WSL 2
Installed RHEL on WSL
Launch the RHEL distro on WSL
This article assumes that you have successfully installed the WSL CLI on your machine, obtained the RHEL image from the hybrid cloud, and imported the RHEL image into WSL.
Note: All following commands are performed in PowerShell wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Mungale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to get more from OpenShift Service Mesh monitoring]]></title>
        <id>0aa6b0e7-68d5-4806-9455-e5d3b1222a06</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/21/how-get-more-openshift-service-mesh-monitoring"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Service Mesh brings tracing and monitoring to your system with little effort. However, the information is basic. In this article, we will create three applications in the Quarkus, Node.Js, and Java languages to collect more detailed statistics with Jaeger, collect custom application specific metrics with Prometheus, and create new dashboards with Grafana.
Jaeger
Jaeger, installed by default in OpenShift Service Mesh, allows developers to configure their services to gather runtime statistics about their performance.
It is important to understand the following terms:
Span: Represents a logical unit of work, which has a unique name, a start time, and the duration of execution.
Trace: This is an execution path of services in OpenShift Service Mesh. In other words, a trace is …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Falero Otiniano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[우리에게 뭘 팔았던 거냐… 테크 기업의 두 얼굴]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101239</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101239"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T06:10:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[빅테크 기업들은 프리젠테이션을 할 때마다 지구의 이미지를 보여주고 거대한 자연을 보여주기도 한다. 자신들의 기술이 세상을 이롭게 하고, 인류의 지속성에 이바지하고 있음을 나타내기 위해서다. 단적으로 지난 9월 애플은 자사 제품 발표회 때 유명 배우인 ‘옥타비아 스펜서’를 대자연 역할을 맡게 하고 애플의 탄소중립에 대한 비전을 효과적으로 전달했다. 짧은 필름이었지만 전 세계적으로 큰 반향을 일으키며 애플의 친환경 이미지를...
The post 우리에게 뭘 팔았던 거냐… 테크 기업의 두 얼굴 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김정철</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 21, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955132/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955132/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T00:45:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 21, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/21, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593146</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593146/12-21-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T23:22:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈은 윤석열 아바타? 뒷말 끊이지 않는 이유: 슬로우레터 12월21일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101209</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101209"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T21:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김순덕의 태세 전환. 영국 이코노미스트가 국민의힘 과반을 점쳤다고? 쟁점과 현안. 한동훈은 김종인이 아니다. 짠돌이 예산 합의. 다르게 읽기. 한국 경제 성적이 OECD 2위라고? 나이롱 산재 환자? 김건희 특검법은 악법 맞나. 더 깊게 읽기. 내란 혐의 인정, 트럼프 내년 선거 못 나올까. 연동형과 병립형, 끝나지 않은 토론. 해법과 대안. 기본소득 말고 안심소득? 오세훈의 실험. 오늘의 TMI....
The post 한동훈은 윤석열 아바타? 뒷말 끊이지 않는 이유: 슬로우레터 12월21일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 errors found in C# projects in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1094/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1094/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, PVS-Studio developers have written a lot of articles on checking open-source C# projects. As always, we're sharing the top 10 bugs we found this year. Have fun reading!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QEMU 8.2.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955832/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955832/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T20:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 8.2.0 of
the QEMU emulator is out.  Changes include new emulations for virtio-sound
devices, universal flash storage devices, Xilinx Versal boards, and much
more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Looking back at 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954535/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954535/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:40:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yet another year has come to an end.  Much to our dismay, 2023 did not, in
fact, happen exactly as we predicted back in
January.  So it seems that, once again, we will have to go through the
process of looking at the predictions that we made and mocking each in
turn, before getting into what was missed altogether.  A lot happened in
2023, not all of which was predictable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating AI Safety & Compliance: A guide for CTOs]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/navigating-ai-safety-and-compliance-cto-guide.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/navigating-ai-safety-and-compliance-cto-guide.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Fergus Hurley – Co-Founder & GM, Checks, and Pedro Rodriguez – Head of Engineering, Checks







The rapid advances in generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) have brought about transformative opportunities across many industries. However, these advances have raised concerns about risks, such as privacy, misuse, bias, and unfairness. Responsible development and deployment is, therefore, a must.
AI applications are becoming more sophisticated, and developers are integrating them into critical systems. Therefore, the onus is on technology leaders, particularly CTOs and Heads of Engineering and AI – those responsible for leading the adoption of AI across their products and stacks – to ensure they use AI safely, ethically, and in compliance with relevant policies, regulations, an…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LSFMM+BPF 2024 call for proposals]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955827/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955827/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Linux Storage, Filesystem, Memory-Management, and BPF Summit will
be held May 13 to 15 in Salt Lake City, Utah, USA.  The call
for proposals has already gone out, with a deadline of March 1.
"LSF/MM/BPF is an invitation-only technical workshop to map out
improvements to the Linux storage, filesystem, BPF, and memory management
subsystems that will make their way into the mainline kernel within the
coming years."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955812/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955812/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T16:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.6.8,
6.1.69,
5.15.144,
5.10.205,
5.4.265,
4.19.303, and
4.14.334
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.

Note that 5.15.145
is already in the review process, with a due date of December 22.  It
consists almost exclusively of ksmbd patches in a flurry of backporting
that was seemingly inspired by the recent marking
of ksmbd as broken in 5.15.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955786/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955786/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T15:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (ansible and ansible-core), Gentoo (Minecraft Server and thunderbird), Mageia (fusiondirectory), Red Hat (gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, opensc, and openssl), Slackware (libssh and mozilla), SUSE (avahi, firefox, ghostscript, gstreamer-plugins-bad, mariadb, openssh, openssl-1_1-livepatches, python-aiohttp, python-cryptography, xorg-x11-server, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (libssh and openssh).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[월가 분석가들이 코스트코 주식에 흥분하는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593144</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593144/%ec%bd%94%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%ec%bd%94-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T12:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 2024년 소매업 전망, 2024년 소매업은 힘든 시기를 겪을 수 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593141</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593141/2024%eb%85%84-%ec%86%8c%eb%a7%a4%ec%97%85-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T08:45:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/20,  월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593128</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593128/12-20-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Migrate to Red Hat JBoss Web Server 6 using Ansible]]></title>
        <id>d6b3d482-7467-41d2-a842-ba0ab52fabfb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/20/migrate-red-hat-jboss-web-server-6-using-ansible"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll discuss how to use the redhat.jws Ansible collection to automate the upgrade of a Red Hat JBoss Web Server instance from 5.7 to the version 6.0. First, we'll use Ansible to install JBoss Web Server 5.7 on the target system and then we'll use another playbook to perform the migration, thus ensuring that the target JBoss Web Server instance has been upgraded successfully.
Prerequisites
To support this demonstration you will first need to have a working Ansible environment. This involves having Ansible installed on the local (control) machine and one or several target hosts. As we are using the certified Ansible collection provided by Red Hat, Ansible needs to be configured to use Red Hat Ansible automation hub to retrieve content. Refer to the official documentation on…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Romain Pelisse</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The new oracles of GCC]]></title>
        <id>7394ef0a-fef0-4600-828e-b24c00e93b38</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/20/new-oracles-gcc"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new infrastructure has been added to GCC optimizers over the past few years. This was nominally in support of Ranger, the new range generation engine that I have been working on. The primary goal is to modernize the code base and provide flexible usage options throughout the rest of the compiler.
One of the major changes was moving to an on-demand model for calculating ranges. Traditionally range information was created by the VRP (Value Range Propagation) pass and some basic global information was then made available outside this pass. The more accurate context sensitive ranges were only available within the pass. There were some attempts to integrate the old VRPs mechanisms into other passes, but these were awkward and ultimately unsatisfactory.
Ranger however can be enabled in any pas…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew MacLeod</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2016년 총선넷 낙선운동, 6년만에 재심 무죄]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101170</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101170"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T03:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[참여연대 사법감시센터 ‘광장에 나온 판결’] 무죄 확정된 유권자 낙선운동, 선거법 개혁의 첫걸음 지난 11월 22일 서울고등법원은 총선넷 낙선운동을 유죄로 처벌했던 지난 2018년 서울고등법원 판결(2017노3849판결)의 잘못을 인정하고 기본적으로 무죄로 바로잡는 재심결정을 내렸다. 이번 재심에 의해 파기된 항소심 판결의 원심판결은 2017년 12월 1일 서울중앙지방법원에서 내려졌다. 이렇게 시작된 지루한 법정공방이 드디어 대단원의 막을 내린 셈이다. 우여곡절이 있었지만 유권자...
The post 2016년 총선넷 낙선운동, 6년만에 재심 무죄 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Logging on Embedded Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/device-logging</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/device-logging"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I discuss some of the problems I’ve encountered in producing and analyzing device logs over the years, on single digit number of devices up to hundreds of thousands, and concepts I’ve applied to manage that complexity. My background is in Android development, so some of the examples may skew towards much more powerful hardware than simple microcontrollers.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recovering a bricked Wiznet W7500 using the bootloader]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2023-12-20:/w7500-brick-recovery.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/w7500-brick-recovery.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I "bricked" a Wiznet W7500 MCU during development. After flashing yet another build of the firmware
the J-Link disconnected suddenly and I was not able to connect to the chip again (even under reset).
What's funny is that the LEDs blinked as usual and I was able to ping my application so
the chip was far from being dead. I quickly found the suspected piece of code:
pin muxing. When changing PORTA muxing options I must have un-muxed the SWD pins. 🙁]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 연금, 정해진 미래가 만든 ‘방 안의 코끼리’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78092</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/19/npsp_pension/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_pension"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 11월 1일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 20세기 인류 평균수명의 증가는 자연에 대한 인간의 승리를 나타내는 상징입니다. 경제학자 맥스 로저에 따르면 20세기 동안 인간의 평균 수명은 1900년 32세에서 2000년 66.5세로 증가했습니다. 그리고 2020년 아프리카를 제외한 지역의 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사람들이 전두광을 보면서 윤석열을 떠올리는 이유: 슬로우레터 12월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101146</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101146"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:05:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 특검, 한동훈의 답변은. 물가에 내놓은 한동훈, 불안한 보수 언론. 윤석열의 승소는 한동훈의 작정한 패소. 김건희에서 송영길로 프레임 전환. 여론 보니 아니었나, 이낙연은 주춤. 더 깊게 읽기. “병립형 퇴행, 또 다른 윤석열 부른다.” 독립적인 인간? 도움을 요청해야 산다. 다르게 읽기. 총선 앞두고 ‘공룡 플랫폼’ 규제법. 오늘의 TMI. 노인 빈곤율 한국이 1위. “동성 커플에 축복”, 교황청...
The post 사람들이 전두광을 보면서 윤석열을 떠올리는 이유: 슬로우레터 12월20일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create smart chips for link previewing in Google Docs]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/create-smart-chips-for-link-previewing-in-google-docs.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/create-smart-chips-for-link-previewing-in-google-docs.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Chanel Greco, Developer Advocate







Earlier this year, we announced the general availability of third-party smart chips in Google Docs. This new feature lets you add, view, and engage with critical information from third party apps directly in Google Docs. Several partners, including Asana, Atlassian, Figma, Loom, Miro, Tableau, and Whimsical, have already created smart chips so users can start embedding content from their apps directly into Docs. Sourabh Choraria, a Google Developer Expert for Google Workspace and hobby developer, published a third-party smart chip solution called “Link Previews” to the Google Workspace Marketplace. This app adds information to Google Docs from multiple commonly used SaaS tools. 
In this blog post you will find out how you too can create you…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A hard quiz to crack for C++ programmers by Sergei Kushnirenko]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1093/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1093/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, fun seekers and brainstorming enthusiasts! It's the PVS-Studio team. Now you have an opportunity to pass a new awesome quiz on our website. It has challenging questions from the programming...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The Linux graphics stack in a nutshell, part 1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955376/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955376/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T17:19:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux graphics developers often speak of modern Linux graphics
when they refer to  a number of individual software components and how they
interact 
with each other.
Among other things, it's a mix of kernel-managed display resources, 
Wayland for compositing, accelerated 3D rendering, and decidedly not X11.
In a two-part series, we will take a fast-paced journey
through the graphics code to see how it converts application data
to pixel data and displays it on the screen. In this installment, we look
at application rendering, Mesa internals, and the
necessary kernel features.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global developers use Google tools to build solutions in recruiting, mentorship and more]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/global-developers-use-google-tools-to-build-solutions-in-recruiting-mentorship-and-more.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/global-developers-use-google-tools-to-build-solutions-in-recruiting-mentorship-and-more.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lyanne Alfaro, DevRel Program Manager, Google Developer Studio






Developer Journey is a monthly series highlighting diverse and global developers sharing relatable challenges, opportunities, and wins in their journey. Every month, we will spotlight developers around the world, the Google tools they leverage, and the kinds of products they are building. 
This month we speak with global developers across Google Developer Experts, and Women Techmakers, to learn more about their favorite Google tools, the applications they’ve built to serve diverse communities and the role of inclusive design in their process.
Miguel Ángel Durán Garcí






Barcelona, Spain
Google Developer Expert, Web Technologies
Content Creator & Software Engineer
Twitter
Twitch
What Google tools have you used…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qubes OS 4.2.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955691/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955691/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 4.2.0 of the Qubes OS distribution has been released; changes
include a switch to Xfce for the Fedora and Debian templates, a number of
rewritten graphical applications, PipeWire support, and more.  See the release
notes for details.  (Qubes OS was last covered here in 2021).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Revolutionizing memory barriers in AI and HPC]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481079</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/revolutionizing-memory-barriers-in-ai-and-hpc/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:26:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The insatiable demand for memory bandwidth and capacity has been dragging down the overall performance of AI and HPC applications, even with the significant advancement...
The post Revolutionizing memory barriers in AI and HPC appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jianping (JP) Jiang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AI can assist embedded system design]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481074</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-ai-can-assist-embedded-system-design/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:22:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you look at PCB design, it’s obvious that there is a huge opportunity for AI to make the process faster, easier, and more successful...
The post How AI can assist embedded system design appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Matthias Wagner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH 9.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955680/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955680/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:05:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH
9.6 has been released.  It includes some minor improvements and a fix
for the so-called Terrapin
attack.


	While cryptographically novel, the security impact of this attack
   is fortunately very limited as it only allows deletion of
   consecutive messages, and deleting most messages at this stage of
   the protocol prevents user authentication from proceeding and
   results in a stuck connection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 121.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955679/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955679/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T14:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
121.0 of the Firefox browser is out.  Along with the usual pile of
security fixes, this release add the ability to force links to be rendered
with underlines and use of Wayland by default if it is available: "This
brings support for touchpad & touchscreen gestures, swipe-to-nav,
per-monitor DPI settings, better graphics performance, and more."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955678/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955678/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T14:49:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (webkit2gtk), Fedora (rdiff-backup and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Mageia (cjose and ghostscript), Oracle (avahi), Red Hat (postgresql:10), and SUSE (avahi, freerdp, libsass, and ncurses).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 엔비디아는 Magnificent 7주 중에서 가장 저평가된 기술주]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593124</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593124/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ea%b3%a0%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T14:14:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2030년 엔비디아 시총은 애플 시총을 앞설까요?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593117</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593117/2030%eb%85%84-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%9c%ec%b4%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T13:42:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[질서에서 혼돈으로, 우열에서 우연으로: 별의별 아름다움에 관하여]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=95750</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/95750"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:56:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우민트] 뉴스페퍼민트 이효석 대표가 추천하는 좋은 책에 관한 이야기. 두 번째 책은 다윈의 ‘성선택’ 이론의 복권을 시도한 ‘아름다움의 진화'(리처드 프럼, 2017). 민노: [아름다움의 진화]는 자연선택과 성선택 중 후자에 관해 이야기하고 있습니다. 이효석: 네, 그런데 자연선택과 성선택을 구별하기 전에 먼저 이야기할 것이 있는데요. 사실 이 두 개념을 구별하는 방식에 이미 이 책의 핵심 주장과 또 이...
The post 질서에서 혼돈으로, 우열에서 우연으로: 별의별 아름다움에 관하여 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LG그룹 경영권 분쟁 뒷이야기: “아들로 태어나지 않았다는 사실에 죄책감을 느꼈어요.”]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101110</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101110"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:50:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[컨텍스트] 유언장도 없는데 아들이 상속재산 독식, “우리 가족은 이런 식이에요.” 뉴욕타임스가 LG그룹의 경영권 분쟁을 추적한 기사를 내보내 눈길을 끈다. 구광모(LG 회장)의 어머니와 두 동생의 인터뷰도 실렸다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 사건의 개요. 지금까지의 이야기. “우리 가족은 이런 식이에요.” 핵심 쟁점: 유언장은 없고 메모는 사라졌다. 알려지지 않은 이야기. LG그룹의 해명. 뉴욕타임스의 평가.
The post LG그룹 경영권 분쟁 뒷이야기: “아들로 태어나지 않았다는 사실에 죄책감을 느꼈어요.” appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI가 추천하는 유망 자율주행 주식]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593106</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593106/%ec%9c%a0%eb%a7%9d-%ec%9e%90%ec%9c%a8%ec%a3%bc%ed%96%89-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Contributions to the ComplianceAsCode project for OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>6a98a921-e4d5-4b5e-bb40-7d04b0985bd0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/19/contributions-complianceascode-project-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ComplianceAsCode project provides security guidance, baselines, and associated validation mechanisms utilizing the Security Content Automation Protocol (SCAP) to achieve security hardening for various products. ComplianceAsCode provides content for Red Hat OpenShift to comply with the requirements set by local government regulations and industry standards required for deploying the solution.
The ComplianceAsCode content follows the SCAP format to help translate the generic requirements set by the regulatory frameworks into implementation specifics and automate the remediations where possible. Refer to the SCAP Security Guide for more information on SCAP format.
ComplianceAsCode content guide provides the best practices and security relevant configuration guidelines to securely configur…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bharath B</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/19, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593095</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593095/12-19-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T04:00:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern On-Target  Embedded System Testing with CMake and CTest]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=39676</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2023/12/18/modern-on-target-embedded-system-testing-with-cmake-and-ctest/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post discusses the use of continuous integration and delivery (CI/CD) pipelines in embedded system testing. It presents a case study on an embedded project, where the author applies automated testing using CTest, Unity testing framework, and CMake, a software building tool, to ensure the project's robustness. The post also exhibits the usage of JRun tool for execution on the hardware and provides detailed instructions on adding and running tests either manually or through Visual Studio Code. It suggests that following this approach would facilitate a modern environment for hardware testing in embedded systems. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘검은 코끼리’의 비극, “바보야, 문제는 대통령이야”: 슬로우레터 12월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101061</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101061"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T22:01:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김기현은 억울하다. 송영길 구속. 민주당이 한동훈 비대위원장을 반기는 이유. 39개월 동안 11번 바꿨다. 강감찬을 임진왜란 때 쓰나. 한동훈 비대위가 맞닥뜨릴 첫 질문은 김건희. 이재명의 ‘안 한다’ 리더십에 부글부글. “민주화 다음 시대정신은 절제와 공존.” 다르게 읽기. 김건희 특검법, 동아일보의 제안. 반값 아파트가 로또가 됐다. 해법과 대안. 인천에서 태어나면 1억 원 받는다. 비빌 언덕이 필요했다. 고등학생 절반이...
The post ‘검은 코끼리’의 비극, “바보야, 문제는 대통령이야”: 슬로우레터 12월19일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year's Eve show: Top 10 errors in C and C++ projects in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1092/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1092/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's December, the first snow has already fallen, and it means New Year's Eve is around the corner. Ahead of the holidays, we'll show you the most interesting errors found in the code of the popular...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking down the C++ quiz by Sergei Kushnirenko]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1091/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1091/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PVS-Studio team along with Sergei Kushnirenko prepared a quiz based on his publications. Take the quiz, challenge your focus and coding skills while looking for errors in the C++ code. This...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay | Meet Steven from Indonesia. More stories from around the world]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/weareplay-meet-steven-from-indonesia-more-stories-from-around-the-world.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/weareplay-meet-steven-from-indonesia-more-stories-from-around-the-world.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Leticia Lago, Developer Marketing



As we bid farewell to 2023, we're excited to unveil our last #WeArePlay blog post of the year. From Lisbon to Dubai, let’s meet the creators behind the game-changing apps supporting communities, bringing innovation and joy to people.






We’re starting off in Indonesia, where Steven remembers his pocket money quickly running out while traveling around rural areas of Indonesia with his parents. Struck by how much more expensive food items were in the villages compared to Jakarta, he was inspired to create Super, providing more affordable goods outside the capital. The app allows shop owners to buy items stored locally and supply them to their communities at lower prices. It's helped boost the hyperlocal supply chain and raise living standards…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The intersection of mlx5, netdev, and lockdown]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955001/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955001/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:01:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NVIDIA Mellanox ConnectX HW family of adapters is a complex beast,
supporting networking, InfiniBand, RDMA, and more.  As a result, the mlx5
kernel driver that supports this hardware is also complex, as is the
interface that it provides to user space.  The mlx5 developers have, for a
while now, been proposing
the addition of a new control interface, in the form of a separate virtual
device exported by the kernel, that would make vast amounts of debugging
information available.  This driver has encountered some significant
opposition on its way toward the mainline, though, raising a number of
questions about appropriate interfaces and when subsystem maintainers have
veto power over submissions.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955566/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955566/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T14:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (freeimage, ghostscript, intel-microcode, spip, and xorg-server), Fedora (chromium, perl, perl-Devel-Cover, perl-PAR-Packer, polymake, PyDrive2, seamonkey, and vim), Gentoo (Leptonica), Mageia (audiofile, gimp, golang, and poppler), Oracle (buildah, containernetworking-plugins, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, kernel, kernel-container, libxml2, pixman, podman, postgresql, postgresql:15, runc, skopeo, tracker-miners, and webkit2gtk3), and SUSE (fish).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023년 미디어 이슈 결산 세계 편: 생성형 AI]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100956</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100956"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T11:46:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[캡:콜드케이스] 미디어를 통해 반영·증폭·구성되는 문제적 현상과 사고방식을 ‘캡콜드’ 김낙호 교수가 명쾌하게 분석합니다. 캡콜드에게 2023년을 돌아볼 수 있는 키워드를 뽑아달라고 요청했다. 그는 챗GPT로 상징되는 생성형 AI와 정권 유지를 위한 억압적인 담론 전략으로서 ‘가짜뉴스’를 각각 가장 중요한 세계구 이슈와 국내 이슈로 뽑았다. 그 두 개의 키워드를 중심으로 이야기했다. 이 글은 그 첫 번째 글이다. 참고로 캡콜드가 선정한...
The post 2023년 미디어 이슈 결산 세계 편: 생성형 AI appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[선수와 감독으로 모두 성공한, 축구계 이단아, 과르데올라 감독 리더쉽]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593089</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593089/%ea%b3%bc%eb%a5%b4%eb%8d%b0%ec%98%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ea%b0%90%eb%8f%85-%eb%a6%ac%eb%8d%94%ec%89%bd"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T09:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이재명이 유시민의 제안을 받을까.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=101004</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/101004"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T07:46:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[컨텍스트] 양당+지역주의 타파 고민 없는 정치공학적 계산, 최병천도 유시민도 모두 틀렸다. 민주당은 결국 병립형 비례제로 갈 것인가. 최병천(신성장경제연구소 소장)이 권역별 병립형을 밀고 있고 몇 차례 논쟁이 있었지만 여전히 결론을 내리지 못한 상태다. 김어준의 ‘뉴스공장’에서 최병천을 몇 차례 띄웠고 이대로 가면 국민의힘이 과반을 얻는다는 공포가 확산되면서 병립형으로 기우는 분위기다. 이탄희(민주당 의원)가 위성정당 금지법을 발의하면서 연동형 포기는...
The post 이재명이 유시민의 제안을 받을까. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top application development articles of 2023]]></title>
        <id>8f039fd4-41a4-49b3-b631-4e381a67dd29</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/18/top-application-development-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're wrapping up our Best of 2023 series by highlighting our most popular application development articles from the past year.
The business of delivering cloud-native applications gets more complex every day. It’s no surprise that solutions for improving developer experience are in high demand, especially for enterprise teams. Red Hat Developer Hub, based on the open source Backstage project, is one such solution that provides easy access to curated tools, resources, and Golden Path templates for quicker and easier software development. By reducing complexity and automating tedious tasks, developers are free to focus on what they do best: write code and ship new features.
The 10 most popular application development articles of 2023
Our most-read articles on application development focus o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java monitoring: Exploring Cryostat 2.4 features on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>41267961-eaea-41b9-a9e7-4fc50c72ac2f</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/18/java-monitoring-exploring-cryostat-24-features-openshift"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat's latest build of Cryostat 2.4, designed specifically for the Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform, brings a wealth of features and enhancements that cater to various monitoring needs for Java applications.
At its core, Cryostat 2.4 excels in comprehensive Java Flight Recorder (JFR) data management. Users can effortlessly start, stop, retrieve, archive, import, and export JFR data, all through an intuitive web console or an accessible HTTP API. This enhances the ease with which developers can handle JVM performance data. Moreover, Cryostat 2.4 provides flexibility in terms of data storage and analysis. Users can store and analyze JFR data directly on their Red Hat OpenShift or export it to external monitoring applications for a deeper dive into the data.
ARM (aarch64)
A significant…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaaf, Syed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.7-rc6]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955485/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955485/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T00:19:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.7-rc6 for testing.
" Please do give this a test in between the last-minute xmas shopping or
whatever else is going on ..."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Implement Image Processing Algorithms in FPGA Hardware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1616.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1616.php"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T23:54:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image processing plays a crucial role in various applications, from medical imaging to computer vision and multimedia systems. Field-Programmable Gate Arrays (FPGAs) offer a versatile and efficient platform for implementing image processing algorithms. The unique features of FPGA hardware, such as parallelism and reconfigurability, enable high-performance and real-time processing, making it an...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사람들 착각이 아니라 그들이 ‘진짜 현실’을 못 보는 것 아닐까요]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78366</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/17/npsp_vibecession/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_vibecession"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T23:15:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[뉴욕타임스 오피니언 란에는 최근의 거시경제를 설명해 주는 글이 자주 올라옵니다. 이런 칼럼들은 대개 “바이든 행정부의 경제 성적표가 생각만큼 나쁘지 않다”는 결론으로 글을 맺곤 합니다. 구구절절 드는 이유를 읽다 보면 논리적으로 이해가 가다가도 한편으론 주변 사람들 사는 모습은 여전히 팍팍해 보이던데 경제가 정말 잘 돌아가고 있는 게 맞나 의구심이 들기도 합니다. 칼럼니스트 트리시 맥밀란 커텀이 이 괴리를 자세히 분석한 칼럼을 썼습니다. 소위 경제학자들이 거시경제 지표에 파묻혀 오히려 쉽게 확인할 수 있는 ‘필수 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patches for the code of Peter Turchin’s Attrition Warfare Model]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8447</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/12/17/patches-for-the-code-of-peter-turchins-attrition-warfare-model/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T22:40:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The paper Empirically Testing Predictions of an Attrition on Warfare Model for the War in Ukraine, by Peter Turchin, recently showed up during one of my regular searches for software engineering data. A quick scan of the paper founded that it is very empirical, and that the analysis coding was done in R; I could […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“이러다 또 탄핵 당한다”, 한동훈 비대위 두고 갈등 폭발: 슬로우레터 12월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100978</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100978"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T22:17:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[탄핵 막으려 한동훈? “한동훈 되면 탄핵될 수도.” “이러다 또 탄핵 당한다.” 한동훈 정치력 시험대는 김건희. 류호정, 정의당 텔레그램에서 쫓겨났다. 적격이라던 정의찬, 없던 일로. 국민 89%가 의대 증원 찬성. 감액된 예산, 민주당이 단독 처리하나. 더 깊게 읽기. 지드래곤과 검사 처남의 전혀 다른 마약 수사. 다르게 읽기 화이트칼라 이그젬션. “민주당은 뭐했냐”고 묻는 조선일보. 오늘의 TMI. ‘오래 사는...
The post “이러다 또 탄핵 당한다”, 한동훈 비대위 두고 갈등 폭발: 슬로우레터 12월18일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Min: sched_ext: a BPF-extensible scheduler class (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955481/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955481/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T20:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changwoo Min provides
an introduction to the sched_ext scheduling class:


	Sched_ext was proposed to address the problems mentioned above. It
	allows users to write a custom scheduling policy using BPF without
	modifying the kernel code. You don't need to struggle to maintain
	the out-of-tree custom scheduler. In addition, BPF provides a safe
	kernel programming environment. In particular, the BPF verifier
	ensures that your custom scheduler has neither a memory bug nor an
	infinite loop. Also, if your custom scheduler misbehaves -- like
	failing to schedule a task for too long (say 30 seconds), the
	kernel portion of sched_ext kills your custom scheduler and falls
	back to the default kernel scheduler (CFS or EEVDF). Last but not
	least, you can update the BPF scheduler without reinstalling the
	kernel and rebooting a server.


(LWN looked at sched_ext in February 2023).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[So you want custom allocator support in your C library]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/12/17/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2023/12/17/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T17:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of mature C libraries conventionally get to choose how memory is
allocated — that is, when it cannot be avoided entirely. The C
standard never laid down a convention — perhaps for the better —
so each library re-invents an allocator interface. Not all are created
equal, and most repeat a few fundamental mistakes. Often the interface is
merely a token effort, to check off that it’s “supported” without actual
consideration to its use. This article describes the critical features of
a practical allocator interface, and demonstrates why they’re important.
Before diving into the details, here’s the checklist for library authors:
All allocation functions accept a user-defined context pointer.
The “free” function accepts the original allocation size.
The “realloc” function accepts both old …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[논문리뷰] Row hammer 논문 리뷰]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15845156</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15845156"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T14:52:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이 논문은 흔히 Row-hammer attack 으로 알려져 있는 공격에 대한 연구이다. 
Kim, Yoongu, et al. "Flipping bits in memory without accessing them: An experimental study of DRAM disturbance errors." ACM SIGARCH Computer Architecture News 42.3 (2014): 361-372.
이 방식은 Hardware 에 대한 공격이라고 할 수 있다. 거의 모든 종류의 DRAM이 공통적으로 가지고 있는 이슈를 이용한 공격이다. (논문의 저자진은 삼성 및 Intel에서 인턴쉽을 수행한적이 있는 카네기 멜론 출신의 연구자들인데, 이 현상을 발견한 후 논문으로 발표를 하게 되어 회사들 입장에서는 약간 곤란했었다고 한다.)

DRAM이란 트랜지스터와 커패시터로 구성된 메모리 셀을 통해 데이터를 저장한다. 그리고 DRAM에 Access하거나 Refresh하는 방식으로 데이터를 관리한다. 원칙적으로 하나의 메모리 주소에 대한 접근은 다른 주소에 저장된 데이터에 의도하지 않은 영향을 미쳐서는 안된다. 이에 1970년대부터 DRAM 제조 업체들은 셀 간 간격을 유지하고 테스트를 통해 오류 발생 가능성을 최소화하고 있었다. 그러나 DRAM 공정 기술이 미세화됨에 따라 DRAM 셀 간의 전기적 상호 작용을 방지하기가 점점 더 어려워지고 있다. 


2014년 본 연구진의 실험에 따르면 상용 DRAM의 동일한 주소에 읽기 작업을 반복하다보면 인근 주소의 데이터를 손상시킬 수 있다는 것이 확인되었다. 마치 특정 row에 있는 부분을 해머로 계속 때리면 그 옆의 row들이 영향을 받는다는 취지에서 이름을 붙인 것이다. 일종의 Fault Injection 이라고 볼 수 있다. 
의도적으로 DRAM에 부하를 가하는 악의적인 프로그램을 통해, DRAM의 동일한 행을 활성화하는 것은 인근 행의 데이터를 손상시킬 수 있다는 사실을 인텔 및 AMD 주요 DRAM모듈(129개 중 110개)에서 확인하였다. 


해머링을 수행하다보면 트랜지스터 행에서 주변 인접한 행으로 전하가 누출되고, 그로 인해 메모리상의 특정 비트 값이 1에서 0으로, 또는 0에서 1로 뒤집힌다(flipping). 이 사소한 비트 전환으로 인해 운영체제 수준에서 권한 상승이 발생할 수도 있다. 실제로 이를 악용하여 시스템에서의 권한 상승이나 네트워크 기반 공격도 가능하다고 알려져 있다.


후속 연구에 대해서는 추후 더 다룰 예정.


참고: (유머)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[자율주행 테마주 넥스트칩, 자율주행 성장 수혜를 받는 글로벌 영상신호처리 1위 기업]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593086</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593086/%ec%9e%90%ec%9c%a8%ec%a3%bc%ed%96%89-%ed%85%8c%eb%a7%88%ec%a3%bc-%eb%84%a5%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%ec%b9%a9"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T15:47:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/16, 월가의 투자의견 및  주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593073</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593073/12-16-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T12:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 당신이 먹는 것의 먹는 것까지 생각해 보자는 제안]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78071</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/15/npsp_seafoodchain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_seafoodchain"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T22:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 30일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난 4월, 저는 방글라데시 라나 플라자 의류공장 붕괴 사고 10주기를 맞아 쓴 글에서 윤리적인 소비에 관해 생각할 거리를 나눴습니다. 그 글에서 저는 의식주의 공급망을 하나씩 따져보면서 음식은 신선도를 유지하지 못하면 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Congratulations to the winners of Google’s Immersive Geospatial Challenge]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/googles-immersive-geospatial-challenge-winners.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/googles-immersive-geospatial-challenge-winners.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Bradford Lee – Product Marketing Manager, Augmented Reality, and Ahsan Ashraf – Product Marketing Manager, Google Maps Platform






In September, we launched Google's Immersive Geospatial Challenge on Devpost where we invited developers and creators from all over the world to create an AR experience with Geospatial Creator or a virtual 3D immersive experience with Photorealistic 3D Tiles.

"We were impressed by the innovation and creativity of the projects submitted. Over 2,700 participants across 100+ countries joined to build something they were truly passionate about and to push the boundaries of what is possible. Congratulations to all the winners!" 



– Shahram Izadi, VP of AR at Google


We judged all submissions on five key criteria:

Functionality - How are the APIs us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DeMaio: Insights from the openSUSE Logo Contest]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955366/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955366/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T16:23:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In response to the expressed unhappiness over the recent logo-selection
process in the openSUSE project (covered in this article), the project has announced
that there will be a new vote:


	During the community meeting this week where the results were
	discussed, participants expressed the view that members of the
	openSUSE Project have an opportunity to participate in the
	selection of our new logo, and that SUSE, which holds the trademark
	to the openSUSE logo, be involved with the process for selecting a
	branding decision with regard to the results. After all, this
	decision impacts the collective identity.

	To facilitate this, there is a plan to organize a vote between the
	current logo and the proposed new design, allowing our community to
	have a say in this important decision. Furthermore, members of the
	project are collaborating with SUSE on the implications of the
	branding initiatives and some have expressed the desire for SUSE’s
	input to ensure there is an aligned vision for the future of
	openSUSE.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Progress toward a GCC-based Rust compiler]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954787/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954787/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T15:04:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The gccrs project is an ambitious
effort started in 2014 to implement a Rust compiler within The GNU Compiler
Collection (GCC).  Even though the task is far from complete, progress has
been made since LWN's previous coverage,
according to reports from the project.  Meanwhile, another hybrid and more
mature approach to GCC Rust code generation is available in rustc_codegen_gcc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955336/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955336/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T14:13:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bluez and haproxy), Fedora (curl, dotnet6.0, dotnet7.0, tigervnc, and xorg-x11-server), Red Hat (avahi and gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free), Slackware (bluez), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, cont, cosign, curl, gstreamer-plugins-bad, haproxy, ImageMagick, kernel, kernel-firmware, libreoffice, tiff, traceroute, tracker-miners, webkit2gtk3, and xrdp), and Ubuntu (audiofile, budgie-extras, libreoffice, strongswan, vim, and yajl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이제 『이제 공간에 주의하십시오』에 주의하십시오]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3195</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2023/book/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T09:10:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["이 책은 우리가 살고 느끼고 경험하는 공간을 다각도로 해석한다. 점유한다는 의미에서 공간이나 두 공간을 잇는 공간, 혹은 공간 그 아래의 공간에 대해 풀어내는 방식이 사뭇 흥미를 불러일으킨다. 독자들에게 자신이 살아가고 인식하는 공간의 종류와 특성에 대해 생각해 보게 하며, 이를 바탕으로 우리의 몸, 주변의 건물과 동네, 그리고 도시와 세계에 이르는 여러 장소의 성격을 다채롭게 보여줌으로써 공간에 대한 이해의 폭을 깊고 넓게 만들고 있다."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/15, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593059</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593059/12-15-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T03:59:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[25 years of Postfix]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955248/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955248/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T23:11:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Wietse Venema posted a note to the postfix-users mailing list about the 25th anniversary of the Postfix mail server.  As can be seen, it had a pivotal role in bringing more awareness of open-source software to IBM.  Beyond that, of course, it is an excellent piece of software in its own right.


As a few on this list may recall, it is 25 years ago today that the
"IBM secure mailer" had its public beta release. This was accompanied
by a nice article in the New York Times business section.

There is some literature at https://www.postfix.org/press.html that
attests how this project accelerated open-source adoption by a very
large company.


That release was even noticed by a small publication in its first year of operation.

(Thanks to Kees van Vloten.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7년 동안 초등학생 100만 명 줄어든다: 슬로우레터 12월15일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100927</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100927"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T22:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아이 키우기 힘든 세상의 참담한 미래. 출마만 하면 당선인데… 세 번째 비대위원장은 원희룡? 나경원? 이재명도 퇴진 압박. 다르게 읽기. “권역별 병립형 비례제는 개악이다” “권역별 병립형이 정치 개혁이다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명 분신, 김용 유죄 선고가 말하는 것. 학교폭력 신고 10년 만에 최다. 챗GPT, 언론사에 뉴스 이용료 낸다. 긴축 21개월, 미국 금리 내리나. 잃어버린 30년, 이제...
The post 7년 동안 초등학생 100만 명 줄어든다: 슬로우레터 12월15일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.28: support for ARM, .NET 8, analysis of Unreal Engine projects without Unity Build, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1090/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1090/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.28 has been released. Now you can run the analyzer on the ARM architecture, analyze .NET 8 projects, and check Unreal Engine projects without Unity Build — and there is more to come! See...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Ext4 data corruption hits the stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954770/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954770/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:45:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's stable-update process is intended to produce kernels that are,
well, stable; when that promise is lived up to, users can update to newer
stable updates without fear.  By any account, a bug that corrupts data on
ext4 filesystems constitutes a failure to hold to that promise.  As is so
often the case, this problem is the result of a chain of failures in a
system that works well most of the time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/955130/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/955130/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium and rabbitmq-server), Fedora (chromium, kernel, perl-CryptX, and python-jupyter-server), Mageia (curl), Oracle (curl and postgresql), Red Hat (gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, linux-firmware, postgresql, postgresql:10, and postgresql:15), Slackware (xorg), SUSE (catatonit, containerd, runc, container-suseconnect, gimp, kernel, openvswitch, poppler, python-cryptography, python-Twisted, python3-cryptography, qemu, squid, tiff, webkit2gtk3, xorg-x11-server, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (xorg-server and xorg-server, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top automation articles for developers in 2023]]></title>
        <id>7232edba-77ff-4483-8ee2-297cfd899929</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/14/top-automation-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome back to Red Hat Developer’s Best of 2023 series, as we take a look back at the articles that captured developers’ attention over the past 12 months.
Automation and artificial intelligence (AI) were the talk of the town this year, with significant breakthroughs in open source and generative AI. 2023 also saw many advancements in Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform; new offerings like Ansible Lightspeed and Event-Driven Ansible increase the efficiency of teams writing automation code and let developers focus on more strategic tasks.
The 10 most popular Ansible and automation articles of 2023
Based on our most-read articles this year, developers were particularly interested in learning about Ansible Automation Platform and ways to utilize it. Our list of top articles features tutorial…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction to Kafka consumers]]></title>
        <id>d4a9e391-556e-4330-904b-e1f949b97e47</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/14/introduction-kafka-consumers"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes and Apache Kafka are becoming de-facto platforms for developing and deploying microservice architectures. 
Kafka is a distributed data streaming platform that enables applications to publish, subscribe to, store, and process streams of messages (or events) in real-time.
These messages are stored inside Kafka topics. A topic is a set of messages you aim to organize for consumption. Each topic is stored on disk, replicated across brokers to ensure fault tolerance, and messages within the topic are retained for a designated time. Figure 1 shows an overview of a Kafka cluster.


  Figure 1: Shows a Kafka broker with three topics, where different applications produce and consume messages from topics.
We can consider topics as a logical grouping for messages. A Kafka topic, however, i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Soto Bueno</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to improve Go FIPS test coverage with Packit]]></title>
        <id>09c1b271-dcca-4d3c-a4a1-0186f5d6d810</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/14/how-improve-go-fips-test-coverage-packit"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, Fedora contributors use Packit a lot to keep packages up to date. In general, using the service is extremely easy, but as we will see, integrating it with a complex multi-source project with an extensive cryptographic test suite like the Go FIPS project needed a little tweaking. But the effort will be worth it.
The Go FIPS CI before Packit
In the Go FIPS repository, we use GitHub Actions to test the pull requests before merging them. We run the whole test suite with each pull request's changes in several containers to ensure it works on Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 7, 8, and 9. The differences between these three versions of RHEL give us fantastic coverage, but there is a limitation. We can only build on AMD64 if we rely on GitHub Actions without external systems.
Accessing a …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alejandro Sáez Morollón</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 14, 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953980/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953980/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T00:45:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for December 14, 2023 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 예술은 정치로부터 자유로워야? 그렇게 단순하지만은 않은 문제]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78031</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/13/npsp_literaturewar/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_literaturewar"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T22:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 25일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 지난 18일 개막된 독일의 프랑크푸르트 도서전은 세계 최대의 도서전으로 불립니다. 이 도서전에는 제3세계 여성작가의 작품 중 독일어로 번역된 작품에 주어지는 리베라투르 상이 있습니다. 올해 리베라투르 상은 팔레스타인 출신인 아다니아 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희가 무섭나? 보수 언론의 공포와 분노: 슬로우레터 12월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100901</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100901"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:57:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김기현 사퇴 카드 먹힐까. “김건희 문제, 직언할 수 있어야 한다.” “김기현 탓 아니다”, 이준석의 조언. 윤석열은 격노? 김건희 특검법 거부하면 민주당에 꽃놀이패. “욕심대로라면 제1당이 돼야 한다.” 네덜란드 반도체 동맹, 실체가 있나. 더 깊게 읽기. 학생을 버린 대학. YS의 당이 ‘서울의봄’ 흥행에 왜 떠나. 가계 부채는 문재인 정부 탓? 오늘의 TMI. “제로섬 정치 떠난다.” 돈 봉투...
The post 김건희가 무섭나? 보수 언론의 공포와 분노: 슬로우레터 12월14일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Logo and trademark issues for openSUSE]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954760/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954760/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A contest for new logos
for the openSUSE project and for
four separate distributions of it, 
Tumbleweed, Leap, Slowroll, and  
Kalpa, has turned into a
bit of an uproar in that community.  A vote
has been held on the candidates and winners have been announced, but
some are questioning why there is a need to change the existing logo (the
"Geeko" 
chameleon) at all.  In addition, there are questions about whether the
new logo will be trademarked (as previous ones have been)—and how many
years that will take.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operation K. Looking for bugs in the IntelliJ IDEA code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1089/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1089/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we check the IntelliJ IDEA Community Edition project for errors and send the fixes to its developers. A large project, an open-source base, and a static analyzer that helps the...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954983/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954983/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T20:39:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.6.7,
6.1.68,
5.15.143,
5.10.204,
5.4.264,
4.19.302, and
4.14.333
stable kernel updates have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust for Linux — in space]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954974/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954974/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:28:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust for Linux (RFL) project may not have (yet) resulted in user-visible
changes to the Linux kernel, but it seems the wider world has taken notice.
Hongyu Li has announced
that the Rust for Linux code is now part of a satellite just launched
out of China.  The satellite is running a system called RROS, which follows the old
RTLinux pattern of running a realtime kernel alongside Linux.  The realtime
core is written in Rust, using the RFL groundwork.


	Despite its imperfections, we still want to share RROS with the
	community, showcasing our serious commitment to using RFL for
	substantial projects and contributing to the community's
	growth. Our development journey with RROS has been greatly enriched
	by the support and knowledge from the RFL community. We also have
	received invaluable assistance from enthusiastic forks here,
	especially when addressing issues related to safety abstraction


(Thanks to Dirk Behme).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenPGP for application developers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954964/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954964/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T16:37:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new book called OpenPGP for application
developers has been released under the Creative Commons BY-SA license.


	This document is not intended for end-users or implementers of
	OpenPGP libraries (or other software that directly handles internal
	OpenPGP data structures).

	Instead, this document is focused on the second group, application
	developers, who use OpenPGP functionality in their software
	projects. It describes the properties of the OpenPGP system and its
	uses. It presupposes solid knowledge of software development
	concepts and of general cryptographic concepts. Thus, this text
	describes OpenPGP at the “library-level,” teaching concepts that
	will help software developers get started as a user of any
	implementation (e.g., OpenPGP.js, Sequoia-PGP).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's time for developers and enterprises to build with Gemini Pro]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/build-with-gemini-pro.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/build-with-gemini-pro.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jeanine Banks – VP/GM, Developer X and Developer Relations, and Burak Gokturk – VP/GM, Cloud AI and Industry Solutions






Learn more about how to integrate Gemini Pro into your app or business at ai.google.dev
This article is also published on the Keyword blog. 


Last week, we announced Gemini, our largest and most capable AI model and the next step in our journey to make AI more helpful for everyone. It comes in three sizes: Ultra, Pro and Nano. We've already started rolling out Gemini in our products: Gemini Nano is in Android, starting with Pixel 8 Pro, and a specifically tuned version of Gemini Pro is in Bard.
Today, we’re making Gemini Pro available for developers and enterprises to build for your own use cases, and we’ll be further fine-tuning it in the weeks and months…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954921/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954921/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T14:49:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (debian-security-support and xorg-server), Fedora (java-17-openjdk, libcmis, and libreoffice), Mageia (fish), Red Hat (buildah, containernetworking-plugins, curl, fence-agents, kernel, kpatch-patch, libxml2, pixman, podman, runc, skopeo, and tracker-miners), SUSE (kernel, SUSE Manager 4.3.10 Release Notes, and SUSE Manager Client Tools), and Ubuntu (gnome-control-center, linux-gcp, linux-kvm, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-6.2, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.2, linux-nvidia-6.2, linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, netatalk, and pydantic).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[엔비디아 주가 전망, 엔비디아 주가는 2024년에도 계속 상승할 것인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593057</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593057/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-3"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 채권 수익률 하락은 주식 시장에 엄청난 호재가 될 수 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593055</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593055/%eb%b0%b0%eb%9f%b0%ec%8a%a4-%ec%b1%84%ea%b6%8c-%ec%88%98%ec%9d%b5%eb%a5%a0-%ed%95%98%eb%9d%bd%ec%9d%80-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5%ec%97%90-%ec%97%84%ec%b2%ad%eb%82%9c-%ed%98%b8%ec%9e%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:07:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[가트너, 2024년 기술 트렌드 10가지 : 전략 읽기]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=13110</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2023/12/13/gartner-hype-cycle-2024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T08:12:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[가트너에서 지난 10월 17일, 2024년 트렌드를 발표했습니다. 보통 이런 자료들은 정부 쪽으로 넘어가 그 해의 정책방향에 반영됩니다.또는 은행권이나 통신사 처럼 정책방향에 발을 맞춰주는 기업들이 기술구매를 시도하기도 합니다. 당연히 프로젝트 수요가 생깁니다.다만, AI 로 넘어가면서 상황이 어려워졌습니다만… 내용이 조금 어렵습니다.초보자분들을 위해 설명해 봅니다. 01. AI Trust, Rish and Security Management (AI TRiSM) AI를 쓰면 뭐가 좋을까요?글쎄요.... Continue Reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[학생을 버린 대학: 한신대 우즈벡 학생 강제 출국 사건]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100878</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100878"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:57:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아시아에서 가장 취약한 전통이 사림(士林)의 존재감이다. 그나마 조선이 나라답게 작동했던 시절이 훈구파와 사림파가 적절하게 견제하며 권력을 주고받았던 때가 마지막이었다. 물론 이러한 균형은 여러 차례의 잔혹한 사화(士禍)로 막을 내렸으며, 이후는 교조화된 노론과 외척 세력이 정치와 사회를 지배하면서 체제 몰락으로 이어졌다. 지식이라는 형이상학적 권력을 제도화한 게 대학(大學)이라는 기관인데, 당연히 중세 종교사회와 연관이 깊다. 성직자는 당대 최고 지식인이어야...
The post 학생을 버린 대학: 한신대 우즈벡 학생 강제 출국 사건 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정호재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[차트로 살펴본 빅테크의 미래 by CB Insights]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593040</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593040/%eb%b9%85%ed%85%8c%ed%81%ac%ec%9d%98-%eb%af%b8%eb%9e%98"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:21:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: SoftwareAndEngineering]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/SoftwareAndEngineering.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/SoftwareAndEngineering.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Throughout my career, people have compared software development to
  “traditional” engineering, usually in a way to scold software developers for not
  doing a proper job. As someone who got his degree in Electronic Engineering,
  this resonated with me early in my career. But this way of thinking is flawed
  because most people have the wrong impression of how engineering works in
  practice.
Glenn Vanderburg has spent a lot of time digging
  into these misconceptions, and I strongly urge anyone who wants to compare
  software development to engineering to watch his talk Real Software Engineering. It's also well worth
  listening to his interview on the podcast Oddly
  Influenced. Sadly I've not been able to persuade him to write this
  material down - it would make a great article.
Another good thinker on this relationship is Hillel Wayne. He interviewed a
  bunch of “crossovers” - people who had worked both in traditional engineering
  and in software. He wrote up what he learned in a series of essays, starting
  with Are We Really Engineers?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/13, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593026</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593026/12-13-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T02:30:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘기회의 평등’에 기반했던 아메리칸 드림에 빨간 불이 켜진 까닭은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78341</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/12/npsp_collegeamericandream/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_collegeamericandream"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T01:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“미국판 스카이 캐슬”로 불리던 바시티 블루 스캔들이 있었습니다. 미국의 부유한 기득권층이 자기 자녀에게 남들보다 앞서서 출발할 수 있는 특혜를 주려고 법까지 어겨가며 대학 입시에 부정을 저지른 일인데요, 칼럼니스트 제시카 그로즈가 왜 자식에게 물려줄 돈도 많은 부유층, 기득권층 부모들이 법을 어겨가면서까지 자녀를 명문대에 보내려 혈안이 돼 있는지 짚은 칼럼을 썼습니다. 흔히 미국을 누구든 열심히 일하면 성공할 수 있는 기회의 땅이라 부르고, 아메리칸 드림이란 말도 있지만, 계층 이동의 사다리 역할을 하는 교육에 공정함과 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LTE and IoT - How We Got Here]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/lte-and-iot</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/lte-and-iot"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I describe some of my findings from a recent investigation of how LTE technology was built for IoT systems. Complete with some history
and a few diagrams to illustrate cellular network architecture and LTE power-saving features like eDRX and PSM, this read will give a nice introduction to LTE in embedded systems.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“사소한 게 아니야”]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=84822</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/84822/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:37:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[잡스는 창과 문서, 화면 등의 상단에 위치한 제목 표시 줄에도 똑같은 관심을 쏟아 부었다. 그것들의 디자인에 대해 고뇌하면서 앳킨슨과 케어에게 수없이 반복해서 수정하게 만들었다. [중략] 앳킨슨은 회상한다. “그가 만족할 때까지 아마 스무 개가 넘는 제목 표시 줄 디자인을 만들었을 거예요.” 어느 시점에서 케어와 앳킨슨은 더 중요한 일이 있는데 잡스 때문에 제목 표시 줄에 사소한 수정을 […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The end of vger.kernel.org]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954783/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954783/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Konstantin Ryabitsev has announced
that the movement of kernel mailing lists away from the venerable
vger.kernel.org system is nearly complete:


	Over the past few months we've migrated all of the vger.kernel.org
	mailing lists, with the exception of the Big One (linux-kernel, aka
	LKML). This list alone is responsible for about 80% of all vger
	mailing list traffic, so we left it for the last.

	This Thursday, December 14, at 11AM Pacific (19:00 UTC), we will
	switch the MX record for vger to point to the new location
	(subspace.kernel.org), which will complete the mailing list
	migration from the legacy vger server to the new infrastructure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘습관성 각설이 외유’? 윤석열 순방 왜 더 많아 보일까: 슬로우레터 12월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100862</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100862"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:01:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“습관성 각설이 외유다.” 윤석열 순방, 왜 더 많아 보일까. 쟁점과 현안. 장제원을 밟고 어디로 가나. 김기현 손절한 조선일보. 민주당은 여전히 이재명 충성 경쟁. ‘사쿠라’와 ‘김민새’. 더 깊게 읽기. 위성 정당을 막을 방법이 없다. 오늘의 TMI. 6070이 30대보다 신차 더 뽑았다. 구글 글로벌 검색어 1위 레시피 비빔밥. 억만장자 비밀금고 아부다비로 몰린다. 해법과 대안. ‘단계적 퇴출’이 빠졌다....
The post ‘습관성 각설이 외유’? 윤석열 순방 왜 더 많아 보일까: 슬로우레터 12월13일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bazel 7 Release]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/bazel-7-release.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2023/12/bazel-7-release.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by the Google Bazel team






Bazel 7 is now released. Bazel is Google's open source build system for fast and correct builds. It has built-in support for building both client and server software, including client applications for both Android and iOS platforms. It also provides an extensible framework that you can use to develop your own build rules. Bazel builds almost all Google products, including Google Search, GMail, and Google Docs.



What’s new in Bazel 7?
Bazel 7 is the latest major release on the long-term support (LTS) track.  It includes:
Bzlmod: Bzlmod, Bazel's new modular external dependency management system, is now enabled by default (i.e. --enable_bzlmod defaults to true). If your project doesn't have a MODULE.bazel file, Bazel will create an empty one for you. Th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graber: LXD now re-licensed and under a CLA]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954777/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954777/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T21:48:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The story of Canonical's takeover of the LXD container manager, and the
subsequent creation of the Incus fork, has been
simmering for a while.  Now Incus developer Stéphane Graber reports
that Canonical has changed the license and contribution terms for LXD:


	Per the commit message performing the re-licensing, all further
	contributions will be under the AGPLv3 license and all
	contributions from Canonical employees have been re-licensed to
	AGPLv3.

	However, Canonical does not own the copyright on any contribution
	from non-employees, such as the many changes they have imported
	from Incus over the past few months. Those therefore remain under
	the Apache2 license that they were contributed under.

	As a result, Canonical cannot release LXD under the AGPLv3 license
	and likely never will be able to.  LXD is now under a weird mix of
	Apache2 and AGPLv3 with no clear metadata indicating what file or
	what part of each file is under one license or the other.


He also notes that this change will put an end to the flow of patches — in
either direction — between the two projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What IoT developers need to know about cybersecurity labels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481056</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/what-iot-developers-need-to-know-about-cybersecurity-labels/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T19:05:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the IoT and cybercrime have grown, IoT device security has become a more prominent concern. Regulators have been slow to adapt to these trends,...
The post What IoT developers need to know about cybersecurity labels appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Emily Newton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Project Bluefin: A customized Fedora Silverblue desktop image]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954059/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954059/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:56:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So-called "immutable" Linux distributions have been in development for
some time, but (unless you count Chrome OS) haven't gained much traction. Project Bluefin, is a heavily
customized set of Fedora
Silverblue images coming from the Universal Blue community; they are
designed to deliver a reliable Linux desktop that's as easy to use as a
Chromebook but more customizable. Bluefin's mission is to change up
the desktop experience and attract a new generation of open-source
contributors with a "cloud-native"
take on developing and delivering the operating system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: what are hierarchical state machines?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481053</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-what-are-hierarchical-state-machines/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T17:46:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this sixth lesson on state machines, I’d like to give you the first glimpse of modern hierarchical state machines (HSMs). In this sixth lesson...
The post Programming embedded systems: what are hierarchical state machines? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954706/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954706/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T15:32:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libreoffice and webkit2gtk), Fedora (java-1.8.0-openjdk and seamonkey), Oracle (apr, edk2, kernel, and squid:4), Red Hat (postgresql:12, tracker-miners, and webkit2gtk3), SUSE (curl, go1.20, go1.21, hplip, openvswitch, opera, squid, and xerces-c), and Ubuntu (binutils, ghostscript, libreoffice, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15,
 linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gke,
 linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-nvidia,
 linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4,
 linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm,
 linux-ibm-5.4, linux-kvm, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, postfixadmin, python3.11, and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[11월 미국 소비자물가지수(CPI) 요약과 평가]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593022</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593022/11%ec%9b%94-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%86%8c%eb%b9%84%ec%9e%90%eb%ac%bc%ea%b0%80%ec%a7%80%ec%88%98cpi"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[역대 대법관 156명 중 여성은 얼마나 될까]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100848</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100848"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T13:22:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[민언련 이달의 좋은 보도상 수상자 인터뷰] 기획보도 ‘이토록 XY한 대법원’을 쓴 경향신문 이혜리·김희진·김혜리 기자 “당신이 성범죄 사건의 피해자가 되었다고 가정해보자.” “만약 당신이 남성이라면 성별이 같은 남성 판사를 적어도 한 명은 법정에서 만날 수 있다.” “그러나 당신이 여성이라면 이야기가 달라진다.” “재판부 전원이 여성 판사일 가능성은 전국 모든 고등법원에서 0%다.” 경향신문, ‘이토록 XY한 대법원’ (연재) 중에서 성범죄...
The post 역대 대법관 156명 중 여성은 얼마나 될까 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YTN MBC KBS2, 왜 팔아먹지 못해서 안달인가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100840</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100840"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T08:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아무리 생각해도 쉽게 답이 나오지 않는다. 국민의힘이나 그 전신에 해당하는 정당이 집권했을 때는 대체로 공영방송을 매각해야 한다는 뜻을 밝히거나 시도했는데 그 이유가 쉽게 떠오르지 않는다. 박근혜 전 대통령이 후보 시절인 2012년에는 정수장학회가 갖고 있는 MBC 주식을 기업에 매각하려 했다. 한바탕 소란만 피우고 끝났지만, MBC를 개인 기업이 사유하도록 하는 이른바 ‘사영화’를 추진해야 한다는 이야기는 끊임없이 제기되었다....
The post YTN MBC KBS2, 왜 팔아먹지 못해서 안달인가 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘멋진 패배’ 무용론? 전두광 닮은 현실론… 정치인 ‘이태신’을 기대하며]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100822</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100822"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T07:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[1. 병립형 회귀 vs. 준연동형, 민주당 갈등이 실망스러운 네 가지 이유 (김형철)2. ‘멋진 패배’ 무용론? 전두광 닮은 현실론… 정치인 ‘이태신’을 기대하며 (유성진) 영화 ‘서울의봄’을 보았다. 1979년 겨울 벌어진 역사적 사실을 기초로 감독의 허구적 상상력이 더해진 영화는 반전과 반전을 거듭하며 두 시간이 넘는 러닝타임이 무색하게 그야말로 순식간에 지나갔다. 권력에 대한 욕망에 수단과 방법을 가리지 않는 ‘전두광’과...
The post ‘멋진 패배’ 무용론? 전두광 닮은 현실론… 정치인 ‘이태신’을 기대하며 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top Kubernetes articles for developers in 2023]]></title>
        <id>52463bed-3ca9-4f94-9404-4838136fa822</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/12/top-kubernetes-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As we bid farewell to 2023, we’re highlighting the most popular articles published on Red Hat Developer this year.  Kubernetes continues to be a vital area of innovation; new tools and solutions intended to simplify application development and operations are proliferating, as developers seek ways to cope with the growing complexity of managing infrastructure. It was also an exciting year in the world of Red Hat OpenShift, the hybrid cloud application platform powered by Kubernetes.
  [ Learn about what’s new with Red Hat OpenShift 4.14 ] 
The 10 most popular Kubernetes articles of 2023
Read on for our most-read articles on Kubernetes topics from the past year. We’ve got a guide to using Kubernetes on OpenShift, patterns for managing and deploying Helm charts, testing libraries for Kubernet…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use Skupper to expose services over TLS]]></title>
        <id>7b8d1814-6134-447d-b091-32fcc4c45ffb</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/12/how-use-skupper-expose-services-over-tls"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Securing inter-cloud connections through end-to-end with TLS is necessary, ensuring not only the confidentiality and integrity of data exchanged between cloud environments but also safeguarding against unauthorized access. While inter-router communication in Skupper is always fortified with mutual TLS, it's essential to note that, by default, communication between services and routers does not have this encryption layer. Deploying TLS in client-router and router-service is possible to fortify the entire communication ecosystem.
Skupper ensures mutual TLS (mTLS) for inter-router communications by default, and users have the option to enhance security by enabling TLS specifically between services and the Skupper routers, with the flexibility to either auto-generate certificates through Skupp…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Noe Luaces</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[KBS는 평정? 고 김용균 무죄 판결엔 무관심, 서해 공무원 피살 감사 발표엔 쌍심지]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100810</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100810"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T05:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[민언련 언론 모니터] 2007년 17대 대선에서 진성호(당시 한나라당 간사)는 “네이버 평정” 발언을 했습니다. 박민 사장 취임 이후 KBS는 평정된 걸까요? 고 김용균 원청 무죄 판결과 서해 공무원 피살 감사 발표에 관한 방송사 리포트를 민언련이 모니터링했습니다. 2018년 12월 태안화력발전소에서 일하다 숨진 하청노동자 김용균 씨의 사망 책임을 원청에 물을 수 없다며 대법원이 12월 7일 한국서부발전 전 사장에게...
The post KBS는 평정? 고 김용균 무죄 판결엔 무관심, 서해 공무원 피살 감사 발표엔 쌍심지 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/12, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593010</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593010/12-12-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T23:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 뛰어난 업적을 남기고도 공로를 인정받지 못한 여성의 역사]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78026</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/11/npsp_goldin/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_goldin"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T22:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 23일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 뛰어난 재능을 보였지만 꽃 피울 기회를 얻지 못했거나, 업적을 남기고도 제대로 된 인정과 평가를 받지 못한 여성들의 명단은 성차별과 남성 중심주의의 역사만큼이나 깁니다. 자신도 뛰어난 조각가였지만, ‘로댕의 연인’으로만 알려졌던 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[나라가 망해간다는 지표와 신호, 절박하긴 한 건가: 슬로우레터 12월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100785</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100785"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[네덜란드에 간 윤석열 최대 고민은 쌍특검. ‘윤핵관’ 장제원 불출마. “윤석열과 화해? 망상이다.” 낙준연대 빅 텐트, 가능할까. 다르게 읽기. 직방 금지법 만드나. 총선 출발선이 다르다. 행복하다는 비율, 세계 꼴찌 수준인 이유. 더 깊게 읽기. 재벌 내부거래 41조 원 늘었다. 김건희 김영란법 위반, 검찰이 계속 뭉갤 수 있을까. “국감 전에 팩트체크 페이지 내려야 한다 했다.” 오늘의 TMI....
The post 나라가 망해간다는 지표와 신호, 절박하긴 한 건가: 슬로우레터 12월12일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to lure programmers to your conference booth?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1088/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1088/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will share some thoughts on what a booth staffer actually does, what types of activities visitors prefer, and how to keep the booth busy.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bottomley: Solving the Looming Developer Liability Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954528/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954528/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:55:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[James Bottomley writes
that open-source developers are increasingly likely to be held liable for
flaws in their code and suggests a solution:


	Indemnification means one party, in particular circumstances,
	agreeing to be on the hook for the legal responsibilities of
	another party. This is actually a well known way not of avoiding
	liability but transferring it to where it belongs. As such, it’s
	easily sellable in the court of public opinion: we’re not looking
	to avoid liability, merely trying to make sure it lands on those
	who are making all the money from the code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bliki: TestDrivenDevelopment]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/bliki/TestDrivenDevelopment.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/bliki/TestDrivenDevelopment.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T19:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Test-Driven Development (TDD) is a technique for building
	software that guides software development by writing tests. It was
	developed by Kent
	Beck in the late 1990's as part of
	Extreme Programming. In essence we follow three simple
	steps repeatedly:
Write a test for the next bit of functionality you want to add.
Write the functional code until the test passes.
Refactor both new and old code to make it well structured.


Although these three steps, often summarized as Red - Green -
  Refactor, are the heart of the process, there's also a vital initial
  step where we write out a list of test cases first. We then pick one of these
  tests, apply red-green-refactor to it, and once we're done pick the next.
  Sequencing the tests properly is a skill, we want to pick tests that drive us
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Some recent and notable changes to Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954033/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954033/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:35:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust project makes incremental releases every six
weeks, a fact that makes it easy to overlook some of the
interesting changes coming to the language, such as new
ABIs, better debugger support, asynchronous traits, and
support for C strings.
The end of the year provides an opportunity to look back
over the past several months of updates, and to look
forward to what to expect in 2024.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The era of digital therapeutics is just beginning]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481045</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-era-of-digital-therapeutics-is-just-beginning/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T17:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Electronics devices that monitor various physical phenomena – activity, pulse rates – have been available for two decades now, but more and more manufacturers are now developing digital therapeutic products. 
The post The era of digital therapeutics is just beginning appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Santo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.7-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954469/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954469/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T14:51:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.7-rc5 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	Nothing looks particularly scary, which is good, because if it had
	been, I wouldn't have had the capacity to deal with it last week.

	Let's hope it stays that way even as I am getting better. Because the
	holidays are almost upon us, and I'm woefully underprepared.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954454/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954454/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T14:13:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.6.6 and 6.1.67 stable kernels.  Both contain a single
reversion of the "wifi: cfg80211: fix CQM for non-range use" patch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954449/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954449/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T14:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Fedora (bluez, chromium, and curl), Red Hat (apr), Slackware (libxml2), and Ubuntu (squid3 and tar).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How embedded development shift is influencing future compute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481037</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-embedded-development-shift-is-influencing-future-compute/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T13:52:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers are now leveraging secure, performance-enhancing technologies to enable small, low-power embedded systems for previously unimaginable voice, vision and vibration applications that are changing the world.
The post How embedded development shift is influencing future compute appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Paul Williamson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 연말 테슬라 판매전략은 가격인하에서 인센티브 강화로 변경]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593004</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593004/%ec%97%b0%eb%a7%90-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ed%8c%90%eb%a7%a4%ec%a0%84%eb%9e%b5%ec%9d%80-%ec%9d%b8%ec%84%bc%ed%8b%b0%eb%b8%8c-%ea%b0%95%ed%99%94"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T12:17:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Our top Linux articles for developers in 2023]]></title>
        <id>e05def17-6b6d-4bf6-9e22-4118960fd108</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/11/top-linux-articles-2023"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We're kicking off our annual year-end roundup with a look back at the Linux content that engaged our readers the most in 2023. Linux remains a dominant player in the cloud thanks to its stability and flexibility, and Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) continues to evolve for the containerized future, with the General Availability release of RHEL 9.3 last month.
Our 10 most popular Linux articles of 2023
Here are 10 of our most-read articles on Linux from 2023, which cover a mix of topics including containers, new milestones for RHEL, and various ways to simplify Linux systems management with the latest compilers and tools.
New improvements in Red Hat Enterprise Linux
How the new RHEL 9.2 improves the developer experience by Nikhil Mungale and Alex Krikos: This article highlights new features …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Colleen Lobner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over-provisioning nodes on OpenShift Service on AWS]]></title>
        <id>0173c929-42f8-46e1-bf11-a3324971e0c5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2023/12/11/over-provisioning-nodes-openshift-service-aws"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There might be occasions where over-provisioning your cluster will provide great benefit. If there are sudden bursts of pods being created in a short amount of time, there can be situations where a new node is spinning up but is not ready. This can cause issues as pods will stuck in a pending phase for about ten minutes whilst waiting for the new node. A solution to this is to over-provision your cluster. This enables a spare node at all times, or pre-emptily create a new node when the workflow starts to pick up.
Use cases
With this solution, pods are created that are considered low priority. When the more important workloads are created, the low priority pods get removed from the nodes. This leaves the low priority pods in a pending state. This forces Red Hat OpenShift to spawn a new node…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Maz Arslan, Anton Giertli</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡과 파리바게뜨, 소비자가 무섭지 않은 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100701</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100701"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T06:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 고 김용균 원청기업 및 대표 무죄 판결에 관하여… 국제노동기구 고용정책국장 이상헌 박사와 나누는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기. 5년 전. 김용균, 24살. 2018년 12월 10일 태안화력발전소 비정규직으로 일하면서 한밤중에 혼자 점검에 나섰다. 그게 마지막이었다. 석탄 운반용 컨베이어 벨트가 김용균을 삼켰다. 청년의 죽음을 우리는 슬퍼했다. 겨우겨우 중대재해처벌법을 만들었다. 지난 12월 7일, 김용균...
The post 쿠팡과 파리바게뜨, 소비자가 무섭지 않은 이유 appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[인간은 합리적이지만 또 비합리적인데요…]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78319</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/11/npsp_nudge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_nudge"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T04:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[행동경제학을 바탕으로 한 넛지(nudges)는 지난 10년 사이 많은 주목을 받은 개념입니다. 다양한 부문에서 넛지가 도입되고 접목됐죠. 그러나 넛지의 효과를 둘러싼 논란도 처음부터 꾸준히 제기됐습니다. 행동경제학을 창시하는 데 중요한 역할을 했다고 볼 수 있는 대니얼 카네만도 비판에서 자유롭지 못하죠. 뉴욕대학교 디지털이론 연구소장 레이프 웨더비가 넛지의 효과와 한계에 관해 글을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 대세가 된 ‘넛지’, 그러나 과학적 근거는 부족하다 해설: 인간은 합리적이지만 또 비합리적인데요…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주목해야할 구글 마피아 스타트업 10개 by CB Insight]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592992</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592992/%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80-%eb%a7%88%ed%94%bc%ec%95%84-%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%80%ed%8a%b8%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T02:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Six Handy Operations for String Processing in C++20/23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2023/six-handy-ops-for-string-processing/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2023/six-handy-ops-for-string-processing/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll explore six practical string processing operations introduced in C++20 and C++23. These features represent an evolution in this crucial area, covering a spectrum of operations from searching and appending to creation and stream handling.
Let’s start with a simple yet long-awaited feature…
contains(), C++23 
  




     
    


Finally, after decades of standardization, we have a super easy way to check if there’s one string inside the other. No need to use .find(str) != npos!
Before C++23:
#include <string>
#include <iostream>

int main() {
    const std::string url = "https://isocpp.org";

    if (url.find("https") != std::string::npos &&
        url.find(".org") != std::string::npos &&
        url.find("isocpp") != std::string::npos)
        std::cout << "You're us…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[원전으로 탈탄소? 워싱턴포스트가 윤석열을 ‘팩폭’했다: 슬로우레터 12월11일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100736</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100736"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T22:03:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[살생부 돌면 김건희 특검법 반란표? “선거는 안중에도 없습니까.” 지지율 32%인데 또 외국 방문. “류호정 나가달라”, “못 나간다.” 이낙연, “이준석은 보기 드문 인재.” 더 깊게 읽기. 이준석 신당이 성공하기 어렵다고 보는 이유. 부울경·호남 이탈 80%가 청년이었다. 다르게 읽기. 문과 침공 이대로 좋은가. 유럽은 ‘마이너리티 리포트 법’ 만들었다. 해법과 대안. 워싱턴포스트의 윤석열 ‘팩폭’. 연 날려서 전기 만든다....
The post 원전으로 탈탄소? 워싱턴포스트가 윤석열을 ‘팩폭’했다: 슬로우레터 12월11일. appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.11.7 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3117-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3117-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T16:10:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is the sixth maintenance release of Python 3.11
Python 3.11.7 is the newest major release of the Python programming language, and it contains many new features and optimizations. Get it here:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3117/
Major new features of the 3.11 series, compared to 3.10

Among the new major new features and changes so far:


PEP 657 – Include Fine-Grained Error Locations in Tracebacks
PEP 654 – Exception Groups and except*
PEP 673 – Self Type
PEP 646 – Variadic Generics
PEP 680 – tomllib: Support for Parsing TOML in the Standard Library
PEP 675 – Arbitrary Literal String Type
PEP 655 – Marking individual TypedDict items as required or potentially-missing
bpo-46752 – Introduce task groups to asyncio
PEP 681 – Data Class Transforms
bpo-433030– Atomic group…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas books for 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8438</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2023/12/10/christmas-books-for-2023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T13:40:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This year’s Christmas book list, based on what I read this year, and for the first time including a blog series that I’m sure will eventually appear in book form. “To Explain the World: The discovery of modern science” by Steven Weinberg, 2015. Unless you know that Steven Weinberg won a physics Nobel prize, this […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA, 주식 시장 괴물 랠리가 과매수 수준에 가까워지면서 주식 시장의 ‘매수’신호가 죽었다고 주장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592990</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592990/bofa-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5-%ea%b4%b4%eb%ac%bc-%eb%9e%a0%eb%a6%ac%ea%b0%80-%ea%b3%bc%eb%a7%a4%ec%88%98-%ec%88%98%ec%a4%80%ec%97%90-%ea%b0%80%ea%b9%8c%ec%9b%8c%ec%a7%80%eb%a9%b4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-10T11:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ext4 data corruption in stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954285/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954285/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T22:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is a problem in multiple stable kernel releases that is causing data corruption in ext4 filesystems.  It is caused by a problematic commit that is in multiple stable kernels:

The commit got merged in 6.5-rc1 so all stable kernels that have
91562895f803 ("ext4: properly sync file size update after O_SYNC direct
IO") before 6.5 are corrupting data - I've noticed at least 6.1 is still
carrying the problematic commit.


More information can be found in a Debian bug report. It has also delayed the release of Debian 12.3 images. "Please do not upgrade any systems at this time, we urge caution for users
with UnattendeUpgrades configured."

(Thanks to Alex Ridevski for giving us a heads up on this.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sign in with GitHub in Go]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/sign-in-with-github-in-go/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/sign-in-with-github-in-go/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T22:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It's common to see web applications that let you log in through third-party
services. &quot;Sign in with Google&quot; is particularly popular; on developer-oriented
websites, &quot;Sign in with GitHub&quot; also pops up quite a bit. In this post, I want
to briefly explore OAuth - the technology that enables these delegated logins …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[30 years of DOOM: new code, new bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1087/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1087/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today marks the 30th anniversary of the first game in the DOOM series! We couldn't miss the event. To honor the occasion, we decided to see what the code of this legendary game looks like after all...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/9, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592976</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592976/12-9-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T17:46:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 고 이율 시대는 계속될 것이다. 그것이 경제에 미치는 영향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592965</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592965/%ea%b3%a0-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a8-%ec%8b%9c%eb%8c%80-%ec%98%81%ed%96%a5"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T10:28:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I have been copied on Aliexpress!]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2023-12-09:/i-have-been-copied-on-aliexpress.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/i-have-been-copied-on-aliexpress.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery. A while ago I published a design of a basic coax switch for HF antennas. To my surprise, a fellow ham messaged me that I am "famous" on Aliexpress. 🙂]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go Changes]]></title>
        <id>http://research.swtch.com/gochanges</id>
        <link href="http://research.swtch.com/gochanges"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The way Go changes, and how to improve it with telemetry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>research!rsc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Modern C for Fedora (and the world)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954018/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954018/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T16:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It can be instructive to pull down the dog-eared copy of the first edition
of The C Programming Language that many of us still have on our
bookshelves; the language has changed considerably since that book was
published.  Many "features" of early C have been left behind, usually for
good reasons, but there is still a lot of code in the wild that is still
using those features.  A concerted effort is being made in both the Fedora
and GCC communities to fix that old code and enable some new errors in the
GCC 14 release (which is in
stage 3 of its development cycle and likely to be released by
mid-2024), but a fair amount of work remains to be done.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A bunch of new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954107/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954107/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:42:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.6.5, 6.1.66, 5.15.142, 5.10.203, 5.4.263, 4.19.301, and 4.14.332 stable kernels have been released.
As usual, they contain important fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statistical Profile Extension: extracting value from SPE for SoC Telemetry]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:46715707-f121-4a6a-9bc0-ddb24d9f4e75</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/statistical-profile-extension"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We refer to the SPE performance methodology whitepaper published by Arm for details on the content of this blog.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brian Jeff</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[베런스, 미국 전기차 거품이 꺼지고 있다. 이는 수치로 증명되고 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592961</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592961/%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ea%b1%b0%ed%92%88-%eb%b6%95%ea%b4%b4"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T15:13:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/954092/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/954092/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T14:53:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium), Mageia (firefox, thunderbird, and vim), SUSE (kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-tools- container, virt-operator-container), and Ubuntu (freerdp2, glibc, and tinyxml).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 1: Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) introduction]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:65dfa3dd-b3dd-42ee-930d-1301a6ee028b</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/p1-arm-scalable-matrix-extension-introduction"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog series provides an introduction to the Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) including SVE and SVE2.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zenon Xiu (修志龙）</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI 답변 – 구글 제미나이에도 마소 빙챗 사용 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592959</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592959/%eb%b9%99%ec%b1%97-%ec%82%ac%ec%9a%a9-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T04:05:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12/8, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=592943</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/592943/12-8-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T03:22:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.1 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3121-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2023/12/python-3121-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T00:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.1 is now available.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3121/
 

This is the first maintenance release of Python 3.12
Python 3.12 is the newest major release of the Python programming language, and it contains many new features and optimizations. 3.12.1 is the latest maintenance release, containing more than 400 bugfixes, build improvements and documentation changes since 3.12.0.

 
Major new features of the 3.12 series, compared to 3.11
 
New features
More flexible f-string parsing , allowing many things previously disallowed (PEP 701).
Support for the buffer protocol  in Python code (PEP 688).
A new debugging/profiling API  (PEP 669).
Support for isolated subinterpreters  with separate Global Interpreter Locks (PEP 684).
Even more improved error messages. More exc…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 가자지구는 ‘창살 없는 무덤’이 돼 버릴 것인가]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=77999</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2023/12/07/npsp_israelhamas/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_israelhamas"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T22:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 10월 20일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 이스라엘과 하마스 사이에 벌어진 전쟁이 시작된 지 12일째입니다. 해묵은 원한과 증오의 역사가 또다시 되풀이되고 있습니다. 이스라엘은 주변 국가의 우려와 만류를 뿌리치고, 가자지구에 지상군을 투입할 준비를 마쳤습니다. 지난 7일 기습 공격에 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“민주당 200석도 가능하다”, 설레발일까, 자신감일까: 슬로우레터 12월8일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100673</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100673"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:48:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“4년 전과 비슷하다. 이대로면 참패.” “‘수포당’으론 희망이 없다.” “민주당 200석도 가능하다.” “김용균 사망, 원청 기업은 책임 없다.” “여기서 져도 다른 데서 이긴다.” 쟁점과 현안. “공무원 ‘자진 월북’ 사건은 조작됐다.” “나치 정당이냐”, 민주당 당헌 개헌 논란. “정치가 얼마나 험난한지 배웠다.” 더 깊게 읽기. ‘로또 영장’, 문제는 발급 기준이 없다는 것. 오늘의 TMI. 김건희 7시간 통화 공개,...
The post “민주당 200석도 가능하다”, 설레발일까, 자신감일까: 슬로우레터 12월8일.  appeared first on .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Few words about Java code hygiene]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1086/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1086/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While reviewing code or working on a new project, we can get annoyed by many things: style, approaches, quality. However, the most frustrating is the trite lack of code hygiene. Since the issue is...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Controlling shadow-stack allocation in clone3()]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953794/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953794/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T16:28:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User-space shadow stacks are a relatively new feature in Linux; support was
only added for 6.6, and is limited to the x86
architecture.  As support for other architectures (including arm64 and RISC-V) approaches readiness,
though, more thought is going into the API for this feature.  As a recent
discussion on the integration of shadow stacks with the clone3() system call shows, there are
still some details to be worked out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Just about every Windows and Linux device vulnerable to new LogoFAIL firmware attack
(ars technica)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953985/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953985/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T15:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
ars technica article describes how secure-boot firmware on a huge range
of systems can be subverted with a malicious image file:


	As its name suggests, LogoFAIL involves logos, specifically those
	of the hardware seller that are displayed on the device screen
	early in the boot process, while the UEFI is still running. Image
	parsers in UEFIs from all three major IBVs [independent BIOS
	vendors] are riddled with roughly a dozen critical vulnerabilities
	that have gone unnoticed until now. By replacing the legitimate
	logo images with identical-looking ones that have been specially
	crafted to exploit these bugs, LogoFAIL makes it possible to
	execute malicious code at the most sensitive stage of the boot
	process.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/953977/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/953977/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:18:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (tzdata), Fedora (gmailctl), Oracle (kernel), Red Hat (linux-firmware, postgresql:12, postgresql:13, and squid:4), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, cont, frr, libtorrent-rasterbar, qbittorrent, openssl-3, openvswitch, openvswitch3, and suse-build-key), and Ubuntu (bluez, curl, linux, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-laptop, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-oem-6.5, linux-oracle, linux-raspi, linux-starfive, linux-gcp, open-vm-tools, postgresql-12, postgresql-14, postgresql-15, and python-cryptography).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>