<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-02-13T20:14:49.530Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel becomes its own CNA]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961961/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961961/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T19:13:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced
that the kernel project has been accepted as a CVE numbering authority
(CNA).  The way that CVE numbers will be handled by the kernel is described
in this
documentation patch:


	As part of the normal stable release process, kernel changes that
	are potentially security issues are identified by the developers
	responsible for CVE number assignments and have CVE numbers
	automatically assigned to them.  These assignments are published on
	the linux-cve mailing list as announcements on a frequent basis.

	Note, due to the layer at which the Linux kernel is in a system,
	almost any bug might be exploitable to compromise the security of
	the kernel, but the possibility of exploitation is often not
	evident when the bug is fixed.  Because of this, the CVE assignment
	team are overly cautious and assign CVE numbers to any bugfix that
	they identify.  This explains the seemingly large number of CVEs
	that are issued by the Linux kernel team.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LWN.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federated Credential Management (FedCM) Migration for Google Identity Services]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/federated-credential-management-migration-for-google-identity-services.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/federated-credential-management-migration-for-google-identity-services.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Gina Biernacki, Product Manager







Chrome is phasing out support for third-party cookies this year, subject to addressing any remaining concerns of the CMA. A relatively new web API, Federated Credential Management (FedCM), will enable sign-in for the Google Identity Services (GIS) library after the phase out of third-party cookies. Starting in April, GIS developers will be automatically migrated to the FedCM API. For most developers, this migration will occur seamlessly through backwards-compatible updates to the GIS library. However, some websites with custom integrations may require minor changes. We encourage all developers to experiment with FedCM, as previously announced through the beta program, to ensure flows will not be interrupted. Developers have the ability to te…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Engineering Practices for LLM Application Development]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/engineering-practices-llm.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/engineering-practices-llm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLM engineering involves much more than just prompt design or prompt
       engineering. Here David Tan and Jessie
       Wang reflect on how regular engineering practices such as
       testing and refactoring helped them deliver a prototype LLM
       application rapidly and reliably.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A look at dynamic linking]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961117/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961117/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T14:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The dynamic linker is a critical component of modern Linux systems, being
responsible for setting up the address space of most processes. While statically
linked binaries have become more popular over time as the tradeoffs that
originally led to dynamic linking become less relevant, dynamic linking is still
the default. This article looks at what steps the dynamic linker takes to
prepare a program for execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LWN.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961937/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961937/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T14:47:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (clamav and virtiofsd), Oracle (gimp), Red Hat (gnutls and nss), SUSE (kubevirt, virt-api-container, virt-controller-container, virt-exportproxy-container, virt-exportserver-container, virt-handler-container, virt-launcher-container, virt-libguestfs-t and squid), and Ubuntu (openssl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>LWN.net</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[번역] 프로그래머를 위한 카테고리 이론 - 3. 다양한 카테고리들]]></title>
        <id>20240213-category-theory-for-programmers-3-categories-great-and-small</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/02/13/category-theory-for-programmers-3-categories-great-and-small/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T09:09:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리는 다양한 예시들을 연구해보면서 카테고리에 대한 진정한 이해에 한발짝 더 다가갈 수 있다. 카테고리는 매우 다양한 형태와 크기를 가지고 있기 때문에 종종 전혀 예상하지 못 했던 곳에서 나타나기도 한다. 일단 가장 간단한 것부터 한번 시작해보도록 하자.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connect a Quarkus app to an external SQL Server database]]></title>
        <id>01b77d2d-6db2-47fe-bd18-17fe3b79b62a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/13/connect-quarkus-app-external-sql-server-database"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Quarkus is a full-stack, Java-based framework for building, deploying, and running applications, including building and deploying applications in containers without manually creating YAML files. It offers a zero-configuration database container using its dev services feature, enabling rapid development and testing. However, having an external database for your application is vital for regulatory compliance. It brings benefits such as isolation, a simplified development workflow, and independence from the development environment. 
This article refers to a fictitious company called Pedal. Pedal is a commerce application platform with a microservices architecture for listing and selling bicycles. 
In this tutorial, you’ll build the Pedal bike service, using Quarkus to retrieve all listed bike…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Mungale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[백트래킹과 n-Queens 문제]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16247669</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16247669"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T06:36:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[n-Queens 문제
N퀸 문제는 1848년 막스 베첼이 처음으로 제안한 퍼즐 문제로, 수학과 컴퓨터 과학에서 알고리즘 문제로 많이 거론된다.
예를들어 8×8 체스판에 8개의 퀸을 배치하는데, 이 때 어떤 퀸도 다른 퀸을 위협해서는 안된다는 조건이 있다. 체스에서 퀸은 상하좌우, 대각선 4방향으로 거리 제한 없이 이동할 수 있다. 위협하지 못한다는 것은 결국 특정 퀸이 다른 퀸의 움직이는 경로에 존재하지 않도록 모든 퀸들을 적절하게 배치하는 것이다.
위와 같이 8퀸 문제의 경우 12개의 unique 형태가 있으며, 이를 근본해라고 한다. 
대칭인 마지막 패턴(4개, 180도 회전과 상하대칭이 겹침)을 제외하고, 나머지 8개를 회전(4개) 및 대칭이동(4개) 으로 만들 수 있으므로, 여덟 퀸의 경우 총 92개의 해가 있다.
n개의 퀸을 n × n 판에 나타내는 해의 수는 다음 사이트에 공개되어 있다. 
예를들어 N=8이면 92, N=9이면 352, N=10이면 724, N=11 이면 2,680이고 N=12이면 14,200이다.
https://oeis.org/A000170

백트래킹
문제 해결 알고리즘 중 백트래킹(Backtracking)은 해결책으로 가능한 모든 경로를 탐색하면서, 각 단계에서 현재의 선택이 문제의 조건을 만족하지 않을 경우 이전 단계(또는 여러 단계)로 "되돌아가서"(backtrack) 다른 가능한 선택을 시도하는 방식의 알고리즘이다. 이 과정은 모든 가능한 경우의 수를 시험하지만, 불필요한 경로의 탐색을 최소화하여 시간과 자원을 절약할 수 있게 해준다. 백트래킹은 주로 결정 문제(예/아니오로…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Big Should Active Objects Get?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.state-machine.com/?p=16129</id>
        <link href="https://www.state-machine.com/how-big-should-active-objects-get"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T00:39:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Q: How big should active objects get?
A: As big as possible, but not bigger.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quantum Leaps</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 사람들 착각이 아니라 그들이 ‘진짜 현실’을 못 보는 것 아닐까요]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78366</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/02/12/npsp_vibecession/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_vibecession"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T22:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 12월 18일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 미국 언론의 사명 가운데 “기계적인 정치적 중립”은 없습니다. 이번에 공화당을 비판하는 기사를 썼으니, 다음에는 민주당을 비판하는 기사를 써야 한다는 원칙 같은 건 없다는 말입니다. 할 수 있는 최대한의 팩트체크를 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘좋빠가’가 민주주의 좀 먹는다: 슬로우레터 2월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103872</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103872"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T22:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 이슈가 설 민심 뒤흔들었나. 우리에겐 왜 박절한가. “아들이 맞으면서 간다.” 쟁점과 현안. 조국, 오늘 출마 선언한다. “정부는 의사를 이길 수 없다.” 개혁신당 빅 텐트의 후폭풍. 더 깊게 읽기. 미국인 86%, “바이든, 너무 늙었다”. 오픈AI의 1경 프로젝트. 다르게 읽기. ‘밸류업’이 만병통치약이 될 수는 없다. ‘밸류업’의 전제조건. 해법과 대안. 죽음의 선택권을 묻는다. 대학 투자 가장 적은...
The post ‘좋빠가’가 민주주의 좀 먹는다: 슬로우레터 2월13일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.29: Java code check in VS Code, Boost smart pointers, and plugin for Qt Creator on macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1102/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1102/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.29 has been released. Now you can analyze Java projects in a plugin for VS Code, check Boost smart pointers, use the PVS-Studio plugin for Qt Creator 12 on macOS, and that's not all! See...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD phasing out 32-bit platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961871/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961871/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T19:27:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FreeBSD Project has announced that it intends to deprecate 32-bit platforms "over the next couple of major releases". 


We anticipate FreeBSD 15.0 will not include the armv6, i386, and powerpc platforms, and FreeBSD 16.0 will not include armv7. Support for executing 32-bit binaries on 64-bit kernels will be retained through at least the lifetime of the stable/16 branch if not longer.


The announcement notes that support for some 32-bit platforms "may be extended if there is both demand and commitment to increased developer resources". More details about the current plans for 32-bit platforms are available in the FreeBSD 14.0-RELEASE Release Notes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Another runc container breakout]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961086/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961086/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Once again, runc—a tool
for spawning and running OCI containers—is drawing attention due to a high
severity container breakout attack. This vulnerability is interesting for
several reasons: its potential for widespread impact, the continued difficulty
in actually containing containers, the dangers of running containers
as a privileged user, and the fact that this vulnerability is made possible
in part by a response to a previous
container breakout flaw in runc.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961842/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961842/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T14:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (libgit2), Fedora (chromium, firecracker, libkrun, openssh, python-nikola, runc, rust-event-manager, rust-kvm-bindings, rust-kvm-ioctls, rust-linux-loader, rust-userfaultfd, rust-versionize, rust-vhost, rust-vhost-user-backend, rust-virtio-queue, rust-vm-memory, rust-vm-superio, rust-vmm-sys-util, virtiofsd, webkitgtk, and wireshark), Mageia (filezilla and xpdf), Oracle (gimp), Red Hat (libmaxminddb, linux-firmware, squid:4, and tcpdump), Slackware (xpdf), SUSE (cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, cont and suse-build-key), and Ubuntu (python-glance-store and webkit2gtk).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debug ACPI issues in Windows virtual machines on RHEL]]></title>
        <id>240e1e75-deaf-4d35-844d-65eb86deac6d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/12/debug-acpi-issues-windows-virtual-machines-rhel"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) 8/9 provides virtualization functionality, which enables a machine running RHEL to host multiple virtual machines (VMs), also referred to as guests. The basis of creating VMs on RHEL is the hypervisor software stack that controls hardware and enables running multiple operating systems on a host machine. The hypervisor stack consists of the kernel based virtual machine module (KVM) and virtualization kernel drivers, the QEMU emulator that simulates a complete virtualized hardware platform and manages how resources are allocated on the host and presented to the guest and the libvirt software suite that serves as a management and communication layer, making QEMU easier to interact with, enforcing security rules.
This article will describe how to set up an ACPI …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ani Sinha, Igor Mammedov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with the Red Hat build of Keycloak 22]]></title>
        <id>3e03d834-e04b-4c65-ad55-cc92dff4a79e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/12/getting-started-red-hat-build-keycloak-22"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Red Hat build of Keycloak offers a new era of identity and access management. This product is based on the Keycloak project, which enables you to secure your web applications by providing web single sign-on (SSO) capabilities based on OpenID Connect, OAuth 2.0, and SAML 2.0. The release of this product replaces any plans for a future single sign-on (8.0 or higher) feature release. 
While preserving the power and functionality of single sign-on, the Red Hat build of Keycloak is faster, more flexible, and efficient. For example:
This product uses a streamlined distribution model based on Red Hat build of Quarkus.
Getting started is simpler than with single sign-on; you choose from multiple configuration source instead of editing XML files.
Interactive command-line help supplements documentation for quick answers to questions.
Video demo
Watch this two-minute getting started video, which shows the initial steps to use the product.
Try out Red Hat build of Keycloak
The documentation and software are available so you can try it out for yourself.
Log on to the Red Hat customer portal to download the Red Hat build of Keycloak and try the Getting Started Guide.
Check out more Red Hat build of Keycloak articles at Red Hat Developer.
Getting started with the Red Hat build of Keycloak 22 appeared first on Red Hat Developer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Munro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[부자들에게 더욱 더 보장된 ‘표현의 자유’는 괜찮을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78695</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/02/12/npsp_wealthpower/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_wealthpower"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T05:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘날 돈만 있으면 뭐든지 할 수 있는 것처럼 보이는 자본주의 사회에서 부자들이 돈을 쓰는 새로운 용처 가운데 하나가 바로 영향력을 사는 일입니다. 특히 소셜미디어를 통해 주목받게 되면 그렇게 쌓은 명성과 영향력을 이용해 다시 돈을 벌 수 있는 선순환이 일어날 수 있는데, 부자들에겐 진입장벽이 상대적으로 낮다고 할 수 있습니다. 소셜미디어의 영향력을 십분 활용해 권력을 누리는 대표적인 인물로 보통 도널드 트럼프나 일론 머스크를 떠올리는데, 뉴욕타임스에 월스트리트의 헤지펀드 매니저 빌 애크먼을 예로 든 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some information on story point estimates for 16 projects]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8572</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/02/11/some-information-on-story-point-estimates-for-16-projects/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-11T23:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Issues in Jira repositories sometimes include an estimate, in story points, but no information on time to complete (an opening/closing date is usually available; in some projects issues pass through various phases, and enter/exit date/time may be available). Evidence-based software engineering is a data driven approach to figuring out software development processes. At the practical […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.8-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961764/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961764/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-11T20:43:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.8-rc4 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Commit counts and contents look normal for this phase of the
release, nothing here really stands out."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공정과 상식의 붕괴, 이재용 무죄 판결이 말하는 것.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103806</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103806"/>
        <updated>2024-02-11T16:15:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이재용(삼성전자 회장)의 불법 승계 재판은 여러 가지 쟁점을 남겼다. 이재용이 박근혜(전 대통령)에게 뇌물을 준(국정농단) 사건은 대법원까지 가서 유죄가 확정됐는데 뇌물을 주고 합병을 밀어붙인(불법승계) 사건은 무죄로 1심 선고가 났다. 두 재판 결과가 충돌한다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 핵심은 이것이다. 무죄가 나올 거라고 예상한 사람은 많지 않았던 것 같다. 간단히 판결 요지를 정리해 보자. 두 사건이 충돌한다. 그러니까...
The post 공정과 상식의 붕괴, 이재용 무죄 판결이 말하는 것. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CNC + Laser = Personalized Cutting Board]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40173</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/02/11/cnc-laser-personalized-cutting-board/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-11T14:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The post showcases recent designs for cutting boards made from 20 mm oak sheets using a desktop CNC and laser cutter. The simple design takes 5-6 minutes to cut and results in a raw cutting board, which can be produced in different sizes. The boards are treated with olive oil for a personalized finish. Links to related projects are provided. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[멋지게 지고도 이기는 방법, 이재명은 다른 선택을 할 수 있었다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103787</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103787"/>
        <updated>2024-02-11T09:01:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“민주-진보 빅텐트라는 달콤한 거짓말”이라는 조귀동(‘이탈리아로 가는 길’ 저자)의 글과 “민주당의 연합 위성정당 꼼수, 정의당이 가장 큰 피해를 본다”는 최병천(신성장경제연구소 소장)의 글을 읽으면서 이런 생각을 해봤다. 만약 이재명(민주당 대표)이 준연동형을 유지하되 위성정당을 만들지 않겠다고 선언했다면 어떻게 됐을까. 시뮬레이션을 해보자. 멋지게 지는 방법. 멋지게 졌을 때 얻을 수 있는 정치적 효과. 이것은 간단한 산수다. 핵심은 이것이다. 지난...
The post 멋지게 지고도 이기는 방법, 이재명은 다른 선택을 할 수 있었다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 성장하는 전기차 시장에서 관심가질 차트 3가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593809</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593809/%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%8b%9c%ec%9e%a5"/>
        <updated>2024-02-10T14:48:02.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Fedora Atomic Desktops (Fedora Magazine)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961653/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961653/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T22:19:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Magazine has announced the creation of Fedora Atomic Desktops: a way of branding Fedora's growing set of rpm-ostree spins. Joseph Gayso wrote "we’ve seen more of our mainline Fedora Linux spins make the jump to offer a version that implements rpm-ostree. It’s reached the point where it can be hard to talk about all of them at the same time. Therefore we’ve introduced a new brand that will serve to simplify how we discuss rpm-ostree and how we name future atomic spins." LWN covered Project Bluefin, which is based on Fedora's rpm-ostree work, in December 2023.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DRM-CI: A GitLab-CI pipeline for Linux kernel testing (Collabora Blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961655/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961655/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T22:15:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over on the Collabora blog, Helen Koike writes
about the DRM-CI project for running automated continuous integration (CI)
tests on multiple graphics devices in several different labs.  It uses the
IGT GPU
tools for testing, though there are plans to expand:

The roadmap for DRM-CI includes enabling other devices, incorporating
additional tests like kselftests, adding support for vgem driver, and
implementing further automations. DRM-CI builds upon the groundwork laid by
Mesa3D CI,
including its GitLab YAML files and most of its setup, fostering 
collaboration and mutual strengthening.

[...] Adapting the DRM-CI pipeline to other subsystems is feasible with a
few modifications. The primary consideration is setting up dedicated
GitLab-CI runners since Freedesktop's infrastructure is meant only for
graphics. 

In light of this, our team is developing a versatile and user-friendly
GitLab-CI pipeline. This new pipeline is envisioned to function as a
flexible interface for kernel maintainers and developers that can be
evolved to connect with different test environments that can also be hooked
with CI systems such as KernelCI. This approach aims to simplify the
integration process, making GitLab-CI more accessible and beneficial to a
broader range of developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Gnuplot 6 comes with pie]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961003/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961003/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T17:53:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gnuplot 6.0 was released in
December 2023, bringing a host of significant improvements and new
capabilities to the open-source graphing tool. Here we survey the major
new features, including 
filled contours in 3D, adaptive plotting resolution, watchpoints, clipping
of surfaces, sector plots for making things like pie charts, and new
syntax for conditionals in gnuplot's scripting language. In addition, there
are
detailed examples of the features described.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rowley: What’s new in the Postgres 16 query planner / optimizer]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961545/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961545/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T14:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[David Rowley looks
deeply into the improvements coming to the query planner in
PostgreSQL 16.


	For a long time now, PostgreSQL has been able to remove a LEFT JOIN
	where no column from the left joined table was required in the
	query and the join could not possibly duplicate any rows.

	However, in versions prior to PostgreSQL 16, there was no support
	for left join removals on partitioned tables. Why? Because the
	proofs that the planner uses to determine if there’s any
	possibility any inner-side row could duplicate any outer-side row
	were not present for partitioned tables.

	The PostgreSQL 16 query planner now allows the LEFT JOIN removal
	optimization with partitioned tables.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961584/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961584/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T14:50:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (webkit2gtk), Fedora (atril, chromium, gnutls, python-aiohttp, and webkitgtk), Gentoo (libxml2), Mageia (gnutls, gpac, kernel, kernel-linus, microcode, pam, and postfix), Red Hat (container-tools:2.0, container-tools:3.0, container-tools:4.0, container-tools:rhel8, gimp, libmaxminddb, python-pillow, runc, and unbound), SUSE (cosign, netpbm, python, python-Pillow, python3, and python36), and Ubuntu (libde265, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, and linux-intel-iotg).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Silicon Labs partners with Arduino to democratize Matter]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481453</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/silicon-labs-partners-with-arduino-to-democratize-matter/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T10:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Partnership aims to democratize development of Matter applications, enabling developers to go from new board to commissioned device in under two minutes.
The post Silicon Labs partners with Arduino to democratize Matter appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 디즈니 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 원가절감에 의존한 수익 개선은 긍정적이나…]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593805</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593805/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%94%94%ec%a6%88%eb%8b%88-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T02:48:49.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[분기별 삼성전자 미국 스마트폰 점유율 추이]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593791</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593791/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ec%8a%a4%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8%ed%8f%b0-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8-%ec%b6%94%ec%9d%b4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T02:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘김건희의 사랑이 필요한 거죠’, 조중동의 불만이 끓어오른다: 슬로우레터 2월9일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103759</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103759"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T22:19:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 이슈, 조중동의 불만이 심상치 않다. 의문의 1패는 KBS. 클린스만이 고마워 할 일. “우리의 사랑이 필요한 거죠.” “참모들 도움을 왜 안 받나.” 한동훈과 김경률의 반응이 달랐다. 중대재해 처벌해도 사고 늘었다는 거짓말. 쟁점과 현안. 조국 항소심도 징역 2년. 의원 꿔주고 지역구 나눠먹고. 더 깊게 읽기. 차이메리카의 종말, 미국의 최대 수입국은 멕시코. 다르게 읽기. “북한이 전쟁할 결심?...
The post ‘김건희의 사랑이 필요한 거죠’, 조중동의 불만이 끓어오른다: 슬로우레터 2월9일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Made the CES 2024 AR Experience: Android Virtual Guide, powered by Geospatial Creator]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/how-we-made-ces-2024-ar-experiencandroid-virtual-guide-geospatial-creator.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/how-we-made-ces-2024-ar-experiencandroid-virtual-guide-geospatial-creator.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Kira Rich – Senior Product Marketing Manager, AR and Bradford Lee – Product Marketing Manager, AR




 




Navigating a large-scale convention like CES can be overwhelming. To enhance the attendee experience, we've created a 360° event-scale augmented reality (AR) experience in our Google booth. Our friendly Android Bot served as a digital guide, providing:

Seamless wayfinding within our booth, letting you know about the must try demos
 
Delightful content, only possible with AR, like replacing the Las Vegas Convention Center facade with our Generative AI Wallpapers or designing an interactive version of Android on Sphere for those who missed it in real life 
 
Helpful navigation tips and quick directions to transportation hubs (Monorail, shuttle buses)
 

In partnership with L…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio extension for Visual Studio Code: searching for errors in Java code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1101/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1101/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a Java developer and prefer to work in VS Code? Good news! Now you can enhance code safety with the PVS-Studio extension, which helps detect errors in Java projects and much more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google announces 2024 season of docs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961405/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961405/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T20:14:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[, a program complementing its Summer of Code program
by providing funding to open source projects to hire technical writers to improve
their documentation. Interested projects have until April 2 to apply.



Google Season of Docs provides direct grants to open source projects to improve their documentation and gives professional technical writers an opportunity to gain experience in open source. Together we raise awareness of open source, of docs, and of technical writing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brennan: What's Inside a Linux Kernel Core Dump]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961414/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961414/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T19:53:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Stephen Brennan describes
kernel core dumps in excruciating detail.


	Kernel core dumps are complex. They are not simply copies of system
	memory; they contain plenty of extra metadata which is critical to
	understanding their contents. And like any other type of data, the
	design of the file formats can enable lots of flexibility and
	power. However, due to the broad variety of tools out there, the
	diversity of dump formats is overwhelming, and the lack of
	documentation or specifications compounds the problem.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[People of AI – Season 3]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/people-of-ai-season-3.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/people-of-ai-season-3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Ashley Oldacre






If you are joining us for the first time, you can binge listen to Seasons 1 and 2 wherever you get your podcasts. 
We are back for another season of People of AI with a new lineup of incredible guests! I am so excited to continue co-hosting with Luiz Gustavo Martins as we meet inspiring people with interesting stories in the field of Artificial Intelligence.
Last season we focused on the big shift in technology spurred on by Generative AI. Fast forward 12 months, with the launch of multimodal models, we are at an interesting point in history.
In Season 3, we will continue to uncover our guests' personal and professional journeys into the field of AI, highlighting the important work/products they are focusing on. At the same time we want to dig deeper into the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new CEO for Mozilla]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961359/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961359/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T15:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mitchell Baker has announced
that she is stepping down from the role of Mozilla CEO, effective
immediately.  Laura Chambers will be the new CEO "for the remainder of
the year".


	We’re at a critical juncture where public trust in institutions,
	governments, and the fabric of the internet has reached
	unprecedented lows. There’s a tectonic shift underway as everyone
	battles to own the future of AI. It is Mozilla’s opportunity and
	imperative to forge a better future. I’m excited about Laura’s
	day-to-day involvement and the chance for Mozilla to achieve
	more. Our power lies in the collective effort of people
	contributing to something better and I’m eager for Mozilla to meet
	the needs of this era more fully.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Pitchforks for RDSEED]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961121/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961121/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T15:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The generation of random (or, at least, unpredictable) numbers is key to
many security technologies.  For this reason, the provision of random data
as a CPU feature has drawn a lot of attention over the years.  A proper
hardware-based random-number generator can address the problems that make
randomness hard to obtain in some systems, but only if the manufacturer can
be trusted to not have compromised that generator in some way.  A recent
discussion has brought to light a different problem, though: what happens
if a hardware random-number generator can be simply driven into exhaustion?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glibc becomes a CVE Numbering Authority]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961355/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961355/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T15:07:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNU C Library project has
been accepted as a CVE Numbering Authority (CNA), meaning that the
project is now in control of the CVE numbers assigned to its code.


	As a CNA the glibc security team will be working to improve the
	quality and response time of security advisories and mitigations.

	Over the coming months, the glibc security team will define the
	process for the CNA and establish best practices that can also be
	used by the rest of the GNU Toolchain.


See this article for some background on
this change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961330/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961330/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T14:40:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium), Red Hat (gimp, kernel, kernel-rt, and runc), Slackware (expat), SUSE (libavif), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke,
 linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15,
 linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-nvidia, linux-oracle,
 linux-oracle-5.15, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4,
 linux-bluefield, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4,
 linux-iot, linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, and linux, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-hwe-6.5, linux-laptop,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-oem-6.5, linux-oracle,
 linux-raspi, linux-starfive).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s involved in simulation of a complex SoC FPGA like Versal ACAP?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481434</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/whats-involved-in-simulation-of-a-complex-soc-fpga-like-versal-acap/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T14:14:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As SoC FPGAs become more complex so do the verification challenges. This article explains what’s involved in simulating AMD’s latest SoC FPGA.
The post What’s involved in simulation of a complex SoC FPGA like Versal ACAP? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Louie De Luna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unraveling the Enigma: Object Detection in the World of Pixels]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1631.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1631.php"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:57:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction:
In our journey through the intricacies of embedded systems co-design for object recognition, we have embarked on a transformative exploration. We have delved into the symbiotic relationship between hardware and software, catalyzing revolutions across industries like consumer electronics, healthcare, and autonomous vehicles. Our path now leads us to the ever-evolving realm of...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘청부민원’ 넣고 ‘셀프심의’, 류희림 패밀리를 폭로하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103746</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103746"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[지난해 12월 뉴스타파가 류희림 방송통신심의위원회(이하 방통심의위) 위원장이 가족과 지인을 동원해 ‘청부민원’을 넣고 ‘셀프심의’를 벌였다는 의혹을 제기했다. 국민권익위원회에 접수된 공익신고서가 그 근거였다. 방송심의, 통신심의는 일반 시민도 신청할 수 있다. 그러나 방통심의위 구성원이 주변을 동원해 심의를 신청하고 이를 처리하는 건 문제다. 비슷한 일로 2018년 방통심의위 팀장이 파면되기도 했다. 법원은 방통심의위가 다른 기관보다 높은 수준의 공공성과 공정성을 요구받기...
The post ‘청부민원’ 넣고 ‘셀프심의’, 류희림 패밀리를 폭로하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[분기별 스마트폰 점유율 및 스마트폰 출하량 추이(23년 4분기 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593776</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593776/%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0%eb%b3%84-%ec%8a%a4%eb%a7%88%ed%8a%b8%ed%8f%b0-%ec%a0%90%ec%9c%a0%ec%9c%a8-%ec%b6%94%ec%9d%b4"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T12:03:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to visualize your OpenSCAP compliance reports]]></title>
        <id>b16327bf-57a7-462e-a4bd-2069dbfacfe1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/08/how-visualize-your-openscap-compliance-reports"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Keeping your systems safe and secure is something that every organization and every individual should be concerned about, and there are many aspects to that topic. One of them is to harden systems according to a standard and also assess the systems against these standards. OpenSCAP is an open standard that lets you achieve exactly that. You can use it to check Linux-based systems as well as Red Hat OpenShift clusters against industry standards such as CIS, ACSC E8, or NIST.
The basics of creating a compliance report
The simplest way to run evaluate the compliance status of a system is to use the oscap tool and run it against a profile such as ACSC E8. Here an example on a Red Hat Enterprise Linux 9 system:
$ oscap xccdf eval --profile xccdf_org.ssgproject.content_profile_e8 --results-arf a…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Juerg Ritter</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[북리뷰] 처음 읽는 헌법]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16202197</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16202197"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T04:24:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이 책은 <처음 헌법 연구소>의 조유진 소장님의 저서로, 2013년 처음 출간된 후 청소년 및 일반 시민들이 헌법에 입문하기 위한 교재로 많은 호응을 받고 있다. 헌법재판소의 박근혜 대통령 탄핵심판 이후 2017년 개정판에서는 관련된 내용도 보강되어 있다. 
이 책은 1부(헌법에 대한 소개)와 2부(우리나라에 있었던 주요 헌법 재판을 소개)로 내용을 시작한다. 3부에서는 우리나라 뿐만 아니라 미국이나 프랑스 등 전세계적으로 헌법이 어떻게 태동해는지를 설명한다. 
4부부터 본격적으로 헌법의 조항에 대해 설명한다. 우리 헌법은 전문과 130개의 조문으로 이루어져 있으며 본문과 부칙을 간단히 설명한다. 본문은 다시 총 10개의 장으로 구성되어 있고, 제1장 '총강'은 헌법 전반을 관통하는 기본 원리를, 제2장 '국민의 권리와 의무'는 헌법이 보장하는 기본권 목록과 국민의 기본 의무를 규정한다. 제3장 '국회'는 입법부인 국회의 구성과 기능을, 제4장 '정부'는 대통령, 행정부, 국무총리와 국무위원, 국무회의, 행정 각부, 감사원을, 제5장 '법원'은 대법원의 구성과 법관의 독립 등 사법권을, 제6장 '헌법재판소'는 헌법재판소의 구성과 기능을 규정한다. 그리고 제7장 '선거 관리', 제8장 '지방자치', 제9장 '경제', 제10장 '헌법 개정'이 이어진다.
특히 4부의 마지막에는 대한민국헌법 개정의 절차 및 역사도 함께 다룬다. 우리나라 헌법은 1948년 제정된 이후 지금까지 총 9차례 개정되었고, 현재 대한민국헌법은 1987년에 개정된 헌법이다.

이승만, 제1차 개헌(발췌 개헌, 1952년)
이승만, 제2차 개헌(사사오입 개헌, 1954년)
이승만, 제3, 4차 개헌(4.19 혁명, 1960년)
박정희, 제5차 개헌(5.16 군사정변, 1962년)
박정희, 제6차 개헌(3선개헌, 1969년)
박정희, 제7차 개헌(유신헌법, 1972년)
전두환, 제8차 개헌(5공헌법, 1980년)
(사실상)노태우, 제9차 개헌(현행헌법, 1987년)

일제시대 이후 임시정부 수립, 남북전쟁, 군사정권 등 굵직한 역사를 지나온 한국 근현대사에서 헌법은 최초의 정신을 잃었을 때도 있었고(특히 유신헌법), 국민의 저항에 부딪혀서 다시 제헌헌법의 정신으로 복귀하기를 반복했다. 현행헌법은 1980년 5.18 광주민주화 운동 및 1987년 6월에 이르러 어렵게 쟁취하였으며 37년간 유지되고 있다. 


5부, 6부에서는 기본권을 다룬다. 사실 우리 헌법에 '기본권'이라는 단어는 없다. 헌법학자들이 헌법 제2장 "국민의 권리와 의무(제10조~제39조)"를 기본권이라고 부르면서 이것을 다음으로 분류하고 있다.
- 자유권적 기본권: 국가로부터 간섭받지 않을 권리(신체, 거주와 이전, 직업, 사생활 비밀, 통신비밀, 양심, 종교, 언론출판집회결사, 학문과 예술, 재산권
- 정치적 기본권: 국가의 의사 결정에 참여할 권리(선거권, 공무담임권, 국민투표권)
- 청구적 기본권: 국가에 대하여 특정한 행위를 요구할 권리(청원권, 재판청구권, 국가배상청구권, 형사보상청구권, 범죄피해자구조청구권)
- 사회적 기본권: 국가로부터 인간다운 삶을 보장받을 권리. 물질적 생활 기반을 뜻하며, 이는 개인과 사회의 공동 노력을 통해서 실현될 수 있기에 국회의 입법이 필요하다(교육을 받을 권리, 근로의 권리, 근로3권, 인간다운 생활을 할 권리, 환경권 등).


7부에서는 국가구조론(=통치구조론)을 다루며, 입법부, 대통령 및 행정부, 사법부, 헌법재판소 등을 다룬다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[죽음을 기억하는 방법: 이태원 특별법마저 거부한 정부에 전하는 다정한 조언]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103252</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103252"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T02:35:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[특별 인터뷰] 이태원 참사에 관한 책 [정부는 없다]를 펴낸 정혜승(전 청와대 디지털소통센터장)이 말하는 윤석열(대통령)의 아홉 번째 거부권 행사. 무능하고 비정한 정부에 전하는 ‘다정한’ 조언. 9.11 추모공원, 일명 ‘그라운드 제로’. 여기 올린 사진은 9.11 추모 공원 홈페이지에 올려진 순서 그대로다. 우선 반가운 환영(Welcome) 인사를 건넨다. 우리는 방문하고(Visit), 배우며(Learn), 서로서로 연결(Connect)한다. 그 끝에 이걸 모두 지원(Support)하겠다는 다짐이...
The post 죽음을 기억하는 방법: 이태원 특별법마저 거부한 정부에 전하는 다정한 조언 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UBS, 미국 경제 골디락스 가능성 증대로 S&P 500 지수 전망 5300까지 상승 가능]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593747</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593747/ubs-%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad-%ea%b2%bd%ec%a0%9c-%ea%b3%a8%eb%94%94%eb%9d%bd%ec%8a%a4-%ea%b0%80%eb%8a%a5%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T00:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for February 8, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960456/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960456/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T00:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for February 8, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[오래 기다린 해명, 키워드는 “몰카 공작”과 “아쉽다” 뿐: 슬로우레터 2월8일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103706</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103706"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T22:38:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 디올 백, 사과는 한 마디도 없었다. ‘명품’이라고 말을 왜 못하나. 조선일보의 키워드는 “몰카 공작”과 “아쉽다.” “다른 정상들도 지지율 낮다.” “한동훈, 총선 뒤에 보자 했다.” 쟁점과 현안. 뭉툭한 질문, 일방적인 홍보였다. 한동훈, “총선 목표 못 채우면 사퇴.” 더 깊게 읽기. 반쪽 방통위가 YTN 매각을 승인했다. 용산 개발이 놓친 네 가지. 해법과 대안. 양호 선생님이 주사...
The post 오래 기다린 해명, 키워드는 “몰카 공작”과 “아쉽다” 뿐: 슬로우레터 2월8일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2/8, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593757</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593757/2-8-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-%eb%b3%b4%ea%b3%a0%ec%84%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T22:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How recommerce startup Beni uses AI to help you shop secondhand]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/recommerce-startup-beni-uses-ai-to-help-you-shop-secondhand.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/recommerce-startup-beni-uses-ai-to-help-you-shop-secondhand.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lillian Chen – Global Brand and Content Marketing Manager, Google Accelerator Programs







Sarah Pinner’s passion to reduce waste began as a child when she would reach over and turn off her sibling’s water when they were brushing their teeth.  This passion has fueled her throughout her career, from joining zero-waste grocery startup Imperfect Foods to co-founding Beni, an AI-powered browser extension that aggregates and recommends resale options while users shop their favorite brands. Together with her co-founder and Beni CTO Celine Lightfoot, Sarah built Beni to make online apparel resale accessible to everyday shoppers in order to accelerate the circular economy and reduce the burden of fashion on the planet. 
Sarah explains how the platform helps connect shoppers to secondh…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA, S&P 500 수익이 플러스로 돌아섰지만 S&P 500 약세 조짐이 보인다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593748</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593748/bofa-sp-500-%ec%95%bd%ec%84%b8-%ec%a1%b0%ec%a7%90"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T21:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please welcome Joe Brockmeier to LWN]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961116/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961116/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T19:58:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the beginning of November, we let it be
known that we were looking to hire a writer/editor to augment the LWN
team.  In past attempts, we have found it difficult to attract writers who
could produce the kind of content that LWN readers expect.  This time
around, as we have said before, was different; we had a number of
candidates who could have filled the bill and were forced to make some
difficult choices.

While "hire them all" was an attractive idea, it was not one that our
budget would support.  We did conclude, however, that we could stretch to a
second hire.  So we are pleased to announce that the opportunity to bring
Joe Brockmeier on board was too good to pass up — so we didn't.  You will
start to see his work return to LWN within the next few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[임종석, 정치 낭만주의의 비극]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103646</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103646"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T17:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[영화 [밀정] (2016, 김지운)은 독립군 의열단 지도자 정채산(이병헌)과 일제에 적당히 협력하는 경찰 이정출(송강호)의 ‘상상 속 만남’을 매우 흥미롭게 묘사한다. 한국 현대사를 탐구한 작가라면 소설 속에 꼭 그려 넣고 싶은 장면이기도 한데, 의외로 소설이 아닌 영화에 먼저 등장했다. 나는 이 장면으로 영화 [밀정]은 명작의 반열에 올랐다고 생각한다. 의열단 지도자 정채산은 아주 귀한 분을 모셨다며 술 한...
The post 임종석, 정치 낭만주의의 비극 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정호재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 신년 대담 전문. (2023년 2월7일)]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103682</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103682"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T16:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“도어스태핑 효과적이지 못했다.” The buck stops here. “물가 관리 하고 있다.” “저출산은 최우선 국정 과제.” “코리아 디스카운트 해소는 규제 개혁부터.” “중대재해, 사후 처벌 보다는 예방 강화로.” “영수회담? 여당 지도부 무시하면 안 되니까.” “한동훈, 총선 끝나고 보자 했다.” “대통령 후광이 작동하겠나.” “다른 나라도 지지율 들쭉날쭉.” “승부사 윤석열? 검찰총장 때와 다를 수밖에.” “반지성주의, 안타깝다.” “집에서 이야기 많이...
The post 윤석열 신년 대담 전문. (2023년 2월7일) appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go 1.22 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961196/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961196/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T16:20:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Go 1.22, the most recent version of the Go programming language, has been released.  It comes with two language changes to for loops: a fix for a longstanding "gotcha" with accidentally sharing loop variables between iterations and adding the ability to range over integer values.  There are also additions to the standard library, improved performance, and more.  See the release notes for further information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] So you think you understand IP fragmentation?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960913/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960913/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T16:06:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is IP fragmentation, why is it important, and do people understand
it? The answer to that last question is "not as well as they think". This
article will also answer the rest of those
questions and introduce fragquiz, a game that I
wrote to allow players to guess how IP packets will behave when they are
too large for the network. As evidence that IP fragmentation is not
well-understood, a room full of networking experts played fragquiz and got
a score that was
nowhere close to perfect.  In addition, I will describe a new algorithm for
fragmentation avoidance, which some colleagues and I
developed, that helped motivate development of fragquiz.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.2 and 3.11.8 are now available.]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/02/python-3122-and-3118-are-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/02/python-3122-and-3118-are-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T15:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.2 and 3.11.8 are now available. In addition to all the usual bugfixes, these releases contain a small security fix: hidden .pth files are no longer automatically read and executed as part of Python startup. (New releases of 3.8, 3.9 and 3.10 containing the same fix are expected next week.)
 
Python 3.12.2
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3122/

Python 3.12’s second bugfix release. In addition to the mentioned 
security fix and the usual slew of bug fixes, build changes and 
documentation updates (more than 350 commits), this is also the first 
release to include a Software Bill-of-Materials for the source packages (Python-3.12.2.tgz and Python-3.12.2.tar.xz). Full changelog.
 
Python 3.11.8
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3118/

More than 300 commits of bug fixes, build changes and documentation updates. Full changelog.
 
We hope you enjoy the new releases!
 
Thanks to all of the many volunteers who help make Python Development
 and these releases possible! Please consider supporting our efforts by 
volunteering yourself, or through contributions to the Python Software Foundation  or CPython itself.
 
Thomas Wouters
 
Ned Deily
Steve Dower
Łukasz Langa]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961173/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961173/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T14:32:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Red Hat (gimp) and Ubuntu (firefox, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.15, and python-django).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민주-진보 빅텐트라는 달콤한 거짓말: 선거법 개정만으로 세상 안 바뀝니다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103623</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103623"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T08:08:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이재명 민주당 대표가 현행 준연동형 비례대표제를 유지하기로 결단하고, 민주당 외부의 다른 여러 세력을 참가시켜 통합형 비례 정당을 만들겠다고 선언했다. “안타깝지만 여당의 위성정당을 막을 방법은 없다”면서 “서생의 문제의식과 상인적 현실 감각으로, 이상을 추구하되 현실을 인정하겠다”고 말했다. 민주당은 세 가지 옵션이 있었다. 세 가지 옵션의 이해득실을 따져보자. 서생의 문제의식과 상인의 현실 감각. 위성정당, 네가 만들면 나도 만든다....
The post 민주-진보 빅텐트라는 달콤한 거짓말: 선거법 개정만으로 세상 안 바뀝니다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>조귀동</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[개인정보자기결정권의 헌법상 근거]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16202411</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16202411"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T07:07:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[서론
우리나라에서는 과거에 개인정보에 대한 인식이 다소 부족하였던 것 같다. 어렸을 때 초등학교 졸업 앨범의 뒷장에는 전교생의 이름과 집 주소, 전화번호 등이 버젓이 기록되어 있었는데 그것이 큰 문제라고 생각하지 않았다. 인터넷이 활성화 된 이후부터 많은 개인정보 유출 침해 사건 사고가 있었으나, 대다수의 국민들은 "약간 기분 나쁜" 정도에서 일상을 살아왔다. 그나마 개인정보에 대한 인식이 과거보다는 많이 개선되고 있다. 개인정보 유출은 이제 범죄로 처벌받고 있다. 


헌법재판소 주요 결정
1) 주민등록시 지문날인제도 사건
대한민국의 헌법재판소가 '개인정보자기결정권'을 인정한 것은 2005.5.26. 99헌마513 으로 알려져있다. 요약하면, 주민등록법상 열 손가락 지문을 날인하는 관례에 대해 이의를 제기하여 그 위헌확인을 구하는 이 사건 헌법소원심판을 청구한 것이다. 결과적으로 이 사건 자체는 기각되었지만, 개인정보자기결정권에 대한 헌법상 근거를 최초로 언급했다는 점에서 의미가 있다.

개인정보자기결정권은 자신에 관한 정보가 언제 누구에게 어느 범위까지 알려지고 또 이용되도록 할 것인지를 그 정보주체가 스스로 결정할 수 있는 권리, 즉 정보주체가 개인정보의 공개와 이용에 관하여 스스로 결정할 권리를 말하는바, 개인의 고유성, 동일성을 나타내는 지문은 그 정보주체를 타인으로부터 식별가능하게 하는 개인정보이므로, 시장·군수 또는 구청장이 개인의 지문정보를 수집하고, 경찰청장이 이를 보관·전산화하여 범죄수사목적에 이용하는 것은 모두 개인정보자기결정권을 제한하는 것이다.

개인정보자기결정권을 처음으로 인정한 이 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to use LLMs in Java with LangChain4j and Quarkus]]></title>
        <id>67865431-234a-488f-a811-5f1e4679940b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/07/how-use-llms-java-langchain4j-and-quarkus"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving landscape of artificial intelligence (AI), large language models (LLMs) have emerged as a game-changer, transforming how we interact with and derive insights from textual data. As a Java developer, diving into the world of AI might seem intimidating, but it's not! This tutorial is your gateway to use the power of LLMs through the integration of LangChain4j and Quarkus.
Exploring the capabilities of LangChain4j and Quarkus
LangChain4j, a Java library specializing in natural language processing (NLP), will play a crucial role in this tutorial. Using LangChain4j with Quarkus, a cloud-native, container-first framework, we will develop a tool proficient in analyzing and summarizing the content of blog posts. 
The objective here is not just to create a tool, but rather to pr…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Helber Belmiro</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[무임승차 논쟁의 맹점, 노인과 철도노조는 적이 아니라 협력자다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103617</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103617"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T05:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개혁신당이 총선 공약으로 ‘노인 지하철 무임승차 폐지’를 들고 나오자, 대한노인회가 반발하는 등 논쟁이 뜨겁다. 여권 내 볼썽사나운 권력투쟁이 언론을 도배하고 있을 때 교통정책 공론화를 시도한 일은 반가운 일이다. 김호일 대한노인회장과 이준석 개혁신당 대표의 라디오 공개토론도 성사됐지만 각 주장만 나열할 뿐 논리의 모순점을 비판하는 보도는 찾기 어렵다. 이준석, 정책 목표와 주장의 불일치 이준석 대표의 주장은 1984년...
The post 무임승차 논쟁의 맹점, 노인과 철도노조는 적이 아니라 협력자다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이것은 “혁신의 탈을 쓴 불평등”인가 아닌가]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78667</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/02/06/npsp_gigworkers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_gigworkers"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T00:30:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[보통 “플랫폼 노동자”로 번역되는 단어가 영어로는 “gig workers”라서 “긱 노동자”로 번역되기도 합니다. 우버 기사, 앱 기반 배달원 등이죠. 예전에는 “공유경제”라고 불리던 이런 형태의 노동에 관해 많은 논의가 있었습니다. 특히 플랫폼 업체들이 노동자들을 직접 고용하지 않고 개인사업자와 계약을 맺는 형태로 파견 근무를 보내 비용과 책임은 지지 않고 막대한 이윤만 챙기며, 그 과정에서 수많은 부작용이 발생한다는 비판이 끊이지 않았습니다. 최근 미국 콜로라도주 덴버시 노동국이 비슷한 이유로 플랫폼 업체 두 곳에 과태료 처분을 내렸습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why it's impossible to agree on what's allowed]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/impossible-agree/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/impossible-agree/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On large platforms, it's impossible to have policies on things like moderation, spam, fraud, and sexual content that people agree on. David Turner made a simple game to illustrate how difficult this is even in a trivial case, No Vehicles in the Park. If you haven't played it yet, I recommend playing it now before continuing to read this document.
The idea behind the site is that it's very difficult to get people to agree on what moderation rules should apply to a platform. Even if you take a much simpler example, what vehicles should be allowed in a park given a rule and some instructions for how to interpret the rule, and then ask a small set of questions, people won't be able to agree. On doing the survey myself, one of the first reactions I had was that the questions aren't chosen to be…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in January (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/january-2024-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/january-2024-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this
January.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wiznet W7500 flash programming]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-02-07:/w7500-flash-programming.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/w7500-flash-programming.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[W7500 is a nice little MCU from Wiznet with a built-in hardware TCP/IP stack and Ethernet MAC. You can get quite far with your IoT application on a Cortex-M0
running at 48 MHz when the networking is offloaded in hardware.
The device begins to show its age in 2023 (it was released around 2016). There is no crypto acceleration
whatsoever, no AES. Only an RNG is available. I think that modern TLS is practically impossible but some lighter
cryptography should be possible. Nevertheless, if you can put the device on an isolated VLAN the chip can still
be useful today.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Versatile OSHW Mini MCU-Link Debug Probe: External, On-Board, or Embedded]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40130</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/02/06/versatile-oshw-mini-mcu-link-debug-probe-external-on-board-or-embedded/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T22:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At HSLU IET we have developed an Open Source Hardware (OSHW) CMSIS-DAP debug probe in KiCad for versatile use in hardware development. The probe offers multiple integration options, USB-C connectivity, and a 3D printable enclosure, making it a compact and cost-effective solution. The project is available on GitHub. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘조선제일검’ 맞나, 검사 윤석열과 한동훈의 실력에 대한 의문: 슬로우레터 2월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103576</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103576"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T22:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“기소할 때 내가 관여한 사건 아니다.” 수사 이렇게 해놓고 큰소리쳤나. 쟁점과 현안. 빅 텐트? 서로 다른 꿈을 꾸는 이유. 조국 신당도 같이 탈 수 있나. 산토끼 쫓는 한동훈과 집토끼 지키는 이재명. 설날 특사 선물, 미리 흘렸나. 최은순도 가석방? MBC와 법무부 공방. 김장겸‧안광한도 사면. 더 깊게 읽기. 트럼프의 네 가지 인기 비결. 의대 2000명 증원, 의사...
The post ‘조선제일검’ 맞나, 검사 윤석열과 한동훈의 실력에 대한 의문: 슬로우레터 2월7일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] GNU C Library version 2.39]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960309/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960309/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T21:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[on January 31, including
several new features. Notable highlights include new functions for spawning
child processes, support for shadow stacks on x86_64, new security features, and
the removal of libcrypt. The glibc maintainers had also hoped to include
improvements to qsort(), which ended up not making it into this
release. Glibc releases are made every six months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering motor control: measurements sensors and parameters]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481425</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mastering-motor-control-measurements-sensors-and-parameters/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T17:04:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this installment of the motor control series, we explore feedback sensors, analog-to-digital converters, and measurement methods. As previously mentioned, the feedback sensors include position...
The post Mastering motor control: measurements sensors and parameters appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Radonic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 reasons embedded teams need to embrace simulation]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481422</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3-reasons-embedded-teams-need-to-embrace-simulation/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While it will take a little bit of time to get used to, simulating code will help you to modernize how you develop embedded software...
The post 3 reasons embedded teams need to embrace simulation appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961083/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961083/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T14:34:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (firefox, gstreamer1-plugins-bad-free, and tigervnc), Debian (ruby-sanitize), Fedora (kernel, kernel-headers, qt5-qtwebengine, and runc), Oracle (gnutls, kernel, libssh, rpm, runc, and tigervnc), Red Hat (runc), and SUSE (bouncycastle, jsch, python, and runc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘핼러윈 특조위’라고? 조선일보의 상징조작과 서울신문의 표절.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103552</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103552"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T11:48:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[노동인권저널리즘센터는 2024년 ‘1월의 나쁜 사설’로 조선일보와 서울신문 사설을 선정했다. 심사위원단은 ‘인간 존중’과 ‘진실 추구’ 보도 의무를 외면한 채, 사실 왜곡과 상징조작을 통해 이태원 참사 특별법의 공적 담론을 훼손하고 진상 규명 목소리를 축소·생략하고 정치 쟁점화했다고 평가했다. 조선일보가 1월 10일 “민주당 ‘핼러윈 특조위’ 강행, 제2의 ‘세월호 특조위’ 불 보듯”이란 제목의 사설을 내보낸 다음날 서울신문은 “야(野) 핼러윈 특조위...
The post ‘핼러윈 특조위’라고? 조선일보의 상징조작과 서울신문의 표절. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>노동인권저널리즘센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[우리 시대의 결혼]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103542</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103542"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T08:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리 시대에 결혼하고 아이를 낳아 키우겠다는 것은 너무도 매력 없는 선택지가 되었다. 당장 SNS만 켜더라도, 온갖 쇼츠와 릴스, 각종 광고는 우리에게 매일 ‘버킷리스트’를 쌓아 올린다. 그리스 산토리니에 가서 하룻밤을 보내는 것, 치앙마이에서 한 달 살기 하는 것, 몽골의 은하수나 노르웨이의 오로라를 보는 것. 돈은 그런 데 쓰라고 있는 것이지, 결혼하고 아이 낳고 키우는 데 쓰는...
The post 우리 시대의 결혼 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정지우</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security policies in open source software]]></title>
        <id>2f1a577f-f5c0-4c99-af1f-543854ea1d13</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/06/security-policies-open-source-software"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The open source community saw a number of new advances in security processes in the last year. One of those advances was the GNU toolchain community rallying around the idea of adopting security policies, with GCC and binutils already adopting one, guided by the precedent set by the glibc project as early as in 2014. The idea of a security policy in the context of software is not new; many large open source projects understand the need to define policies and procedures for reporting security issues. Some even have dedicated teams to handle security issues. Forges like GitHub actively promote the idea of adding a SECURITY.md file in the code repository that explains how to report security issues.
However, while the idea is not new, the usage of the security policy across open source communi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Siddhesh Poyarekar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to integrate Quarkus applications with OpenShift AI]]></title>
        <id>b242953f-63a0-40a5-be48-a16d40567e85</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/06/how-integrate-quarkus-applications-openshift-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Quarkus community recently released the first version of the Red Hat OpenShift AI integration with Quarkus. You can now invoke large-language models (LLMs) served by OpenShift AI from Quarkus applications (as illustrated in Figure 1). And that’s the topic of this article.


  Figure 1: Invoking LLMs served by OpenShift AI from Quarkus.
A brief history: Quarkus and Quarkus LangChain4J
Quarkus is a Java framework designed to build truly cloud-native applications. It offers a faster startup time and reduces the memory footprint, making it highly efficient. Tailored specifically for the cloud, containers, and Kubernetes, Quarkus has become a go-to framework for many sectors, including banking, logistics, and Software-as-a-Service (SaaS). Despite being under five years old, its impact is si…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Clement Escoffier, Georgios Andrianakis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[번역] 프로그래머를 위한 카테고리 이론 - 2. 타입과 함수]]></title>
        <id>20240206-category-theory-for-programmers-2-types-and-functions</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/02/06/category-theory-for-programmers-2-types-and-functions/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T02:12:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[타입과 함수로 이루어진 카테고리는 프로그래밍에서 꽤나 중요한 역할을 한다. 자 이제 타입이라는 것이 무엇이며 왜 이런 개념이 필요한지에 대해 이야기를 해보자.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘기회의 평등’에 기반했던 아메리칸 드림에 빨간 불이 켜진 까닭은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78341</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/02/05/npsp_collegeamericandream/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_collegeamericandream"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T22:59:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 12월 13일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. “아메리칸 드림” 하면 뭐가 가장 먼저 떠오르시나요? 기회의 땅 미국을 상징하는 이 말의 정의는 사람마다 조금씩 다를 수 있겠지만, 옥스퍼드 사전이 정의한 범주를 크게 벗어나는 독특한 정의는 없을 것 같습니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사회주의에 있어서 개량경제학의 유용성]]></title>
        <id>http://economicview.net/?p=84977</id>
        <link href="http://economicview.net/84977/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T22:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[때때로 정치경제학에서 정식화된 어떤 법칙을 이에 대응하는 구체적인 경제 과정의 규칙성과 실천적으로 동정하는 것이 곤란할 때가 있다. 상품가격과 판매량을 시계열 형태로 파악한 통계자료에 기초하여 가격과 수요 또는 공급 사이의 함수적 상관관계를 결정하려고 할 때, 얻어진 경험적 관련이 수요함수를 표시하고 있는지 공급함수를 표시하고 있는지, 혹은 그 어느 것도 아닌지 알 수 없는 경우가 잘 알려진 예이다. […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>sticky</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[악어가 입을 벌리면 그때는 이미 너무 늦다: 슬로우레터 2월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103514</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103514"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T22:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 아침 신문, 엇갈린 논조와 기사 가치 판단. 쟁점과 현안. 뇌물 준 사건은 유죄, 뇌물 줘서 합병한 사건은 무죄. 이재용의 승리는 윤석열의 완패다. 엘리엇 소송에 미칠 영향은? 가장 욕먹지 않을 선택, 연합 위성정당이란 출구 전략. 더 깊게 읽기. 새로운 게임의 룰, 누가 웃을까. 의원 꿔주기? 정의당이 1번? 해법과 대안. 야쿠르트 아줌마의 노인 돌봄 30년. 무상...
The post 악어가 입을 벌리면 그때는 이미 너무 늦다: 슬로우레터 2월6일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shall we check pointer for NULL before calling free function?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1100/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1100/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The short answer is no. However, since this question keeps popping up on Reddit, Stack Overflow, and other websites, it's time to address the topic. There are a lot of interesting things to ponder...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/961009/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/961009/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T20:37:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.7.4, 6.6.16,
and 6.1.77 stable kernels.  As usual, they
contain important fixes all over the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An improved chkstk function on Windows]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/02/05/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/02/05/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T17:56:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve spent much time developing with Mingw-w64 you’ve likely seen the
symbol ___chkstk_ms, perhaps in an error message. It’s a little piece of
runtime provided by GCC via libgcc which ensures enough of the stack is
committed for the caller’s stack frame. The “function” uses a custom ABI
and is implemented in assembly. So is the subject of this article, a
slightly improved implementation soon to be included in w64devkit as
libchkstk (-lchkstk).
The MSVC toolchain has an identical (x64) or similar (x86) function named
__chkstk. We’ll discuss that as well, and w64devkit will include x86 and
x64 implementations, useful when linking with MSVC object files. The new
x86 __chkstk in particular is also better than the MSVC definition.
A note on spelling: ___chkstk_ms is spelled with three unde…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence launches digital twin CFD multiphysics analysis platform]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481412</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/cadence-launches-digital-twin-cfd-multiphysics-analysis-platform/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T17:10:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence said its new Millenium platform combines digital twin, AI and HPC technology to provide best multiphysics simulation solution for automotive, A&D, energy, turbomachinery and data center markets.
The post Cadence launches digital twin CFD multiphysics analysis platform appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latest MIKROE IDE has increased graphics and Clang for Arm and RISC-V]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481407</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/latest-mikroe-ide-has-increased-graphics-and-clang-for-arm-and-risc-v/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T16:55:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Six new features added to NECTO Studio 6.0 include enhanced graphics library with new UI designer, enabling users to bring circuits to life with algorithmic precision and graphical creativity.
The post Latest MIKROE IDE has increased graphics and Clang for Arm and RISC-V appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[골드만삭스, AI붐으로 엔비디아 매출의 대폭적인 증가 예상, 골드만삭스 엔비디아 목표주가를 800달러 상향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593745</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593745/%ea%b3%a8%eb%93%9c%eb%a7%8c%ec%82%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T15:56:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The end of tasklets]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960041/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960041/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T15:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A common problem in kernel development is controlling when a
specific task should be done.  Kernel code often executes in contexts where
some actions (sleeping, for example, or calling into filesystems) are not
possible.  Other actions, while possible, may prevent the kernel from
taking care of a more important task in a timely manner.  The kernel
community has developed a number of deferred-execution mechanisms designed
to ensure that every task is handled at the right time.  One of those
mechanisms, tasklets, has been eyed for removal for years; that removal
might just happen in the near future.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960952/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960952/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T15:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (rear, runc, sudo, and zbar), Fedora (chromium, grub2, libebml, mingw-python-pygments, and python-aiohttp), Gentoo (FreeType, GNAT Ada Suite, Microsoft Edge, NBD Tools, OpenSSL, QtGui, SDDM, Wireshark, and Xen), Mageia (dracut, glibc, nss and firefox, openssl, packages, perl, and thunderbird), Slackware (libxml2), SUSE (java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, perl, python-uamqp, slurm, and xerces-c), and Ubuntu (libssh and openssl).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in JBoss Enterprise Application Platform 8.0]]></title>
        <id>45c0a195-69f8-4b22-a8f4-620ca81b6251</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/05/whats-new-jboss-enterprise-application-platform-8"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat recently announced the latest release of their Jakarta EE compliant platform, JBoss EAP 8.0. With this release, companies will be able to take advantage of the latest Jakarta EE APIs and significantly extend the life cycle of their enterprise Java applications.
JBoss EAP 8.0 introduces improvements across many areas of the platform, including the management console and CLI, security, clustering, datasource and EJB subsystems. For a more detailed list of the new features and enhancements, as well as the removed and deprecated features, refer to the JBoss EAP 8.0 release notes.
In this article, we will describe the new JBoss EAP 8.0 features and the tools provided by Red Hat to help customers migrate from older versions of JBoss EAP.
Long-life support for Jakarta EE applications
JBos…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Philip Hayes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 23년 4분기 빅테크 실적 시사점 7가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593728</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593728/%eb%b9%85%ed%85%8c%ed%81%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%8b%9c%ec%82%ac%ec%a0%90"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T09:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민주당의 연합 위성정당 꼼수, 정의당이 가장 큰 피해를 본다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103490</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103490"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T08:03:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[가장 욕먹지 않는 선택… 군소 정당 다당제 본격화할 듯 이재명 민주당 대표가 연동형 선거제를 유지하고 비례 위성정당을 만들겠다고 밝혔다. 큰 틀에서 용혜인 기본소득당 의원의 제안을 수용한 셈이다. 용혜인 의원은 ‘연합비례당’이라고 표현했지만 내용적으로 보면 ‘연합 위성정당’을 만들기로 했다. 모양새만 보면, 2020년 총선 시기에는 위성정당을 만들면 비난을 받았는데, 2024년 총선에서는 위성정당을 만들면서도 박수받는 상황이 됐다. 연합 위성정당을...
The post 민주당의 연합 위성정당 꼼수, 정의당이 가장 큰 피해를 본다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>최병천</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[There's a State in This Machine!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1625.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1625.php"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T08:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hardly you can find a concept so powerful yet so simple as the State Machine. It shouldn't come as a surprise that State Machines are so widespread, what may came as a surprise is how many bad implementations of this concept  I found over the years.
In this post, I'll try to go through the basics, present a simple state machine, and evolve its design until you get a basic minimal, but sound...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to cache data using GDB's Python API]]></title>
        <id>51ad72dd-271e-422e-91a6-0855584412e1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/05/how-cache-data-using-gdbs-python-api"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GNU Debugger (GDB) has an extensive, and growing Python API which can be used to customize and extend GDB as needed. Different object types exist within the Python API to represent different parts of GDB and the processes being debugged. 
Often when writing extensions using the Python API is is useful to cache information about the objects with which you are working. This information might be temporal; it needs to be recorded at a precise moment in time, and can't be re-calculated later; or the information might be expensive to calculate, so computing once and caching gives a significant performance boost.
This article describes how information can be cached for different object types within GDB's Python API; some object types provide special support for data caching, while for other o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Burgess</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2/5, 주요 기업 움직짐으로 살펴본 IT 트렌드]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593722</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593722/2-5-it-%ed%8a%b8%eb%a0%8c%eb%93%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T05:02:03.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmable position sensor module connects with CAN FD]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481402</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programmable-position-sensor-module-connects-with-can-fd/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T04:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PCAN-GPS FD has a satellite receiver, a magnetic field sensor, an accelerometer, and a gyroscope, providing position and orientation via CAN FD connection.
The post Programmable position sensor module connects with CAN FD appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NoC configuration tool takes makes complex SoC design easier]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481396</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/noc-configuration-tool-takes-makes-complex-soc-design-easier/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T03:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iNoCulator NoC EDA tool is processor agnostic and can connect many other on-chip IP blocks such as PCIe, CXL, and AI acceleration.
The post NoC configuration tool takes makes complex SoC design easier appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using std::expected from C++23]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/expected-cpp23/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/expected-cpp23/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll go through a new vocabulary type introduced in C++23. std::expected is a type specifically designed to return results from a function, along with the extra error information.



     
    


Imagine you’re expecting a certain result from a function, but oops… things don’t always go as planned:
/*RESULT*/ findRecord(Database& db, int recordId) {
    if (!db.connected())
        return /*??*/
    
    auto record = db.query(recordId);
    if (record.valid) {
        return record;

    return /*??*/
}


What can you do? What should you return or output through /*RESULT*/ ?
Here are a few options:
Throw an exception,
Terminate the application,
Use std::optional to return a value or “nothing” to indicate an error,
Use a separate struct like my_func_result that would stor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why did organizations fund the creation of the first computers?]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8548</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/02/04/why-did-organizations-fund-the-creation-of-the-first-computers/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T22:43:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What were the events that drove organizations to fund the creation of the first computers? I suspect that many readers do not appreciate how long scientific/engineering calculations took before electronic computers became available, or the huge number of clerical staff employed to process the paperwork associated with running any sizeable business. If somebody wanted to […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈의 거짓말, 목련 피어도 김포가 서울 될 일 없다: 슬로우레터 2월5일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103458</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103458"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T22:09:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[기자회견 없이 단독 대담만. ‘한핵관’ 김경율의 출마 포기가 의미하는 것. 윤석열 지지율 29%로 추락. ‘용핵관’ 공천이 변수. 쟁점과 현안. 윤석열-한동훈 갈등 끝나지 않았다. 반쪽으로 출발한 ‘새로운미래’. 더 깊게 읽기. 물고 물리는 프레임 전쟁. 스윙 선거구 62곳에 달렸다. 다르게 읽기. “아무도 나서지 않았다.” 해법과 대안. 범죄 피해 보상을 월급 기준으로? 의대 정원 1700명 늘린다. 병원 자주...
The post 한동훈의 거짓말, 목련 피어도 김포가 서울 될 일 없다: 슬로우레터 2월5일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.8-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960842/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960842/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T15:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.8-rc3 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "A slightly larger rc3 that I'd have hoped for, although at
this stage in the release process it's not something that really worries me
yet."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SI 산업의 정체는 “기업시장”]]></title>
        <id>http://subokim.wordpress.com/?p=13285</id>
        <link href="https://subokim.wordpress.com/2024/02/04/definition-of-si/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T07:10:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SI 산업, IT서비스 산업.이렇게 말하니까 초보자들은 헷갈려 합니다. 그냥 남의 허드렛일 하는 노예시장처럼 치부하기도 합니다.실제로 SI를 하고 있는 적지 않은 개발자들이 이렇게 생각하기도 합니다.하지만, 그거 아닙니다. SI 산업의 정체 이 시장의 정체는 B2B 마켓,즉, 기업이 IT를 사주는 시장, 기업시장입니다.물론 정부가 물건을 사주는 B2G 시장도 있습니다.하지만, 편의상 다 “기업시장”이라고 하겠습니다. 네비어, 직방 같은 서비스는 “일반 사용자”가... Continue Reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>subokim</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 메타 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 강력한 기존 비즈니스와메타버스의 강력한 성장]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593706</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593706/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T01:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 아마존 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 모든 부문에서 만족스럽다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593705</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593705/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T01:16:32.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 애플 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선은 차갑다.]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593704</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593704/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-02-04T01:06:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 인간은 합리적이지만 또 비합리적인데요…]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78319</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/02/03/npsp_nudge/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_nudge"/>
        <updated>2024-02-03T22:59:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 12월 11일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 인간이 합리적인 존재인지에 대한 논쟁의 역사는 무척 깁니다. 소크라테스가 남긴 ‘너 자신을 알라’는 말은 인간의 무지, 곧 비합리성을 지적한 것입니다. 반면 플라톤은 인간의 이성, 곧 합리성이 인간을 다른 동물과 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>veritaholic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이재용 재판, 한국 사회의 공정과 상식을 묻는다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103421</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103421"/>
        <updated>2024-02-03T22:43:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[다음주 월요일 5일 이재용(삼성전자 회장)의 불법 승계 재판 1심 결과가 나온다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 핵심은 이것이다. 30년에 걸쳐 완성된 이재용의 후계구도. 이번 재판의 쟁점은. 좀 더 깊이 들어가 보자. 2100배 수익률, 이재용 왕국의 기반. 어떻게 될까.
The post 이재용 재판, 한국 사회의 공정과 상식을 묻는다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Zig 2024 roadmap]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959915/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959915/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T15:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zig language
2024 roadmap
was presented in a talk last week on
Zig Showtime (a show covering
Zig news). Andrew Kelley, the benevolent dictator for life of the Zig project,
presented his goals
for the language, largely focusing on compiler performance and continuing
progress toward stabilization for the language. He discussed details of his plan
for incremental compilation, and addressed the sustainability of the project in
terms of both code contributions and financial support.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phipps: The European regulators listened to the Open Source communities]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960606/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960606/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T14:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simon Phipps writes
on the Open Source Initiative blog that the latest version of the
European Cyber Resilience Act is much improved: "As a result of all this
effort from so many people, the final text of the CRA mitigated pretty much
all the risks we had identified to individual developers and to Open Source
foundations."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960604/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960604/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T14:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium, man-db, and openjdk-17), Fedora (chromium, indent, jupyterlab, kernel, and python-notebook), Gentoo (glibc), Oracle (firefox, thunderbird, and tigervnc), Red Hat (rpm), SUSE (cpio, gdb, gstreamer, openconnect, slurm, slurm_18_08, slurm_20_02, slurm_20_11, slurm_22_05, slurm_23_02, squid, webkit2gtk3, and xerces-c), and Ubuntu (imagemagick and xorg-server, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023년 백화점 매출 순위]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593700</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593700/23%eb%85%84-%eb%b0%b1%ed%99%94%ec%a0%90-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c-%ec%88%9c%ec%9c%84"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:40:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[망각이란 무엇인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://attention2.space/?p=3406</id>
        <link href="https://attention2.space/2024/esquecer/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T07:06:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[하지만 망각은 문제 해결을 원천적으로 불가능하게 만든다. 문제 자체를 잊어버리기 때문이다. 모든 변화의 가능성은 망각과의 싸움에서 싹튼다. 위기의 망각은 위기를 심화시킨다. 망각이 ‘지구 생태계의 위기’, ‘사회경제적 위기’와 맞물린 ‘인간생태학적 위기’의 결과이면서 동시에 조건인 이유다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>attention2space</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[노인 무임승차 폐지? 오히려 전 국민 대중교통 무료를  이야기해야 할 때다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103360</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103360"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T04:56:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이준석(개혁신당 대표)이 노인 지하철 무임승차를 폐지하자는 정책을 내놔서 논란이 됐다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 지속가능성과 형평성, 두 가지 이슈가 있다. 이준석은 월 1만 원 교통카드을 지급하자고 했다. 이준석은 대중교통 패스가 보편적 복지라고 주장한다. 지하철 적자, 구조적인 원인이 뭔가. 노인들 때문에 적자? 오해와 진실. 누적 적자가 17조 원이나 된다. 무임승차가 지하철 누적 적자에 미치는 영향이 어느 정도일까....
The post 노인 무임승차 폐지? 오히려 전 국민 대중교통 무료를  이야기해야 할 때다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이재명의 선택, “명분도 리더십도 다 잃었다”는 비판을 받는 이유: 슬로우레터 2월2일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103317</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103317"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T22:10:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[소방관의 죽음. 정답 정해놓고 당원 투표. 이재명의 선택. 쟁점과 현안. 의석 5석이면 보조금이 23억 원. 필수 의료 패키지, 10조 원 쏟아붓는다. 다르게 읽기. 중대재해법 유예 외면? 더 깊게 읽기. “사람 죽이는 제품 만들고 있다.” 기후 의제에 30석 달렸다. 오늘의 TMI. 트럼프가 비행기 타고 재판 다니는 이유. 국가대표 해병대 캠프라는 도시 전설. 결국 KBS만 찍어 신년...
The post 이재명의 선택, “명분도 리더십도 다 잃었다”는 비판을 받는 이유: 슬로우레터 2월2일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carbon Limit’s concrete technology is saving the environment using AI]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/carbon-limits-concrete-technology-saving-the-environment-using-ai.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/02/carbon-limits-concrete-technology-saving-the-environment-using-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T22:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Lillian Chen – Global Brand and Content Marketing Manager, Google Accelerator Programs







Located in Boca Raton, Carbon Limit aims to decarbonize the industry and take part in  saving, protecting, and healing the environment. Cofounder Tim Sperry explains that for him and his cofounders Oro Padron, and Christina Stavridi, the mission is personal. “I’ve lost family members [to polluted air]. Oro has his own story, Christina has her own story, and our other core team member Angel just had kids. All of us have our own connection to our mission. And with that, we've developed a really strong company culture,” he says.
Today, Carbon Limit is evolving to create sustainable solutions for the built environment. Their flagship product, CaptureCrete, is an additive that gives concrete …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Embedded Linux is used in Spacecrafts !]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1614.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1614.php"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T17:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How Embedded Linux is used in outer space ! EP1: SpacecraftsSeries introduction :
We will take a technical dive with Tux around the galaxy to see how Embedded Linux is used in outer space, fasten your seat belt and let the journey begin.
Ten years ago, the mainstream embedded systems consisted of just a Microcontroller with a few kilobytes of memory and either a bare-metal...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The hard life of a virtual-filesystem developer]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960088/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960088/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:56:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Filesystem development is not an easy task; the performance demands are
typically high, and the consequences for mistakes usually involve lost data
and irate users.  The implementation of a virtual (or "pseudo") filesystem
— a filesystem implemented within the kernel and lacking a normal backing
store — can also be challenging, but for different reasons.  A series of
conversations around the eventfs virtual filesystem has turned a spotlight
on the difficulty of creating a virtual filesystem for Linux.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 퀄컴 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593690</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593690/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%80%84%ec%bb%b4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T16:28:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Damn Small Linux 2024 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960446/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960446/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T14:53:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new version of the Damn Small
Linux distribution has come out with an updated definition of "damn
small":


	The new goal of DSL is to pack as much usable desktop distribution
	into an image small enough to fit on a single CD, or a hard limit
	of 700MB. This project is meant to service older computers and have
	them continue to be useful far into the future. Such a notion sits
	well with my values. I think of this project as my way of keeping
	otherwise usable hardware out of landfills.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stable kernels 6.7.3, 6.6.15, and 6.1.76]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960439/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960439/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T14:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.7.3, 6.6.15, and 6.1.76 stable kernels have been released.
These contain a large number of important fixes throughout the tree, as is
the norm.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to configure granular access in OpenShift Dev Spaces]]></title>
        <id>08a6220d-2337-477e-90eb-ebf455edffbd</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/01/how-configure-granular-access-openshift-dev-spaces"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even though the current trend is to split an infrastructure into a number of "fit-for-purpose" clusters instead of having a gigantic monolith Red Hat OpenShift cluster, administrators still want to provide granular access and restrict certain functionality for particular users.
 
Info alert: Info alert titleNote
A "fit-for-purpose" OpenShift cluster refers to a cluster that is specifically designed and configured to meet the requirements and goals of a particular use case or workload, tailored to optimize performance, resource utilization, and other factors based on the characteristics of the workloads it will be managing. For Red Hat OpenShift Dev Spaces, it is recommended to have this type of cluster provisioned.
Previously, all users provisioned on an OpenShift cluster had access to Ope…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilya Buziuk</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Meteor.js applications to OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>67dfddaf-e149-46cc-9ae8-fbb7c7b58314</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/02/01/how-deploy-meteorjs-applications-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift is a unified platform to build, modernize, and deploy applications at scale. OpenShift offers a great developer experience in shipping your applications to the cloud. 
JavaScript is the most popular programming language in the world and is used by millions of developers around the world. While it’s one programming language, there are many popular frameworks within JavaScript that need different approaches.
In this series of articles, we are providing step-by-step guides to help you get up and running with JavaScript applications on OpenShift. For this tutorial, we expect you to have some familiarity with Meteor.js and Red Hat OpenShift. If you need a quick recap, check out these resources: 
Video: Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift 
Developer Sandbox for Red Hat Open…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960436/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960436/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T13:57:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (debian-security-support, firefox-esr, openjdk-11, and python-asyncssh), Fedora (glibc, python-templated-dictionary, thunderbird, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Gentoo (Chromium, Google Chrome, Microsoft Edge and WebKitGTK+), Red Hat (firefox, gnutls, libssh, thunderbird, and tigervnc), SUSE (mbedtls, rear116, rear1172a, runc, squid, and tinyssh), and Ubuntu (glibc and runc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[나에게 세금을 매겨라, 360억 상속받고 분노한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103286</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103286"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T02:54:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“나는 아무 일도 하지 않았지만, 큰 돈과 그에 따르는 힘을 상속받았다. 하지만 국가는 여기에 세금도 매기지 않는다. 불공평하다고 생각한다. 정치인들이 제 역할을 못 하고 부의 재분배에 힘쓰지 않으니, 나 스스로 내가 가진 것을 재분배해야겠다.” 마를렌 엥겔호른. 이런 신선한 부자를 보았나?! 360억 상속에 분노한 마를렌 만약 360억 원이 생기면 어떻게 하시겠어요? 이렇게 행복한(?) 고민을 하는 사람이 있습니다....
The post 나에게 세금을 매겨라, 360억 상속받고 분노한 이유 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>북극여우</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for February 1, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959457/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959457/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T00:57:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for February 1, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Zephyr - Devicetree basics (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/practical_zephyr_dt</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/practical_zephyr_dt"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this third article of the “Practical Zephyr” series, we’ll see how we configure and use hardware. For this, Zephyr borrows another tool from the Linux kernel: Devicetree.
In contrast to Kconfig, the Devicetree syntax and its use are more intricate. Therefore, we’ll cover Devicetree in two articles. In this article, we’ll see what Devicetree is and how we can write our own Devicetree source files. In the next article, we’ll look at so-called Devicetree bindings, which add semantics to our Devicetree. Be prepared for a fair bit of theory, but as usual, we’ll use an example project to follow along.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GNU C Library 2.39 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960357/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960357/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T23:41:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.39
of the GNU C Library has been released.  Changes include integration with
the x86 shadow-stack mechanism, a couple of
new posix_spawn() variants for working with control groups, pidfd_spawn() and
pidfd_spawnp(), the C2X stdbit.h header, the removal
of the libcrypt library, and more.  See the release notes
for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 전쟁 중인 나라보다 낮은 출생률, 우리가 해야 할 고민은]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78296</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/31/npsp_koreadissapearing/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_koreadissapearing"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T22:59:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 12월 6일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. “대한민국은 ‘집단 자살 사회’다(South Korea is a collective suicide society).” 지난 2017년, 크리스틴 라가르드 IMF 총재가 방한했을 때 한국의 저출생 문제에 관해 한 말입니다. 현재 유럽중앙은행(ECB) 총재인 라가르드 박사는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rukahs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“윤석열 주변 정치 초짜들이 총선 불태울 뻔”, 조선일보가 분노한 이유: 슬로우레터 2월1일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103258</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103258"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T22:09:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아직도 결정 못했다. 당원들이 원한다면. 이재명의 히든카드는 ‘출생 기본소득’. 고발 사주, 윤석열이 몰랐을까. 쟁점과 현안. “정치 초짜들이 총선 판을 불태울 뻔했다.” ‘돈봉투’ 윤관석 징역 2년. 더 깊게 읽기. 아낌없이 풀어주는 노후 도시 특별법. 지난해 세수 펑크 56조 원. 제조업 생산지수 급락, 외환위기 이후 최대폭. 유승민 역할론? 윤석열이 불편해한다. 오늘의 TMI. 신혼부부 42%가 7000만 원 이상...
The post “윤석열 주변 정치 초짜들이 총선 불태울 뻔”, 조선일보가 분노한 이유: 슬로우레터 2월1일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qt Creator* in search of Qt Creator bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1099/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1099/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Strange things happen: for almost a year, PVS-Studio has a plugin for Qt Creator. However, we haven't yet published a good old article with the IDE check. We've made amends and invite you to see how...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 AMD 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 데이타센터는 훌륭하나 나머지는 실망스럽다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593675</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593675/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-amd-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T20:52:26.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 구글 알파벳 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 우려를 벗지 못하다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593672</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593672/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ea%b5%ac%ea%b8%80-%ec%95%8c%ed%8c%8c%eb%b2%b3-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T20:42:13.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LibreOffice 24.2 Community released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960344/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960344/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T20:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
24.2 of the LibreOffice office suite is available.  Changes include
AutoRecovery enabled by default, styling of comments, better floating-table
support, improved accessibility, and more.  See the release
notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 4분기 마이크로소프트 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 여전히 긍정적]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593669</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593669/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%9c%ec%86%8c%ed%94%84%ed%8a%b8-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T20:33:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] OpenBSD system-call pinning]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959562/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959562/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T19:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(ROP) attacks are hard to defend against.
Partial mitigations such as address-space layout randomization, stack
canaries, and other techniques are commonly deployed to try and frustrate
ROP attacks. Now, OpenBSD is experimenting with a new
mitigation that makes it harder for attackers to make system
calls, although some security researchers have expressed doubt that it will
prove effective at stopping real-world attacks.
In his
announcement message, Theo de Raadt said that this work
"makes some specific low-level attack
methods unfeasable on OpenBSD, which will force the use of other methods."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding bottleneck: final installment]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html#PairProgrammingAsACriticalOnboardingTechnique</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html#PairProgrammingAsACriticalOnboardingTechnique"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T16:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim and Prem finish their article on effective
      onboarding. They discuss the value of pair programming, setting up
      personal environments, and removing friction from the process.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A locally exploitable glibc vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960289/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960289/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T16:25:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualys has disclosed
a vulnerability in the GNU C Library that can be exploited by a local
attacker for root access.  It was introduced in the 2.37 release, and also
backported to 2.36.


	For example, we confirmed that Debian 12 and 13, Ubuntu 23.04 and
	23.10, and Fedora 37 to 39 are vulnerable to this buffer
	overflow. Furthermore, we successfully exploited an up-to-date,
	default installation of Fedora 38 (on amd64): a Local Privilege
	Escalation, from any unprivileged user to full root. Other
	distributions are probably also exploitable.


Vulnerable systems with untrusted users should probably be updated in a
timely manner.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[포퓰리즘 시대 전쟁이 된 선거, 결국 그들 손에 달렸다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78643</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/31/npsp_swatting/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_swatting"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T16:00:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[스와팅(swatting)이란 말을 아시나요? 긴급 전화에 거짓 내용을 신고해 무장한 특수 경찰이나 병력이 출동하도록 하는 행위를 뜻합니다. 총기 소유가 사실상 자유로운 미국에선 신고를 받고 출동하는 경찰이 보통 중무장한 채로 현장에 가는 경우가 많아 자칫 총기 사고가 날 수 있습니다. 그래서 정적이나 정치적인 견해가 다른 사람들을 향한 스와팅이 새로운 형태의 정치 폭력으로 분류됩니다. 스와팅의 부상이 민주주의에 얼마나 큰 위협인지 지적한 칼럼을 번역하고, 해설을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 공직자를 겨냥한 ‘거짓 신고'(Swatting)와 정치 폭력의 위험한 부상 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960248/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960248/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T14:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (bind9 and glibc), Fedora (ncurses), Gentoo (containerd, libaom, and xorg-server, xwayland), Mageia (python-pillow and zlib), Oracle (grub2 and tomcat), Red Hat (avahi, c-ares, container-tools:3.0, curl, firefox, frr, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, libfastjson, libmicrohttpd, linux-firmware, oniguruma, openssh, perl-HTTP-Tiny, python-pip, python-urllib3, python3, rpm, samba, sqlite, tcpdump, thunderbird, tigervnc, and virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel modules), SUSE (python-Pillow, slurm, slurm_20_02, slurm_20_11, slurm_22_05, slurm_23_02, and xen), and Ubuntu (libde265, linux-nvidia, mysql-8.0, openldap, pillow, postfix, and xorg-server, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging Open vSwitch logs: long poll interval, blocked waiting]]></title>
        <id>f3fe1348-96cc-4f35-920c-ebbfd3443563</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/31/debugging-open-vswitch-logs-long-poll-interval-blocked-waiting"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unfortunately, we often receive reports of users escalating the "long poll interval" and "blocked waiting" log messages as issues with Open vSwitch (OVS). Regrettably, in most cases, the problems are tied to system resource issues. Because OVS raises alerts about them, it ends up being wrongly identified as the culprit.
Before delving into the debugging process, let's first clarify the meaning of these messages.
Within its internal operations, OVS employs a mechanism known as a poll loop to handle various events. Its function is similar to more advanced solutions like libevent or glib. In essence, it comprises a set of APIs enabling the registration of events, such as a timeout or the availability of data on a socket. After registering these events, your process can enter a sleep state, aw…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eelco Chaudron</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using Gemini models in Go with LangChainGo]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/using-gemini-models-in-go-with-langchaingo/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/using-gemini-models-in-go-with-langchaingo/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T02:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In <a class="reference external" href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2023/using-gemini-models-from-go/">a previous post</a> I've
discussed how to access Google's multimodal Gemini models from Go (with a nice
free tier!)</p>
<p>Recently, Google's SDKs were added as providers for <a class="reference external" href="https://github.com/tmc/langchaingo">LangChainGo</a>; this makes it possible to use the
capabilities of the LangChain framework with Google's Gemini models as LLM
providers.</p>
<p>This post …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“한국 출산율 낮은 이유 알겠더라.”: 슬로우레터 1월31일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103223</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103223"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T22:04:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[위로도 없이 돈을 내밀었다. 이태원 특별법, 재협상 가능할까. 쟁점과 현안. 그 많던 친윤은 어디로 갔을까. 권역별 비례로 가면 제3지대 궤멸. 이재명이 공천 룰의 기준. “사직구장에서 야구를 봤다고 한 것 아니다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 빚은 전염된다. 다르게 읽기. 철도 지하화, 사업성이 있나. 65세 이상=노인 맞나. 오늘의 TMI. 징역형 받고 도주, 6000명 넘는다. 인감증명 사라진다. 한국 성장률...
The post “한국 출산율 낮은 이유 알겠더라.”: 슬로우레터 1월31일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Looking ahead to Emacs 30]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959931/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959931/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T21:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EmacsConf 2023 was, like its
recent predecessors, an online conference with lots of talks about various
aspects of the Emacs
editor—though, of course, it is way more than just an editor.  Last year's
edition was held in early December.  One of the
talks that looked interesting was on Emacs
development, which was given live by John Wiegley.  In it, he briefly
described some 
of the biggest features coming in Emacs 30, which is the next major version
coming for the tool.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The state of eBPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960036/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960036/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T16:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The eBPF Foundation has published a glossy document called The
State of eBPF; it seems mostly concerned with how a small number of
large companies are using and developing this technology.


	No doubt, eBPF will become the new layer in the new cloud native
	infrastructure stack, impacting the observability, performance,
	reliability, networking, and security of all applications,
	supporters say. Platform engineers will cobble together
	eBPF-powered infrastructure building blocks to create platforms
	that developers then deploy software on, adding business logic to
	the mix, and replacing aging Linux kernel internals that cannot
	keep up with today’s digital and, increasingly, cloud native world.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 tips for performing code reviews]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481390</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3-tips-for-performing-code-reviews/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:38:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional code review methods are often painful at best and a waste of time at worst. That doesn’t have to be the case. Performing code...
The post 3 tips for performing code reviews appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding bottleneck: more steps for good onboarding]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html#IncludeNewHiresInTheCompanyCulture</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html#IncludeNewHiresInTheCompanyCulture"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim and Prem continue outlining the steps for an
      effective onboarding process. They talk about including new hires in the
      company culture, nailing the post-offer and first-day experience, and
      investing in self-service knowledge management
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: active objects in real-time]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481387</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-active-objects-in-real-time/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video tutorial, we explore Active Objects’ properties related to preemption and real-time deadlines and thus tie together multiple concepts. In an earlier episode...
The post Programming embedded systems: active objects in real-time appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/960008/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/960008/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (pillow, postfix, and redis), Fedora (python-templated-dictionary and selinux-policy), Red Hat (gnutls, kpatch-patch, libssh, and tomcat), and Ubuntu (amanda, ceph, linux-azure, linux-azure-4.15, linux-kvm, and tinyxml).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Book review: Developing IoT Projects with ESP32 (2nd Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://medium.com/p/facdef7545bb</id>
        <link href="https://blog.espressif.com/book-review-developing-iot-projects-with-esp32-2nd-edition-facdef7545bb?source=rss----d5414d5dee73---4"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T14:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Juraj Michálek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[번역] 프로그래머를 위한 카테고리 이론 - 카테고리: 합성의 본질]]></title>
        <id>20240130-category-theory-for-programmers-1-category</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/01/30/category-theory-for-programmers-1-category/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T12:47:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[카테고리는 부끄러울 정도로 간단한 개념이다. 카테고리는 대상과 그 사이를 이어주는 화살표로 구성되기 때문에 그림으로 나타내기도 매우 쉽다. 대상은 원이나 점으로 그리면 되고, 화살표는 그냥 화살표로 그리면 된다. (쉬운 이해를 위해 객체를 돼지 모양으로 그리고 화살표는 폭죽으로 그릴 것이다.)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[번역] 프로그래머를 위한 카테고리 이론 - 0. 서문]]></title>
        <id>20240130-category-theory-for-programmers-0-preface</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/01/30/category-theory-for-programmers-0-preface/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T11:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[나는 한동안 프로그래머를 대상으로 하는 카테고리 이론에 대한 책을 작성하려는 아이디어를 생각해왔다. 즉 이 책은 컴퓨터 과학자가 아닌 프로그래머, 그리고 과학자보다는 엔지니어들을 대상으로 하는 책이다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[민들레당, 느리더라도 푸근하게 모자라도 함께 뭐 좀 해보는 그런 은평구]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102812</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102812"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T09:28:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[인터뷰] 1962년 군사정권이 기획한 헌법 8조와 정당법(62년 체제). 그 항체로서 지역정당의 의미에 관해 ‘행인’ 윤현식 박사가 말한다. 62년 체제를 넘어서 민주노동당에서 진보신당, 노동당을 거쳐 민들레당까지 민노: 행인 님께선 우리나라 진보정당의 역사를 망라하는 과정을 겪어오셨다고 저는 생각합니다. 민주노동당 활동을 하셨고, 진보신당을 거쳐, 노동당 창당 그리고 지금은 민들레당 당원으로 활동하시는데요. 그 과정 과정에서 자신의 정치적 정체성이 변화하고,...
The post 민들레당, 느리더라도 푸근하게 모자라도 함께 뭐 좀 해보는 그런 은평구 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지역의 협치? 거버넌스로 포장된 통치]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102809</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102809"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T09:27:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[인터뷰] 1962년 군사정권이 기획한 헌법 8조와 정당법(62년 체제). 그 항체로서 지역정당의 의미에 관해 ‘행인’ 윤현식 박사가 말한다. 62년 체제를 넘어서 정당 시스템의 하부 단위로 전락한 지역 시민 조직 민노: 지금 활동하고 계신 은평민들레당은 은평구에 있는 기존 정치 조직이나 시민 조직과의 관계가 어떤가요? 행인: 좀 민감한 문제라고 생각하는데요. 기존 거버넌스 시스템에 관해서는 시민사회가 반성적 입장에서 처음부터...
The post 지역의 협치? 거버넌스로 포장된 통치 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지역소멸과 지역정당]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102804</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102804"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T09:26:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[인터뷰] 1962년 군사정권이 기획한 헌법 8조와 정당법(62년 체제). 그 항체로서 지역정당의 의미에 관해 ‘행인’ 윤현식 박사가 말한다. 62년 체제를 넘어서 지방소멸과 지역정당 민노: 어려운 질문이고, 광범위하고 다소 추상적일 수 있는 질문입니다만, 지방소멸을 막거나 그 속도를 늦추고, 지역을 활성화하는 큰 과제에서 지역정당은 어떤 역할을 할 수 있다고 보십니까. 행인: 저에게는 그렇게 추상적이지 않아요. 왜냐하면 지역정당으로서 고민하지...
The post 지역소멸과 지역정당 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[위성정당, 정치가 아니라 게임을 하는 사람들]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102800</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102800"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T09:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[인터뷰] 1962년 군사정권이 기획한 헌법 8조와 정당법(62년 체제). 그 항체로서 지역정당의 의미에 관해 ‘행인’ 윤현식 박사가 말한다. 62년 체제를 넘어서 박정희 전두환 시절의 유령을 되살리다 민노: 앞서 지난 총선의 위성정당 사건을 언급하셨는데요. 따로 질문하려던 주제기도 하고요. 어떻게 평가하십니까. 행인: 제가 따로 평가하지 않아도 이미 사회적인 평가는 끝난 거 아니겠습니까. 민노: 저로선 이게 좀 아이러니하달까요. 현재처럼...
The post 위성정당, 정치가 아니라 게임을 하는 사람들 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[나팔새와 대깨문: 62년째 1962년 체제]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=100119</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/100119"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T09:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[62년 체제를 넘어서] 1962년 군사정권이 기획한 헌법 8조와 정당법(62년 체제). 그 항체로서 지역정당의 의미에 관해 ‘행인’ 윤현식 박사가 말한다. 62년 체제를 넘어서 일제의 폭압이 있었고, 미군정의 대리 통치가 있었으며, 반민특위의 좌절이 있었고, 60년 미완의 혁명이 있었으며, 5.16 쿠데타가 있었고, 72년의 유신이 있었으며, 10.26 정변이 있있고, ‘서울의 봄’을 짓밟은 12.12와 광주민주항쟁/학살이 있었다. 87년 대항쟁과 노동 대투쟁이...
The post 나팔새와 대깨문: 62년째 1962년 체제 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Next.js applications to OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>f04c49dd-821c-4044-b285-e35c1958e462</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/30/how-deploy-nextjs-applications-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift is a unified platform to build, modernize, and deploy applications at scale. OpenShift offers a great developer experience in shipping your applications to the cloud.
JavaScript is the most popular programming language in the world and is used by millions of developers around the world. While it’s one programming language, there are many popular frameworks within JavaScript that need different approaches.
In this series of articles, we are providing step-by-step guides to help you get up and running with JavaScript applications on OpenShift. For this tutorial, we expect you to have some familiarity with Next.js and Red Hat OpenShift. If you need a quick recap, check out these resources:
Video: Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift 
Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShif…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With Zephyr: Bluetooth Low Energy]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1630.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1630.php"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T02:52:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Overview
Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) is one of the most popular communication protocols for IoT devices. While it may share a name with Bluetooth Classic, which is the traditional Bluetooth technology, Bluetooth Low Energy is considered an entirely different technology and is targeted for different devices altogether. The key difference between Bluetooth Classic and BLE is duty...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세상에서 가장 우울한 나라와 그들의 특별한 회복력: 슬로우레터 1월30일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103132</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103132"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T22:01:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희만 빼고. 자식 잃은 어미‧아비들이 기어간다. 김건희 특검법 총선 이후에 표결한다. 쟁점과 현안. 민주당에 병립형이 최악의 선택인 이유. 이재명의 오랜 침묵. 한동훈의 프레임 전쟁. 더 깊게 읽기. “김부겸이 비대위원장을 맡아야 한다.” 만약 국민의힘이 이긴다면? 다르게 읽기. 세상에서 가장 우울한 나라. “정신과 폐쇄병동, 청소년들로 꽉 차 있다”. 오늘의 TMI. 스팸 가장 많이 보내는 나라는 튀니지. 부동산...
The post 세상에서 가장 우울한 나라와 그들의 특별한 회복력: 슬로우레터 1월30일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blue/green deployment strategy with Argo Rollouts]]></title>
        <id>fb4ee101-43df-4314-98ae-683b7cf743db</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/29/bluegreen-deployment-strategy-argo-rollouts"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T20:12:45.981Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical topic in cloud-native applications is the deployment strategy. We are no longer dealing with one monolithic application. We have several applications that have dependencies on each other and also have other dependencies like brokers or databases.
Applications have their own life cycle, so we should be able to execute independent blue/green deployment. All the applications and dependencies will not change their version at the same time.
Another important topic in the cloud-native space is continuous delivery. If we are going to have several applications doing blue/green deployment independently, we have to automate it. We will use Helm, Argo Rollouts, Red Hat OpenShift GitOps, and, of course, Red Hat OpenShift to help us.
Argo Rollouts is a Kubernetes controller and set of Custom…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>David Severiano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The developer's guide to Kubernetes Operators]]></title>
        <id>255cb02a-1ee0-4983-b4bf-2f338ca14c96</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/29/developers-guide-kubernetes-operators"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T20:12:45.980Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Operators are constructed from different parts and components. This cross-referenced guide will list components you need to know to get started developing operators using the Operator Framework. You'll find a handy list of the links used at the end.
 

NoteNote
Excerpts in this guide are in Go. Tools used are part of the Operator Framework.
What is an Operator?
An Operator—aka a Kubernetes-native application—is software running and configured in a Kubernetes-based cluster, adhering to the Operator Pattern. We can write operators in any language Kubernetes has a client for. The Operator Framework offers two SDKs: Operator SDK for Go and Java Operator SDK for Java.
An operator typically describes an API and configures a manager to run controllers. Operators are deployed like any o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tomer Figenblat</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Defining the Rust 2024 edition]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958792/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958792/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T17:22:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[for inclusion in the 2024 edition. Rust handles
backward incompatible changes by using
Editions,
which permit projects to specify a single stable edition for their code
and allow libraries written
in different editions to be linked together. Proposals for Rust 2024 are
now in, and have until the end of February to be debated and decided on. Once
the proposals are accepted, they have until May to be implemented in time for
the 2024 edition to be released in the second half of the year.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959882/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959882/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T16:04:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (gstreamer-plugins-bad-free, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, kernel, LibRaw, python-pillow, and xorg-x11-server), Debian (gst-plugins-bad1.0, libspreadsheet-parsexlsx-perl, mariadb-10.3, and slurm-wlm), Fedora (atril, dotnet8.0, gnutls, prometheus-podman-exporter, python-jinja2, sudo, and vips), Oracle (frr, kernel, php:8.1, python-urllib3, python3.9, rpm, sqlite, and tomcat), Slackware (pam), SUSE (cpio, rear23a, rear27a, sevctl, and xorg-x11-server), and Ubuntu (exim4 and firefox).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Motley Fool, 새로운 강세장을 이끌 인공지능(AI) 주식 3가지]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593663</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593663/%ec%9d%b8%ea%b3%b5%ec%a7%80%eb%8a%a5ai-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%ec%b6%94%ec%b2%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T14:50:45.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아이디어 발상법 ‘브레인스토밍(brainstorming)’을 대신하는 ‘브레인라이팅(brainwriting)’]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593658</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593658/%eb%b8%8c%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b8%ec%8a%a4%ed%86%a0%eb%b0%8dbrainstorming%ec%9d%84-%eb%8c%80%ec%8b%a0%ed%95%98%eb%8a%94-%eb%b8%8c%eb%a0%88%ec%9d%b8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b4%ed%8c%85brainwriting"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:17:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[퇴사 전, 퇴사계획서 작성이 중요한 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593655</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593655/%ed%87%b4%ec%82%ac-%ea%b3%84%ed%9a%8d%ec%84%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T10:39:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F# 연립 합동방정식과 중국인 나머지 정리]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15200259</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/15200259"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T07:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[앞서 선형 합동식의 해를 찾는 것을 학습했다. 또한 모듈러 연산에서의 곱셉 역원을 찾는 방법을 확인했다. 
예를 들어 ax ≡ b (mod n) 를 만족하는 선형합동식 중, 특히 b 가 1인 상황이라면 a * a^-1 ≡ 1(mod n)을 찾는 것을 곱셈에 대한 역원이라고 한다. 이 역원을 찾는 방법은 (0..n-1)에 대하여 전수조사를 해도 되지만, 확장 유클리드 알고리즘을 사용하면 쉽게 찾을 수 있다. 
선형 합동식이 한개만 있으면 쉽게 찾을 수 있지만, 만약 식이 여러개라면 어떨까? 중국에서는 3세기 후반 혹은 4세기 초반 즈음에 <손자산경>이라는 수학책에 다음의 내용이 나온다고 알려져 있다. (참고: 중국인 나머지 정리)

우리는 몇 개의 물건을 가지고 있는데, 정확히 몇 개인지 모른다. 만일 이들을 세 개씩 묶어서 세면 두 개가 남고, 다섯 개씩 묶어 세면 세 개가 남고, 일곱 개씩 묶어 세면 두 개가 남는다. 과연 몇 개가 있을까?

즉, 이는 다음과 같은 연립 합동 방정식의 해를 찾으라는 뜻이다.
여기서 x는 위 3개의 합동식을 모두 만족해야 한다. 
나무위키의 풀이 설명을 보면 다음과 같다.
답은 23인데, 이는 가장 작은 값이고 실제로는 23 + 105k (단 k >=0) 인 형태의 값들이 모두 답이 될 수 있다. 만약 문제에서 500~600 사이로 정했다면, k=5일 때 23 + 525 = 548  이 답이 될 것이다. 
이 풀이법은 어떻게 나온 것인지를 정리한 내용이다. (출처: 한빛수학교재연구소, "정수론 첫걸음", 173page)
이 공식은 해가 존재하며, 유일한 해를 갖는다는 것이 증…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘장바구니 물가 상승’이나 ‘손실 회피 성향’이라고만 넘길 수 없는 것들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78631</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/29/npsp_inflationsnickers/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_inflationsnickers"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T06:30:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[거시경제 지표와 사람들이 체감하는 경기 사이의 간극에 관해 썼던 글에서 경제학자들이 예로 드는 각종 지표가 물론 경제 전반을 충실히 그려내고 담아낸 숫자지만, 사람들이 현실을 팍팍하다고 느끼는 데도 여전히 일리가 있다는 점을 살펴봤습니다. 이번에는 UBS 글로벌 자산관리 부문 수석 경제학자 폴 도노번이 주제를 좀 더 좁혀 치솟는 물가에 대한 소비자들의 인식 이면에 어떤 기제가 작동하는지 살펴보는 글을 썼습니다. 글을 번역하고, 해설을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 그들이 왜 화났냐고요? 스니커즈 바를 예로 들어 봅시다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[옷, 이제 더 사지 않기로 하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103091</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103091"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T05:59:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, [정부가 없다] 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기…. 오늘 달릴 곳은 ‘패스트 패션’, ‘노동자 착취’, ‘패션산업과 환경’입니다. 오늘 ‘마냐의 북라이딩’에서 소개할 책은 이소연의 [옷을 사지 않기로 했습니다] (2023. 11.)입니다. 이 책은 “패션업계 안팎의 현실에 관한 고백뿐만 아니라 저자의 딜레마와 노하우도 두루 담겨 있어, 스타일과 환경 보호를 나란히 추구하려는...
The post 옷, 이제 더 사지 않기로 하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.8-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959815/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959815/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T02:03:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.8-rc2 for testing.
"So go out and test. It's safe now. You trust me, right?"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes on Cruise's pedestrian accident]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/cruise-report/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/cruise-report/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is a set of notes on the Quinn Emanuel report on Cruise's handling of the 2023-10-02 accident where a Cruise autonomous vehicle (AV) hit a pedestrian, stopped, and then started moving again with the pedestrian stuck under the bottom of the AV, dragging the pedestrian 20 feet. After seeing some comments about this report, I read five stories on this report and then skimmed the report and my feeling is that the authors of four of the stories probably didn't read the report, and that people who were commenting had generally read stories by journalists who did not appear to read the source material, so the comments were generally way off base. As we previously discussed, it's common for summaries to be wildly wrong, even when they're summarizing a short paper that's easily read by laypeop…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agile and Waterfall as community norms]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8535</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/01/28/agile-and-waterfall-as-community-norms/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T23:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While rapidly evolving computer hardware has been a topic of frequent public discussion since the first electronic computer, it has taken over 40 years for the issue of rapidly evolving customer requirements to become a frequent topic of public discussion (thanks to the Internet). The following quote is from the Opening Address, by Andrew Booth, […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“우리가 알던 그 윤석열이 아니다”, 조선일보의 멘탈붕괴: 슬로우레터 1월29일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103062</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103062"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T22:11:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우리가 알던 그 윤석열이 아니다. 윤석열은 총선 승리에 별 관심 없다. 쟁점과 현안. ‘사법 농단’ 맞지만 결국은 무죄. 실버 포퓰리즘, 재원은 있나. 개혁신당과 개혁미래당. 더 깊게 읽기. 성별 격차가 커지고 있다. “미투는 과거와 미래의 싸움.” “부끄럽지 않기 위해 싸웠다.” 다르게 읽기. 10년 동안 25%밖에 안 오른 이유. 누가 대통령 귀에 엉터리 경제 이론을 속삭이나. 해법과...
The post “우리가 알던 그 윤석열이 아니다”, 조선일보의 멘탈붕괴: 슬로우레터 1월29일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two handy GDB breakpoint tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/01/28/</id>
        <link href="https://nullprogram.com/blog/2024/01/28/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T21:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past couple months I’ve discovered a couple of handy tricks for
working with GDB breakpoints. I figured these out on my own, and I’ve not
seen either discussed elsewhere, so I really ought to share them.
Continuable assertions
The assert macro in typical C implementations leaves a lot to be
desired, as does raise and abort, so I’ve suggested
alternative definitions that behave better under debuggers:

#define assert(c)  while (!(c)) __builtin_trap()
#define assert(c)  while (!(c)) __builtin_unreachable()
#define assert(c)  while (!(c)) *(volatile int *)0 = 0


Each serves a slightly different purpose but still has the most
important property: Immediately halt the program directly on the defect.
None have an occasionally useful secondary property: Optionally allow the
program to co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>null program</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeRTOS with Heap Protector]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40092</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/01/28/freertos-with-heap-protector/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T17:46:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The latest FreeRTOS V11 release introduces heap protection, which detects memory corruption during runtime. When enabled, the heap block pointers are obfuscated with an XOR operation and validated within the heap boundaries. This enhancement improves early detection of heap issues, although it only protects part of the heap management structure. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parsing Numbers At Compile Time with C++17, C++23, and C++26]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/constexpr-number-parsing-cpp23/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/constexpr-number-parsing-cpp23/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-28T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thanks to the powerful constexpr keyword and many enhancements in recent C++ standards, we can now perform a lot of computations at compile time. In this text, we’ll explore several techniques for parsing integers, including the “naive” approach, C++23, from_chars, std::optional, std::expected, and even some upcoming features in C++26.
But first… why would this even be needed?



     
    


While it may sound like a theoretical experiment, since C++11 we can shift more and more computations to compile-time. Here are some key areas and examples where constexpr can be beneficial:
Building lookup tables
Working with embedded resources (like fonts or bitmaps)
Parsing configuration strings
Regular Expressions at compile time
Working with bit flags and bits
UB program verification (constexpr c…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중대재해 처벌법, 빵집 사장님들을 설득하는 방법.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103041</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103041"/>
        <updated>2024-01-27T08:10:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[중대재해 처벌법이 시행된 건 2년 전인 2022년 1월27일이다. 50인 미만 사업장은 2년 뒤부터 적용하기로 했는데 그게 바로 오늘이다. 국민의힘은 아직 준비가 되지 않았다며 2년을 더 미루자는 법안을 발의했지만 민주당 등의 동의를 얻지 못했고 드디어 오늘부터 5인 이상 사업장에 전면 적용된다. 그런데 반응이 왜 이래? 핵심은 이것이다. 프레임의 왜곡. 돌려 말할 것 없다. TMI. 헛소리에 맞서는...
The post 중대재해 처벌법, 빵집 사장님들을 설득하는 방법. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Tech Trends, plus 100 days to smart connected device law]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481367</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-tech-trends-plus-100-days-to-smart-connected-device-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T15:59:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my embedded diary this week, I look back at the Embedded Tech Trends 2024 conference, plus highlight news about the new UK smart device consumer protection law being enforced soon, and news from Infineon and GlobalFoundries, Microchip, Siemens, Morse Micro, Sondrel and EnOcean.
The post Embedded Tech Trends, plus 100 days to smart connected device law appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Better handling of integer wraparound in the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959189/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959189/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T15:41:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the mathematical realm of numbers is infinite, computers are only
able to represent a finite subset of them.  That can lead to problems when
arithmetic operations would create numbers that the computer is unable to
store as the intended type.  This condition, called "overflow" or
"wraparound" depending on the 
context, can be the source of bugs, including unpleasant security
vulnerabilities, so it is worth avoiding.  This patch
series from Kees Cook is intended to improve the kernel's handling of
these situations, but it is running into a bit of resistance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959640/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959640/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T14:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (xorg-server), Fedora (chromium, dotnet8.0, firefox, freeipa, and thunderbird), Red Hat (avahi, c-ares, curl, edk2, expat, freetype, frr, git, gnutls, grub2, kernel, kernel-rt, libcap, libfastjson, libssh, libtasn1, libxml2, linux-firmware, ncurses, oniguruma, openssh, openssl, perl-HTTP-Tiny, protobuf-c, python-urllib3, python3, python3.9, rpm, samba, shadow-utils, sqlite, tcpdump, tomcat, and virt:rhel and virt-devel:rhel modules), SUSE (cpio, jasper, rear23a, thunderbird, and xorg-x11-server), and Ubuntu (jinja2, kernel, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-gke,
 linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-hwe-5.15, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.15,
 linux-kvm, linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-raspi, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4,
 linux-bluefield, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4,
 linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4, linux-iot, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4,
 linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-6.2, linux-azure, linux-azure-6.2,
 linux-azure-fde-6.2, linux-gcp, linux-hwe-6.5, linux-laptop,
 linux-lowlatency, linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-oem-6.5, linux-oracle,
 linux-raspi, linux-starfive, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-hwe, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-4.15, linux-hwe,
 linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux, linux-aws, linux-kvm, linux-lts-xenial, linux-aws, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.15, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure-fde-5.15, linux-oem-6.1, and mariadb, mariadb-10.3, mariadb-10.6).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[중대재해처벌법, 소상공인 앞세워 ‘무논리’ 공포마케팅 나선 보수언론]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103037</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103037"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T13:22:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[중대재해처벌법이 1월 27일부터 노동자 5~49명의 소규모 사업장까지 확대 적용됩니다. 전국의 사업장 83만여 곳(전체 사업장의 24%)과 이들 사업장에서 일하는 800만여 명 노동자가 대상입니다. 노동계는 안전하게 일할 권리를 보장받는 노동존중 사회의 밑거름이 될 것이라고 기대를 내비쳤지만, 한국경영자총협회 등은 산재 취약 기업에 대한 지원 대책을 모색해야 한다고 밝혔습니다. 전과자 줄폐업 운운하며 ‘공포’ 조성하는 보수언론 중대재해처벌법은 중대한 인명 피해를...
The post 중대재해처벌법, 소상공인 앞세워 ‘무논리’ 공포마케팅 나선 보수언론 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국회의원 수 줄이면 오히려 특권만 커진다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103025</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103025"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T12:38:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[국회는 여러 기관들 가운데 국민들로부터 가장 신뢰받지 못하는 기관이다. 국회 신뢰 고작 24% 한국행정연구원이 펴낸 2022년 사회통합실태조사에서 국회는 고작 24.1%의 신뢰도를 받았다. 새로울 것은 없다. 국회는 늘 불신의 대상이었다. 그러나 2021년도 조사에비해서도 약 10%의 신뢰도 하락이 나타난 것은 지금의 국회가 본연의 역할을 수행하지 못하고 있는지를 잘 보여준다. 물론 국회에 대한 낮은 신뢰에 대해서 국회의원을 비롯한...
The post 국회의원 수 줄이면 오히려 특권만 커진다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘설마 전쟁 나겠어?’ 불감증 언론의 무심한 받아쓰기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=103017</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/103017"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T07:22:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[자본주의 체제 속의 대중매체는 제4부라고 호칭될 정도로 그 역할이 중요하다. 대중매체가 제대로 역할을 할 경우 민주주의를 보호, 확대하는 데 크게 기여할 수 있지만 그 역기능도 심각하다는 것을 경계해야 한다. 오늘날 한국 대중매체가 ‘기레기’ 비판을 받는 것은 그 책무를 다하지 못하고 있기 때문이다. 국가적 지표로 보면 한국이 선진국으로 진입해 사회 여러 분야의 민주주의 의식화가 진행되면서 그...
The post ‘설마 전쟁 나겠어?’ 불감증 언론의 무심한 받아쓰기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Community support for Spring Boot applications on OpenShift and RHEL]]></title>
        <id>07632d41-43d4-4c57-956b-699a7579e2a1</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/26/community-support-spring-boot-applications-openshift-and-rhel"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift and Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) customers deploying Spring Boot applications can now comfortably do so with Red Hat community support for Spring Boot. This is a step to ensure the user experience and adoption of runtimes on the OpenShift platform for the developer community. Red Hat also supports other runtimes such as Quarkus and Node.js, and has for many years provided container images for OpenJDK on RHEL and UBI.
The Red Hat product team has designed a new offering that lets customers use the community version of Spring Boot 3 without replacing the individual components with Red Hat supported components. Instead of providing Red Hat components for Spring Boot, which was the case for Red Hat support of Spring Boot 2, the new community support offering will focus on …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Shaaf, Syed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F# 모듈러 연산과 합동(congruence)]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16105526</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16105526"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T05:58:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[나머지
양의 정수 a, b가 있고, a를 b로 나눈 몫을 q, 나머지를 r라고 하자.
이는 곧 a = q*b + r 로 나타낼 수 있다. 초등학교에서는 r을 '나머지'라고 불렀다. 일반적으로 나머지는 나누는 수보다 작은 것으로 간주하여 0≤r<m로 가정했었다. 
초등학교에서는 양수만 고려했지만 이제 음수에 대해서도 생각해볼 수 있다. 예를 들어 -7 mod 12를 구하려면, -7 = 12*q+ r인 꼴로 표현하되 0≤r<12 인 것을 고르면 된다. q= -1, r=5 이면 가능하다. 그러므로 나머지는 5이다. 마찬가지로 -14 mod 5를 구하라고 하면, -14는 (-3) * 5 + 1 이므로 나머지가 1임을 알 수 있다. 
모듈로 연산
컴퓨터공학에서는 나머지를 구하고 싶을 때 모듈로 연산(modular arithmetic)을 사용한다. 즉, A mod B = R 이 된다. (몫 Q에 대해서는 특별히 신경쓰지 않는다)
모듈로 연산에는 다음과 같은 성질들이 존재한다.

덧셈: (A+B) mod C = (A mod C + B mod C) mod C
뺄셈: (A-B) mod C = (A mod C - B mod C) mod C
곱셈: (A*B) mod C = (A mod C * B mod C) mod C
거듭제곱: A^B mod C = ( (A mod C)^B ) mod C

특히, 암호학에서는 종종 매우 큰 수를 처리하게 되는데, 모듈러 거듭제곱 연산의 최적화를 통해 큰 수를 효율적으로 계산할 수 있다. 예를 들어 3^4 mod 5 은 3^4 가 81이 되는 것 정도는 쉽게 계산이 되므로 81 mod 5 = 1 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“엄마, 선생님이 내가 항상 맛이 갔대” 이럴 땐 어떻게 하면 좋을까요]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102551</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102551"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T05:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[인터뷰] ‘초3 가방 몰래 녹음기'(2024) 사건 판결에 교사단체는 찬성 입장을, 학부모단체는 반대 입장을 표했습니다. 내가 학부모였다면? 교사들께 물었습니다. 교사-학부모 갈등, ‘우리 아이’를 위해서 이제 풀어내야 합니다. “엄마, 선생님이 내가 항상 맛이 가 있대.” 학기 초 어느날, 학교에서 돌아온 초등학교 3학년 자녀가 ‘나에게’ 이렇게 말한다면, 여러분은 어떻게 하시겠습니까? 일단 침착하게… 여러 가능성을 생각해봅시다 나쁜 선생님일 수...
The post “엄마, 선생님이 내가 항상 맛이 갔대” 이럴 땐 어떻게 하면 좋을까요 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4분기 테슬라 실적]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593630</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593630/4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T05:41:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven new stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959509/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959509/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-26T00:22:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced the release of the 6.7.2, 6.6.14,
6.1.75, 5.15.148, 5.10.209, 5.4.268, and 4.19.306 stable kernels.  As usual, they
contain a long list of fixes throughout the kernel tree.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 기대한만큼 나쁘나 미래가 안보인다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593641</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593641/23%eb%85%84-4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%ed%85%8c%ec%8a%ac%eb%9d%bc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T23:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[빨라진 레임덕 시계, “윤석열의 김건희 사랑은 진심이었다”: 슬로우레터 1월26일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102977</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102977"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T22:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“사과 요구한 적 없다”고? “한동훈 잘한다”는 평가가 47%. ‘사랑꾼’ 윤석열만 남았다. 가장 큰 패자는 윤석열. 여름부터 낙엽이 진다. 사과하지 않고 선거를 치르면 어떻게 될 것 같은가. 쟁점과 현안. 또 정치 테러, 이번엔 배현진 피습. 외환위기도 아닌데 1.4% 성장률이라니. 다르게 읽기. “빵집 사장도 감옥 간다”는 공포 마케팅. GTX로 원주까지? 빨대 효과로 지방 소멸 앞당길 수도. 공판...
The post 빨라진 레임덕 시계, “윤석열의 김건희 사랑은 진심이었다”: 슬로우레터 1월26일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Off we go! Digging into the game engine of War Thunder and interviewing its devs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1098/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1098/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As Yuri Gagarin once said, "In the future, we will fly, we will fly a lot". To some extent, Gaijin's Dagor Engine makes these flights possible. Let's get a glimpse of the engine's innards and talk...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implement MLOps with Kubeflow Pipelines]]></title>
        <id>a2ae58f5-7c0b-45ea-a76a-91fb30ccd120</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/25/implement-mlops-kubeflow-pipelines"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T20:12:47.418Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MLOps, short for machine learning operations, is a set of practices and tools that combines DevOps principles applied to the development cycle of artificial intelligence applications.
Kubeflow Pipelines is an open source platform for implementing MLOps, providing a framework for building, deploying, and managing machine learning workflows in a scalable, repeatable, secure, and cloud-oriented manner on Kubernetes.
With the ability to drive agility and efficiency in the development and deployment of machine learning models, MLOps with Kubeflow Pipelines can also improve collaboration between data scientists and machine learning engineers, ensuring consistency and reliability throughout every step of the workflow.
MLOps
Created from the DevOps discipline, MLOps can be defined as a combination…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tarcisio Oliveira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network observability with eBPF on single node OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>1255f610-5f17-4953-aff4-1a835c2e879c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/25/network-observability-ebpf-single-node-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T20:12:47.416Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Network Observability Operator is GA (generally available) in Red Hat OpenShift 4.12. You can install it to get metrics about cluster networking, including a network topology graph of all namespaces on that cluster. You can view and monitor the network traffic data in different graphical representations. The Network Observability Operator uses eBPF technology to create the network flows.
Network Observability Operator provides many other metrics and network traffic measurements. You can find more details here.
This article demonstrates how to install and configure the Network Observability Operator on a single node OpenShift (SNO) cluster, based on the Red Hat OpenShift documentation. It includes details on configuring and using Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation storage external to the…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Lazhar Halleb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Android emulators, iOS simulators, and other product updates from Project IDX]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/project-idx-product-updates.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/project-idx-product-updates.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by the IDX team






Six months ago, we launched Project IDX, an experimental, cloud-based workspace for full-stack, multiplatform software development. We built Project IDX to simplify and streamline the developer workflow, aiming to reduce the sea of complexities traditionally associated with app development. It certainly seems like we've piqued your interest, and we love seeing what IDX has helped you build.
For example, we recently learned about Tanaki, an AI-enhanced content creation app built using Project IDX:





Pasquale D’Silva one of the developers that built Tanaki, said:
"Using the IDX shared workspace to build Tanaki has been so fun. It allows our remote team of imagineers to build together in one place. It is a magic collaboration portal!"
Developers at Google have …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving my Emacs experience with completion]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-emacs-completion.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/2024-emacs-completion.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T18:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve been using Emacs for many years, using it for any writing for my website, writing my books, and most of my programming. (Exceptions have been IntellJ IDEA for Java and RStudio for R.) As such I’ve been happy to see a lot of activity in the last few years to improve Emacs’s capabilities, making it feel rather less than a evolutionary dead end. One of the biggest improvements to my Emacs experience is using regexs for completion lists.
Many Emacs commands generate lists of things to pick from. I want to visit (open) a file I type the key combination to find a file, and Emacs pops up a list of candidate files in the minibuffer (a special area for to interact with commands). These file lists can be quite long, particularly should I ask for a list of all files in my current project.
To spe…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The things nobody wants to pay for]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959069/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959069/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The free-software community has managed to build a body of software that is
worth, by most estimates, many billions of dollars; all of this code is
freely available to anybody who wants to use or modify it.  It is an
unparalleled example of independent actors working cooperatively on a
common resource.  Free software is certainly a success story, but all is
not perfect.  One of the community's greatest strengths — convincing
companies to contribute to this common resource — is also part of one of
its biggest weaknesses.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GCC security features from AdaCore]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959461/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959461/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T15:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The AdaCore blog describes
some hardening features contributed to GCC for the GCC 14 release.


	With -fharden-control-flow-redundancy, the compiler now verifies,
	at the end of functions, whether the traversed basic blocks align
	with a legitimate execution path. The purpose of this protective
	measure is to detect and thwart attacks attempting to infiltrate
	the middle of functions, thereby enhancing the overall security
	posture of the compiled code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959455/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959455/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T14:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (chromium, firefox-esr, php-phpseclib, phpseclib, thunderbird, and zabbix), Fedora (dotnet7.0, firefox, fonttools, and python-jinja2), Mageia (avahi and chromium-browser-stable), Oracle (java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, LibRaw, openssl, and python-pillow), Red Hat (gnutls, kpatch-patch, php:8.1, and squid:4), SUSE (apache-parent, apache-sshd, bluez, cacti, cacti-spine, erlang, firefox, java-11-openjdk, opera, python-Pillow, tomcat, tomcat10, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (paramiko and puma).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[++i and i++ : what’s the difference?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1629.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1629.php"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T13:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A facet of the C language that has always appealed to me is its size - it is not a complex sprawling language. A thorough understanding of it can be gleaned quite quickly and many programmers actually use a very significant proportion of the language. Using it well is a challenge. The important thing is to write clear, understandable, maintainable code. Efficiency is very important for many...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4분기 넷플릭스 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선, 넷플릭스 목표주가 상향]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593632</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593632/4%eb%b6%84%ea%b8%b0-%eb%84%b7%ed%94%8c%eb%a6%ad%ec%8a%a4-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-3"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T11:42:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 2024년은 ‘덜지출 챌린지’ 계획해보면 어떨까요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78276</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/24/npsp_patagonia/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_patagonia"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T03:30:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 12월 4일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 매년 이맘때면 어김없이 나오는 멘트들이 있죠. “올해 달력도 벌써 마지막 장이네요.”, “숨 가쁘게 달려온 올 한 해, 어느덧 12월이네요.” 이런 말이 들리는 걸 보니, 1년을 마무리하는 시즌이 왔나 봅니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 25, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958597/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958597/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:23:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 25, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why do people post on [bad platform] instead of [good platform]?]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/why-video/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/why-video/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There's a class of comment you often see when someone makes a popular thread on Mastodon/Twitter/Threads/etc., that you also see on videos that's basically "Why would make a Twitter thread? This would be better as a blog post" or "Why make a video? This would be better as a blog post". But, these comments are often stronger in form, such as:
I can't read those tweets that span pages because the users puts 5 words in each reply. I find common internet completely stupid: Twitter, tiktok, Instagram, etc. What a huge waste of energy.
or
When someone chooses to blog on twitter you know it's facile at best, and more likely simply stupid (as in this case)
These kinds of comments are fairly common, e.g., I pulled up Foone's last 10 Twitter threads that scored 200 points or more on HN and 9 out of …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python, packaging, and pip—again]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959236/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959236/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:19:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python packaging discussions seem like they often just go around and
around, ending up where they started and recapitulating many of the points that
have come up before.  A recent discussion revolves around the pip package installer, as they
often do.  The central role that is occupied by pip has both
good points and bad. There is a clear need for something that
can install from the Python Package Index
(PyPI) immediately after Python itself is installed. Whether there
should be additional features, including project management, that come
"inside the box", as well, 
is much less clear—not unlike the question of which project management
"style" should be chosen.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 역린 건드린 김경율, 조선일보가 “감사패 줘야 한다”고 말한 이유: 슬로우레터 1월25일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102904</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102904"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T22:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우아함이란 구별과 자연스러움, 돌봄과 단순성이라는 네 가지의 바른 조합에서 만들어진다. 이를 벗어나면 가식만이 있을 뿐이다. “디올 핸드백이 한국을 뒤흔들었다.” 조선일보의 역습, “김경율에 감사패라도 줘라.” 겁나서 못하는 것 누가 모르겠나. 쟁점과 현안. 이준석이 ‘약속 대련’이라고 우기는 이유. ‘친윤’ 말고 ‘친한’이 뜬다. 중대재해법 50인 미만 사업장에도 확대 적용한다. 더 깊게 읽기. 다시 나온 병립형 카드. 해법과 대안....
The post 김건희 역린 건드린 김경율, 조선일보가 “감사패 줘야 한다”고 말한 이유: 슬로우레터 1월25일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scraping Prometheus metrics from Red Hat build of Keycloak]]></title>
        <id>efcb319d-0a5a-43e9-bf76-e6bf3c043cab</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/24/scraping-prometheus-metrics-red-hat-build-keycloak"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T20:13:37.760Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Observability is a crucial aspect of efficiently maintaining complex environments. It provides the capability to understand the internal state of the system by scraping runtime data. The collected data gives better view of the system at runtime and can be used to configure alerts and identify trends and insights about the element being monitored.
Prometheus is a widely used monitoring tool that scrapes data from configured targets using a pull-based approach. Prometheus expects the metric to be exposed in specific data exposition format. There are also projects like OpenMetrics, which aims to convert the Prometheus exposition format into a standard to help transmit metrics at scale.
In this article, we will see how we can scrape metrics from the newly released Red Hat build of Keycloak dep…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rishabh Singh</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How it's Made - Exploring AI x Learning through ShiffBot, an AI experiment powered by the Gemini API]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/how-its-made-learning-through-shiffbot-powered-by-gemini-api.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/how-its-made-learning-through-shiffbot-powered-by-gemini-api.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T17:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Jasmin Rubinovitz, AI Researcher






Google Lab Sessions is a series of experimental collaborations with innovators. In this session, we partnered with beloved creative coding educator and YouTube creator Daniel Shiffman. Together, we explored some of the ways AI, and specifically the Gemini API, could provide value to teachers and students during the learning process.
Dan Shiffman started out teaching programming courses at NYU ITP and later created his YouTube channel The Coding Train, making his content available to a wider audience. Learning to code can be challenging, sometimes even small obstacles can be hard to overcome when you are on your own. So together with Dan we asked - could we try and complement his teaching even further by creating an AI-powered tool that can h…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Onboarding bottleneck: creating a path to effectiveness]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html#exit</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html#exit"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T15:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tim and Premand begin their discussion of how to get out of the
       difficulties of onboarding by explaining how to create a path to
       effectiveness for new hires. Such a path outlines the needs of employee
       and how the onboarding process should fulfill them.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959325/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959325/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T14:46:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (jinja2, openjdk-11, ruby-httparty, and xorg-server), Fedora (ansible-core and mingw-jasper), Gentoo (GOCR, Ruby, and sudo), Oracle (gstreamer-plugins-bad-free, java-17-openjdk, java-21-openjdk, python-cryptography, and xorg-x11-server), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, LibRaw, python-pillow, and python-pip), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (python-Pillow, rear118a, and redis7), and Ubuntu (libapache-session-ldap-perl and pycryptodome).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘그리스인 조르바’를 읽고 잡낭을 장만한 까닭]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102896</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102896"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T09:54:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이튿날, 조르바의 목소리가 나를 깨웠다. “아니, 아침부터 웬 수선입니까? 그리고 이건 또 무슨 소리고요?” 내가 물었다. 그는 잡낭에다 음식을 꾸리면서 대답했다. “두목, 정신을 번쩍 차리고 일을 처리해야 할 땝니다. 벌써 노새 두 마리 몰아다 놓았어요. 일어나서 수도원으로 갑시다. 케이블 고가 선로 계약서에 서명을 받아야 합니다. 사자도 겁내는 게 하나 있는데 그게 바로 이(蝨)라는 놈이지요. 두목,...
The post ‘그리스인 조르바’를 읽고 잡낭을 장만한 까닭 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/24, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593615</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593615/1-24-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T06:53:12.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤 정부의 총선용 포퓰리즘 식단표: 감세 중심으로]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102865</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102865"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T02:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 정부가 민생정책이라는 이름으로 잇따라 다양한 정책을 내놓고 있으나 현실성 부족 등 여러 문제가 지적되고 있습니다. 특히 4.10 총선을 앞둔 포퓰리즘 정책 아니냐는 비판마저 나오는 상황입니다. 민주언론시민연합은 1월 15일부터 19일 사이 정부의 감세 정책을 중심으로 윤석열 정부의 정책 보도를 살펴봤습니다. 세수 감면 정책… 선심성 말잔치 세수감면 정책으로 세수가 줄면 재정 수입 감소가 불가피한데 대체 예산...
The post 윤 정부의 총선용 포퓰리즘 식단표: 감세 중심으로 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[몰려드는 이민자들, 미국 정치권이 해결할 수 있을까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78582</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/23/npsp_2024electionimmigration/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_2024electionimmigration"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T01:00:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이민자와 남부 국경 지역의 치안 문제는 2024년 미국 대선의 중요한 의제 중 하나가 될 것으로 보입니다. 특히 자신들이 이 문제에서 더 긍정적인 평가를 받는다고 믿는 트럼프 전 대통령과 그 지지자들은 계속해서 바이든 행정부의 대표적인 실정으로 이민 문제를 들먹일 가능성이 큽니다. 이민 문제가 심각한 건 맞지만, 그 잘못이 반드시 민주당에만 있다고 보긴 어렵습니다. 그러던 중 오바마와 바이든 행정부에서 이민 정책을 담당했던 안드레아 플로레스가 뉴욕타임스에 이민 문제를 근본적으로 해결하기 위한 노력에 관한 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Zephyr - Kconfig (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/practical_zephyr_kconfig</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/practical_zephyr_kconfig"/>
        <updated>2024-01-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second article of the “Practical Zephyr” series, we’ll explore the kernel configuration system Kconfig by looking at the printk logging option in Zephyr. We won’t explore the logging service as such in detail but instead use it as an excuse to dive deep into Kconfig. Finally, we’ll create our own little application-specific Kconfig configuration.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Microdot: a web framework for microcontrollers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959067/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959067/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T22:51:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many different Python web frameworks, from
nano-frameworks all the way up to the full-stack variety.  One that
recently caught my eye is Microdot, the
"impossibly small web framework for Python and MicroPython"; since
it 
targets MicroPython, it is
plausible for running the user 
interface of an "internet of things" (IoT) device, for example.  Beyond
that, it is Flask-inspired,
which should make it reasonably familiar to many potential web
developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[어떤 의제도 없는 저열한 정치, 이렇게 망가진 적은 없었다: 슬로우레터 1월24일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102824</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102824"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T22:07:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈의 폴더 인사가 의미하는 것. “불구경 왔나.” 봉합 열차, 레임덕이 시작됐나. 모든 언론이 사과를 요구하고 있다. 김경율은 “사퇴할 뜻 없다.” 쟁점과 현안. 미래 권력에 줄 서나, ‘친윤’의 침묵. 민주당은 ‘찐명’ 인증 경쟁. 더 깊게 읽기. 이렇게 망가진 적은 없었다. 연봉 두 배를 주식으로, 한화 김동관의 RSU. 다르게 읽기. 윤석열 거부권 남용, 탄핵 사유 될까. 이거...
The post 어떤 의제도 없는 저열한 정치, 이렇게 망가진 적은 없었다: 슬로우레터 1월24일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How do you select an RTOS?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481364</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-do-you-select-an-rtos/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T16:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s common to choose an RTOS only to discover after a few months or quarters that it isn’t quite meeting your expectations. Real-time operating systems...
The post How do you select an RTOS? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Understanding open source security risks in IoT applications]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481360</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/understanding-open-source-security-risks-in-iot-applications/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T16:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The use of open source in the IoT raises a host of security challenges that requires a comprehensive security strategy. The Internet of Things (IoT)...
The post Understanding open source security risks in IoT applications appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Gilad David Maayan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 122.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959163/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959163/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T16:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
122.0 of the Firefox browser it out.  Changes include improved search
suggestions, improvements to the in-browser
translation feature, better line-breaking compatibility, and a shiny
new .deb package.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959127/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959127/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T14:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (kodi and squid), Fedora (ansible-core, java-latest-openjdk, mingw-python-jinja2, openssh, and pgadmin4), Gentoo (Apache XML-RPC), Red Hat (gnutls and xorg-x11-server), Slackware (postfix), SUSE (bluez and openssl-3), and Ubuntu (gnutls28, libssh, and squid).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bottlenecks of  Scaleups #06: Onboarding]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/bottlenecks-of-scaleups/06-onboarding.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last year has been a hard one for the technology industry, which
      faced its greatest waves of cutbacks and layoffs since the dotcom crash at
      the beginning of the century. As 2024 begins, we're seeing the early signs of a
      turn-around, which hopefully means technology organizations will soon be thinking of
      hiring again. Should such happy days return, firms will again run into
      the common problem of
      taking too long for new hires to become effective. Tim
      Cochran and Premanand Chandrasekaran address this in the sixth part of our
      series on the bottlenecks of scaleups. In this first installment, Tim and Prem
      look the signs that a growing organization is running into this bottleneck.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Speed up Java application startup time with AppCDS]]></title>
        <id>f5d600b4-8e6d-421c-a17c-b922b0674e37</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/23/speed-java-application-startup-time-appcds"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application startup time for OpenJDK apps can be important for cloud use cases. Start/stop cycles are much more frequent for an application deployed in Kubernetes since configuration changes usually result in a new deployment—a.k.a restart—of the application. Oftentimes, changing something as simple as an environment variable results in redeployments. The time it takes until the application is ready to handle requests matters. In this article, we’ll show how application class data sharing (AppCDS) can help reduce startup time of your Java application.
In our example, we achieve a startup time as low as ~440 milliseconds or ~47% faster than the corresponding startup time without AppCDS. The actual numbers will vary depending on the precise deployment and resource configuration in use as wel…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Severin Gehwolf</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/23, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593584</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593584/1-23-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-23T03:25:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사과해도 괜찮아, 조선일보의 조언에 담긴 보수 진영의 분노: 슬로우레터 1월23일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102765</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102765"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T22:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[실세는 김건희, ‘약속 대련’은 아니었다. “내 임기는 총선 이후까지다.” “눈에 넣어도 아프지 않을 후배였다.” 생방송 30분 전에 펑크. 사과하지 않을 거라고 보는 이유. 조선일보 말 안 듣는 보수 대통령. 쟁점과 현안. 마트 휴업 규제 12년 만에 푼다. 단통법도 10년 만에 폐지? 다르게 읽기. 이래서 주가 끌어올릴 수 있겠나. 세 가지 통상 리스크. 더 깊게 읽기....
The post 사과해도 괜찮아, 조선일보의 조언에 담긴 보수 진영의 분노: 슬로우레터 1월23일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing SAST into the development process]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1097/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1097/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattacks on applications are on the rise, and zero-day vulnerability exploitation is leading the way. Introducing SAST into the development process makes the product safer for users. However, for...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The rest of the 6.8 merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958178/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958178/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:20:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus Torvalds was able to release 6.8-rc1
and close the 6.8 merge window on time despite losing power to his home for
most of a week.  He noted that this merge window is "maybe a bit smaller
than usual", but 12,239 non-merge changesets found their way into the
mainline, so it's not that small.  About 8,000 of those changes were
merged since the first-half summary was
written; the second half saw a lot of device-driver updates, but there
were other interesting changes as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[강원도형 최저임금, 기업천국? 게토화 위험 크다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102623</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102623"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T17:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)이 전하는 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기… 지난주 금요일 오전 8시엔 ‘기업천국’ 간판을 단 ‘강원도형 최저임금’에 관해 물었다. 강원연구원이 2024년 새해 첫 보고서로 ‘강원도형 최저임금 제도가 필요하다’를 발표했다. 2023년 9월에 기업천국 세미나에서 사용한 발제와 토론을 정리한 작은 책자다. 보고서는 다른 지역보다 낮은 강원도형 최저임금을 통해 자원 배분의 효율성을 높이고, 기업...
The post 강원도형 최저임금, 기업천국? 게토화 위험 크다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/959006/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/959006/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T14:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (keystone and subunit), Fedora (dotnet6.0, golang, kernel, sos, and tigervnc), Mageia (erlang), Red Hat (openssl), SUSE (bluez, python-aiohttp, and seamonkey), and Ubuntu (postfix and xorg-server).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지주회사의 마법, 윤석민 일가는 어떻게 SBS를 장악했나.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102686</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102686"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T08:22:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] SBS의 눈물, 방송 사유화의 가장 안 좋은 결말. “태영이 이대로 무너지면 협력업체들 줄 도산을 피할 수 없다. 국가 경제 위기의 불씨가 될 수 있다.” 지난 3일 태영건설 채권자 설명회에서 윤세영(태영그룹 창업회장)의 말은 언뜻 협박처럼 들렸다. 워크아웃을 신청한 건설사 경영진이 이렇게 당당한 건 본 적이 없다. 다음은 뉴스토마토 이원재의 ‘끝내주는 경제’에서 태영건설과 SBS의 지난 35년을...
The post 지주회사의 마법, 윤석민 일가는 어떻게 SBS를 장악했나. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Convert CentOS Linux to RHEL using Red Hat Insights]]></title>
        <id>ff32cd5a-3c01-477d-9ebc-a54847644345</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/22/convert-centos-linux-rhel-using-red-hat-insights"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On June 30, 2024, CentOS Linux 7 will reach its end-of-life (EOL), marking the conclusion of official support and security updates. This development has prompted organizations and users relying on CentOS 7 to seek alternative solutions to ensure ongoing security and support. One prevalent and strategic choice is migrating from CentOS 7 to Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL). The transition to RHEL is advantageous for several reasons, including continued access to regular security patches, extended support, and a robust ecosystem of tools and features. By converting to RHEL, organizations can maintain a stable and secure operating environment while aligning with a long-term, commercially supported Linux distribution.
Using Red Hat Insights to convert CentOS 7 to RHEL
In this tutorial, we'll use…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nikhil Mungale</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘트럼프 대세론’ 굳혀줄 부통령 후보는 누구일까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78566</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/22/npsp_trumpveep/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_trumpveep"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T05:00:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[아이오와 코커스에서 낙승을 거둔 도널드 트럼프 전 대통령이 공화당 대통령 후보를 향한 대세론 굳히기에 들어갔습니다. 몇 시간 전 론 드산티스 플로리다 주지사마저 경선에서 사퇴하며, 트럼프를 지지한다고 선언했습니다. 모레 치러지는 뉴햄프셔 프라이머리에서 니키 헤일리 전 UN 대사가 얼마나 선전할지가 변수가 될 수 있겠지만, 2024년 미국 대선은 이변이 없는 한 바이든 대 트럼프의 리턴 매치가 될 가능성이 커 보입니다. 경선에서 후보가 정해지고 나면, 미국에선 대통령과 짝을 이뤄 출마하는 부통령 후보가 누가 될지가 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고니는요, 사람 하기 나름이에요]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102673</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102673"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T03:43:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[일본 효고현 도요오카시(인구 7.4만, 2023. 12. 현재)로 여행을 다녀온 적이 있다. 9년 전인 2015년 2월이었다. 도요오카시는 멸종됐던 황새를 민관이 힘을 합해 야생에서 복원해 낸 일본 으뜸 생태도시로 꼽힌다. 황새를 보러 갔던 그 도시에서 나는 고니도 보았다. 도요오카에서 보았던 일본 고니 우리는 이른 아침에 주택가를 걸어서 지나가는 중이었다. 아스콘으로 포장된 도로가 깔끔하게 뻗어 있었다. 우리나라와 달리...
The post 고니는요, 사람 하기 나름이에요 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.8-rc1]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958945/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958945/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-22T00:47:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.8-rc1 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.


	So this wasn't the most pleasant merge window, but most of the
	unpleasantness was entirely unrelated to the code base and almost
	entirely related to nasty weather. Just a few technical
	hiccups. And after a very big 6.7 release, 6.8 looks to actually be
	smaller than average, although not really all that significantly
	so.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How did Agile become the product development zeitgeist?]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8523</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/01/21/how-did-agile-become-the-product-development-zeitgeist/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T23:10:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[From the earliest days of computing, people/groups have proposed software development techniques, and claiming them to be effective/productive ways of building software systems. Agile escaped this well of widely unknowns to become the dominant umbrella term for a variety of widely used software development methodologies (I’m talking about the term Agile, not any of the […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[주말 사이에 벌어진 일, 김건희 지키려 한동훈 버리나: 슬로우레터 1월22일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102637</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102637"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T22:04:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열-한동훈 벌써 갈라서나. 윤석열이 한동훈 지지를 철회했다고? 김건희 사과가 쟁점. 납작 엎드린 김경율. 쟁점과 현안. 김건희 출구 전략이 ‘김치찌개’ 점심? 배짱 튕기는 이준석. 여야 모두 꼼수 위성정당 만드나. 더 깊게 읽기. 총선 전망, ‘족집게’에게 물어봤다. 기업들이 검사를 모셔가는 이유. 재정적자 내년이 더 걱정이다. 다르게 읽기. “위험한 일탈”이라는 한국일보. “정신 바짝 차릴 때”라는 한겨레. “정치 경호‧뒷북...
The post 주말 사이에 벌어진 일, 김건희 지키려 한동훈 버리나: 슬로우레터 1월22일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using GPIO in (Apache) NuttX RTOS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1623.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1623.php"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T16:34:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the previous article (https://embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1610.php) we saw how to compile and run NuttX on three low cost boards (RaspberryPi Pico, ESP32-Devkit and STM32F4Discovery). Today we will see how to use GPIO pins and read and write logic level signals from/to the MCU pins.


Everybody knows that blinking a LED is the "Hello World" program of embedded system engineer....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[은퇴자 배당주 투자, 배당주 선정 체크리스트]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593577</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593577/%eb%b0%b0%eb%8b%b9%ec%a3%bc-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90-%eb%b0%b0%eb%8b%b9%ec%a3%bc-%ec%84%a0%ec%a0%95-%ec%b2%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a6%ac%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T11:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[반도체 장비주, ASML 투자의견 및 ASML 주가 전망(1/20 업뎃)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593568</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593568/asml-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-asml-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T01:47:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/20, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593549</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593549/1-20-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-21T01:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some weekend stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958860/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958860/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T17:00:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.7.1,
6.6.13, and
6.1.74
stable kernel updates have been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[embedded diary: Synopsys to acquire Ansys for $35 billion]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481347</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-diary-synopsys-to-acquire-ansys-for-35-billion/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T12:53:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the last week's news, including Synopsys' announcing it is acquiring Ansys, plus new and products from Renesas Electronics, ROHM Group, FRAMOS, and POLYN Technology.  
The post embedded diary: Synopsys to acquire Ansys for $35 billion appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[2023, Year in review]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/01/20/2023-in-review.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/01/20/2023-in-review.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-20T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It should come as no surprise that a blog with no
advertisements has never
paid my bills–at least not directly.  I blog for fun, and to some extent for
rubber duck debugging.
As I learn new concepts, I enjoy sharing them here.  Going through the rigor
to write about a topic also helps to make sure I understand the topic as well.
Why are there no
advertisements?  For
two reasons.  First, because I’m not doing this to make money.  Second, because
because I want more control over any advertising from this site than
most advertisers want to provide.  Perhaps some day the site will be supported
by advertising.  Until then, the web site works fine without advertisements.
So how then does the blog fit into my business model?  Simply because the blog
helps me find customers via those who read arti…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Sneak Peek at the 2024 Embedded Online Conference]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1626.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1626.php"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T21:27:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The embedded systems industry is evolving at a rapid pace. Just a few years ago, most embedded products were disconnected systems that used bare-metal scheduling techniques. Today, the drive to connect devices and add intelligence at the edge is revolutionizing how we build embedded products. The only way to stay current and not get left behind is to learn and network with colleagues and...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SourceHut outage post-mortem]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958794/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958794/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[of its
outage earlier this month.
The post-mortem covers the causes of the outage and what steps SourceHut
took to mitigate it, ending by saying:



    As unfortunate as these events were, we welcome opportunities to stress-test
    our emergency procedures; we found them to be compatible with our objectives
    for the alpha and we learned a lot of ways to improve our reliability
    further for the future. We are going to continue working on our
    post-incident tasks, building up our infrastructure’s resilience,
    reliability, and scalability as planned. Once we address the high-priority
    tasks, though, our first order of business in the immediate future will be
    to get some rest.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Jujutsu: a new, Git-compatible version control system]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958468/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958468/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T20:15:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Jujutsu is a Git-compatible
distributed version control system originally started as a hobby project by
Martin von Zweigbergk in 2019. It is intended to be a simpler, more performant
Git replacement. Jujutsu boasts a radically simplified user interface and integrates
ideas from patch-based version control systems for a novel take on resolving
merge conflicts. It is written in Rust and available under an Apache 2.0 license.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Mills RIP]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958781/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958781/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T16:39:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet pioneer and Network Time Protocol (NTP) inventor Dave Mills has died, as reported by Vint Cerf:

His daughter, Leigh, just sent me the news that Dave passed away peacefully
on January 17, 2024. He was such an iconic element of the early Internet.
Network Time Protocol, the Fuzzball routers of the early NSFNET, INARG
taskforce lead, COMSAT Labs and University of Delaware and so much more.


More information about Mills can be found on his Wikipedia page.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] mseal() gets closer]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958438/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958438/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T15:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proposed mseal() system call
stirred up some controversy when it was first posted in October 2023.
Since then, it has been evolving in a quieter fashion, and seems to have
reached a point where the relevant commenters are willing to accept it.
Should mseal() be merged in a future development cycle, it will
look rather different than it did at the outset.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clarifying Misunderstandings of Slowroll (openSUSE News)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958759/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958759/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T14:56:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE News site has put up a
brief article on how Slowroll fits into the spectrum of openSUSE
distributions.


	The idea behind Slowroll is to offer a distribution that improves
	stability without losing access to new features in the base
	packages such as the kernel, desktop environments and
	packaging. These slower update cycles allow for more extensive
	testing and validation of packages before their inclusion. Think of
	Slowroll as more of a skip than a Leap.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958760/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958760/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T14:55:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (chromium, golang-github-facebook-time, podman, and xorg-x11-server-Xwayland), Oracle (.NET 6.0, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, and python3.11-cryptography), Red Hat (java-11-openjdk, python-requests, and python-urllib3), SUSE (chromium, kernel, libcryptopp, libuev, perl-Spreadsheet-ParseExcel, suse-module-tools, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (filezilla and xerces-c).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[디지털 인형 눈 붙이기: AI는 자원과 노동을 잠식한다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102586</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102586"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T06:45:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[마냐의 북라이딩] 북살롱 목요일 언니, 청와대 국민청원 기획자, 얼룩소 설립자, [정부가 없다] 저자 정혜승의 종횡무진 독서 탐험기…. 오늘 책을 싣고 달릴 곳은 ‘AI와 노동’, ‘AI와 자원’, ‘AI와 불평등’입니다. 오늘 ‘마냐의 북라이딩’ 책은 케이트 크로퍼드의 [AI 지도책]입니다. 저자는 네바다의 리튬 광산, 시카고 도축장, 서부의 로켓 기지, 파우아뉴기니의 산악 마을, 아마존 창고와 데이터 센터에서 AI가 실제로 어떻게 만들어지고 있는지...
The post 디지털 인형 눈 붙이기: AI는 자원과 노동을 잠식한다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “인류를 위한 인공지능” 누가, 어떻게 할 것인가?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78255</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/19/npsp_openai/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_openai"/>
        <updated>2024-01-19T04:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 11월 29일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. *** 이번 해설은 뉴욕대학교 컴퓨터과학과 조경현 교수가 아메리카노에서 정리한 인터뷰를 바탕으로 썼습니다. 지난 17일부터 22일까지 닷새간 오픈AI의 CEO 샘 알트만이 갑자기 해고됐다가 복귀하는 과정은 하루하루, 매 순간이 마치 한 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열과 악수하다 끌려나간 국회의원, 신문 1면에는 없다: 슬로우레터 1월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102563</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102563"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T22:03:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대통령과 악수하다 끌려나간 국회의원. 저출생 공약 쏟아졌지만. 쟁점과 현안. “국민들 걱정할 부분 있다.” 프레임 전쟁. 끝나지 않는 조국 수사, 하나 더 얹었다. “민주당 총선 승리 기준은 151석.” “이 나라에 살 수 없습니다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 무임승차 폐지, 서 있는 곳에 따라 달리 보인다. 해법과 대안. 1000원의 아침밥, 계속 갈 수 있을까. 빅 5와 공생하는 항암...
The post 윤석열과 악수하다 끌려나간 국회의원, 신문 1면에는 없다: 슬로우레터 1월19일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Villa: Will the new judicial ruling in the Vizio lawsuit strengthen the GPL?]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958682/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958682/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T19:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Luis Villa writes
about the recent ruling in the Software Freedom Conservancy's
GPL-violation lawsuit against Vizio, wherein the judge refused to agree
that the SFC lacks standing to sue.


	In some sense, not much has changed: if you were obligated to
	comply with the GPL two weeks ago, you have the same obligations
	today. If you didn’t have obligations then, you don’t have them
	now.

	What has changed is who can enforce those obligations. Two weeks
	ago, we mostly believed that enforcement could only come from the
	authors of the code. Those folks rarely had time, money, or
	interest for litigation, and they might also face a lot of pressure
	from their peers and employers to avoid litigation.

	If this ruling holds up at the end of the case, the number of
	potential enforcers just went way up.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Improved code generation in the CPython JIT]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958350/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958350/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:57:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Faster CPython 
project has been working on
taking Python's 
recently-added just-in-time (JIT) compiler 
further by adding 
support for a peephole optimizer 
that rewrites the JIT's intermediate representation to introduce 
constant folding, type specialization, and other optimizations.
Those techniques should provide significant benefits for the
performance of many different types of code running on CPython.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958676/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958676/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:41:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (ImageMagick), Debian (chromium), Fedora (golang-x-crypto, golang-x-mod, golang-x-net, golang-x-text, gtkwave, redis, and zbar), Mageia (tinyxml), Oracle (.NET 7.0, .NET 8.0, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, python3, and sqlite), Red Hat (gstreamer-plugins-bad-free, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, java-17-openjdk, and java-21-openjdk), SUSE (kernel, libqt5-qtbase, libssh, pam, rear23a, and rear27a), and Ubuntu (pam and zookeeper).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HealthPulse AI Leverages MediaPipe to Increase Health Equity]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/healthpulse-ai-leverages-mediapipe-to-increase-health-equity.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/healthpulse-ai-leverages-mediapipe-to-increase-health-equity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A guest post by Rouella Mendonca, AI Product Lead and Matt Brown, Machine Learning Engineer at Audere
  






Please note that the information, uses, and applications expressed in the below post are solely those of our guest authors from Audere.
  
  


About HealthPulse AI and its application in the real world
Preventable and treatable diseases like HIV, COVID-19, and malaria infect ~12 million per year globally with a disproportionate number of cases impacting already underserved and under-resourced communities1. Communicable and non-communicable diseases are impeding human development by their negative impact on education, income, life expectancy, and other health indicators2. Lack of access to timely, accurate, and affordable diagnostics and care is a key contributor to high mortality…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A major revision of Continuous Integration]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/continuousIntegration.html</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/continuousIntegration.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T15:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the turn of the century, I was lucky to involved in several
       projects that developed the practice of Continuous Integration. I wrote
       up our lessons from this work in article on my website, where it
       continues to be a oft-referenced resource for this important practice.
       Late last year a colleague contacted me to say that the article, now
       nearly twenty years old, was still useful, but was showing its age. He
       sent me some suggested revisions, and I used this as a trigger to do a
       thorough revision of the article, considering every section in the
       original, and adding new ones to deal with issues that have appeared in the last
       two decades.
During those decades Feature Branching has been widely adopted in the
       industry. Many colleagues of mine feel that Continuous Integration is a
       better fit for many teams, I hope this article will help readers assess
       if this is the case, and if so, how to implement Continuous Integration
       effectively.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, TSMC 실적 전망은 엔비디아에 긍정적 신호를 준다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593546</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593546/tsmc-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T12:12:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WSJ, 오디오 스트리밍을 장악한 스포티파이, 이익은 낼 수 있을까?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593543</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593543/%ec%8a%a4%ed%8f%ac%ed%8b%b0%ed%8c%8c%ec%9d%b4-%eb%b6%84%ec%84%9d"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T11:12:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[F# 확장된 유클리드(Extended Euclidean) 알고리즘 이용한 선형방정식 풀이]]></title>
        <id>https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16054457</id>
        <link href="https://cpuu.postype.com/post/16054457"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T07:56:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개요
앞서, 유클리드 호제법(Euclidean algorithm) 이용한 최대공약수, 최소공배수 계산 하는 방법을 배웠다. 유클리드 알고리즘을 이용하면 최대공약수(gcd)를 빠르게 구할 수 있다.
한편, a와 b가 0이 아닌 정수이고, g = gcd(a, b)에 대하여
ax + by = g를 만족하는 정수해(x1, y1)이 항상 존재한다. 
이때의 x1, y1을 찾기 위한 방법에서 유클리드 알고리즘을 거꾸로 활용할 수 있으며 이를 확장된 유클리드 호제법(Extended Euclidean) 이라고 한다.



설명
가장 이해가 쉬운 예시는 한빛수학교재연구소에서 번역한 Kuldeep Singh의 정수론 첫걸음(Number Theory step by step)의 49페이지 설명인 것 같아서 첨부해둔다.
5291x + 3108y = gcd(5291, 3108)의 정수해를 찾는 과정이다. 
우선 5291과 3108의 최대공약수를 찾기 위해 다음과 같이 유클리드 알고리즘을 사용한다. 뒤에 설명할 편의를 위해 식에 번호를 붙였다.
(6)을 통해 얻은 결과 0이 아닌 마지막 나머지인 37이 두 수(5291, 3108)의 최대공약수가 된다.
이때 5291x + 3108y = 37 을 만족하는 두 수 x, y 를 찾아야 한다.
이 과정은 (1) ~ (6) 을 거꾸로 활용하여 찾아간다. 기본적으로 값을 치환한 뒤 항을 넘겨서 동류항끼리 정리하는 과정이다.
이를 통해 최종적으로 63 * 3108 - 37 * 5291 이라는 식을 계산하면 37으로 만들 수 있다. 
그러면 5201x + 3108y = 37이었으므로, x = -37, y = 63 이라는 것을 알 수 있다. 
기타 다른 해로는 (-121,206), (47, -80) 도 있다. 
이러한 해를 더 찾을 때는 다음 공식에 정수값 k를 대입하여 찾을 수 있다.
즉, a, b에 대하여 gcd는 37임을 알았고, x1 = -37, y1 = 63 을 찾았으므로 
( -37 + k*3108/37 , 63 - k*5291/37) =  (-37 + 84k, 63 - 143k)라는 것을 알게 된다. k에 임의의 정수를 넣게 되면 모든 해 쌍을 찾아갈 수 있다. 
참고로 37은 5291x + 3108y가 될 수 있는 양의 정수 중에서 가장 작은 값, 즉 최솟값이다. 만약 5291x + 3108y = 36이라는 방정식의 해를 구하라고 묻는다면, 이 식의 최솟값이 37이므로 36을 만족하는 해는 없다고 볼 수 있다.
F# 구현
extenedGCD 함수를 반복문을 사용하는 구조로 간단하게 구현할 수 있다. 
// 확장된 유클리드 알고리즘 함수
let extendedGCD a b =
    let rec loop a b x0 y0 x1 y1 =
        if b = 0 then (a, x0, y0)
        else loop b (a % b) x1 y1 (x0 - (a / b) * x1) (y0 - (a / b) * y1)
    loop a b 1 0 0 1

// 테스트
let a = 5291
let b = 3108
let (gcd, x, y) = extendedGCD a b

// 결과 출력
printfn "GCD: %d, x: %d, y: %d" gcd x y
실행결과
$ dotnet run
GCD: 37, x: -37, y: 63


다음 시간에..
만약 x와 y가 서로소인 경우 gcd가 1이 되며 이때는 ax + by = 1을 만족하는 형태의 답을 찾는 문제가 된다. 이런 것을 합동식이라던지 모듈러 역원 등으로 설명할 수 있는데 다음 시간에..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CPUU</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/18, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593524</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593524/1-18-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T05:22:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 18, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958030/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958030/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:55:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for January 18, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 alpha 3 is now available.]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/01/python-3130-alpha-3-is-now-available.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/01/python-3130-alpha-3-is-now-available.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:30:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We silently skipped releasing in December (it was too close to the 
holidays, a lot of people were away) so by date you may have been 
expecting alpha 4, but instead it’s alpha 3:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130a3/




This is an early developer preview of Python 3.13
Major new features of the 3.13 series, compared to 3.12
Python 3.13 is still in development. This release, 3.13.0a3, is the third of six planned alpha releases.
Alpha releases are intended to make it easier to test the current 
state of new features and bug fixes and to test the release process.
During the alpha phase, features may be added up until the start of 
the beta phase (2024-05-07) and, if necessary, may be modified or 
deleted up until the release candidate phase (2024-07-30). Please keep 
in mi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Accelerating startup growth through technology, expertise, and community]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/accelerating-startup-growth-through-technology-expertise-community.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/accelerating-startup-growth-through-technology-expertise-community.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Nivedita Kumari – Technical Anchor Mentor, Accelerator Program, and Prabhu Thiagarajan – Accelerator Success Mentor, Accelerator Program






This International Mentoring Day, we recognize that mentorship is a critical part of the startup journey. Google for Startups Accelerator programs provide founders and teams with the technology, expertise, and mentorship they need to grow and succeed. As program mentors, we had the opportunity to engage with and empower many early stage startups helping them scale and grow.


The Startup Challenge 
Although the startup ecosystem is rapidly expanding, success is rarely a smooth journey. On an average, it takes startups two to three years years to turn a profit, and fewer than 10% of startups that raise a seed round successfully raise a Seri…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Nordic nRF-Connect SDK Projects with GitHub Actions]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/ncs-github-actions</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/ncs-github-actions"/>
        <updated>2024-01-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recently we ran through a re-vamp of our CI builds targeting the Nordic
nRF-Connect SDK, and I wanted to share some of the things we learned along the
way! This article walks through setting up a GitHub Actions workflow for
building nRF-Connect SDK projects.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김부겸과 이철희, 이탄희의 절박한 호소, 이재명에 닿을까: 슬로우레터 1월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102527</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102527"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T22:06:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[10조 원 감세, 총선 끝나고 감당할 수 있겠나. 쟁점과 현안. 시스템 공천한다더니 김경율을 꽂았다. “3선 이상 하기가 얼마나 어려운데.” “법으로, 펜으로, 칼로 죽이려 해도.” 탈당 막으려 뭐 한 게 있나. 한동훈의 정치 혐오, 뼈 때린 이준석. 다르게 읽기. “민주당 과반, 당연한 거 아니다.” 진영 정치를 끊는 쪽이 이긴다. 더 깊게 읽기. ‘김정은 선언’을 이해하는 다섯...
The post 김부겸과 이철희, 이탄희의 절박한 호소, 이재명에 닿을까: 슬로우레터 1월18일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Growing pains for typing in Python]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958326/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958326/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T20:32:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Python's static-typing feature has come a long way since it was introduced in 2014.  Adding type
information to functions has always been—and will remain—optional, but typing
still remains somewhat contentious.  There are multiple kinds of
consumers of the information, each with their own needs and
wishes, as well as users of the feature with expectations of their own.  That has
led to the formation of a Python typing council
to govern the type system for the language, though, as might be guessed,
there are still grumblings from various quarters.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HiPEAC Vision 2024: what’s the next computing paradigm?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481324</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/hipeac-vision-2024-whats-the-next-computing-paradigm/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T20:19:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“A holistic approach is needed to create future computing systems that genuinely meet social needs while keeping people safe and respecting planetary boundaries.”
The post HiPEAC Vision 2024: what’s the next computing paradigm? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Please welcome Daroc Alden]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958444/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958444/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T20:13:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When, at the beginning of November, we posted an open position at LWN, we were only so
hopeful; experience has shown that finding writers who are both capable of
and interested in writing our sort of material is a challenging task.  This
time, though, hope was justified: we got a surprising number of
applications from highly qualified applicants.  The hardest part of the
task has, instead, been narrowing down the choice to a hiring decision.

We are pleased to announce that Daroc Alden has just joined LWN's staff.

Daroc is a programmer from New England, where they live with their
spouse and their cat. They graduated with a Master's degree in Computer
Science from the University of New Hampshire. In their spare time, they
enjoy fiction writing and musicals. They are especially interested in 
programming language theory and implementation.


Daroc will be taking on some of the load of keeping LWN interesting while
helping us to expand our content mix in the areas that our readers are
interested in.  Please give them your support as they come up to speed
within our operation.  We are looking forward to having Daroc as part of a
reinforced and more energetic LWN going forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kicinski: netdev in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958518/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958518/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T19:52:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Networking maintainer Jakub Kicinski (along with several collaborators) has
put up a summary of
what happened in the kernel's network stack during 2023.


	Throughout those releases netdev patch handlers (DaveM, Jakub,
	Paolo) applied 7243 patches, and the resulting pull requests to
	Linus described the changes in 6398 words. Given the volume of work
	we cannot go over every improvement, or even cover networking
	sub-trees in much detail (BPF enhancements… wireless work on WiFi
	7…). We instead try to focus on major themes, and developments we
	subjectively find interesting.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[#WeArePlay | Learn how a childhood experience with an earthquake shaped Álvaro's entrepreneurial journey]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/weareplay-how-a-childhood-experience-shaped-alvaros-entrepreneurial-journey.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/weareplay-how-a-childhood-experience-shaped-alvaros-entrepreneurial-journey.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Leticia Lago – Developer Marketing








Being trapped inside a house following a major earthquake as a child motivated Álvaro to research and improve the outcomes of destructive, large-scale quakes in Mexico. Using SkyAlert technology, sensors detect and report warnings of incoming earthquakes, giving people valuable time to prepare and get to safety.
Álvaro shared his story in our latest film for #WeArePlay, which spotlights the founders and creatives behind inspiring apps and games on Google Play. We caught up with him to find out his motivations for SkyAlert, the impact the app’s had and what his future plans are.


What was the inspiration behind SkyAlert?
Being in Colima near the epicenter of a massive earthquake as a kid had a huge impact on me. I remember feeling powerl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958497/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958497/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T15:00:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (zabbix), Gentoo (OpenJDK), Red Hat (kernel), Slackware (gnutls and xorg), SUSE (cloud-init, kernel, xorg-x11-server, and xwayland), and Ubuntu (freeimage, postgresql-10, and xorg-server, xwayland).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Monolith to microservices: Breaking down apps the useful way]]></title>
        <id>c111124b-248c-4e1c-8d4d-d72d3ac6ae63</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/17/monolith-microservices-breaking-down-apps-useful-way"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Don’t break your toys… unless it’s to have 2 playable toys.”
A significant part of my 10-year career as a consultant in middleware and applications development has been centered on microservices architectures, still an important topic for IT modernization nowadays.
At the very beginning, it was important to just explain the concepts, what it was about and why it wasn’t just another way to speak about service-oriented architecture (SOA). Then came best practices, patterns, and pitfalls.
Some projects were greenfields, of course, but there were also many initiatives around modernizing monoliths by splitting them into smaller pieces.
After a few years, I started to hear some negative feedback. That feedback highlighted and emphasized the higher complexity of the resulting solution. People we…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Thirion</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install and upgrade Data Grid 8 Operator]]></title>
        <id>ab1c96df-9a02-4e7d-85e2-387e42e24c1a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/17/how-install-and-upgrade-data-grid-8-operator"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Red Hat OpenShift 4, the Operator framework became a fundamental part of the daily cluster operations. An operator is a custom controller that listens to a few custom resources. Operators can be used for networking, cluster management, or installing and running applications. They provide a custom mechanism that extends the default OpenShift Container Platform capabilities.
Specifically, in terms of application operators, Data Grid Operator (a Go application) deploys Red Hat Data Grid (a Java application) by providing five APIs for creating a Data Grid cluster/caches/custom settings. The Data Grid Operator provides Custom Resources (CRs), which are based on template files called Custom Resource Definitions (CRDs). The CRDs are installed together with the Data Grid Operator and will be lo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior, Alexander Barbosa Ayala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[1/17, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593488</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593488/1-17-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T04:55:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[장르가 된 범죄실화물, 어떻게 소비하는 게 정답일까]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=78547</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/01/17/npsp_truecrimestory/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_truecrimestory"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T04:45:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘날 범죄실화는 신문과 잡지, 도서와 TV, 라디오, 팟캐스트, 유튜브, 영화 등 매체를 가리지 않고 인기를 누리고 있는 하나의 장르입니다. ‘범죄실화 장르’라는 용어가 익숙지 않더라도, 이 글을 읽는 여러분은 대부분 이 장르를 이미 접해보셨을 겁니다. 범죄 다큐멘터리나 범죄실화를 바탕으로 한 영화, 드라마는 스트리밍 사이트 인기 콘텐츠 목록에서 늘 상위를 차지하고 있으니까요. 지난 8일 뉴욕타임스에는 이처럼 범람하는 범죄실화 장르에 대한 통렬한 비판이 실렸습니다. 범죄 피해자 가족이 쓴 글이기 때문에 더욱 와닿는 글을 번역하고, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Julia v1.10: Performance, a new parser, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958337/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958337/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-17T01:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The new year arrived bearing a new version of Julia, a general-purpose, open-source
programming language
with a focus on high-performance
scientific computing.
Some of Julia's unusual features are Lisp-inspired
metaprogramming, the ability to examine compiled representations of code in
the REPL or in a "reactive
notebook", an advanced type and dispatch system, and a sophisticated,
built-in package manager.
Version 1.10 brings big increases in
speed and developer convenience,
especially improvements in code precompilation and loading times. It also
features a new parser written in Julia.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wine 9.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958443/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958443/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T22:32:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
9.0 of the Wine Windows-compatibility system has been released.
"This release represents a year of development effort and over 7,000
individual changes. It contains a large number of improvements that are
listed below. The main highlights are the new WoW64 architecture and the
experimental Wayland driver."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈이 이랬더라면 정말 무서울 뻔했다, 조선일보의 깊은 탄식: 슬로우레터 1월17일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102479</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102479"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T22:04:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[폭주하는 북한, 맞불 놓는 윤석열. 한동훈 딸 허위 스펙 의혹, 모두 ‘혐의 없음’. 쟁점과 현안. 윤석열은 오늘도. 이재명-원희룡, 인천 계양에서 붙는다. 더 깊게 읽기. 제3지대 신당, 민주당에 더 타격. 8년 전 ‘샤이 트럼프’, 이제는 대놓고 지지한다. 다르게 읽기. 의원 수 줄이는 게 개혁? 허경영인가. “탈원전하게 되면 반도체 포기해야 돼요.” “72억짜리 벤틀리를 타봤더니.” 그들에게 명예가 있나....
The post 한동훈이 이랬더라면 정말 무서울 뻔했다, 조선일보의 깊은 탄식: 슬로우레터 1월17일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[YouTube Ads Creative Analysis]]></title>
        <id>http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/youtube-ads-creative-analysis.html</id>
        <link href="http://developers.googleblog.com/2024/01/youtube-ads-creative-analysis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Posted by Brian Craft, Satish Shreenivasa, Huikun Zhang, Manisha Arora and Paul Cubre – gTech Data Science Team







Introduction

  
Why analyze YouTube ads?
YouTube has billions of monthly logged-in users and every day people watch billions of hours of video and generate billions of views.  Businesses can connect with YouTube users using YouTube ads, which are promotional videos that appear on YouTube's website and app, with a variety of video ad formats and goals.


A sample YouTube in-stream skippable video ad


The Challenge
An effective video ad focuses on the ABCDs.

Attention:  Capturing the viewer's attention till the end.
Branding:  Helping them hear or visualize the brand.
Connection:  Making them feel something about the brand.
Direction:  Encouraging them to take action.


B…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google for Developers Blog - News about Web, Mobile, AI and Cloud</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A glitch in the merge window]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958424/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958424/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T16:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On January 13, Linus Torvalds let
it be known that he had lost power due to the bad weather in the US
Pacific Northwest.  As of this writing, he has not yet resurfaced, so the
6.8 merge window has ground to a halt.


	There's apparently about 100k people without power, and I doubt our
	neighborhood is the priority, so I expect to be without power for
	some time still. I hope I'm wrong, but a few years ago it took more
	than a week to restore power due to all the downed trees. It's
	hopefully nowhere near that, but..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 critical habits for faster, more reliable firmware]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481319</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/3-critical-habits-for-faster-more-reliable-firmware/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many great habits that will help you develop faster, more reliable firmware. Here are a few thoughts on habits you may want to...
The post 3 critical habits for faster, more reliable firmware appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programming embedded systems: semantics of hierarchical state machines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481316</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/programming-embedded-systems-semantics-of-hierarchical-state-machines/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T15:47:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video tutorial, you will see the rich semantics resulting from hierarchical state nesting, allowing you to model nuances of behavior. You first encountered...
The post Programming embedded systems: semantics of hierarchical state machines appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miro Samek</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958416/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958416/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T14:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Gentoo (KTextEditor, libspf2, libuv, and Nettle), Mageia (hplip), Oracle (container-tools:4.0, gnutls, idm:DL1, squid, squid34, and virt:ol, virt-devel:rhel), Red Hat (.NET 6.0, krb5, python3, rsync, and sqlite), SUSE (chromium, perl-Spreadsheet-ParseXLSX, postgresql, postgresql15, postgresql16, and rubygem-actionpack-5_1), and Ubuntu (binutils, libspf2, libssh2, mysql-5.7, w3m, webkit2gtk, and xerces-c).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Developer Hub: Your gateway to seamless development]]></title>
        <id>f3808583-5454-4d36-91d8-aa62ca106b91</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/16/red-hat-developer-hub-your-gateway-seamless-development"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Developer Hub is now generally available. This article introduces Developer Hub and explains how it streamlines the development process. We also dive into the core concepts to ensure you're well-equipped to use Red Hat Developer Hub to leverage the power of Backstage in your projects.
What is Backstage?
In the dynamic world of software development, teamwork and efficiency are essential, and the Backstage project promises to simplify and save development teams headaches. Originally created by Spotify and shared as an open source project with the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), Backstage serves as a central hub for development teams, enabling the software development life cycle to become more manageable, accelerating new member onboarding, and centralizing resources require…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Eisele, Hugo Guerrero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“내가 벤틀리를 타봤는데 말이야”, 윤석열 발언에 빠진 것.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102449</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102449"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T08:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열(대통령)의 벤틀리 발언은 기묘하다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 정확한 워딩은. 벤틀리 발언의 논리 구조. 진실은. 핵심은. 더 깊이 들어가 보자. 결론.
The post “내가 벤틀리를 타봤는데 말이야”, 윤석열 발언에 빠진 것. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[풍자의 전성시대]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102440</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102440"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:25:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[박미숙의 새 필드] 한국학이 활발한 영국 셰필드에서 대중문화를 공부한 박미숙 박사와 함께 대중문화에 비친 우리 자신의 모습을 이야기합니다. 오늘 추가할 새 필드는 풍자.   2023년 MBC연예대상 여자 신인상을 ‘풍자’가 받았다. 풍자의 수상과 수상소감은 새해에도 잔잔한 화제다. 2023년 유난히 유튜버나 BJ와 같은 1인 방송으로 인기를 얻어 공중파 텔레비전으로 진출한 경우가 많았다. 풍자 걱정하는 아빠, 그 아빠...
The post 풍자의 전성시대 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>박미숙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to deploy Vue.js apps to OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>52ba9f26-60e4-4590-8b06-18ca889cf86a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/01/16/how-deploy-vuejs-apps-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift is a unified platform to build, modernize, and deploy applications at scale. Red Hat OpenShift offers a great developer experience in shipping your applications to the cloud.
JavaScript (JS) is the most popular programming language, used by millions of developers around the world. While it’s one programming language, there are many popular frameworks within JavaScript that need different approaches.
In this series of articles, we are putting together a step-by-step guide that will enable you to be up and running JS applications on OpenShift. We expect you to have some familiarity with Vue.js and Red Hat OpenShift. Just in case you need a quick recap, check out these resources:
OpenShift video
Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift
Vue.js website
Containerfile
How to depl…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yashwanth Maheshwaram</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 2024년 매그니피센트 7 예상, 애플과 테슬라는 명단에서 빠질 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=593480</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/593480/2024%eb%85%84-%eb%a7%a4%ea%b7%b8%eb%8b%88%ed%94%bc%ec%84%bc%ed%8a%b8-7-%ec%98%88%ec%83%81"/>
        <updated>2024-01-16T03:52:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[마케팅 경영 사례 연구 및 트렌드 탐구]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[묻지도 따지지도 않고 1억 원 대출, 애 낳으면 탕감해 준다면?: 슬로우레터 1월16일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=102409</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/102409"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T22:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한동훈이 요즘 윤석열 이야기를 안 하는 이유. 떴다방 위성정당 또 만드나. 기자회견 안 한다. 기자회견 대신 민생 토론회, 총선 개입 논란. 쟁점과 현안. 김무성 7선 도전, 올드보이들의 귀환. 헤쳐모여 본격화. 더 깊게 읽기. 청부 민원 제보했더니 제보자를 압수수색. 한화, RSU로 경영권 승계 논란. 다르게 읽기. 부자+포퓰리즘이 말이 되는 이유. 해법과 대안. 도루묵이 돌아올 수 있을까....
The post 묻지도 따지지도 않고 1억 원 대출, 애 낳으면 탕감해 준다면?: 슬로우레터 1월16일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A new crop of stable kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958341/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958341/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T19:02:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.6.12, 6.1.73, 5.15.147, 5.10.208, 5.4.267, and 4.19.305 stable kernels have been
released. They contain a relatively small number of important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Programmer Job Interviews: The Hidden Agenda]]></title>
        <id>3639444</id>
        <link href="http://queue.acm.org/detail.cfm?ref=rss&amp;id=3639444"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T16:59:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>ACM Queue - All Queue Content</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[High-bandwidth memory (HBM) options for demanding compute]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4481288</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/high-bandwidth-memory-hbm-options-for-demanding-compute/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T16:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While unbeatable in terms of performance, HBM is expensive and power hungry for many applications. We review the many memory different options for demanding compute applications.
The post High-bandwidth memory (HBM) options for demanding compute appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anton Shilov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploring Serverless CI/CD for Embedded Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://embeddedartistry.com/?p=39867</id>
        <link href="https://embeddedartistry.com/blog/2024/01/15/exploring-serverless-ci-cd-for-embedded-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[15 January 2024 by Kayode AladeToday we have a guest post from Kayode Alade. Kayode is an IoT Solutions Architect with a knack for making things work. He considers himself a perpetual learner, always enthusiastic about acquiring new knowledge, whether from an engineering perspective or a business standpoint. You can find Kayode on GitHub and … 
Continue reading "Exploring Serverless CI/CD for Embedded Devices"
The post Exploring Serverless CI/CD for Embedded Devices appeared first on Embedded Artistry.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kayode Alade</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Expertise: Beyond Fixed-Size Integers; Exploring Fast and Least Types]]></title>
        <id>https://blog.feabhas.com/?p=3912</id>
        <link href="https://blog.feabhas.com/2024/01/embedded-expertise-beyond-fixed-size-integers-exploring-fast-and-least-types/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T15:23:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[About
 Latest Posts


  
 

Niall Cooling
Director at Feabhas Limited
Co-Founder and Director of Feabhas since 1995.
Niall has been designing and programming embedded systems for over 30 years. He has worked in different sectors, including aerospace, telecomms, government and banking.
His current interest lie in IoT Security and Agile for Embedded Systems.
 


 

Latest posts by Niall Cooling (see all)

				
					Embedded Expertise: Beyond Fixed-Size Integers; Exploring Fast and Least Types - January 15, 2024				
				
					Disassembling a Cortex-M raw binary file with Ghidra - December 20, 2022				
				
					Using final in C++ to improve performance - November 14, 2022				

 
 
The Challenge of Fixed-Size Integers Before C99
In embedded programming, before adopting the C99 standard (ISO/IEC 9899:1999), a significant challenge was ensuring the consistent sizing of key data objects. This complexity stemmed from the C standard’s (ISO/IEC 9899) non-committal stance on the size of an int. We knew:
A short is a minimum of 16-bits.
This flexibility boosted C’s portability, making it a favourite for various architectures, including [...] 

The post Embedded Expertise: Beyond Fixed-Size Integers; Exploring Fast and Least Types appeared first on Sticky Bits - Powered by Feabhas.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Niall Cooling</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSUSE Leap 16 is coming]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958319/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958319/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T15:21:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE project has confirmed
that there will be a successor to openSUSE Leap 15, but is not sharing
a lot of details at this point.


	The transition to Leap 16 is not just a numerical step-up but
	symbolizes a significant path forward in technology and user
	experiences. The future of openSUSE Leap is based on the innovative
	concept of SUSE’s Adaptable Linux Platform.

	The Adaptable Linux Platform powers the next-generation openSUSE
	Leap, Leap Micro, and SUSE solutions. It makes distributions more
	adaptable and suitable for cloud-native workloads while also being
	capable of handling a rapid pace of innovation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stawinski: How We Executed a Critical Supply Chain Attack on PyTorch]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958318/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958318/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T15:16:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Stawinski IV describes,
in detail, how he and a partner were able to compromise the security of the
heavily used PyTorch project.


	Our exploit path resulted in the ability to upload malicious
	PyTorch releases to GitHub, upload releases to AWS, potentially add
	code to the main repository branch, backdoor PyTorch dependencies –
	the list goes on. In short, it was bad. Quite bad. 

	As we’ve seen before with SolarWinds, Ledger, and others, supply
	chain attacks like this are killer from an attacker’s
	perspective. With this level of access, any respectable
	nation-state would have several paths to a PyTorch supply chain
	compromise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rust and C filesystem APIs]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958072/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958072/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the Rust-for-Linux project
advances, the kernel is gradually 
accumulating abstraction layers that enable Rust code to interface with the
existing C code.  As the discussion around the set of filesystem
abstractions posted by Wedson Almeida Filho in December shows, though,
there is some tension between two approaches to the design of those
abstractions.  The approach favored by most of the kernel's C programmers
looks set to win out, but this is a discussion that is likely to return as
the use of Rust in the kernel grows.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/958315/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/958315/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-15T14:05:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (bind, cups, curl, firefox, ipa, iperf3, java-1.8.0-openjdk, java-11-openjdk, kernel, libssh2, linux-firmware, open-vm-tools, openssh, postgresql, python, python3, squid, thunderbird, tigervnc, and xorg-x11-server), Fedora (chromium, python-flask-security-too, and tkimg), Gentoo (libgit2, Opera, QPDF, and zlib), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, gnutls, openssh, packages, and vlc), Oracle (.NET 6.0, fence-agents, frr, ipa, kernel, nss, pixman, and tomcat), and SUSE (gstreamer-plugins-bad).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>