<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html</id>
    <title>News Feed</title>
    <updated>2024-06-30T20:13:45.847Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://newsfeed.mononn.com/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro and 1.5 Flash GA, 1.5 Flash tuning support, higher rate limits, and more API updates]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemini-15-pro-and-15-flash-now-available/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T20:13:38.109Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re incredibly excited to see what you build with these new models. Get started with Gemini 1.5 Flash and 1.5 Pro free of charge in Google AI Studio.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Customizable DIY RFID Business Card and Badge Holder with Victorinox Swiss Army Knife Tools]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40800</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/06/30/customizable-diy-rfid-business-card-and-badge-holder-with-victorinox-swiss-army-knife-tools/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T18:31:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article discusses the creation of a versatile business card and badge holder with RFID and addressable RGB LEDs. The project includes PCB designs for both standard business card size and larger badge holders, as well as hardware and software details. It also incorporates features such as customizable laser engravings, rechargeable battery, and integration with Victorinox Swiss Cards. The files for this project are available on GitHub. Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of reading: April - June 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/summary-of-reading-april-june-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/summary-of-reading-april-june-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T14:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<ul class="simple">
<li>&quot;River of the Gods: Genius, Courage, and Betrayal in the Search for the
Source of the Nile&quot; by Candice Millard - while the book is readable, I found
it disappointing because it focuses much more on the personalities involved
and their numerous feuds than on the actual exploration, geography and history …</li></ul>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[단종 유배지, 영월 청령포 출사기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595233</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595233/%eb%8b%a8%ec%a2%85-%ec%9c%a0%eb%b0%b0%ec%a7%80-%ec%98%81%ec%9b%94-%ec%b2%ad%eb%a0%b9%ed%8f%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T12:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[넷플릭스 드라마 ‘돌풍’, 클리셰 떡칠인데 재밌는 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111112</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111112"/>
        <updated>2024-06-30T07:20:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[몇 가지 포인트, 재미가 곧 한계. 한국판 ‘하우스 오브 카드’라고 불리는 드라마다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 큰 줄거리(스포일러 포함.) 박동호는 왜 그랬을까, 세 가지 의문. 독특한 캐릭터. 클리셰. 반전의 반전. 결론.
The post 넷플릭스 드라마 ‘돌풍’, 클리셰 떡칠인데 재밌는 이유. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API for Custom LLMs on Device]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-generative-api-for-custom-llms-on-device/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T20:13:20.468Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch Generative API enables developers to bring powerful new capabilities on-device, such as summarization, content generation, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Google Pay at I/O 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-google-pay-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T20:13:20.468Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’re adding new features to Google Pay so you can offer richer and more accessible payment experiences for your customers, and improved APIs to simplify your payments integrations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고화질 컬러TV와 아이돌의 탄생: 마츠다 세이코 1980 & 뉴진스 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111087</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111087"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T00:58:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 국내 뉴스가 하도 흉흉해 아이돌 보는 즐거움이 한풀 꺾인 상황이다. 사람이 죽고 사는 문제가 급박한데 때깔 고운 케이팝이나 반전 넘치는 K-드라마에 몰입하기 쉽지 않다. 엔터테인먼트라는 것도 물난리나 경제 침체 속에서는 다 헛짓거리가 될 수밖에 없는 것이다. 여전히 잘 나가는 ‘한류 비즈니스’의 묘한 모순이기도 하다. 케이팝의 대세이자 미래로 불리는 ‘뉴진스’가 또 한번 신곡을 공개하고 나섰다....
The post 고화질 컬러TV와 아이돌의 탄생: 마츠다 세이코 1980 & 뉴진스 2022 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정호재</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 미국 대학 캠퍼스 시위를 외면할 수 없는 ‘바이든의 딜레마’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79291</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/28/npsp_campusprotestbiden/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_campusprotestbiden"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T22:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 싱가포르 난양공대의 이종혁 교수가 5월 6일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 뉴욕 컬럼비아대학교에서 시작된 반전 시위가 미국 전역으로 번졌습니다. 2주 차를 맞아 시위는 더 거세지는 양상입니다. 대학 측은 시위에 참여한 학생들에게 잇따라 정학 등 징계를 내렸고, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] FreeDOS turns 30]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979780/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979780/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T19:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FreeDOS is an open-source
operating system designed to be compatible with the now-defunct MS-DOS. Three decades
have now passed since the FreeDOS project was first announced, and it
is still alive and well with a small community of developers and
users committed to running legacy DOS software, classic DOS games, and
developing modern applications that extend its functionality well beyond the
original MS-DOS. It may well be around in another 30 years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FSF Europe condemns Apple's DMA noncompliance]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/980003/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/980003/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:37:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Free Software Foundation Europe has

submitted a joint position to the European Commission (EC), claiming that Apple
has failed to comply with the EU's Digital Markets Act (DMA). This is the law
that requires Apple to support alternative application stores on the devices it
makes.



Apple's unfair behaviour against Free Software highlights the critical need to
monitor the implementation of the DMA. The FSFE collaborated with F-Droid, the
AppFair project, and other interoperability experts to scrutinize Apple's DMA
compliance, and it's impact on Free Software. Since then, we coordinated several
expert workshops with stakeholders,

discussed with regulators in FOSDEM, had

official meetings with the EC's DMA team, and submitted a

comprehensive position
to the EC detailing several problematic elements in the Apple compliance that
will harm the Free Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multicore avionics systems safety and certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482643</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/multicore-avionics-systems-safety-and-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:20:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article examines the progress in multicore systems, the potential of eVTOLs, and the critical role of certification, emphasizing the relevance of the ARM V8...
The post Multicore avionics systems safety and certification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Jakob</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Redox: An operating system in Rust]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979524/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979524/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T13:36:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the

Rust-for-Linux project starting to gain some ground, it is worth
looking at other operating systems that use Rust in their kernels. There
are 
many attempts to use
Rust for operating system development, but Redox
may be the most complete.
Redox is an MIT-licensed microkernel and corresponding user space, designed
around concepts taken from

Plan 9. While nowhere near being usable as a
replacement for Linux, it already provides a graphical user interface and

the ability to run many POSIX programs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979999/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979999/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T12:53:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (pki-core), Debian (dlt-daemon and plasma-workspace), Fedora (emacs and kernel), Mageia (erofs-utils, libheif, libopenmpt, and wget), Red Hat (pki-core and python3), SUSE (frr), and Ubuntu (fontforge, sqlite3, and squid3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“그렇게만 할 거면… 올림픽 왜 하니?” 배제와 포용, 답은 정해져 있다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79588</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/28/npsp_sextestingolympics/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_sextestingolympics"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:30:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[스포츠에서 같은 종목이라도 남자부와 여자부 경기를 따로 치르는 건 당연한 규정으로 여겨집니다. 그런데 성별을 손쉽게 구분할 수 있다는 통념이 적용되지 않는 소수의 사례에 해당하는 선수들을 여자부 대회에 출전하게 허용하는 것이 정당하냐를 두고 오랫동안 논란이 이어졌습니다. 올림픽에서 성별 검사의 역사만 해도 1930년대로 거의 한 세기를 거슬러 올라가야 합니다. 전문 번역: 올림픽 출전 선수의 ‘성별 검사’는 공정 경쟁을 위한 것? 이전부터 그렇게 해왔을까 해설: “그렇게만 할 거면… 올림픽 왜 하니?” 배제와 포용, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[곽재우와 이순신, 아홉 가지 공통점과 네 가지 차이점]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111056</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111056"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:16:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다 보니 곽재우 장군에게 관심을 갖게 되었고 그러다 보니 있는 자료 없는 자료 모두 구해 읽게 되었다. 여태 곽재우 장군의 일대기를 밝혀 적은 책이 없다 보니 옛 기록을 찾을 수밖에 없었다. 또 그렇게 하다 보니 곽재우 장군의 진면목을 조금이나마 알게 되었고 그러다 보니 겨레의 성웅 이순신 장군과 비교·대조해 볼 생각을 ‘감히’ 먹게 되었다. 이순신 장군의...
The post 곽재우와 이순신, 아홉 가지 공통점과 네 가지 차이점 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김훤주</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[공소권 남용 검사에 면죄부 준 헌재: 폭력은 그들의 것, 수치는 우리의 몫]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111051</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111051"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T08:01:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2021년 대법원은 역사상 최초로 검찰의 공소권 남용을 인정했습니다. 유우성 씨에 대한 ‘간첩 조작’으로 무죄가 선고된 후, 검찰이 자행한 ‘보복 기소’가 공소권의 남용이라고 판단한 것입니다. 하지만 검찰은 검사들의 공소권 남용에 관해서는 책임을 묻지 않았습니다. 이에 국회는 당시 ‘보복 기소’의 담당 검사였던 안동완 탄핵소추안을 통과시켰습니다. 그러나 헌재는 안동완 검사에 대한 탄핵심판청구를 ‘기각’했습니다. 대법원에서 인정한 공소권 남용이 인정되지...
The post 공소권 남용 검사에 면죄부 준 헌재: 폭력은 그들의 것, 수치는 우리의 몫 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scale testing image-based upgrades for single node OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>402a5d5d-cf25-4eec-af05-403f2b4d07a6</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/28/scale-testing-image-based-upgrades-single-node-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Image-based upgrades (IBU) are a developer preview feature in Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform 4.15 that reduce the time required to upgrade a single node OpenShift cluster. The image-based upgrade can perform both Z and Y stream upgrades, include operator upgrades in the image, and rollback to the previous version manually or automatically upon failure. Image-based upgrade can also directly upgrade OpenShift Container Platform 4.y to 4.y+2, whereas a traditional OpenShift upgrade would require two separate upgrades to achieve the same end result (4.Y to 4.Y+1 to 4.Y+2). 
An image-based upgrade consists of several stages that the Lifecycle Agent will take a cluster through. Those stages are prep, upgrade, rollback, and idle. The prep stage can be completed outside a maintenance window …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex Krzos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[감기 걸린 바이든, 선수 교체 말이 나오는 이유.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=111015</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/111015"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T04:41:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[트럼프는 막 질렀고 바이든은 제대로 받아치지 못했다. 트럼프는 불만을 늘어놓으면서 막말과 거짓말을 쏟아냈다. 바이든은 가끔 더듬고 말끝을 흐렸다. (감기에 걸렸다고 한다.) 미국시간으로 6월27일 저녁, 조 바이든(미국 대통령)과 도널드 트럼프(전 미국 대통령)의 대선 토론이 열렸다. 이게 왜 중요한가. 종합 평가. 슬로우뉴스의 평가. “우리는 마침내 메디케어를 이겼다.” 멕시코 국경. 새로운 토론 규칙. 선거 결과에 승복할 건가. 1월6일....
The post 감기 걸린 바이든, 선수 교체 말이 나오는 이유. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크론 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595217</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595217/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80-3"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T02:02:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“조작된 사건일 가능성”, 윤석열의 믿을 수 없는 발언: 슬로우레터 6월28일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110976</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110976"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T22:24:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“이태원 사고, 조작된 사건일 가능성.” 쟁점과 현안. “근로 계약서 쓸 거면 나가라 했다.” 소화기 39대 모두 리튬에 무용지물. 일단 1년 미룬 유보통합. 방통위원장 탄핵 간다. 더 깊게 읽기. “개처럼 뛰고 있어요.” 쪼개기 알바 늘어나는 이유는. 내년 R&D 예산 원복. 엄마 돈 훔치면 감옥 간다. 다르게 읽기. 벌금 대신 감옥을 선택한 사람들. 오늘 미국 대선 토론회....
The post “조작된 사건일 가능성”, 윤석열의 믿을 수 없는 발언: 슬로우레터 6월28일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compilation of C# conference talks from 2023-2024]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1138/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/csharp/1138/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've recently posted a compilation of C++ talks, but we don't want to leave out C# developers. So, here are some interesting conference talks from the world of .NET and C#.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fine-tuning Gemma 2 with Keras - and an update from Hugging Face]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/fine-tuning-gemma-2-with-keras-hugging-face-update/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/fine-tuning-gemma-2-with-keras-hugging-face-update/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:13:53.167Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The next generation of Gemma models is now available in KerasNLP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gemini 1.5 Pro 2M context window, code execution capabilities, and Gemma 2 are available today]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/new-features-for-the-gemini-api-and-google-ai-studio/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/new-features-for-the-gemini-api-and-google-ai-studio/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:13:53.167Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers will now be able to give Gemini 1.5 Flash a set of pre-trained data of their own and tune it to improve model performance significantly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing the I/O magic to Berlin]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/bringing-the-io-magic-to-berlin/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/bringing-the-io-magic-to-berlin/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:13:53.167Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are some highlights from what we announced both on stage in Berlin and elsewhere in the world in celebration of this event!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights from the FreeBSD Developer Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979935/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979935/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T20:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FreeBSD Foundation has published
a
set of reports from the May
2024 FreeBSD Developer Summit held in Ottawa, Canada. The topics
include FreeBSD Core Team updates, FreeBSD 15 release planning,
Integration with Rust, and OCI
containers on FreeBSD:


Doug Rabson began by providing an overview of the current state of
FreeBSD support for OCI containers, noting that while FreeBSD has long
supported containers through its jail and vnet features, the ecosystem
around OCI containers requires further development. "FreeBSD has been
able to do containers for a long time, but we need to align better
with OCI standards to make our containers more compatible and easier
to use," Rabson remarked​​.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 beta 3 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3130-beta-3-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3130-beta-3-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T19:57:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.13 beta 3.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130b3/
 
This is a beta preview of Python 3.13
Python 3.13 is still in development.  This release, 3.13.0b3, is the third of four beta release previews of 3.13.

Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the 
opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their 
projects to support the new feature release.
We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects to test with 3.13 during the beta phase and report issues found to the Python bug tracker 
 as soon as possible. While the release is planned to be feature 
complete entering the beta phase, it is possible that features may be 
modified or, in rare cases, deleted up until the start …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mourning Daniel Bristot de Oliveira]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979912/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979912/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T18:14:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The academic and the Linux real-time and scheduling community mourns the
premature death of Daniel Bristot de
Oliveira. Daniel died at the age of 37 on Monday, June 24, 2024.
Juri Lelli, Tommaso Cucinotta, Steve Rostedt, Kate Stewart, and Thomas
Gleixner have come together to share their thoughts on his life and what he
has left behind]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Software Foundation adds three board members]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979918/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979918/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T18:04:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Free Software Foundation (FSF) has announced
the addition of three new members to its board: John Gilmore,
Christina Haralanova, and Maria Chiara Pievatolo. This is part of FSF
governance changes announced
in January 2023. The next step is a review of current board
members:
voting
members will review the feedback
received and decide if each current board member should remain.


More information on the process, and a short biography of each new
board member, is available in the full announcement.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Windows Registry Adventure #3: Learning resources]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/the-windows-registry-adventure-3.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/the-windows-registry-adventure-3.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=4mNYFHt_IKFsPe52toizHz0e5qzIIUg9OvSRGeMDk3I);

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-0>li:before {
        content: "\0025cf   "
    }

    ul.lst-kix_pv42b0usiw40-7 {
        list-style-type: none
    }

    ul.lst-kix_pv42b0usiw40-8 {
        list-style-type: none
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-5>li:before {
        content: "\0025a0   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-4>li:before {
        content: "\0025cb   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-2>li:before {
        content: "\0025a0   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-3>li:before {
        content: "\0025cf   "
    }

    .lst-kix_80vdbxrca7qi-1>li:before {
        content: "\0025cb   "
    }

    ol.lst-kix_hmg5xw3mb42j-2.start {
        counter-reset: lst-ctn-kix_hmg5xw3mb42j-2 0
…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Direct-to-device networking]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979549/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979549/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T15:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been nearly one year since the
first version of the device memory TCP patches was posted by Mina
Almasry.  Now on the 14th
revision, this series appears to be stabilizing.  Device memory TCP is
a specialized networking feature requiring a certain amount of setup, but
it could provide a significant performance improvement for some
data-intensive applications.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Python grapples with Apple App Store rejections]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979671/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979671/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An upgrade from Python 3.11 to 3.12 has led to the rejection of
some Python apps by Apple's app stores. That led to Eric Froemling submitting a bug report
against CPython. That, in turn, led to an interesting
discussion among Python developers about how far the project was
willing to go to accommodate app store review processes. Developers
reached a quick consensus, and a solution that may arrive as soon as
Python 3.13.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three Thursday stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979849/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979849/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T13:12:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.9.7, 6.6.36, and 6.1.96 stable kernel updates have been
released; each contains an important set of fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979847/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979847/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T13:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (ffmpeg, kernel, libvpx, and linux-5.10), Fedora (chromium, firefox, freeipa, moodle, and openvpn), Oracle (git), Red Hat (golang and java-1.8.0-ibm), and Ubuntu (linux-oracle-6.5, netplan.io, openssl, plasma-workspace, ruby2.7, ruby3.0, ruby3.1, sqlite3, and wget).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/27, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595215</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595215/6-27-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac-%eb%b0%8f-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-%eb%b3%b4%ea%b3%a0%ec%84%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T12:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[굿바이, 퓨리오사]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110960</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110960"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T08:29:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[조지 밀러의 걸작, ‘매드맥스’ 시리즈 다섯 번째 영화 [퓨리오사: 매드맥스 사가] (이하 ‘퓨리오사’)를 극장에서 볼 수 있는 시간이 이제 얼마 남지 않았습니다. ‘퓨리오사’의 저조한 흥행으로 이제 또 다른 ‘매드맥스’ 시리즈를 볼 수 없을지도 모릅니다. 1945년생인 조지 밀러의 마지막 영화일지도 모르죠. 물론 더 많은 조지 밀러의 영화를 만나고 싶은 마음이지만요. 희망 없는 시대의 영웅 ‘퓨리오사’를 떠나보내는...
The post 굿바이, 퓨리오사 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>옥토</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to install KServe using Open Data Hub]]></title>
        <id>2ee900bb-a66f-4a81-aa1f-413442c66bc5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/27/how-install-kserve-using-open-data-hub"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KServe is a highly scalable and standards-based model inference platform on Kubernetes for scalable AI. Open Data Hub (ODH) now seamlessly incorporates KServe as an integral component within its ecosystem. In earlier iterations, utilizing KServe necessitated the execution of a relatively intricate installation script. However, with the release of Open Data Hub 2.5, significant strides have been made to streamline and alleviate the complexities associated with this process. Users can now experience a more user-friendly and efficient installation procedure, underscoring our commitment to enhancing accessibility and usability within the Open Data Hub framework.
This article will delve into a simplified method for installing KServe. The installation process can be summarized as follows:

Insta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>JooHo Lee</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[언론재단이 날린 ‘MBC 1위’ 로이터 보고서, 민언련이 번역해 공개합니다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110953</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110953"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T01:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[로이터저널리즘연구소가 해마다 발간하는 디지털뉴스리포트는 한국언론진흥재단이 한국 파트너로 참여합니다. 올해 리포트에서는 한국의 언론 신뢰도(’뉴스를 신뢰한다’는 답변)가 31%로 47개국 가운데 38위를 기록했죠. 언론사 브랜드 신뢰도 조사도 있는데 MBC가 57%로 1위, YTN(56%), JTBC(55%), SBS(54%) 순이었습니다. 지난해에는 번역 출간하면서 아예 이 부분을 누락했는데 올해는 아예 보고서를 내지 않았겠다고 공언했습니다. 이에 민언련이 해당 부분을 번역해 공개합니다. (편집자) 한국언론진흥재단은 영국 옥스퍼드대 부설 로이터저널리즘연구소가 6월...
The post 언론재단이 날린 ‘MBC 1위’ 로이터 보고서, 민언련이 번역해 공개합니다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 27, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979084/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979084/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T23:55:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 27, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“우리도 핵무장” 나경원 주장이 말이 안 되는 이유: 슬로우레터 6월27일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110913</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110913"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T22:09:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[7년 만에 서해 사격 훈련. 쟁점과 현안. “임성근 혐의 빼라” 의견 전달 있었다. “근무자 두 배 늘었다.” 정부는 뭘 했나. 더 깊게 읽기. 분양 실적 0, 대구 상인푸르지오의 딜레마. 대출 부실 괜찮나. 조국혁신당의 검찰개혁 4법. 다르게 읽기. 4월의 축복? 설레발 금지. 핵무장 시나리오? 현실성 없다. 해법과 대안. ‘자립준비청년’ 18% “심각하게 자살 고민.” 빈집 쓰나미. 일본이...
The post “우리도 핵무장” 나경원 주장이 말이 안 되는 이유: 슬로우레터 6월27일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Explorer: Simplifying ML models for Edge devices]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/model-explorer-simplifying-ml-models-for-edge-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/model-explorer-simplifying-ml-models-for-edge-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T20:16:53.025Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Model Explorer, a new graph visualization tool from Google AI Edge, enables developers to overcome the complexities of optimizing models for edge devices.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How We Built It: The I/O Crossword]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-we-built-the-io-crossword/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-we-built-the-io-crossword/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T20:16:53.024Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adding a helpful twist to a classic crossword puzzle with the power of Flutter, Firebase, and the Gemini API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Essential Steps for Reducing Power Consumption in Embedded Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1667.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1667.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T17:26:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing the amount of power your embedded device is consuming is not trivial. With so many devices moving to battery operations today, maximizing battery life can be the difference between a happy, raving customer and an unhappy one that ruins your company's reputation. 

Reducing the power consumption of your embedded device early in the development cycle is a strategic move and a...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSUSE Leap Micro 6.0 is now available]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979748/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979748/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T15:06:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE project has announced
Leap Micro version
6.0. Leap Micro is an image-based, lightweight Linux distribution
that is designed to run containerized and virtualized applications. It
is based on SUSE Linux
Enterprise (SLE) Micro. Changes in this release include the
support for full-disk encryption, the addition of Cockpit for
web-based system management, and an optional real-time kernel for
x86_64. Boot support for legacy BIOS on x86_64 is deprecated with 6.0, and will be removed in a later release. See the SLE
Micro release notes for more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hutterer: GNOME tablet support papercut fixes]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979745/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979745/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:17:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Peter Hutterer has written
a summary of "papercut fixes" for GNOME tablet support that are
planned to ship with GNOME 47.
If you're an avid tablet user, you may have multiple stylus tools -
but it's also likely that you have multiple tools of the same type
which makes differentiating them in the GUI hard. Which is why they're
highlighted now - if you bring the tool into proximity, the matching
image is highlighted to make it easier to know which stylus you're
about to configure. Oh, and in the process we added a new SVG for AES
styli too to make the picture look more like the actual physical
tool. The <blink> tag may no longer be cool but at least we can disco
our way through the stylus configuration now.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[폐광 재생 사례, 동해시 무릉별 유천지 라벤더 출사기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595198</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595198/%eb%8f%99%ed%95%b4%ec%8b%9c-%eb%ac%b4%eb%a6%89%eb%b3%84-%ec%9c%a0%ec%b2%9c%ec%a7%80-%eb%9d%bc%eb%b2%a4%eb%8d%94"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T13:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Finishing the conversion to the "new" mount API]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979166/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979166/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T13:19:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eric Sandeen led a filesystem-track session at 
the
2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit on completing the
conversion of the existing kernel filesystems to use the mount API that was added for the 5.2 kernel in 2019.  That API is
invariably called the "new" API, which it is when compared to the
venerable mount()
system call, but it has been available for five years or so at this point
without really pushing its predecessor aside.  Sandeen wanted to discuss
the status of the conversion process and some other questions surrounding
the new API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Types Team Update and Roadmap (Rust Blog)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979741/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979741/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T13:16:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Rust Blog is carrying an
update on what the Rust Types Team has been up to and its near-future
plans.


	There has been a
	lot of work on the next-generation
	trait solver. The initiative posted a
	separate update at the end of last year. While we would have
	liked to stabilize its
	use in coherence a few months ago, this surfaced additional
	small behavior regressions and hangs, causing delays. We are
	working on fixing these issues and intend to merge the
	stabilization PR soon. We are getting close to compiling the
	standard library and the compiler with the new solver enabled
	everywhere, after which will be able to run crater to figure out
	the remaining issues.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979740/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979740/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T13:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (git, python3.11, and python3.9), Debian (chromium, emacs, git, linux-5.10, and org-mode), Fedora (libopenmpt, nginx-mod-modsecurity, and thunderbird), Mageia (emacs, python-ansible-core, and python-authlib), Oracle (git, python3.11, and python3.9), Red Hat (kernel, kernel-rt, and samba), and Ubuntu (ansible, cups, google-guest-agent, google-osconfig-agent, libheif, openvpn, roundcube, and salt).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Projections and Projection Matrices]]></title>
        <id>https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/projections-and-projection-matrices/</id>
        <link href="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/2024/projections-and-projection-matrices/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We'll start with a visual and intuitive representation of what a projection is.
In the following diagram, we have vector <em>b</em> in the usual 3-dimensional space
and two possible projections - one onto the <em>z</em> axis, and another onto the <em>x,y</em>
plane.</p>
<img alt="Projection of a 3d vector onto axis and plane" class="align-center" src="https://eli.thegreenplace.net/images/2024/projection-3d.png" />
<p>If we think of 3D space as spanned …</p>]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Eli Bendersky's website</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The impact of AI/ML on qualifying safety-critical software]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482636</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/the-impact-of-ai-ml-on-qualifying-safety-critical-software/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As practitioners in safety-critical software, we must understand how to accommodate the huge promise of AI/ML without compromising functional safety processes and certification. Like open-source...
The post The impact of AI/ML on qualifying safety-critical software appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mark Pitchford</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Has C++ Just Become More Popular than C?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482632</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/has-c-just-become-more-popular-than-c/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:36:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the first time in 39 years, at least according to the TIOBE Programming Community Index, the popularity of C has dropped below that of...
The post Has C++ Just Become More Popular than C? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[서양의 양파는 한국의 양파보다 달다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110858</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110858"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:16:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[캐러멀라이즈 양파, 한식의 구원자 (연재 속 특집) 이 자슥은 요리책 쓴다면서 레시피 얘긴 안 하고 왜 틈만 나면 옆길로 새서 요상한 이야기를 늘어놓나 싶으시겠지만, 세상에 나보다 빠르고 맛있는 레시피를 소개하는 뛰어난 요리사들은 지천이다. 그러나 내가 하고자 하는 일은 모두에게 평등하게 다가오는 세끼의 식사가 어떤 의미이며 또 그 모습이 어디서 비롯된 것인지, 무엇보다 우리 남은 생,...
The post 서양의 양파는 한국의 양파보다 달다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>펜타클</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Open innovation: Red Hat’s impact on the Kafka and Strimzi ecosystem]]></title>
        <id>c0fbf1b3-b4bd-46a9-9d91-438fee767490</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/26/open-innovation-red-hats-impact-kafka-and-strimzi-ecosystem"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At Red Hat, open source is at the heart of everything we do. We are the world's largest open source software company, and staying true to our roots is something that is incredibly important to us. From the first versions of Red Hat Enterprise Linux, to the latest release of Red Hat OpenShift, all our code is open and available to our customers. We work with people across a wide spectrum of open source projects, some overseen by foundations such as the Apache Software Foundation (ASF), Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) and the Eclipse Foundation, and some independently run by their community. 
This article explores how Red Hat engineers contribute to open source projects in the data streaming landscape. 
The Strimzi project: Apache Kafka on Kubernetes
In 2018 Red Hat identified an op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Simon Woodman</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect applications with Red Hat build of Keycloak using Kerberos & Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>32739df6-9049-450d-b9e8-5b7cef79ed88</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/26/protect-applications-red-hat-build-keycloak-using-kerberos-active-directory"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I will demonstrate how workstation users authenticating to Active Directory using the Kerberos protocol can use Simple and Protected GSSAPI Negotiation Mechanism (SPNEGO) tokens with Red Hat build of Keycloak (RHBK) technology for single sign-on to web applications.
In summary, the authentication flow is as follows:

The user is authenticated with Active Directory over Kerberos and has a Ticket Granting Ticket (TGT) stored locally on the workstation.
The user makes a request from the browser to access the web application.
The web application redirects the browser to Red Hat build of Keycloak.
Red Hat build of Keycloak responds with a 401 HTTP header: WWW-Authenticate: Negotiate
The browser requests a Service Ticket (ST) from the Ticket Granting Service (TGS) part of the KD…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Torbjorn Dahlen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[아버지를 죽인 간병 청년 사건, 그 뒤로 무엇이 달라졌나.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110832</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110832"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T05:18:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[강도영(가명) 사건을 이야기할 때 우리는 이 질문을 피해 갈 수 없다. 당신은 뇌출혈로 쓰러진 아버지를 모시고 사는 22세 청년이다. 편의점 알바를 하고 있지만 월세와 아버지 기저귓값을 대고 나면 쌀 살 돈도 없는 형편이다. 어느 날 아버지가 이렇게 말했다: “도영아, 미안하다. 너 하고 싶은 거 하면서 행복하게 살아라. 필요한 거 있으면 부를 테니까, 그전에는 들어오지 마.”...
The post 아버지를 죽인 간병 청년 사건, 그 뒤로 무엇이 달라졌나. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[애완견인가, 감시견인가: 언론인 스스로 입증하라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110820</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110820"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T04:27:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘어떤’ 개냐가 문제 언론인에게 감시견(Watch dog)은 찬사다. 우리는 모두 감시견의 사명을 타고났다. 빌 코바치와 톰 로젠스틸이 쓴 [저널리즘의 기본 원칙] 가운데 다섯 번째 원칙이 “기자들은 반드시 권력에 대한 독립적인 감시자로 봉사해야 한다”는 것이다. 이재명 더불어민주당 대표가 6월 14일 “언론은 검찰의 애완견”이라고 비판하자 논란에 불이 붙었다. YTN 기자 출신의 노종면 더불어민주당 국회의원이 논란을 키웠다. “이런 언론...
The post 애완견인가, 감시견인가: 언론인 스스로 입증하라 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/26, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595185</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595185/6-26-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T03:47:51.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Updating NVIDIA Jetson devices with Memfault]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/updating-nvidia-jetson-with-memfault</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/updating-nvidia-jetson-with-memfault"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[NVIDIA offers one of the most comprehensive SDKs for developers of AI-heavy products. It includes a development kit that can emulate other devices in the lineup (Jetson AGX Orin DK), a simpler development kit for “entry-level” products (Jetson Orin Nano DK), a ton of exciting software libraries, AI models and even more examples of how to use them. It’s truly outstanding and out of the box shows up as a Ubuntu workstation which will feel very familiar.
However, it can be a bit daunting to figure out how to take this workstation experience and turn it into a headless unit that you can ship to customers far away and update remotely.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 중국과 미국이 기술 협력한다? 이게 쉽지 않은 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79285</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/25/npsp_chinagreenpolicy/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_chinagreenpolicy"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 싱가포르 난양공대의 이종혁 교수가 5월 4일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 중국은 최근 환경 기술 분야에서 눈부신 진전을 이루며 글로벌 무대에서 크게 주목받고 있습니다. 특히 시진핑의 중국은 기후변화에 적극적으로 대응하는 모습을 보이며, 국제사회에서의 리더십 공백을 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열이 임성근을 감싸고 돌았던 진짜 이유: 슬로우레터 6월26일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110791</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110791"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T22:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[임성근도 김건희 라인이었나. 임성근과 윤석열 친구의 만남. 쟁점과 현안. 배터리 공장, 이틀 전에도 불났었다. 외국인 노동자 더 많이 죽는다. ‘위험의 이주화’, 이대로는 안 된다. 더 깊게 읽기. 방송3법+방통위법 법사위 통과. 어산지의 빅딜. 다르게 읽기. 수업권 침해? 청소 노동자들의 두 차례 승리. “우리도 핵무장 해야 한다.” 여섯 번째 오물풍선, 맞대응 못 하는 이유는. “수사권 없는 수사도...
The post 윤석열이 임성근을 감싸고 돌았던 진짜 이유: 슬로우레터 6월26일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[12 moments of typos and copy-paste, or why AI hallucinates: checking OpenVINO]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1137/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1137/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["OpenVINO is a toolkit that boosts deep AI learning to interact with the real world. Now it's open-source!" This incredible news is a call to action for us. The project code has been checked, errors...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Programming in Unison]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978955/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978955/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T18:18:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unison is a
MIT-licensed programming language, in development since 2013, that
explores the ramifications of making code immutable and stored in a database,
instead of a set of text files.
Unison supports a greatly simplified model for distributed
programming — one that describes the configuration of and communication between
programs in the same language as the programs themselves. Along the way, it
introduces a new approach to interfacing with programming languages, which is tailored to
its design.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darktable 4.8.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979666/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979666/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T17:58:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
4.8.0 of the darktable
photo editor has been released.  Changes include performance
improvements for large collections, addition of more EXIF fields in
the image information module, and two new modules for image
composition: Enlarge Canvas and Overlay. Enlarge Canvas allows adding
areas to an image, while Overlay allows adding new content by
overlaying pixels from the current image or another image. LWN last
looked at darktable in
2022. Users are "strongly advised" to make a backup of their
configuration and library before upgrading, as they will not be
compatible with darktable 4.6.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Making containers bootable for fun and profit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979182/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979182/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T17:10:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dan Walsh, Stef Walter, and Colin Walters all walk into a
presentation and Walter asks, "why would
you want to boot your containers?" This isn't the setup for some technology joke, this is part of the trio's
keynote at
DevConf.cz in Brno, Czech Republic on June 14 about bootable containers
(bootc). The talk, which was streamed to YouTube for those of us who
didn't attend DevConf.cz in person, provided a solid overview of bootc
and the problems it is intended to solve. The idea behind bootc is to
make creating operating-system images just as easy as creating
application-container images while using the same tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RIP Daniel Bristot de Oliveira]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979617/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979617/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T14:39:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have just received the
sad news of the passing of Daniel Bristot de Oliveira at far too young
an age.  He was a strong contributor to the core kernel and associated
realtime infrastructure, and always a joyful presence in person; he will be
deeply missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Not all "open source" AI models are actually open (Nature)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979609/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979609/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T13:31:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nature looks
at a recent paper on the openness of "open-source" language 
models.


	It is not yet clear how many of these models will fit the EU's
	definition of open source. Under the act, this would refer to
	models that are released under a "free and open" licence that, for
	example, allows users to modify a model but says nothing about
	access to training data. Refining this definition will probably
	form "a single pressure point that will be targeted by corporate
	lobbies and big companies", the paper says.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979606/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979606/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T13:18:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (python3.11), Debian (composer), Fedora (thunderbird), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, python-aiohttp, python-gunicorn, python-werkzeug, and virtualbox), Oracle (libreswan and python3.11), Red Hat (git, kpatch-patch, python3.11, python3.9, and thunderbird), and SUSE (avahi, ghostscript, grafana and mybatis, hdf5, kernel, openssl-1_1-livepatches, python-docker, and wget).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generate Ansible Playbooks using natural language prompts]]></title>
        <id>a6b9343b-4eaa-4315-beb8-f49c18599525</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/25/generate-ansible-playbooks-using-natural-language-prompts"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the latest release of Ansible VS Code extension by Red Hat, you can generate complete Ansible Playbooks using natural language prompts. With guided chat experience, this new capability will significantly improve the productivity of automation developers as well as reduce the entry barrier for new Ansible playbook creation. 
Ansible playbook generation
Let’s see how you can start your free trial and generate Ansible Playbooks. To use the service, you need to have a Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform subscription; you can start your no-cost trial here. You will also need an IBM watsonx Code Assistant subscription; you can start your no-cost trial here. 
Set up Ansible VS Code extension by Red Hat
Once you have your subscription credentials in place, click on the extensions options on V…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Himanshu Yadav</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to securely take industrial control systems fully offline]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482621</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-to-securely-take-industrial-control-systems-fully-offline/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T12:19:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial control systems need to be taken offline to ensure security, but how can they then be kept up-to-date with necessary software updates and data?...
The post How to securely take industrial control systems fully offline appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Richard Kanadjian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modeling high-performance sampling clocks in mixed-signal front end devices]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482615</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/modeling-high-performance-sampling-clocks-in-mixed-signal-front-end-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T11:53:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers can now use models of mixed-signal front-end devices to design the high performance sampling clock required for software-designed radio designs. Mixed-signal front-end (MxFE) products...
The post Modeling high-performance sampling clocks in mixed-signal front end devices appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Brigid Duggan</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[드라마 왕국의 열정 노동자]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110773</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110773"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T07:51:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[좋은 드라마, 좋은 작품을 바라는 건 시청자나 제작사나 같은 마음이다. 하지만 좋은 드라마, 좋은 작품의 조건에 관해서는 아직 사회적 정의(定義)도 그 관심도 부족해 보인다. 어떤 드라마가 좋은 드라마인가, 어떤 작품이 좋은 작품인가. 당신을 감동시킨 그 드라마가 누군가의 꿈을 짓밟고, 일터의 희망을 빼앗아 가는 노동 착취로 만들어진 드라마라면, 그때 그 드라마는 좋은 드라마인가. 스타 시스템과 착취...
The post 드라마 왕국의 열정 노동자 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>박미숙</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get started with the bpfman eBPF manager on OpenShift 4.16]]></title>
        <id>039e3d7b-ab06-46da-9fac-e9d853cc5fb0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/25/get-started-bpfman-ebpf-manager-openshift-416"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[eBPF is a low-level technology for running sandboxed kernel programs. Its use in Kubernetes-based applications has grown rapidly due to the revolutionary capabilities it enables, as demonstrated by Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) projects such as Cilium, Datadog, Calico, and Pixie. However, eBPF in Kubernetes also poses a number of new challenges for developers and administrators alike. These challenges include program lifecycle management issues, the widespread use of privileged pods, the lack of eBPF subsystem visibility, and problems with program cooperation.
bpfman is an open source project dedicated to making eBPF easier to secure, manage, and use. The project includes an operator that allows eBPF application developers to package programs via OCI container images and deploy …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrew Stoycos</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[마이크론 실적을 기다리는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595176</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595176/%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81%ea%b3%bc-%eb%a7%88%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac%eb%a1%a0-%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T02:06:15.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/25, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595162</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595162/6-25-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T01:23:37.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[흡연 이상으로 해로운 소셜미디어? “지금은 비상상황”… 여기에 공감하나요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79580</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/24/npsp_socialmediasurgeongeneral/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_socialmediasurgeongeneral"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T00:05:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[소셜미디어와 정신건강의 관계는 오랫동안 논란의 중심에 선 소재였습니다. 소셜미디어 사용이 많아질수록 정신건강에 문제를 일으키는 이용자가 많이 보고됐지만, 소셜미디어 기업들은 인과관계는 발견되지 않은 주장일 뿐이라고 일축해 왔죠. 특히 10대 여성 청소년들의 자살률이 높아진 미국에서는 중독을 일으키고 한껏 꾸민 다른 이의 삶과 비교를 통해 자기자신을 혐오하게 만드는 소셜미디어를 담배나 술처럼 규제해야 한다는 주장이 오래전부터 나왔습니다. 미국 연방정부에서 국민건강 문제를 총괄하는 ‘국민의 의사’ 비벡 머시 의무총감이 소셜미디어 플랫폼이 주는 위험을 경고하는 문구를 삽입하자는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“한동훈의 자기 정치, 대통령이 화가 많이 났다”: 슬로우레터 6월25일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110752</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110752"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T22:09:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[물로 잡을 수 없는 불, 리튬 배터리 폭발 사고. 물 뿌리는 게 맞나? 쟁점과 현안. 국민의힘 7개 상임위원장 수용. 이재명 사퇴? 연임 선언. 다섯 번째 오물 풍선. 더 깊게 읽기. “한동훈의 자기 정치, 대통령이 화가 났다.” 한동훈-민주당 연대 가능할까. 윤석열의 고민. 다르게 읽기. 전공의 복귀 안 하면 후유증 5년 간다. 바닥없는 기시다 지지율. 중국의 ‘제조업...
The post “한동훈의 자기 정치, 대통령이 화가 많이 났다”: 슬로우레터 6월25일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google @ KotlinConf 2024: A Look Inside Multiplatform Development with KMP and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-kotlinconf-2024-a-look-inside-multiplatform-development-with-kmp-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T20:13:56.772Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KotlinConf 2024 reveals Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) for sharing business logic across mobile, web, server, and desktop platforms, and in Google Workspace.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EDA vendors put Intel EMIB interconnect in design flows for 3D ICs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482585</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/eda-vendors-announce-put-intel-emib-interconnect-in-design-flows-for-3d-ics/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:46:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All three EDA vendors announced the addition of Intel Foundry’s EMIB advanced packaging technology into their design reference flows.
The post EDA vendors put Intel EMIB interconnect in design flows for 3D ICs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Siemens gets certification for Solido SPICE on Intel nodes, and adds EMIB]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482581</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/siemens-gets-certification-for-solido-spice-on-intel-nodes-and-adds-emib/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:32:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Intel and Siemens recently certified new Solido SPICE, part of Solido Simulation Suite software, for the foundry’s Intel 16 and Intel 18A nodes, and add EMIB in design flow.
The post Siemens gets certification for Solido SPICE on Intel nodes, and adds EMIB appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence adds Intel 18A and EMIB support]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482577</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/cadence-adds-intel-18a-and-emib-support/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:27:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cadence said its complete AI-driven flow supports Intel’s advanced packaging reference flow that leverages its EMIB technology and is optimized to work seamlessly with Intel 18A technology.
The post Cadence adds Intel 18A and EMIB support appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synopsys adds Intel Foundry EMIB reference flow for multi-die]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482571</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/synopsys-adds-intel-foundry-emib-reference-flow-for-multi-die/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T17:20:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Optimized reference flow provides unified co-design and analysis solution to accelerate exploration and development of multi-die designs at all stages from silicon to systems.
The post Synopsys adds Intel Foundry EMIB reference flow for multi-die appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Min: sched_ext: scheduler architecture and interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979532/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979532/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T16:33:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Changwoo Min has posted an
introduction to writing custom schedulers with sched_ext.


	In a particular situation, when each scheduling policy needs its
	specific action, the core kernel scheduler calls an operation
	defined in struct sched_class. For example, when the core
	kernel scheduler needs to select a task to be scheduled, it calls
	the sched_class.pick_next_task(rq) callback of a concrete
	scheduling policy. When a task becomes runnable, the core kernel
	scheduler calls sched_class.enqueue(rq, p, flags) so the
	concrete scheduling policy enqueues task p to run queue
	rq. When a task's runtime state needs to be updated, the
	core kernel scheduler calls sched_class.update_curr(rq).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Federated simulation working group addresses systems-of-systems]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482559</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/federated-simulation-working-group-addresses-systems-of-systems/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:48:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[EDA and IP standards body forms new working group to focus on interoperability of simulators, models, and other components that together form systems-of-systems simulation environments.
The post Federated simulation working group addresses systems-of-systems appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] The GhostBSD in the machine]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978837/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978837/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T14:35:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GhostBSD is a
desktop-oriented operating system based on FreeBSD and the MATE Desktop Environment. The
goal of the project is to lower the barrier to entry of using FreeBSD
on a desktop or laptop system, and it largely succeeds at this. While it has a few rough edges
that make it hard to recommend for the average desktop user, it is
a fine choice for users who want a desktop with FreeBSD underpinnings
such as the Z File System (ZFS), and the Ports (source) and Packages (binary) software collections.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979520/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979520/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T14:14:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (ipa and libreswan), Debian (netty), Fedora (python-PyMySQL, tomcat, and webkitgtk), Gentoo (Flatpak, GLib, JHead, LZ4, and RDoc), Mageia (thunderbird), Oracle (nghttp2 and thunderbird), Red Hat (dnsmasq, libreswan, pki-core, and python3.11), Slackware (emacs), SUSE (gnome-settings-daemon, libarchive, qpdf, vte, and wget), and Ubuntu (libhibernate3-java).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Emacs 29.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979491/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979491/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T14:07:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
29.4 of the Emacs editor has been released.  This is "an emergency
bugfix release" fixing a vulnerability that can cause
the editor to execute arbitrary shell code in Org mode.  Anybody who runs Emacs on
untrusted files — including those using Gnus or one of the Emacs mail modes
— should be looking to update.  For those who cannot update, a pair of
messages from Russ
Allbery and Florian Weimer
investigates how to disable the Org-mode evaluation, a task that is
seemingly more complicated than it should be.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Part 2: Arm Scalable Matrix Extension (SME) Instructions]]></title>
        <id>dd9e70c8-6d3c-4c71-b136-2456382a7b5c:54aa97f0-2eb4-4fc9-9301-b7197915b8ea</id>
        <link href="https://community.arm.com/arm-community-blogs/b/architectures-and-processors-blog/posts/arm-scalable-matrix-extension-introduction-p2"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T10:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog is the second half of a two-part blog for SME Instructions. See link to Part 1 in the note at the top of this blog post.(read more)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zenon Xiu (修志龙）</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[설탕과 한식, 쾌락과 미개함 사이]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110738</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110738"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T09:00:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[오늘은 레시피가 아닌 하나의 주제에 관해 이야기하고자 한다. 바로 ‘단맛’이다. 단순히 설탕에 관한 이야기가 아니다. 너무나 무겁고 중요한 소재라서 스스로 오랜 시간을 두고 궁리한 주제이기도 하다. 이 글에서는 단맛에 관한 ‘썰’을 풀고 다음에는 본격적으로 캐러멜라이즈 양파에 관해서 설명하겠다. 이후는 그 양파를 활용한 요리들을 시리즈 형식으로 몇 편 써 볼까 한다. 나는 요리를 공부한 사람치고 미식...
The post 설탕과 한식, 쾌락과 미개함 사이 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>펜타클</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/21,BoA, 엔비디아 차익실현 욕구가 대대적 대도세로 이어지지는 않을듯]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595158</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595158/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%b0%a8%ec%9d%b5%ec%8b%a4%ed%98%84"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T08:48:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Parlez vous Fortran?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1672.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1672.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T08:29:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When I first started programming, the only language available to me was Fortran. I punched cards with my code and later received back a print-out with mostly error messages. I was always intrigued by being able to program a computer in such a straightforward way. I understood what assembly language or even machine code was all about, but felt that high level languages had a mystique. In due...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[고교학점제, 잠자는 교실을 깨울 수 없는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110726</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110726"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T07:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[기고] 고교학점제에 관한 현장 교사의 목소리를 전합니다. 김준식 선생님은 수능 입시제도로 인해 고교학점제는 그 취지에 맞게 운용이 어렵다고 지적합니다. 위에 인용한 글은 고교학점제 홈페이지에 있는 고교학점제가 필요한 이유를 설명한 글이다. 이 글이 얼마나 근거 박약하고 허술하며 심지어 기만적인지 고교학점제가 시행되는 인문계 고등학교 교실에서 수업하는 교사는 모두 알 것이다. 특히 잠자는 교실을 깨운다는 말에 분노까지 치민다....
The post 고교학점제, 잠자는 교실을 깨울 수 없는 이유 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>김준식</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Leverage Red Hat Satellite for Insights reporting and automation]]></title>
        <id>c0f9c756-5592-4467-9136-6dc8b5139c09</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/24/leverage-red-hat-satellite-insights-reporting-and-automation"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Satellite is a solution designed to manage and operate Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) infrastructure and environments at scale. While Satellite assists system administrators in ensuring system consistency, reducing errors and meeting compliance requirements by implementing standard operating environments, it also provides the capability to run automation across multiple datacenters.
In this article, we explore Satellite automation and its scheduling capabilities to perform repetitive tasks. We use this functionality to query Red Hat Insights APIs and generate CSV (comma-separated values) files that we attach to an email. With this configured, system administrators can automate the sending of the latest Insights data and reporting straight into their inbox. This setup allows for th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerome Marc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[홍윤희 스토리 2. 회색지대 무지개]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109609</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109609"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T06:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[네 가지 목소리 행글라이더 사고로 비극적 운명이 내게 다가왔지만, 그것도 프로메테우스처럼 내게 주어진 삶이었어요. 싸우면서 확신이 생겼던 것 같아요. 노들야학에서 학생과 교사들은 서로 함께 가르치며 배웠어요. 그들의 힘으로 이동권의 힘을 실질적인 투쟁으로 만들어온 자부심이 저를 계속 남아있게 했어요. 굉장히 자부심이 있어요. 존중은 쟁취해야 하는 거지, 동정으로 주어지는 게 아니더라고요. 그런 것들을 알게 됐는데 안 싸울...
The post 홍윤희 스토리 2. 회색지대 무지개 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모건스탠리, S&P500 전망치 6000 제시]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595154</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595154/%eb%aa%a8%ea%b1%b4%ec%8a%a4%ed%83%a0%eb%a6%ac-sp500-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d%ec%b9%98-6000-%ec%a0%9c%ec%8b%9c"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T04:46:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 역사는 엔비디아의 주가 버블 경고를 보낸다, (feat: 보다 안전한 12가지 AI 주식)]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595149</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595149/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ea%b8%88%eb%93%b1%ea%b3%bc-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%eb%b2%84%eb%b8%94"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T02:38:24.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/24, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595139</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595139/6-24-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:55:10.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“밖에서 편하게 사회생활하니까 애 키우는 게 고된 줄 모른다” 맞는 말일까?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79558</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/23/npsp_dadbrain/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_dadbrain"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T00:30:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한국 사회의 저출생 문제를 진단할 때마다 원인으로 지목되는 것 중 하나가 점점 더 심해지는 젠더 갈등입니다. 특히 육아를 ‘공평하게’ 또는 ‘합리적으로’ 분담하는 문제를 두고는 남녀 간에, 엄마와 아빠 사이에 이견을 좁히기가 생각보다 쉽지 않은 문제처럼 보입니다. 어쨌든 통계로 드러나는 한국은 육아를 비롯한 가사 노동을 엄마와 아빠 사이에 공평하지 않게 나누어 지는, 주로 여성이 대부분 부담을 과중하게 홀로 지는 나라입니다. 아빠가 육아에 더 많이 참여하도록 설득하려면 “아빠 육아”가 자녀의 발달에도 좋고, → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc5]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979442/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979442/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T22:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10-rc5 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "So far, the 6.10 release cycle has been fairly calm, and rc5
continues that trend. Let's hope things stay that way."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[모든 정황과 근거가 윤석열을 가리킨다: 슬로우레터 6월24일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110672</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110672"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T22:08:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[채 상병 청문회에서 맞춰진 퍼즐. 간단한 복습. “참담했다.” 쟁점과 현안. 우크라이나 무기 지원, 괜찮을까. 누구 맘대로 김건희법인가. 더 깊게 읽기. 한동훈발 출구 전략. 한동훈과 나머지 구도. “휴진 중단 찬성”, 서울대의대 교수 74%. 다르게 읽기. 4시간32분 동안 빚 독촉 764통. 망가지는 건 한순간. 노인 빈곤율과 자살률. 초등생 유입, 서울 강남구가 전국 1위. 주담대 3.7조 급증. 국민제안?...
The post 모든 정황과 근거가 윤석열을 가리킨다: 슬로우레터 6월24일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning General relativity at a rudimentary mathematical level]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8880</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/06/23/learning-general-relativity-at-a-rudimentary-mathematical-level/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T21:31:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the longest time, I have wanted to have an understanding of Einstein’s theory of General relativity at a rudimentary mathematical level. Because General relativity has never been a mainstream topic in undergraduate physics, there are almost no books at this level. Also, the mathematics of General relativity is based on tensor calculus, which until […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ programmer's guide to undefined behavior: part 2 of 11]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1136/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1136/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your attention is invited to the second part of an e-book on undefined behavior. This is not a textbook, as it's intended for those who are already familiar with C++ programming. It's a kind of C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Larry Finger RIP]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979419/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979419/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T14:28:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The linux-wireless mailing list carries the terse
notice that longtime networking developer Larry Finger passed away on
June 21.  The LWN Kernel
Source Database shows that Finger contributed to 94 releases in
the (Git era) kernel history, starting with 2.6.16 — 1,464 commits in
total.  He will be missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지금 프로그래밍을 하고 있는 당신은 누구인가]]></title>
        <id>20240623-perspective-on-ai</id>
        <link href="https://evan-moon.github.io/2024/06/23/perspective-on-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T10:10:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI는 우리의 생활을 크게 변화시키고 있다. ChatGPT 모바일 앱을 사용하면서 음성으로 대화를 주고 받다보면 이제는 영화 아이언맨에 나오는 인공지능 비서 자비스가 현실화된 것이 아닌가 하는 착각마저도 일으킬 정도이다.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Evans Library</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[영월 단종 유배지 근처, 붉은 매자나무 언덕, 영월 용마루나무 출사]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595127</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595127/%ec%98%81%ec%9b%94-%ec%9a%a9%eb%a7%88%eb%a3%a8%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4-%ec%b6%9c%ec%82%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-23T04:02:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lost Secrets of the H-Bridge, Part V: Gate Drives for Dummies]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1671.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1671.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T19:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today we’re going to talk about gate drive circuits for MOSFETs and IGBTs. But first I want to share a story.

Magic smoke
About 25 years ago, I shared an office with a nice guy named Larry who was working on a linear actuator, which was basically just a brushed DC motor connected to a lead screw.
Larry had an easy job in some ways, and a tough job in others. 

The easy part...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When a Mongoose met a MicroPython, part II]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1670.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1670.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T18:34:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mongooses and very small pythons develop their established friendship.

In the first part of this blog, we introduced this little framework to integrate MicroPython and Cesanta's Mongoose; where Mongoose runs when called by MicroPython and is able to run Python functions as callbacks for the events you decide in your event handler.
Now we add MQTT to the equation, so we can subscribe to...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Debugging video from across the ocean]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/video/2024/06/22/vidbug.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/video/2024/06/22/vidbug.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I’ve come across two approaches to video synchronization.  The first, used by
a lot of the Xilinx IP I’ve come across, is to hold the video pipeline in
reset until everything is ready and then release the resets (in the right and
proper order) to get the design started.  If something goes wrong, however,
there’s no room for recovery.  The second approach is the approach I like to
use, which is to build video components that are inherently
“stable”: 1) if they
ever lose synchronization, they will naturally work their way back into
synchronization, and 2) once synchronized they will not get out of sync.
At least that’s the goal.  It’s a great goal, too–when it works.
Today’s story is about what happens when a “robust” video display isn’t.
System Overview
Let’s start at the top level: I’m wor…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2024: What’s new in Android Development Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-android-development-tools-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-android-development-tools-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T20:14:49.116Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android Studio Koala feature drop (2024.1.2) is now available in the Android Studio canary channel, with productivity enhancements, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[어제는 대통령, 오늘은 의회, 그땐 다수결, 지금은 대화]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110658</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110658"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T15:06:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[중꺾정 칼럼] 22대 국회가 개원했습니다. 유권자의 소중한 한 표, 한 표를 읍소하며 당선된 300명의 국회의원이 과연 유권자를 위해 제대로 일하는지 지켜보고 감시해야 할 때입니다. 이들이 어떤 일을 하는지, 어떤 일을 해야 하는데 안하는지에 따라 우리의 삶이 달라지니까요. 참여연대 의정감시센터는 칼럼을 통해 유권자의 시각에서 22대 국회와 정치를 비평합니다. 무엇보다 ‘중’요한건 ‘꺾’이지 않는 ‘정’치개혁이니까요. 오늘의 중꺾정 칼럼...
The post 어제는 대통령, 오늘은 의회, 그땐 다수결, 지금은 대화 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 의정감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rust for filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978738/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978738/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T14:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the
2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Wedson Almeida Filho and
Kent Overstreet led a combined storage and filesystem session on using Rust
for Linux filesystems. Back in December 2023, Almeida had posted
an RFC patch set with
some Rust abstractions for filesystems, which resulted in some disagreement over the approach.  On the
same mid-May day as the session, he posted
a second version of the RFC patches, which he wanted to discuss along with
other Rust-related topics.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Friday stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979259/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979259/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:30:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.9.6,
6.6.35,
6.1.95, and
5.10.220
stable kernels have all been released; as usual, users are advised to update
immediately.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979257/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979257/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:11:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (firefox, ghostscript, idm:DL1, and thunderbird), Debian (php8.2 and putty), Mageia (chromium-browser-stable), Oracle (ghostscript and thunderbird), Red Hat (thunderbird), and SUSE (containerd, kernel, php-composer2, podofo, python-cryptography, and rmt-server).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[웨드부시, 엔비디아 인공지능 시대 지배력, 엔비디아 시총 4조달러 낙관]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595123</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595123/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%9c%ec%b4%9d-4%ec%a1%b0%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T09:07:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[스스로 결정한 자기로 살 권리: 성확정수술 요구는 위헌이다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110646</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110646"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T08:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022년, 대법원은 “인간은 누구나 자신의 성정체성에 따른 인격을 형성하고 삶을 영위할 권리가 있다”고 판시했습니다. 그러면서 사람의 성을 결정하는 요소에는 성기 등 생물학적 요소뿐 아니라, 정신적·사회적인 요소들도 포함된다고 명시했죠. 여러 법원에서 성확정수술을 하지 않은 트랜스젠더의 성별 정정을 허가한 것도 이와 같은 맥락입니다. 그리고 2024년, 성별 정정을 위해 수술을 강제하는 것은 ‘위헌’임을 구체적으로 밝힌 결정이 나왔습니다. 법과...
The post 스스로 결정한 자기로 살 권리: 성확정수술 요구는 위헌이다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3일 동안 양파를 볶으며]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110634</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110634"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T07:39:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[모두에게 공평하게 다가오는 세끼의 식사가 어디서 시작되는 것이며, 그 시간이 우리 삶에 주는 의미, 궁극적으로는 개인의 행복을 넘어 요리가 더 나은 사회와 세상을 반드시 만들 수 있다는 믿음. 보물(La joya)을 만들기 위해 3일 동안 양파를 젓던 그때 그 마음으로 매번 찾아올 수 있기를 희망하며. 나는 스페인 북부 산 세바스티안이라는 도시에서 요리를 공부했다. 얼마 전 케이블...
The post 3일 동안 양파를 볶으며 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>펜타클</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[로이터, 갈림길에 선 엔비디아 투자자들, 이익실현이냐 추가 상승을 기다릴 것이냐]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595118</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595118/%ea%b0%88%eb%a6%bc%ea%b8%b8%ec%97%90-%ec%84%a0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9e%90%eb%93%a4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T06:53:08.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[트럼프의 ‘남쪽 이민자’ 공포 마케팅: 대현동을 보라]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109767</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109767"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T05:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[80억 중 20억, 20억 중 6만 명. 2022년 기준 전 세계 인구는 약 80억 명이다. 그중 무슬림은 약 20억 명으로 추산되고, 그중에서 약 6만 명이 한국에 산다. 인도네시아 인구는 약 2.8억 명(2022 기준)인데, 그중 90% 정도가 무슬림이고, 파키스탄 인구는 약 2.3억 명(2021)으로 세계 다섯 번째이며, 무슬림은 인도네시아 다음으로 많다. 파키스탄은 국가의 설립 목적 자체가 이슬람이다....
The post 트럼프의 ‘남쪽 이민자’ 공포 마케팅: 대현동을 보라 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/21, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595106</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595106/6-21-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T02:32:17.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[구글 플레이 앱 자동 업데이트 설정 방법]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595100</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595100/%ec%95%b1-%ec%9e%90%eb%8f%99-%ec%97%85%eb%8d%b0%ec%9d%b4%ed%8a%b8"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T01:33:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 스모킹건, 디올 백보다 큰 것 나오나: 슬로우레터 6월21일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110582</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110582"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T22:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[우크라이나 무기 공급, 레드라인 넘었다. “러시아에 뒤통수를 맞았다.” 쟁점과 현안. 윤석열 명예훼손? 김만배·신학림 구속. 뉴스타파 김만배 인터뷰의 핵심(지난 이야기). 김만배: “윤석열이가 네가 조우형이야? 이러면서.” (중략) “박길배 검사가 커피, 뭐하면서 몇 가지 하더니 보내주더래. 그래서 사건이 없어졌어.” 신학림: “박영수가 그러면 윤석열이하고 통했던 거야?” 김만배: “통했지. 그냥 봐줬지.” 이재명 수사 검사 탄핵 들어간다. 더 깊게 읽기. 디올...
The post 김건희 스모킹건, 디올 백보다 큰 것 나오나: 슬로우레터 6월21일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitwise operators in Java: unpacking ambiguities]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1135/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1135/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The "&" and "|" operators are pretty straightforward and unambiguous when applied correctly. But do you know all the implications of using bitwise operators instead of logical ones in Java? In this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Years of Innovation: Student developers solving real-world problems using Google tech]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/5-years-of-innovation-student-developers-solving-real-world-problems-using-google-tech/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:13:57.904Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Developer Student Clubs globally are tackling the United Nations' Sustainable Development Goals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tor Browser 13.5 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979177/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979177/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T20:10:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
13.5 of the privacy-focused Tor browser has been released.


	Regular readers of our release posts will know that for the past
	two years we've been gradually increasing our capacity to not only
	maintain, but bring tangible improvements to Tor Browser for
	Android. In that respect, Tor Browser 13.5 feels like a milestone:
	in addition to the dozens of bug fixes and minor improvements noted
	in the changelog below, this release features major changes to
	Android's connection experience in preparation for the future
	addition of Connection Assist, including full access to Settings
	before connecting and a new, permanent home for Tor logs.


The release also features desktop user-interface improvements and enhanced
fingerprinting protection.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A capability set for user namespaces]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978846/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978846/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T18:37:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[User namespaces in Linux create an
environment in which all privileges are granted, but their effect is
contained within the namespace; they have become an important tool for the
implementation of containers.  They have also become a significant source
of worries for people who do not like the increased attack surface they
create for the kernel.  Various attempts have been made to restrict that
attack surface over the years; the latest is user namespace
capabilities, posted by Jonathan Calmels.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Updates to pahole]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978727/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978727/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:58:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arnaldo Carvalho de Melo spoke at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit
about his work on

Poke-a-hole (pahole),
a program that has expanded greatly over the years, but which was relevant to the
BPF track because it produces BPF Type Format (BTF) information from DWARF
debugging information. He covered some small changes to the program, and then
went into detail about the new support for data-type profiling. His
slides include
several examples.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Project Naptime: Evaluating Offensive Security Capabilities of Large Language Models]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/project-naptime.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/project-naptime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=DFQxm4rd7fRHgM9OTejWVT5Vho6BE7M80rHXEVKqXWckOnM5xqt2DUw2f5lNcrroidEvLLi3H0BPvcL7ypcd6c76ZZ8PqJ7WOKqynLI9-xo);.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-8>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}ol.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-6>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}li.li-bullet-0:before{margin-left:-18pt;white-space:nowrap;display:inline-block;min-width:18pt}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-7>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}ol.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0.start{counter-reset:lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0 0}ul.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-7{list-style-type:none}.lst-kix_s8mzwdo5vrhy-0>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_s8mzwdo…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/979153/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/979153/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T16:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (ghostscript and thunderbird), Debian (chromium, composer, libndp, and sendmail), Fedora (composer), Mageia (flatpak and python-scikit-learn), Red Hat (curl, ghostscript, and thunderbird), SUSE (hdf5 and opencc), and Ubuntu (gdb and php7.4, php8.1, php8.2, php8.3).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stateful and reactive stream processing applications with Apache Kafka, Quarkus, and Angular on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>c4289561-6575-449d-8709-a47336231e6a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/20/stateful-and-reactive-stream-processing-applications-apache-kafka-quarkus-and"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this in-depth article, you're going to learn how to build an end-to-end reactive stream processing application using Apache Kafka as an event streaming platform, Quarkus for your backend, and a frontend written in Angular. In the end, you'll deploy all three containerized applications on the Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift.
A first look at the final result—a colorful live dashboard tracking the usage of emojis in public 🐘 Mastodon 🐘 posts (a.k.a., toots)—should give you a rough idea of what you may expect throughout this article. See Figure 1.



  
        


        Fig. 1 - Emoji Tracker Live Dashboard
  

Figure 1: Emoji tracker live dashboard.

Let's dive right in.
Developer Sandbox for Red Hat OpenShift
All applications which are part of the complete demo scenario are su…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hans-Peter Grahsl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to find vulnerabilities across millions of Quay.io images]]></title>
        <id>81b44d70-0b3f-40d6-8083-d64f28ab4fb9</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/20/how-find-vulnerabilities-across-millions-quayio-images"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Quay.io was the first private container registry on the internet and began serving images back in 2013. Today, it hosts millions of images for hundreds of thousands of critical customer workloads, including Red Hat’s own product catalog.
One of the marquee features of Quay.io is free security scanning for any image that we host. This happens automatically as soon as you push an image to Quay.io. Not only does it scan your image at upload time, it also provides an up-to-date view of your vulnerabilities, no matter how long ago you pushed it. There is no need to ask Quay.io to rescan your image—that information is available whenever you request it. 
This is critical, as container images typically only gather more and more vulnerabilities as they age. An old container image isn’t alwa…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Dettelback</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[성심당 코레일 월세 4억 원의 비밀.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110519</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110519"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T06:47:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[대전하면 성심당 떠올리는 사람들 많다. 오늘은 두 가지 이야기를 해보자. 코레일이 성심당 대전역사점 임대료를 현재 1억 원에서 4억 원으로 올려 받겠다고 해서 논란이다. 코레일 임대사업자 입찰, 지금까지 5차 유찰. 성심당 대전역에서 나갈까? 지금도 월 1억씩 내는데, 왜 이렇게 임대료 올랐나. 원칙이라고 해도… 돈 벌수록 버티기 어렵다. 부산역 입점했던 삼진어묵도 방 뺐다. 매출과 월세가 비례: 다른...
The post 성심당 코레일 월세 4억 원의 비밀. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 20, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978238/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978238/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T03:42:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 20, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블로그 안내]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/2024-06-19/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/2024-06-19/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T23:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이런저런 글을 올리는 공간입니다.

RSS 피드
사는...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] “숨 쉬는 건 범죄가 아니다”…노숙도 마찬가지? 간단치 않은 사정들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79247</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/19/npsbs_scotushomeless/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsbs_scotushomeless"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:59:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 5월 1일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 미국 연방 대법원은 6월 말이면 회기를 마치고 여름 휴지기에 들어갑니다. 지난주가 이번 회기에 예정된 구두변론을 진행하는 마지막 주였습니다. 5월은 대법관들이 진정인과 피진정인 또는 원고와 피고의 주장을 추가로 듣는 일 없이 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[출구전략 없는 갈등, 이것은 민주주의가 아니다: 슬로우레터 6월20일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110486</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110486"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T22:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[북한과 러시아의 밀착, “침략당하면 상호 지원.” ‘지각 대장’ 푸틴. 쟁점과 현안. “인구 비상사태.” 복지가 부족해서 애 안 낳을까. 무기한 휴진? “처음 듣는 이야기.” 대통령 거부권 포기할 수 있나. 더 깊게 읽기. 한국이 가장 먹고 살기 힘들다. 쿠팡의 네 가지 거짓말. 다르게 읽기. 김건희가 변수다. 선을 넘는 이복현. 당원 중심 정당의 함정. 해법과 대안. 지역 대도시에...
The post 출구전략 없는 갈등, 이것은 민주주의가 아니다: 슬로우레터 6월20일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] How free software hijacked Philip Hazel's life]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978463/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978463/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T18:17:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Philip Hazel was 51 when he began the Exim message transfer agent (MTA)
project in 1995, which
led to the Perl-Compatible Regular
Expressions (PRCE) project in 1998. At 80,
he's maintained PCRE, and its successor PCRE2, for more than 27
years. For those doing the math, that's a year longer than LWN has
been in publication. Exim maintenance was handed off around the time
of his retirement in 2007. Now, he is ready to hand off PCRE2 as well,
if a successor can be found.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mate 1.28 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978946/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978946/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.28 of the MATE Desktop
has been released.
See the announcement for a full list of improvements and bug fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Libgcrypt 1.11.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978939/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978939/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 1.11.0 of Libgcrypt, a general-purpose library of
cryptographic building blocks, has been released by the GnuPG project:


This release starts a new stable branch of Libgcrypt with full API and
ABI compatibility to the 1.10 series.  Over the last years Jussi
Kivilinna put again a lot of work into speeding up the algorithms for
many commonly used CPUs.  Niibe-san implemented new APIs and algorithms
and also integrated quantum-resistant encryption algorithms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Capturing stack traces asynchronously with BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978736/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978736/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T14:15:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Andrii Nakryiko led a session at
the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit giving
a look into the APIs for capturing stack traces
using BPF, and how the APIs could be made more useful. BPF programs can capture the
current stack trace of a running process, including the portion in the kernel
during execution of a system call, which can be useful for diagnosing
performance problems, among other things. But there are substantial problems with
the existing API.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] How kernel CVE numbers are assigned]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978711/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978711/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T13:48:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It has been four months since Greg
Kroah-Hartman and MITRE
announced that the Linux kernel project had become its own CVE Numbering
Authority (CNA).  Since then, the Linux CNA Team has developed workflows
and mechanisms to help manage the various tasks associated with this
challenge.  There does however, appear to be a lack of understanding among
community members of the processes and rules the team have been working
within.  The principal aim of this article, written by a member of the
Linux kernel CNA team, is to clarify how the team works and how kernel CVE
numbers are assigned.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978907/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978907/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T13:13:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (container-tools, firefox, and flatpak), Debian (composer, roundcube, and thunderbird), Fedora (kitty and webkitgtk), Oracle (container-tools and flatpak), Red Hat (flatpak and java-1.8.0-ibm), SUSE (gdcm, gdk-pixbuf, libarchive, libzypp, zypper, ntfs-3g_ntfsprogs, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, podman, python-Werkzeug, and thunderbird), and Ubuntu (git, linux-hwe-6.5, mariadb, mariadb-10.6, and thunderbird).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing sensor capabilities: test characterization and linearization]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482525</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/optimizing-sensor-capabilities-test-characterization-and-linearization/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:53:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The benefits of optimizing sensors are enormous and include improving their accuracy, range, and sensitivity. Characterizing and linearizing sensors can help integrate them into larger...
The post Optimizing sensor capabilities: test characterization and linearization appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernard Ang</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[쿠팡의 거짓말]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110411</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110411"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T08:23:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[0. 극단적 요약 (1분) “쿠팡은 모험가의 도전과 성공을 훔친다” (권호현) 온라인플랫폼공정화법(온플법) 제정이 필요한 이유다. 1. PB상품으로 물가 안정에 기여? 쿠팡이 PB 상품으로 물가 안정에 기여했다고요? 거짓말입니다. 쿠팡은 내부 보고 문건에서 자체 분석하고 있습니다. (쿠팡이 랭킹 조작이나 리뷰 조작 등을 중단할 경우) “1) 소비자 1인당 지출 2) 입점업체 평균 판매가 3) 쿠팡 PB 등 자체 상품...
The post 쿠팡의 거짓말 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>권호현</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/19, 엔비디아 시총 1위 등극을 보며]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595087</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595087/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%8b%9c%ec%b4%9d-1%ec%9c%84-%eb%93%b1%ea%b7%b9"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T08:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation topology considerations]]></title>
        <id>823cacac-3fd9-41b3-977d-11eb58000cb0</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/19/red-hat-openshift-data-foundation-topology-considerations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are many different factors to consider when using Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation to set up a storage cluster. This article dives into some specifics to consider when building a production-grade resilient scalable deployment of OpenShift Data Foundation. We'll need to dig into the following points to design and build out a suitable deployment architecture:

What does the underlying platform environment look like in terms of architecture/topology/design?
What underlying storage is available and how is that presented?
Replication options.

To start, if you're new to OpenShift Data Foundation, please see the architecture documentation to get a high level understanding of what the operator provides and is doing. Under the covers, OpenShift Data Foundation uses Rook and Ceph. If you are…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>James Force, Travis Nielsen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/19, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595078</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595078/6-19-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T01:08:58.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“얻다 대고 애완견인가”, 언론의 반발: 슬로우레터 6월19일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110374</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110374"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T22:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[의료 대란, 해결 의지가 없다. 쟁점과 현안. 방송3법과 방통위법 과방위 통과. “언론 스스로 증명하라.” 저널리즘의 개(犬) 사분면. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명 일극 체제가 완성됐다. 민주당의 속도전. 과반 의석으로 못할 게 뭐냐는 질문에 대한 답변. 국민의힘 전당대회는 반윤 vs 비윤. 다르게 읽기. 창의력은 2위, 자신감은 49위. 김만배 인터뷰 배후가 김만배? 내년 집값? 해법과 대안. 엑스포 외교...
The post “얻다 대고 애완견인가”, 언론의 반발: 슬로우레터 6월19일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[I _____ hate arrays in C++!]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1134/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1134/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Or why I think developers need to know about them but should not use them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embedded Rust: Hello World!]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482510</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/embedded-rust-hello-world/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:57:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series on Embedded Rust, we will look at Rust syntax, resources, and design methodologies that can be applied to embedded systems. It’s a...
The post Embedded Rust: Hello World! appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How It’s Made: AI Roadtrip, a Pixel Campaign Powered by Generative AI and Fans]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-ai-roadtrip-a-pixel-campaign-powered-by-generative-ai-and-fans/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-ai-roadtrip-a-pixel-campaign-powered-by-generative-ai-and-fans/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T20:14:31.967Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best Phones Forever: AI Roadtrip is our first experiment in using generative AI to put fans in the driver's seat and bring characters to life.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Software-defined radar enables hardware to be customized for ADAS]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482512</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/software-defined-radar-enables-hardware-to-be-customized-for-adas/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:58:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arbe SDR architecture is said to offer OEMs and Tier 1s full control over key radar parameters and operation modes, enabling customized performance and optimized operations in various driving scenarios.
The post Software-defined radar enables hardware to be customized for ADAS appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Adding a JIT compiler to CPython]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977855/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977855/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T17:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the big-ticket items for the upcoming Python 3.13 release is an experimental just-in-time (JIT) compiler for the language;
the other is, of course, the removal of the 
global interpreter lock (GIL), which is also an experiment.  Brandt
Bucher is a member of the Faster CPython project, which is
working on making the reference implementation of the language faster via a
variety of techniques.  Last year at PyCon, he gave a talk about the specializing adaptive
interpreter; at PyCon 2024 in Pittsburgh, he described the work he and others have been doing
to add a copy-and-patch JIT compiler to CPython.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] BPF tracing performance]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978335/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978335/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On the final day of the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, the BPF track
opened with a series of sessions on improving the performance and
flexibility of probes and other performance-monitoring tools, in the kernel and in
user space. Jiri Olsa led two sessions about different aspects of probes:
making the API for BPF programs attached to a probe more flexible, and making
user-space probes more efficient.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Plasma 6.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978806/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978806/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.1 of
the Plasma desktop environment has been released.


	Plasma 6 hits its stride with version 6.1. While Plasma 6.0 was all
	about getting the migration to the underlying Qt 6 frameworks
	correct (and what a massive job that was), 6.1 is where developers
	start implementing the features that will take you desktop to a new
	level.


Enhancements include better remote-desktop support, improved customization,
persistent apps, smoother animation under Wayland, and more; see the
changelog for the full list.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978804/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978804/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (php7.3), Fedora (galera, ghostscript, and mariadb), Mageia (cups, iperf, and libndp), Oracle (firefox and flatpak), Red Hat (container-tools:rhel8, Firefox, firefox, and flatpak), SUSE (booth, bouncycastle, firefox, ghostscript, less, libaom, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, podman, python-Authlib, python-requests, python-Werkzeug, webkit2gtk3, and xdg-desktop-portal), and Ubuntu (ghostscript, ruby-rack, ruby2.7, ruby3.0, ruby3.1, ruby3.2, and sssd).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastering motor control: functional safety]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482507</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/mastering-motor-control-functional-safety/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T11:53:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By integrating robust safety measures and compliance with established safety standards, we can ensure that motor control systems not only perform efficiently but also uphold...
The post Mastering motor control: functional safety appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Boris Radonic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat UBI container images]]></title>
        <id>a42ea76d-fc6e-4a7b-b799-779a62bed8de</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/18/build-applications-paketo-buildpacks-and-red-hat-ubi-container-images"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the growth in the use of containers, the need to bundle your application into a container has never been stronger. Many Red Hat customers will be familiar with Source-to-Image (S2I) as an easy way to build container images from application source code. While S2I is a convenient way to build images on Red Hat OpenShift, Red Hat works to support our customers when using a variety of approaches, and we’ve recently seen an increasing interest in building applications using Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) Buildpacks.  
This is the first in a 5-part series of articles on building your applications with C and UBI. The series will include:

Building applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat UBI container images (this post)
Running applications with Paketo Buildpacks and Red Hat…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Michael Dawson, Ozzy Osborne, Costas Papastathis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding support for s390x in LLD, the LLVM linker]]></title>
        <id>0dbb476d-69f9-44cf-b4a6-9481dff86734</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/18/adding-support-s390x-lld-llvm-linker"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LLD is a linker developed by the LLVM project. It is a drop-in replacement for the system linker and aims to consume less resources than them.
LLD provides production-quality support for the following architectures:

AArch64 and ARM
LoongArch
MIPS
PowerPC and PowerPC64
RISC-V
x86-32 and x86-64

Despite this list, there is still one architecture supported by Fedora that was missing: s390x. This absence impacts how Fedora packages are built on s390x, either by prohibiting packages that require LLD or by requiring that the s390x package is linked with a different linker than other architectures. This difference is known to increase the maintenance burden because different linkers can behave differently.
The support for s390x was added to LLD 18.1. In this article, we explore the work involved…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tulio Magno Quites Machado Filho</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[23년 커피 프랜차이즈 매출 및 영업이익 비교]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595064</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595064/23%eb%85%84-%ec%bb%a4%ed%94%bc-%ed%94%84%eb%9e%9c%ec%b0%a8%eb%8b%88%ec%a6%88-%eb%a7%a4%ec%b6%9c-%eb%b0%91-%ec%98%81%ec%97%85%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T06:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/18, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595047</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595047/6-18-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T01:56:59.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[일론 머스크의 관심 값이 64조 원… 인류의 희망을 거는 대가, 맞나요?]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79531</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/17/npsp_muskpaypackage/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_muskpaypackage"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T01:15:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[테슬라 주주들이 창업자이자 CEO 일론 머스크에게 스톡 옵션으로 3억 주를 (할인된 가격에) 지급하는 전례를 찾기 힘든 대형 급여안을 승인했습니다. 첫 번째도 아니고 6년 전에 이미 한 번 승인했던 걸 법원이 무효로 하자 마치 법원에 시위라도 하듯 그대로 다시 승인한 겁니다. 테슬라의 주가에 따라 정확한 가치가 달라지겠지만, 460억 달러, 우리돈 64조 원에 이르는 전례 없는 급여입니다. 이번 급여안을 둘러싼 논란의 배경과 맥락을 분석했습니다. 전문 번역: ‘어그로꾼’이 된 머스크, 그의 급여 460억 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[대왕고래 20% 확률, 공개 검증해야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월18일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110322</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110322"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T22:18:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[푸틴-김정은 만난다. 환자들 분통? 예상보다 적었다? 쟁점과 현안. 다시 등장한 언론 징벌적 손배 카드. 대왕고래 20% 확률, 공개 검증하자. 더 깊게 읽기. 420억 원 상속받는 상위 0.27% 세금 깎아주기. 최태원 판결문 오류. 다르게 읽기. 민주주의에 대한 세 가지 오해. 한국은 왜 징역 100년 안 되나. 해법과 대안. 소득대체율 인상이 개혁 맞나. 종부세 없앨 수 있나....
The post 대왕고래 20% 확률, 공개 검증해야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월18일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.31: new C++ analyzer features, enhanced user annotations, and more]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1133/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/1133/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PVS-Studio 7.31 has been released. We have so much news to share with you! We've enhanced the user annotation system, the mode to analyze individual files, and much more! Learn more release details...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Static keys for BPF]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977993/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977993/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T19:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel has a lot of code paths that are normally disabled: debugging print
statements, tracepoints, etc. To support these efficiently, there
is a common mechanism called

static keys that provides a way to enable or disable a
code path at run time, with effectively no overhead for disabled
branches. BPF programs have not been able to take advantage of static keys so far,
because they aren't compiled into the kernel.
Now, it looks like BPF may be getting support for a similar mechanism —
and the design could also provide one of the components needed to support

jump tables, another missing feature.
Anton Protopovov presented his plans to add static keys to BPF at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PostmarketOS v24.06 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978733/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978733/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T18:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[PostmarketOS is an Alpine Linux
derivative distribution aimed at mobile devices; the v24.06
release claims support for over 250 devices, though the level of that
support varies widely.  "This release is geared mainly towards Linux
enthusiasts. We are working hard on stability improvements and automated
testing, but if you expect Android or iOS levels of polish, then this is
not for you yet."  Changes include an upgrade to Alpine Linux 3.20,
newer GNOME and KDE versions, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Nested bottom-half locking for realtime kernels]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978189/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978189/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:27:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Software-interrupt handlers (also called "bottom halves") have a long
history in the Linux kernel; for much of that history, developers have
wished that they could go away.  One of their unfortunate characteristics
is that they can add unexpected latency to the execution of unrelated
processes; this problem is felt especially acutely in the
realtime-preemption community.  The solution adopted there has created
problems of its own, though; in response Sebastian Andrzej Siewior is proposing
a new locking mechanism for realtime builds of the kernel that may have
benefits for non-realtime users as well.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978709/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978709/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:14:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (389-ds-base, buildah, c-ares, cockpit, containernetworking-plugins, fence-agents, gdk-pixbuf2, gvisor-tap-vsock, libreoffice, podman, python-idna, rpm-ostree, and ruby), Debian (atril, chromium, ffmpeg, libndp, libvpx, nano, plasma-workspace, pymongo, roundcube, sendmail, and thunderbird), Fedora (booth and thunderbird), Mageia (aom, atril, libvpx, nano, nss, firefox, and vte), Red Hat (linux-firmware), SUSE (bind, booth, mariadb, openssl-1_1, php7, php8, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (linux-azure, linux-azure-fde, linux-azure, linux-gke, and linux-nvidia-6.5).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[컴포즈커피 사례, 컴포즈커피의 놀라운 영입이익률 비결은?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595035</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595035/%ec%bb%b4%ed%8f%ac%ec%a6%88%ec%bb%a4%ed%94%bc-%ec%98%81%ec%9e%85%ec%9d%b4%ec%9d%b5%eb%a5%a0-%eb%b9%84%ea%b2%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T11:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[밥 먹여주는 정치: 경제를 알아야 선동에 흔들리지 않는다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110290</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110290"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T10:43:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[낙수효과의 유래 낙수효과. 이 단어는 어느 무능한 대통령을 비판할 때 처음 등장했다. 92년 전 미국 대공황 시절 코미디언이자 사회평론가 윌 로저스가 원조다. 물과 달리 돈은 오히려 아래에서 위로 흐르는 사실을 모른다며, 허버트 후버 대통령을 풍자했다. 낙수효과 따위 없다는 얘기다. 그런데 낙수효과는 1980년대 이후 신자유주의 핵심 키워드가 됐다. [경제신문이 말하지 않는 경제 이야기], 1장의 에피소드다. 경제...
The post 밥 먹여주는 정치: 경제를 알아야 선동에 흔들리지 않는다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>정혜승</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experiment and test AI models with Podman AI Lab]]></title>
        <id>291150c5-b1a4-454e-b94c-727611e85178</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/17/experiment-and-test-ai-models-podman-ai-lab"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Experimenting with AI models and testing different prompts is a key part of developing AI-enabled applications. However, setting up the right environment and managing model dependencies can be challenging. Podman AI Lab's Playground feature solves this by providing an intuitive, containerized environment for exploring open-source machine learning models locally. Let’s explore the Playground feature in-depth and show how it can accelerate your application development workflow when working with generative AI.
What is Podman AI Lab?
Podman AI Lab is an extension for Podman Desktop, the graphical tool for managing containers and Kubernetes, and enables developers to work with large language models (LLMs) and other AI models locally on their machine. It provides an intuitive interface to discov…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Cedric Clyburn, Legare Kerrison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Protect apps with Red Hat build of Keycloak and Active Directory Federation Services]]></title>
        <id>d4d4d891-84f4-467b-b90d-81c8dd8a1d5d</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/17/protect-apps-red-hat-build-keycloak-and-active-directory-federation-services"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Active Directory Federation Services (AD FS) terminology, Red Hat build of Keycloak will be set up as a Resource Federation Server and AD FS as an Account Federation Server. This means that users will reside in Active Directory (AD) on Windows Server, while the protected web app will reside within the realm protected by Red Hat build of Keycloak on Red Hat OpenShift. With this, we want AD FS to authenticate users to give them access to web apps on OpenShift. Hence, when a user with an account in AD tries to access a web app on OpenShift, the user will be redirected to Red Hat build of Keycloak where they can choose to authenticate with AD FS. The user doesn't need to have an account in Red Hat build of Keycloak or in OpenShift for this to work.
In Red Hat build of Keycloak terminology, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Torbjorn Dahlen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Displaying File Time in C++: Finally fixed in C++20]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2024/file-time-cpp20/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2024/file-time-cpp20/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this blog post, we’ll examine the potentially simple task of getting and displaying file time. Usually, we can depend on some library or OS-specific code to get that file property. Fortunately, since C++20, we have a reliable and simple technique from the std::filesystem and std::chrono components.
Let’s jump in.



     
    


In C++, working with files was usually reserved for OS APIs and third-party libraries. Here are two examples of such an approach:



     
    


In Linux or any POSIX-compliant system, you can use the stat function to get file times.
#include <iostream>
#include <fstream>
#include <sys/stat.h>
#include <ctime>

int main() {
    const char* file_path = "example.txt";
    std::ofstream(file_path) << "Hello, World!";

    struct stat file_stat;

    if (stat(file_…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 기후변화로 인한 ‘변화’가 이 정도였어? 뜻밖의 결과들]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79227</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/16/npsp_climatechangeimpact/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_climatechangeimpact"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:59:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 29일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 주말 내내 세계 각지의 이상기후 소식이 전해졌습니다. 에콰도르에서는 극심한 가뭄으로 에너지 비상사태가 선포되었고, 파키스탄과 두바이, 카자흐스탄에서는 이례적인 폭우가 쏟아졌습니다. 하지만 해수면 상승으로 삶의 터전이 눈앞에서 사라지는 바닷가나 폭우로 매년 여름 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>eyesopen1</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc4]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978629/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978629/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:28:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linus has released 6.10-rc4 for testing.
"Apart from a rather unusual spike in the diffstat due to a parisc fix,
things look normal and pretty small."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[장인어른]]></title>
        <id>https://edykim.com/ko/post/father-in-law/</id>
        <link href="https://edykim.com/ko/post/father-in-law/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[올해 초 장인어른께서 야속하게도 소천하셨다.
장인어른은 정말 평생 일만 하셨다. 차량정비를 하셨는데, 주6일 출근하시고도 주말...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>edykim.com 블로그 RSS 피드</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“언론은 검찰의 애완견”, 이재명이 화난 이유는?: 슬로우레터 6월17일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110251</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110251"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T22:09:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“언론은 검찰의 애완견.” 안부수와 이화영 판결 달랐다. 쟁점과 현안. 동해 유전 탐사는 이미 1월에 결정됐다. 한 다리 건너 모두 아는 사람들. 오늘부터 서울대병원 휴진. 더 깊게 읽기. 용산발 감세 드라이브. 지금 이 시점에 부자 감세 맞나. 윤석열의 남은 3년. 다르게 읽기. 권익위가 김영란법을 모르나. 검사 시절과 입장이 달라진 건가. 독일의 한국 정치사 수업. 해법과 대안....
The post “언론은 검찰의 애완견”, 이재명이 화난 이유는?: 슬로우레터 6월17일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Distribution of program sizes]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8866</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/06/16/distribution-of-program-sizes/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T21:43:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Program size, in lines of code (LOC), used to be a topic of conversation among developers and managers. Program size is an issue when computer memory is measured in kilobytes. Large programs would be organized into overlays such that only small subsets needed to be held in memory at any time, i.e., programmer defined memory […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How template method can ruin your Java code]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1132/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1132/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OOP is wonderful. Programmers usually criticize those who don't follow this paradigm, while the knowledge of patterns is often a must. However, even the right approach doesn't completely protect from...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome India to the Google Wallet API]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/welcome-india-google-wallet-api/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T20:13:20.573Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To all developers in India: Welcome to the Google Wallet API! Now you can create digital assets like boarding passes, event tickets, gift cards, loyalty cards, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything you need to know about Google Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/everything-google-wallet-at-io-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T20:13:20.573Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All the new features and enhancements Google Wallet announced at I/O this year, focused on security, wearables, push notifications, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Some weekend stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978591/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978591/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T19:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The
6.9.5,
6.6.34,
6.1.94,
5.15.161,
5.10.219,
5.4.278, and
4.19.316
stable kernels have all been released; each contains another set of
important fixes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[블름버그인텔리전스, 미국인 전기차 선호는 여전하나 내연기관 대체는 어렵다]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595028</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595028/%eb%af%b8%ea%b5%ad%ec%9d%b8-%ec%a0%84%ea%b8%b0%ec%b0%a8-%ec%84%a0%ed%98%b8"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T01:53:47.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘인구소멸’ 한국을 위해 할 수 있는 일]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79516</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/15/npsp_aging/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aging"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:45:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이미 고령화 사회를 지나 초고령화 사회를 향해 빠르게 나아가는 한국 사회에서 나타나는 문제의 많은 부분을 풀 수 있는 열쇠는 나이 든 기성세대가 쥐고 있다고 할 수 있습니다. 노화를 우아하게 수용하는 법에 관해 찰스 블로우가 쓴 글을 번역하고, 해설을 썼습니다. 기성세대가 세상이 바뀌었다는 걸 이해하고, 바뀐 세상에서 살아가야 할 다음 세대의 어려움을 함부로 재단하지 않는 모습을 보여줬으면 좋겠습니다. 전문 번역: 눈가 주름이 지혜와 우아함의 대가라니! – 우아하게 노화를 수용한다는 것 해설: “라떼는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A discussion of discussions on AI bias]]></title>
        <id>https://danluu.com/ai-bias/</id>
        <link href="https://danluu.com/ai-bias/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There've been regular viral stories about ML/AI bias with LLMs and generative AI for the past couple years. One thing I find interesting about discussions of bias is how different the reaction is in the LLM and generative AI case when compared to "classical" bugs in cases where there's a clear bug. In particular, if you look at forums or other discussions with lay people, people frequently deny that a model which produces output that's sort of the opposite of what the user asked for is even a bug. For example, a year ago, an Asian MIT grad student asked Playground AI (PAI) to "Give the girl from the original photo a professional linkedin profile photo" and PAI converted her face to a white face with blue eyes.
The top "there's no bias" response on the front-page reddit story, and one of th…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>danluu.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Constant Integer Type Declarations Initialized With Constant Expressions Should Be Constants]]></title>
        <id>https://thephd.dev/constant-integers-are-actually-constant-wow-finally-someones-writing-the-goddamn-paper-%F0%9F%99%84</id>
        <link href="https://thephd.dev/constant-integers-are-actually-constant-wow-finally-someones-writing-the-goddamn-paper-%F0%9F%99%84"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Constant integer-typed (including enumeration-typed) object declarations in C that are immediately initialized with an integer constant expression should just be constant expressions. That’s it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The Pasture</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google I/O 2024 recap: Making AI accessible and helpful for every developer]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-io-2024-recap-making-ai-accessible-and-helpful-for-every-developer/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-io-2024-recap-making-ai-accessible-and-helpful-for-every-developer/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you for joining us at this year's Google I/O. Check out all of the Google I/O announcements and updates with 150+ sessions and learning content available on demand.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Edge Torch: High Performance Inference of PyTorch Models on Mobile Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-high-performance-inference-of-pytorch-models-on-mobile-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/ai-edge-torch-high-performance-inference-of-pytorch-models-on-mobile-devices/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Released today, AI Edge Torch enables support for PyTorch, JAX, Keras, and TensorFlow with TFLite.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The power of Checks is now available to all Android and iOS Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/checks-now-available-to-all-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/checks-now-available-to-all-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Checks identifies potential privacy issues, provides recommendations, monitors app compliance, and provides results in an intuitive dashboard or directly in your CI/CD.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in Firebase at  I/O '24]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-firebase-io-24/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/whats-new-in-firebase-io-24/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase, is evolving to enable you to rapidly build and run AI-powered experiences in your apps across platforms.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build for Tomorrow in the Gemini API Developer Competition]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-for-tomorrow-in-the-gemini-api-developer-competition/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/build-for-tomorrow-in-the-gemini-api-developer-competition/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.419Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build a new app with the Gemini API or integrate our Gemini API into an existing application for a chance to win some really cool prizes.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start Building with Project IDX Today]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-project-idx-today/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/start-building-with-project-idx-today/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.417Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve removed the waitlist for Project IDX. Now, anyone can sign up to start building with AI-assistance, collaboration capabilities, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Firebase Genkit helped add AI to our Compass app]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-firebase-genkit-helped-add-ai-to-our-compass-app/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.415Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We used Firebase Genkit – Firebase’s open source framework for building powerful AI features into your apps with familiar patterns and paradigms – to add AI to an existing application.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google AR at I/O 2024: New Geospatial AR features and more]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-ar-at-io-2024-new-geospatial-ar-features-and-more/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/google-ar-at-io-2024-new-geospatial-ar-features-and-more/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.415Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've been exploring new ways to create engaging, easy to use, and shareable experiences and connect your Geospatial AR creations with more users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Home APIs: Enabling all developers to build for the home]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/home-apis-enabling-all-developers-to-build-for-the-home/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/home-apis-enabling-all-developers-to-build-for-the-home/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T20:13:56.415Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We've re-envisioned Google Home as a platform for all developers – not just those that build smart home devices – to create innovative experiences for the home.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reports from the Python Language Summit]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978541/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978541/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T19:38:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Software Foundation has published a
set of reports from the 2024 Python Language summit.  Topics covered
include version numbering, the limited C API, a new default read-eval-print
loop, and Python's security model in light of the XZ backdoor:


	For multiple reasons like being able to fix bugs and
	single-maintainer modules, CPython doesn't require reviewers on the
	pull requests of core developers. This can lead to "unilateral
	action", meaning that a change is introduced into CPython without
	the review of someone besides the author. Other situations like
	release managers backporting fixes to other branches without review
	are common.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/15, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595019</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595019/6-15-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T09:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[너무 늦었던 양평 용문사 은행나무 출사기]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594547</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594547/%eb%84%88%eb%ac%b4-%eb%8a%a6%ec%97%88%eb%8d%98-%ec%96%91%ed%8f%89-%ec%9a%a9%eb%ac%b8%ec%82%ac-%ec%9d%80%ed%96%89%eb%82%98%eb%ac%b4-%ec%b6%9c%ec%82%ac%ea%b8%b0"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T08:48:23.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 데이트 상대로 ‘심리 상담’ 받는 사람을 선호한다고? 운동만 자기 관리가 아니다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79211</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/14/npsp_mindsos/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_mindsos"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T22:59:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 24일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 저는 한국에서 의과대학 교육을 받고, 미국에서 일하고 있는 정신과 의사입니다. 미국에서는 정신질환 및 정신건강 서비스를 향한 낙인이 많이 사라졌습니다. 제가 처음 태평양을 건너온 10년 전과 비교하면 피부로 느껴질 정도입니다. → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>rukahs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making development across platforms easier for developers]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/making-development-across-platforms-easier-for-developers/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/making-development-across-platforms-easier-for-developers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:14:08.594Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do what works best for your business; whether you’re sharing both UI and business logic across multiple platforms with Flutter or development with Kotlin Multiplatform.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing PaliGemma, Gemma 2, and an Upgraded Responsible AI Toolkit]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-and-toolkit-expansion-io-2024/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/gemma-family-and-toolkit-expansion-io-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T20:14:08.593Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Gemma family expands further with the introduction of PaliGemma, and a sneak peek into the near future with the announcement of Gemma 2.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Schaller: Fedora Workstation development update – AI edition]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978470/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978470/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T19:09:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Christian Schaller writes about AI and GPU-related features that are in flight and planned for Fedora 41.
streamlined user experience in GNOME Software to let you install the binary NVIDIA driver and provide you with an integrated graphical user interface help to sign the kernel module for use with secure boot. This is a bit different than what we for instance are doing in RHEL, where we are working with NVIDIA to provide pre-signed kernel modules, but that is a lot harder to do in Fedora due to the rapidly updating kernel versions and which most Fedora users appreciate as a big plus. So instead what we are for opting in Fedora is as I said to make it simple for you to self-sign the kernel module for use with secure boot. We are currently looking at when we can make this feature available, but no later than Fedora Workstation 41 for sure.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Human Interface Guidelines for KDE]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978465/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978465/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T17:18:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[KDE developer Nate Graham has announced
a new set of KDE Human
Interface Guidelines (HIG) for the KDE project. Graham says that the goals
for the new HIGs were to reflect how KDE designs software today, make
the content 100% actionable, improve navigation, and to improve the
guidelines so people feel comfortable contributing:
contributing!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Aeon: openSUSE for lazy developers]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977987/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977987/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T14:29:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE project recently announced
the second release candidate (RC2) of its Aeon Desktop, formerly known
as MicroOS Desktop GNOME. Aside from the new coat of naming paint,
Aeon breaks ground in a few other ways by dabbling with technologies not found in other openSUSE releases. The goal for Aeon is to provide
automated system updates using snapshots that can be applied
atomically, removing the burden of system maintenance for
"lazy developers" who want to focus on their work rather than desktop
administration. System-tinkerers need not apply.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving forward in Android drivers (Project Zero)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978441/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978441/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T14:24:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This
Project Zero article looks at the exploitation of a few Android driver
bugs in great detail.


	As it becomes more difficult to find 0-days in core Android,
	third-party Linux kernel drivers continue to become a more and more
	attractive target for attackers. While the bulk of present-day
	detected ITW [in-the-wild] Android exploitation targets GPU
	drivers, it's equally important that other third-party drivers are
	encouraged towards the same security standards.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978418/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978418/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:18:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by CentOS (389-ds-base, bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, and dhcp, firefox, glibc, ipa, less, libreoffice, and thunderbird), Debian (cups), Fedora (chromium and cyrus-imapd), Mageia (golang and poppler), Oracle (bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, and dhcp, gvisor-tap-vsock, python-idna, and ruby), Red Hat (dnsmasq and expat), SUSE (libaom, php8, podman, python-pymongo, python-scikit-learn, and tiff), and Ubuntu (h2database and vte2.91).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPC라고 왜 말을 못하나: 우리는 피에 젖은 빵을 먹고 있다.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110180</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110180"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T09:25:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] SPC 사망 사고 그 이후. 제빵 원료를 만드는 공장에서 일하던 노동자가 소스 배합기에 끼어 숨지는 사고가 있었다. 사람이 죽어나간 그 자리에서 동료 노동자들은 계속 공장을 돌렸다. 다음날 빈소에 찾아온 회사 직원들은 크림빵과 단팥빵을 두 상자 내려놓고 갔다. 한국 최대 규모 제빵 프랜차이즈를 거느린 SPC 그룹 계열사 SPL에서 벌어진 일이다. 유족들은 울부짖었다. “우리 아이가 이...
The post SPC라고 왜 말을 못하나: 우리는 피에 젖은 빵을 먹고 있다. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[석열바라기 KBS: 순방 중에도 “지진 피해 신속 파악” 개별 보도]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110169</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110169"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T04:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[전북 부안에서 6월 12일 오전 8시 26분경 규모 4.8의 지진이 발생했습니다. 2016년 경북 경주의 규모 5.8 지진을 시작으로 경북 포항, 충북 괴산에 이어 전북 부안에서 올해 들어 최대 규모의 지진이 일어난 것입니다. 수도권 등에서도 감지될 만큼 강진이었는데요. 지진 규모와 더불어 한반도가 더 이상 지진 안전지대가 아니라는 위기감에 언론도 긴급히 보도했습니다. 그러나 KBS는 해외순방 중인 대통령의...
The post 석열바라기 KBS: 순방 중에도 “지진 피해 신속 파악” 개별 보도 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/14, 테슬라 주총과 이론 머스크 보상 패키지 승인을 보는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=595001</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/595001/%ec%9d%bc%eb%a1%a0-%eb%a8%b8%ec%8a%a4%ed%81%ac-%eb%b3%b4%ec%83%81-%ed%8c%a8%ed%82%a4%ec%a7%80"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T03:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using NXP i.MX RT685 with pyOCD: Device Support and Debugging Configuration]]></title>
        <id>http://mcuoneclipse.com/?p=40717</id>
        <link href="https://mcuoneclipse.com/2024/06/14/using-nxp-i-mx-rt685-with-pyocd-device-support-and-debugging-configuration/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T23:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The NXP i.MX RT685 features an ARM Cortex M33 with a Cadence Xtensa audio DSP. To use the NXP EVK board with pyOCD, additional device support is required. By installing the RT685 packs, it becomes easy to debug with pyOCD using Eclipse/MCUXpresso for the NXP i.MX RT685 target board. Happy debugging! Continue reading →]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Erich Styger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[탄핵 훨씬 어려워졌다 Vs. 더 큰 불행 막아야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월14일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110142</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110142"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T22:20:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[존재감 없는 국민의힘. 쟁점과 현안. 이화영 재판 판사, 이재명 재판도 맡는다. “나도 ‘배우자’더러 받으라고 해야겠네.” 나쁜 풍선인지 좋은 풍선인지 까봐야 안다? 더 깊게 읽기. 탄핵은 훨씬 더 어려워졌다. 탄핵이 불행인가. “언론이 없으면 얼마나 좋겠나.” 당심과 민심 8:2. 더 깊게 읽기. 경찰 판 ‘스포트라이트’. 우리 PB 상품을 맨 위에. 오늘의 TMI. 요즘 개인택시 수입 월 700만...
The post 탄핵 훨씬 어려워졌다 Vs. 더 큰 불행 막아야 한다: 슬로우레터 6월14일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smile while drowning in bugs]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1131/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1131/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many times, we've written about bugs in games, in space flight software, etc. Now we'd like to honor the tradition. This time, we'll take a look at the bugs that have crept into some of the biggest...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving forward in Android drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/driving-forward-in-android-drivers.html</id>
        <link href="https://googleprojectzero.blogspot.com/2024/06/driving-forward-in-android-drivers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T18:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[@import url(https://themes.googleusercontent.com/fonts/css?kit=MXVwpSGzOOhqOc5hUWJbBLizfYjsfH9XaeDpmRKYJN5bV0WvE1cEyAoIq5yYZlSc);.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-3>li:before{content:"\0025cf   "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-7>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-7,lower-latin) ". "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-2>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-4>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-6>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-6,decimal) ". "}.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-8>li:before{content:"" counter(lst-ctn-kix_m966q2gfyys4-8,lower-roman) ". "}.lst-kix_kbd3zqh16g9u-4>li{counter-increment:lst-ctn-kix_kbd3zqh16g9u-4}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-1>li:before{content:"\0025cb   "}.lst-kix_3dxxrae9diso-5>li:before{content:"\0025a0   "}ol.lst-kix_m966q2gfyys4-3.start{co…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Project Zero</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Simplifying the BPF verifier]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977815/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977815/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T17:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The BPF verifier is a complex program. This has the unfortunate effect of making
it simultaneously more difficult for contributors to work on, and more likely
to harbor unknown bugs. Shung-Hsi Yu had two concrete proposals for how to
simplify the verifier to make it easier to maintain that he presented at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit. Yu proposed changing how the
verifier tracks partially known values and cleaning up the interface to
hide the details of the value-tracker's internal representation.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Improving control-flow integrity for Linux on RISC-V]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977720/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977720/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T16:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Redirecting execution flow is a common malware
technique that can be used to compromise operating systems. To protect from such attacks,
the chip makers of leading architectures like x86 and arm64 have implemented
control-flow-integrity (CFI) extensions, though they need system
software support to function. At the Linux
Security Summit North America,  RISC-V kernel developer Deepak Gupta described the CFI
protections for that architecture and  invited community input on the
kernel support for them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust 1.79.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978323/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978323/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:48:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
1.79.0 of the Rust language has been released.  Changes this time
include inline const expressions, the "associated item bounds
syntax", and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978291/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978291/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:11:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Debian (firefox-esr), Fedora (nginx-mod-modsecurity, php, and tomcat), Mageia (strongswan), Oracle (389-ds-base, buildah, c-ares, cockpit, containernetworking-plugins, fence-agents, firefox, gdk-pixbuf2, idm:DL1, ipa, kernel, libreoffice, podman, rpm-ostree, and thunderbird), Red Hat (dnsmasq and nghttp2), Slackware (mozilla), SUSE (curl, firefox, kernel, kernel-firmware-nvidia-gspx-G06, nvidia-open- driver-G06-signed, openssl-3, and python-Pillow), and Ubuntu (libmatio, libndp, linux, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.4, linux-azure, linux-azure-5.4, linux-gcp,
 linux-gcp-5.4, linux-gkeop, linux-hwe-5.4, linux-ibm, linux-ibm-5.4,
 linux-kvm, linux-oracle, linux-oracle-5.4, linux-raspi, linux-raspi-5.4,
 linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux-oem-6.5, and virtuoso-opensource).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying the role of an automation developer (it's not what you think)]]></title>
        <id>7bcfd2ee-c9d8-4c8e-91d0-d0178b32e01a</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/13/demystifying-role-automation-developer-its-not-what-you-think"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the rapidly evolving field of IT, new roles, titles, and frameworks often emerge, leading to varying terminology across organizations. One such role is the automation developer.
Despite what the title might suggest, an automation developer is not a traditional software developer. In fact, most automation developers (or automation engineers or platform engineers) don’t have extensive development skills or backgrounds in coding, yet they are creating Ansible content every day and are contributing to the successful adoption of automation within their organization.
Traditional developers vs. the automation developers
When we think of a traditional software developer, we imagine someone who writes code to build applications. Their work involves designing, coding, testing, and maintaining sof…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anshul Behl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A practical guide to linker section ordering]]></title>
        <id>02af4efc-1a6a-41e2-a47d-88c451288c05</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/13/practical-guide-linker-section-ordering"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The location of code and data in memory can have a big effect on a program's performance. Placing functions that reference each other frequently in the same area of memory can help reduce the need to load and unload pages of memory. Similarly, pieces of data that are used a lot at the same time benefit from being located in the same region of memory.
Alternatively, sometimes it is better not to group code and data based upon its use, but rather upon its similarity to each other. Placing similar code and data in adjacent memory regions means that the binary image can be compressed to a greater degree, a feature which is often important for mobile applications.
Compilers attempt to address these needs via the use of profile directed optimizations as well as supporting language features like …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Clifton</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to manage and preserve Kafka Connect offsets smoothly]]></title>
        <id>d1be7b84-24e7-42cc-9252-14a96657c986</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/13/how-manage-and-preserve-kafka-connect-offsets-smoothly"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever faced the challenge of needing to recreate a Kafka Connector while preserving its offset position? If so, we have fantastic news for you!
Picture this: your Kafka Connect cluster is perfectly set up, your connectors are finely tuned, and everything is running smoothly. Suddenly, you need to recreate one of your connectors. The thought of losing all the offset information is daunting—nobody wants to risk data duplication or loss.
But worry no more, because Red Hat AMQ Streams 2.6 on Red Hat OpenShift (based on Apache Kafka 3.6.0 and Strimzi 0.38.x) has introduced a revolutionary feature: first-class offsets support with KIP-875. This new feature includes REST API endpoints specifically designed for managing connector offsets, making it seamless to preserve your offset position…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abdellatif Bouchama</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5인 미만 사업장은 언제나 시기상조]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109384</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109384"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T05:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)의 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기 강약약강 국회가 5인 미만 사업장에 대한 근로기준법 전면 적용 논의를 본격적으로 시작한다. 1989년 최저임금, 주휴수당, 퇴직금 등 일부 조항만 예외적으로 적용하기로 개정한 지 32년 만이다. 김윤나영(경향신문), 노동권 사각지대 ‘5인 미만 사업장’ 근로기준법 적용, 이번엔 될까?, 2021.12.15. 중대재해처벌법은 2022년 1월부터 50명 이상 사업장을 대상으로 시행됐다....
The post 5인 미만 사업장은 언제나 시기상조 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bringing up Kimos]]></title>
        <id>https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/06/13/kimos.html</id>
        <link href="https://zipcpu.com/blog/2024/06/13/kimos.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever had one of those problems where you were stuck for weeks?
It’s not supposed to happen, but … it does.
Let me tell you about the Kimos story so far.
What is Kimos?
Kimos is the name of one of the current open source
projects I’m working on.  The project is
officially named the “Kintex-7 Memory controller, Open Source toolchain”, but
the team shortened that to “KiMOS” and I’ve gotten to the point where I just
call it “Kimos” (pronounced KEE-mos).  The goals of the project are twofold.
Test an Open Source DDR3 SDRAM memory
controller.
This includes both performance testing, and performance comparisons against
Xilinx’s MIG controller.
Just as a note, Angelo’s
controller has a couple of
differences with Xilinx’s controller.  One of them is a simpler
“native” interface: Wishbone, with an op…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>The ZipCPU by Gisselquist Technology</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/12, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594989</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594989/6-12-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T03:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 13, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977365/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977365/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T01:26:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 13, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“외국인에게 받은 디올 백이라”… 권익위의 상상초월 답변: 슬로우레터 6월13일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110089</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110089"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T22:10:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[이재명 다섯번째 기소. 핵심은 ‘보고 받았나’. 일주일에 사흘은 법원에서. 쟁점과 현안. 재판 속도에 달렸다. ‘이재명 대통령’이라는 코끼리. “디올 백 준 게 외국인이라.” 더 깊게 읽기. 고용률은 역대 최고, 청년 취업은 하락 전환. 8표 이탈, 김건희 특검법이 가능성 높다. 다르게 읽기. “심판도 선출해야.” 어머니의 편지와 사단장의 탄원서. 헌재는 대북 전단 방관하라고 한 적 없다. 해법과 대안....
The post “외국인에게 받은 디올 백이라”… 권익위의 상상초월 답변: 슬로우레터 6월13일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IoT Innovations: Qualcomm debuts new technologies at Embedded World 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482500</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/iot-innovations-qualcomm-debuts-new-technologies-at-embedded-world-2024/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T19:08:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a discussion on Qualcomm Technologies’ IoT strategy in Europe, Enrico Salvatori, SVP & President of Qualcomm Europe, highlighted the introduction of innovative product offerings...
The post IoT Innovations: Qualcomm debuts new technologies at Embedded World 2024 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Qualcomm</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cockpit project releases Cockpit Files plugin]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978156/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978156/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T17:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cockpit project has
announced
the first release of Cockpit
Files, a plugin for Cockpit that allows file management on your server
via a web browser:
Mahmoud Hamdy
and is now under active development by the Cockpit team. The goal is
to replace the functionality of the cockpit-navigator
plugin from 45Drives and include automated testing per commit, a
standard PatternFly-based interface, and consistency with the rest of
Cockpit.


Development builds for Fedora are available via a
Copr repository, and packages are expected for Arch, Debian, and
Fedora. LWN covered the
Cockpit project in March.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[국가에서 배운 혐오: 조선인 마을을 불태운 증오는 어디에서 왔는가]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110066</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110066"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T16:49:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[특별 기고] 우토로 마을 방화 사건(2021) 피해자 재일조선인 변호인 도요후쿠 세이지를 비언론인 최초로 안종필 언론상을 받은 김보라미 변호사가 인터뷰했습니다. 왜 재일 한국·조선인에 대한 증오가 눈에 띄는 걸까요. 정부가, 헤이트를 뒤에서 지지하고 있는, 말하자면 ‘정부가 승인한다’라고 하는, ‘위로부터의 헤이트’, ‘관제 헤이트’라고 하는 현상이 있다고 생각합니다. 조선학교만 고교 무상화에서 제외된 사례가 전형적인 예입니다. 왜 국가는 재일조선인 차별에...
The post 국가에서 배운 혐오: 조선인 마을을 불태운 증오는 어디에서 왔는가 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>슬로우뉴스</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Elevating CentOS 7 to a new life]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977762/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977762/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T15:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CentOS Linux 7 was first
released in July 2014, and is due to go end-of-life (EOL) on June 30.
By now, anyone who pays attention to such things is aware that Red Hat pulled the plug on
CentOS Linux in late 2020 to be replaced by CentOS Stream
instead. CentOS Linux 8
support was wound
down at the end of 2021 rather than in 2029 as originally stated.
CentOS Linux 7 was allowed to serve out its
full lifespan—but that EOL is approaching rapidly and
there's no direct upgrade path. Users and organizations looking for a lifeline might want to consider
AlmaLinux's ELevate
utility, which allows CentOS users to migrate to alternate enterprise
Linux (EL) operating systems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nominations are open for the PSF Board election]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978149/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978149/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T14:48:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Python Software
Foundation (PSF) has announced
that nominations are open for the PSF Board election through June
25:
The PSF has a video about
serving on the board for those who might be interested. PSF members
can nominate themselves or another member. Candidates
will be announced on June 27. Voting begins on July 2 and will end on
July 16.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Memory sealing for the GNU C Library]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978010/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978010/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:49:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The mseal() system call allows a
process to prevent any future changes to portions of its address space
(thus "sealing" them); it was patterned after the mimmutable() system call in OpenBSD.
mseal() generated a lot of discussion, but it was finally merged
for the upcoming 6.10 kernel release.  While mseal() was initially
aimed at securing the Chrome browser, the hope was that it would be useful
elsewhere; as a step toward realizing that hope, Adhemerval Zanella has
posted a
patch series adding support for — and use of — mseal() to the
GNU C library (glibc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[systemd 256 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978151/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978151/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:35:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Systemd 256 has been released.  As usual, the list of changes is long; see
this article for an overview, or the
announcement for all the details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Three mid-week stable kernel updates]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978139/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978139/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:04:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greg Kroah-Hartman has announced another round of stable kernel
updates: 6.9.4, 6.6.33, and 6.1.93 have been released. Each contains
another set of important fixes, users of these kernels are advised to
upgrade right away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSUSE Leap 15.6 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978137/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978137/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:57:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The openSUSE
Leap 15.6 release is available; this is intended to be the last
Leap 15.x release before Leap 16 comes out.
"Leap 15.6 is projected to receive maintenance and security updates
until the end of 2025 to ensure sufficient overlap with the next
release".  Changes include the addition of the Cockpit server-management tool, a
6.4 kernel, GNOME 45, and many other upgrades.  This release also
removes a long list of unmaintained Python packages.  See the
release notes for details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978136/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978136/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:48:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (booth), Debian (cyrus-imapd and vlc), Fedora (firefox, libarchive, php, and singularity-ce), Oracle (ipa and ruby:3.3), Red Hat (389-ds-base, buildah, c-ares, cockpit, containernetworking-plugins, fence-agents, gdk-pixbuf2, gvisor-tap-vsock, kernel, kernel-rt, kpatch-patch, libreoffice, podman, protobuf-c, python-idna, rpm-ostree, ruby, and tomcat), Slackware (cups and mozilla), SUSE (bind, cups, iperf, kernel, nano, and poppler), and Ubuntu (libapache-mod-jk, linux-aws, linux-aws-5.15, linux-aws, linux-oracle, linux-intel-iotg-5.15, linux-nvidia, and mysql-8.0).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Can AI and developers work in harmony?]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482495</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/can-ai-and-developers-work-in-harmony/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T10:27:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As AI becomes more intelligent, it can code faster than developers. That puts developers in a quandary; we love to write code, but if AI...
The post Can AI and developers work in harmony? appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[애플 세계개발자회의(WWDC24)를 보는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594983</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594983/%ec%95%a0%ed%94%8c-%ec%84%b8%ea%b3%84%ea%b0%9c%eb%b0%9c%ec%9e%90%ed%9a%8c%ec%9d%98"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting started with Red Hat Connectivity Link on OpenShift]]></title>
        <id>8387d247-7986-4f79-879a-3e47528f344e</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/12/getting-started-red-hat-connectivity-link-openshift"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Connectivity Link is a new offering from Red Hat, which brings a Kubernetes/Red Hat OpenShift native solution for complex application connectivity and API management in hybrid and multi-cloud environments. Connectivity Link is based on the upstream Kuadrant project and was released as a Developer Preview at Red Hat Summit 2024, with the goal of going GA in the fall of 2024.
In this article, I will demonstrate how to get started with Connectivity Link on Red Hat OpenShift. Connectivity Link is not limited to OpenShift, and can be installed and used on other Kubernetes distributions like EKS. However, the installation is much simpler on OpenShift as the required operators can be installed and managed through the Operator Lifecycle Manager (OLM).
Prerequisites
The first prerequisite i…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bernard Tison</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 ways to deploy Quarkus applications in OpenShift Container Platform 4]]></title>
        <id>2ca1d9ab-00cd-4a03-8063-b22f41707281</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/12/4-ways-deploy-quarkus-applications-openshift-container-platform-4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As explained in Deploying your Quarkus applications to OpenShift, there are several approaches for deploying in Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform (RHOCP) 4. Each situation might require different a approach from the ones listed in this article given different (project) requirements.
When doing Quarkus builds for OpenShift, there are several approaches. One of the simplest is the Quarkus Maven plug-in, meaning that the usage of quarkus-openshift extension considerably facilitates the deployment.
Either via pom.xml setting the following dependency:
<dependency>
    <groupId>io.quarkus</groupId>
    <artifactId>quarkus-openshift</artifactId>
</dependency>
Or by adding the extension manually via the command line interface (CLI command) using the Maven Wrapper: 
<-- Below has the latest Quar…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Francisco De Melo Junior, Alexander Barbosa Ayala</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[밀양 사건 폭로전: 사이버렉카의 거짓말 돈벌이, 언론의 잔인한 받아쓰기]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110050</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110050"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T06:00:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[※ 민주언론시민연합은 2차 가해에 해당하는 선정적이고 자극적인 보도에는 바로보기 링크를 걸지 않습니다. 한국성폭력상담소는 6월 5일 ‘2004년 밀양에서 발생한 여자 중학생 집단 성폭행 사건 가해자 신상 공개’에 나선 A유튜브가 피해자(가족) 측 동의를 구했다는 것은 사실이 아니라는 입장을 밝혔습니다. 한국성폭력상담소는 다음과 같은 사실을 알렸습니다. 피해자 의사존중과는 거리가 먼 일방적 영상에 우려를 표하며, 언론 역시 자극적 보도행태를 자제해달라고...
The post 밀양 사건 폭로전: 사이버렉카의 거짓말 돈벌이, 언론의 잔인한 받아쓰기 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Diving into JTAG — Usage Scenarios (Part 5)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-5</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/diving-into-jtag-part-5"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In previous articles, we have considered the primary uses of JTAG, including
debugging and testing boards in production. For firmware developers, the first -
debugging - is the most common. In this article, I want to look at two uses of
JTAG Boundary Scan, which are also common tasks for a firmware developer: board
bring-up and reverse engineering.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9개월 동안 거짓말, 윤석열이 감추려는 진짜 비밀이 뭘까: 슬로우레터 6월12일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=110018</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/110018"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T22:19:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[개원 6일 만에 국회의장 사퇴 결의안. 쟁점과 현안. 조민의 장학금과 김건희의 디올 백. “배우자에 금품, 권익위가 괜찮답니다.” 종결 8표, 송부 7표였다. 더 깊게 읽기. 모든 뉴스는 연결돼 있다. “문제는 속도다.” 경향신문과 한겨레의 논조가 미묘하게 다르다. 다르게 읽기. “800만 달러는 주가 조작 자금.” 다시 등장한 방송 3법. 판사 선출제. 박정훈 변호인이 던진 두 가지 질문. 해법과...
The post 9개월 동안 거짓말, 윤석열이 감추려는 진짜 비밀이 뭘까: 슬로우레터 6월12일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Extensible scheduler class to be merged for 6.11]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/978007/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/978007/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T21:49:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The extensible scheduler class
("sched_ext") framework allows the writing of CPU schedulers as a set of
BPF programs.  It has been somewhat
controversial, and its merging into the kernel has been blocked despite
a clear level of interest from users.

Linus Torvalds has now let
it be known that he has made a decision and, overriding the scheduler
maintainer, will merge sched_ext for the 6.11 release.


	I honestly see no reason to delay this any more. This whole
	patchset was the major (private) discussion at last year's kernel
	maintainer summit, and I don't find any value in having the same
	discussion (whether off-list or as an actual event) at the upcoming
	maintainer summit one year later, so to make any kind of sane
	progress, my current plan is to merge this for 6.11.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How it's Made: GenType Alphabet Creator]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/how-its-made-gentype-alphabet-creator/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T20:13:56.413Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of our newest experiments in the series is GenTypeGenType. This tool uses generative AI to create an alphabet out of anything you want.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Securing BPF programs before and after verification]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977394/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977394/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T18:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BPF is in a unique position in terms of security. It runs in a privileged
context, within the kernel, and can have access to many sensitive details of the
kernel's operation. At the same time, unlike kernel modules, BPF programs aren't signed.
Additionally, the mechanisms behind BPF present challenges to implementing
signing or other security features. Three nearly back-to-back sessions at the
2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit
addressed some of the potential security problems.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Advancing memory performance with DDR5]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482488</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/advancing-memory-performance-with-ddr5/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T17:44:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Access to sufficient memory bandwidth will be crucial for engineers and system designers as companies invest further in data centers to meet demand. This article looks at the advances in DDR5 memory that help meet this demand.
The post Advancing memory performance with DDR5 appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Eble</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox 127.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977973/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977973/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:07:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version
127.0 of the Firefox browser is out.  Changes include support for DNS
prefetching and the ability to close duplicate tabs in a window.  The
browser will now try to upgrade images and videos with HTTP URLs that are
found in an HTTPS page to HTTPS as well; if that fails, the non-HTTPS
resources will simply fail to load.

Update: this
Mozilla Secuirty Blog post describes the HTTPS-related changes in
detail.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Dropping the page cache for filesystems]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977486/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977486/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:28:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VFS maintainer Christian Brauner led a discussion about the possibility of
selectively dropping the contents of the page cache for a filesystem in a
session at the
2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  As he described in his
topic
proposal, the use case that started him down this path comes from
GNOME, which wants to be able to safely suspend access to an encrypted home
directory.  While it is known to kernel
developers, it is surprising to others that reads from encrypted
filesystems that have been suspended will succeed if the data to be read
still exists in the 
page cache.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ANCS and HID: Controlling Your iPhone From Zephyr]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1669.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1669.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:16:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
In a previous blog post (https://embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1630.php), we learned how we can configure our nRF52840 development kit (https://www.nordicsemi.com/Products/Development-ha...) as a Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) device using The Zephyr Project. Similarly, we learned how to advertise standard and custom capabilities. 

In this blog post, we will take...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977939/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977939/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T13:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (ruby:3.3), Fedora (efifs, libvirt, podman-tui, prometheus-podman-exporter, and strongswan), Red Hat (firefox, idm:DL1, ipa, nghttp2, and thunderbird), SUSE (aws-nitro-enclaves-cli, cdi-apiserver-container, cdi-cloner-container, cdi- controller-container, cdi-importer-container, cdi-operator-container, cdi- uploadproxy-container, cdi-uploadserver-container, containerized-data-importer, frr, glibc, go1.21, go1.22, gstreamer-plugins-base, kernel, kernel-firmware-nvidia-gspx-G06, nvidia-open- driver-G06-signed, libxml2, mariadb, poppler, python-Brotli, python-docker, python-idna, rmt-server, skopeo, sssd, unbound, unrar, util-linux, and webkit2gtk3), and Ubuntu (giflib, libphp-adodb, linux-gkeop, linux-gkeop-5.15, linux-kvm, linux-laptop, linux-oem-6.8, nodejs, and tiff).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How developers can leverage RTOS functional safety certification]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482483</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/how-developers-can-leverage-rtos-functional-safety-certification/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T12:41:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RTOS functional safety certification benefits not only safety-critical devices but all embedded devices as a means to improve time-to-market, improve product quality, and reduce product...
The post How developers can leverage RTOS functional safety certification appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bill Lamie</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Get system-wide profiles of binaries without frame pointers]]></title>
        <id>c9890276-935c-42b8-aae6-8c44a9326f08</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/11/get-system-wide-profiles-binaries-without-frame-pointers"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many profiling tools on Linux have previously been limited by their reliance on stack unwinding algorithms that require commonly-used frame pointer optimizations to be disabled. This article introduces eu-stacktrace, a prototype tool that uses the elfutils toolkit’s unwinding libraries to support a sampling profiler to unwind frame pointer-less stack sample data.
Background
Developers and customers find benefit in profiling the performance of their applications in both development and production environments. A typical requirement for useful profile data is an accurate stack trace listing the active functions at every sample in the profile. Commonly used profiling tools try to fulfill this requirement with basic unwinder implementations that assume programs to have been compiled with a sta…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Serhei Makarov</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[동의도 영장도 없는 방역 만능주의? 절차와 사생활 보호도 중요하다]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109996</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109996"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T05:34:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[동의도, 영장도 없이 국가가 내 위치를 추적한다면? 나의 중요한 권리인 사생활의 비밀과 자유는 침해될 수밖에 없습니다. 2020년 5월, 코로나19 팬데믹 당시 정부는 이태원 일대에 있었던 약 1만 명의 위치 정보를 동의 없이 수집했습니다. 수집의 근거가 된 감염병예방법 제76조의2에는 누구를 감염의심자로 볼지, 어떤 정보까지 추적할지, 과도한 사생활 침해는 없는지 제어할 수 있는 보호장치조차 없었습니다. 이에 시민사회단체들은...
The post 동의도 영장도 없는 방역 만능주의? 절차와 사생활 보호도 중요하다 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>참여연대 사법감시센터</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[세월호 10년: 세 번의 조사, 가려진 진실, 책임 없는 정부]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109989</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109989"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T03:15:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[민언련 이달의 좋은 보도상 인터뷰] 한국일보 세월호 10주기 ‘산 자들의 10년’ 특별기획팀 (2024년 5월 수상자) 2014년 4월 16일. 우리 모두의 아픔으로 남은 세월호 참사가 일어났다. 그러나 정부, 언론, 수사기관 등은 제 역할을 하지 못했다. 가려진 진실, 정부의 책임 회피, 미흡한 책임자 처벌, 유족과 생존자를 향한 왜곡된 비난 속에 온전한 진상규명은 지금도 현재진행형이다. 세 번의 공적...
The post 세월호 10년: 세 번의 조사, 가려진 진실, 책임 없는 정부 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] ‘사이다 발언’에 박수 갈채? 그에 앞서 생각해 볼 두 가지 용기]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79168</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/10/npsp_openletters/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_openletters"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:59:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 22일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 하마스가 이스라엘을 상대로 테러 공격을 벌인 뒤 그에 대한 반격으로 시작된 이스라엘의 가자지구 군사 작전 혹은 이스라엘과 팔레스타인의 전쟁이 벌써 반년이 더 지났습니다. 평화적인 해결은커녕 잠시 총을 내려놓고 민간인들의 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[디올 백 대신 에코백, 김건희의 발걸음이 가벼웠던 이유: 슬로우레터 6월11일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109953</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109953"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T22:11:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[‘배우자’는 받아도 되나. 권익위는 왜 그랬을까. 에코백을 들었다. 쟁점과 현안. 국민의힘이 깔아준 판, 민주당이 상임위 싹쓸이. “법사위만 달라”, 국민의힘 마지막 제안도 거부. 이재명 맞춤형 당헌 개정. 더 깊게 읽기. 대북 전단 왜 안 막나. 대북 확성기 일단 중지. 바이든-트럼프 초박빙 판세. 유럽에서는 극우의 약진. 다르게 읽기. 헌법 84조 논란, 현직 대통령을 법정에 세울 수 있나....
The post 디올 백 대신 에코백, 김건희의 발걸음이 가벼웠던 이유: 슬로우레터 6월11일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How much UB is in my compiler?]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1130/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1130/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C and C++ developers have two bug-related headaches: memory leaks and undefined behavior. As you can guess, I'll talk about undefined behavior—and about "my" compiler. To be more precise, I'll talk...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microcontroller operations in an OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482477</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/microcontroller-operations-in-an-ocp-orv3-smart-battery-backup-unit/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:59:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a smart battery backup unit, the microcontroller’s software is responsible for guaranteeing the smooth functioning of processes, hence ensuring the unit’s high efficiency and...
The post Microcontroller operations in an OCP ORV3 smart battery backup unit appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Christian Cruz and Marvin Neil Cabueñas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computex 2024: a video roundup from Taiwan]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482473</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/computex-2024-a-video-roundup-from-taiwan/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T18:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a taste of the happenings at Computex 2024 in Taiwan covered through my daily video roundups at the show – summarized here.
The post Computex 2024: a video roundup from Taiwan appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Computex 2024 keynotes focus on data centers and AI PCs]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482457</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/computex-2024-keynotes-focus-on-data-centers-and-ai-pcs/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T17:33:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A look at the announcements in the keynotes at Computex 2024 in Taiwan from Nvidia, AMD, Intel and Qualcomm Technologies.
The post Computex 2024 keynotes focus on data centers and AI PCs appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] P4TC hits a brick wall]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977310/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977310/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:11:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[P4, short for "Programming
Protocol-independent Packet Processors", is a programming language aimed at
networking devices; it is useful for the configuration of firewalls and
complicated routing architectures.  Since a lot of advanced networking is
done with Linux systems, it stands to reason that there would be value in
supporting P4 and, indeed, an
implementation of P4 in the kernel's traffic-control subsystem was
first posted by Jamal Hadi Salim at the beginning of 2023.  After nearly
18 months, though, this feature has not been merged, and the chances
of that happening would appear to be getting worse.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[perl v5.40.0 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977765/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977765/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:08:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 5.40.0 of the Perl language has been released.  "Perl 5.40.0
represents approximately 11 months of development since Perl 5.38.0 and
contains approximately 160,000 lines of changes across 1,500 files from 75
authors".  Significant changes include a new __CLASS__
keyword, a :reader: attribute for field variables, a new
"^^" logical-XOR operator (because two of those were not enough),
moving "try/catch" out of the experimental category, and more; see
this
page for lots of details.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977789/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977789/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T14:45:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (galera and mariadb10.11), Mageia (0-plugins-base and plasma-workspace), Oracle (ruby:3.1 and ruby:3.3), Red Hat (bind, bind-dyndb-ldap, and dhcp), SUSE (apache2, glib2, libvirt, openssl-1_1, openssl-3, opera, python-Jinja2, python-requests, and squid), and Ubuntu (linux, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-5.15, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-5.15, linux-xilinx-zynqmp, linux, linux-gcp, linux-gcp-6.5, linux-lowlatency,
 linux-lowlatency-hwe-6.5, linux-raspi, linux, linux-ibm, linux-lowlatency, linux-raspi, linux-aws, linux-gcp, linux-azure, linux-azure-6.5, linux-starfive, linux-starfive-6.5, and linux-gke, linux-ibm, linux-intel-iotg, linux-oracle).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Synthara gets $11m to bring in-memory computing to embedded AI]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482448</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/synthara-gets-11m-to-bring-in-memory-computing-to-embedded-ai/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T11:26:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seamless integration of in-memory computing into existing chip designs is a game-changer, particularly for AI applications, says Hermann Hauser.
The post Synthara gets $11m to bring in-memory computing to embedded AI appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A platform for building developer portals]]></title>
        <id>690d5adc-605a-45d3-8381-b91ac5f83968</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/10/platform-building-developer-portals"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is an excerpt from Developer Portals: Prepare to Perform with Red Hat Developer Hub. Download the full e-book.
As a cultural initiative, DevOps has probably made software more reliable and its creation more rapid. Its best understood practices have benefited their progenitors, publicizers, and most successful adopters. Developer engagement with deployment concerns engenders a systems thinking that improves application architecture, but DevOps declares for developers an unbounded array of new concepts, terms, and concerns.
This increase in cognitive load can make it feel like the early returns from DevOps practices such as automation and “infrastructure as code” and its progression toward GitOps are diminishing and progress slowing. More than 80% of developers say they have some kind o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hans-Peter Grahsl, Joshua Wood, Ryan Jarvinen</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Satellite webhook and Insights automation for efficient RHEL operations]]></title>
        <id>4d91736c-7cb0-4f30-9ecf-de26ef6c4141</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/10/satellite-webhook-and-insights-automation-efficient-rhel-operations"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Red Hat Satellite is an infrastructure management tool designed for the management and operations of Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) environments. It allows system administrators to scale the management of their datacenters to thousands of hosts at ease, while implementing and enforcing secure and compliant standard operating environments (SOE).
In this article, we investigate the use of Satellite webhooks and automation to interact with third-party tooling and react to events occurring within Satellite. This is traditionally used to improve the overall operational efficiency by either forwarding events to third-party auditing and monitoring tools (e.g., Splunk), or using events as triggers for automation (e.g., Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform, ServiceNow). To this point, we explore ho…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jerome Marc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[미국이 자칫하면 ‘한국 꼴’ 될 수 있다고? 달갑지 않은 최신 ‘K-트렌드’]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79498</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/10/npsp_birthrategendernorm/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_birthrategendernorm"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T04:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[한류를 시작으로 대한민국의 국가 브랜드를 뜻하는 “K-시리즈”는 많은 이들에게 긍지를 안겨줬습니다. 그러나 전례를 찾아보기 힘든 저출생 문제와 그 원인의 하나로 꼽히는 젠더 규범을 둘러싼 갈등 문제에 있어서는 우리나라가 소위 “안 좋은 일로 세계에서 1등”을 달리고 있습니다. 미국의 젊은 세대도 연애도, 섹스도, 결혼도 덜한다는 통계가 꾸준히 나오는데, 이에 관한 우려를 담은 글에서 반면교사로 삼아야 할 사례로 한국이 등장하곤 합니다. 닉 크리스토프의 칼럼을 번역하고, 해설을 썼습니다. 전문 번역: 결혼도, 섹스도 덜 하는 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc3]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977725/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977725/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T03:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 6.10-rc3 kernel prepatch is out.
"So things look good, the water is warm, please jump right in and keep
testing,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++17 in Detail: Filesystem in The Standard Library]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cppstories.com/2017/08/cpp17-details-filesystem/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cppstories.com/2017/08/cpp17-details-filesystem/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Although C++ is an old programming language, its Standard Library misses a few basic things. Features that Java or .NET had for years were/are not available in STL. With C++17 there’s a nice improvement: for example, we now have the standard filesystem!
Traversing a path, even recursively, is so simple now!



     
    


For the last five episodes/articles, I’ve covered most of the language features. Now it’s time for the Standard Library. I’ve planned three posts on that: Filesystem, Parallel STL and Concurrency, Utils.
Maybe I was a bit harsh in the introduction. Although the Standard Library lacks some important features, you could always use Boost with its thousands of sub-libraries and do the work. The C++ Committee and the Community decided that the Boost libraries are so important…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>C++ Stories</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이화영 유죄 변수로 보는 이재명 재판의 경우의 수: 슬로우레터 6월10일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109903</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109903"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T22:12:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[풍선 전쟁에 확성기, 그다음은? 1조 원 풀었는데, 의료 대란 최악의 상황. 쟁점과 현안. 3자 뇌물 혐의, 이재명의 네 번째 리스크. 이화영 미스터리. 대북 송금 특검법 갈 수 있을까. 더 깊게 읽기. 이재명의 네 가지 재판. 이재명 재판의 경우의 수. “형사상 소추를 받지 않는다.” 정청래와 최민희 등 선수들 전면 배치. 다르게 읽기. 20% 가능성의 근거는? 설명...
The post 이화영 유죄 변수로 보는 이재명 재판의 경우의 수: 슬로우레터 6월10일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quantity of source in a given language]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8852</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/06/09/quantity-of-source-in-a-given-language/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T22:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How much source code exists in a particular language? Traditionally, indicators of the quantity of source in a language is the number of people making a living working on software written in the language. Job adverts are a proxy for the number of people employed to write/support programs implemented in a language (i.e., number of […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alphawave Semi develops Arm-based compute chiplet]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482444</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/alphawave-semi-develops-arm-based-compute-chiplet/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T10:25:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Neoverse CSS-based CPU chiplet  delivers features ultra-high-speed interfaces and advanced packaging to help deliver scalable performance for AI, HPC and networking infrastructure.
The post Alphawave Semi develops Arm-based compute chiplet appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nitin Dahad</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[신호와 소음을 구분하는 방법: 슬로우뉴스의 새로운 제안.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109833</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109833"/>
        <updated>2024-06-09T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[슬로우레터 구독자 여러분, 안녕하세요. 슬로우뉴스 재창간 1년을 맞아 보내려던 인사가 벌써 몇 달이 지났습니다.슬로우레터는 벌써 300회를 앞두고 있습니다. 오늘은 지난 1년을 돌아보고 슬로우뉴스의 새로운 계획을 말씀드리려고 합니다. 이 글은 세 가지를 담고 있습니다. 슬로우레터의 1년, Q&A으로 풀어볼까요? 아침에 몇 시에 일어나세요? 뉴스를 잘 읽는 방법이 있나요? 좀 더 의견이 들어가도 좋을 것 같습니다. 편향적이라고 비판하는...
The post 신호와 소음을 구분하는 방법: 슬로우뉴스의 새로운 제안. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 엔비디아 액면분할 후 엔비디아 주가 상승 랠리는 지속될 것]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594975</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594975/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%95%a1%eb%a9%b4%eb%b6%84%ed%95%a0-%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%83%81%ec%8a%b9"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T14:19:57.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[은퇴자 건강을 위한 건강 걸음수 가이드]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594968</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594968/%ea%b1%b4%ea%b0%95%ea%b4%80%eb%a6%ac-%ea%b1%b8%ec%9d%8c%ec%88%98"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T13:39:28.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[배런스, 아마존은 시가총액 3조 달러 클럽에 가입할 수 있을까요? 어떻게 가능할까요?]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594962</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594962/%ec%95%84%eb%a7%88%ec%a1%b4-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%88%ec%95%a1-3%ec%a1%b0%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac-%ea%b0%80%eb%8a%a5%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T08:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[버닝썬 게이트, 우리가 놓치고 있었던 이야기들.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109811</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109811"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T04:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[슬로우리포트] 한류 스타들의 일탈? 자본과 권력의 구조적 유착을 봐야 한다. 영국의 공영 방송 BBC가 한국 K-팝의 그늘을 조명했다. ‘버닝썬: K팝 스타들의 비밀 대화방을 폭로한 여성들’이라는 다큐멘터리다. 5년 전 사건을 다룬 영상에 페이지뷰가 1000만 뷰에 육박한다는 건 세상의 관심이 살아있다는 이야기다. 우리가 이미 충분히 잘 알고 있다고 생각했던 사건을 외부의 시선으로 들여다 보니 우리가 놓치고 있는...
The post 버닝썬 게이트, 우리가 놓치고 있었던 이야기들. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/8, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594906</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594906/6-8-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T03:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Connecting a high speed parallel ADC to SAM E70]]></title>
        <id>tag:m0agx.eu,2024-06-08:/parallel-adc-and-sam-e70.html</id>
        <link href="https://m0agx.eu/parallel-adc-and-sam-e70.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ADCs come in all shapes and sizes. Converters built into MCUs made great progress across the years
but sometimes you need a dedicated discrete ADC. At the extremes of the "speed spectrum"
there are "slow but precise" ADCs (that tend to use SPI or I2C),
and absolute monsters with SerDes outputs that can only be consumed by an FPGA.
My application needed an ADC from the middle ground but with multiple channels and simultaneous sampling.
Interfacing a medium-speed multichannel ADC to an SAM E70 MCU turned out more interesting than I wished for. 😊]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>M0AGX / LB9MG</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 선거제 허점 악용해도 견제할 방법, 저기도 없네?!]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79147</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/07/npsp_electoralcollege/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_electoralcollege"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T22:59:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 17일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 미국 대선에 관해 이야기할 때마다 반드시 언급되는 단골 소재가 바로 선거인단(electoral college)입니다. 우리나라처럼 대통령제를 채택한 나라에서도 쉽게 찾아볼 수 없는 독특한 제도라서 더욱 그렇습니다. 투표권이 있는 유권자들의 표를 더해 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Ladybird browser spreads its wings]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976822/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976822/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T18:27:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ladybird is an open-source
project aimed at building an independent web browser, rather than
yet another browser based on Chrome. It is written in C++ and licensed under a
two-clause BSD license. The effort 
began as part of the SerenityOS project, but
developer Andreas Kling announced
on June 3 that he was "forking" Ladybird as a separate project and stepping away from
SerenityOS to focus his attention on the browser completely. Ladybird
is not ready to replace Firefox or Chrome for regular use, but it is showing
great promise.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux nftables vulnerability exploited in the wild (CrowdStrike)]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977583/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977583/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T17:27:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to CrowdStrike, a

vulnerability in the Linux kernel's nftables code
that was  discovered earlier this
year is being actively exploited in the wild. The vulnerability allows for
local privilege escalation. Most distributions have already released a fix.



As noted by the exploit developer, leveraging this POC is dependent on the
kernel's unprivileged user namespaces feature accessing nf_tables. This access
is enabled by default on Debian, Ubuntu and kernel capture-the-flag (CTF)
distributions. An attacker can then trigger the double-free vulnerability, scan
the physical memory for the kernel base address, bypass kernel address-space
layout randomization (KASLR) and access the modprobe_path kernel variable with
read/write privileges. After overwriting the modprobe_path, the exploit drops a
root shell.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[The Motley Fool]엔비디아 액면분할은 엔비디아 매수 이유가 될 수 없다. 엔비디아 주가에서 주목할 3가지 요인]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594904</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594904/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-%ec%a0%84%eb%a7%9d-4"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:56:52.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Modernizing BPF for the next 10 years]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977013/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977013/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:17:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[BPF was first

generalized beyond packet filtering more than a decade ago. In that time, it
has changed a lot, becoming much more capable.
Alexei Starovoitov kicked off the second day of the BPF track at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit by leading a session
discussing which changes to BPF are going to come in the next ten years as it
continues evolving. He proposed several ideas, including expanding the number of
registers available to BPF programs, dynamic deadlock detection, and relaxing
some existing limits of the verifier.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Friday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977555/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977555/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:11:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (libtiff), Oracle (cockpit, glibc, kernel, less, libxml2, linux-kernel, and tomcat), Red Hat (java-1.8.0-ibm, nghttp2, and ruby:3.3), Slackware (php), SUSE (go1.21, go1.22, and python-docker), and Ubuntu (aom and libvpx).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[The Motley Fool] 월스트리트 최초 시가총액 5조 달러 기업이 될 아마존]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594897</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594897/%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%9d%ec%95%a1-5%ec%a1%b0-%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac-%ea%b8%b0%ec%97%85"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T08:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[The Motley Fool]시총 2조달러 클럽 후보, 3년내 메타 시가총액 2조달러 가능성]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594893</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594893/%eb%a9%94%ed%83%80-%ec%8b%9c%ea%b0%80%ec%b4%9d%ec%95%a1-2%ec%a1%b0%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac-%ea%b0%80%eb%8a%a5%ec%84%b1"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:55:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA, 엔비디아는 향후 10년간 컴퓨팅 시장을 지배할 것이며, 엔비디아 목표주가 1,500달러 제시]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594886</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594886/%ec%97%94%eb%b9%84%eb%94%94%ec%95%84-%eb%aa%a9%ed%91%9c%ec%a3%bc%ea%b0%80-1500%eb%8b%ac%eb%9f%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:24:48.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.12.4 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3124-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3124-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T01:50:00.002Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.12.4:
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3124/
 
This is the third maintenance release of Python 3.12
Python 3.12 is the newest major release of the Python programming 
language, and it contains many new features and optimizations. 3.12.4 is
 the latest maintenance release, containing more than 250 bugfixes, 
build improvements and documentation changes since 3.12.3.
 
Major new features of the 3.12 series, compared to 3.11
 
New features
More flexible f-string parsing, allowing many things previously disallowed (PEP 701).
Support for the buffer protocol in Python code (PEP 688).
A new debugging/profiling API (PEP 669).
Support for isolated subinterpreters with separate Global Interpreter Locks (PEP 684).
Even more improved error…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python 3.13.0 beta 2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3130-beta-2-released.html</id>
        <link href="https://pythoninsider.blogspot.com/2024/06/python-3130-beta-2-released.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T01:46:00.001Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I'm pleased to announce the release of Python 3.13 beta 2.
https://www.python.org/downloads/release/python-3130b2/
 
This is a beta preview of Python 3.13
Python 3.13 is still in development. This release, 3.13.0b2, is the second of four beta release previews of 3.13.
Beta release previews are intended to give the wider community the 
opportunity to test new features and bug fixes and to prepare their 
projects to support the new feature release.
We strongly encourage maintainers of third-party Python projects to test with 3.13 during the beta phase and report issues found to the Python bug tracker 
 as soon as possible. While the release is planned to be feature 
complete entering the beta phase, it is possible that features may be 
modified or, in rare cases, deleted up until the start o…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Python Insider</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/7, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594877</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594877/6-7-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T00:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[이재명의 우향우? “민주당이 무섭다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 6월7일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109773</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109773"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T22:07:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“평화는 힘으로 지킨다.” 오늘 액트지오 기자회견. 영일만 브리핑, 산업부 패싱 논란. 쟁점과 현안. 17일부터 서울대병원 전면 휴진. 방통위원장 탄핵 간다. 다시 나온 언론보도 징벌적 손배 법안. ‘어대한’? 힘 빠진 국민의힘 전당대회. 더 깊게 읽기. 원조 친명과 신친명의 갈등. 44명의 가해자, 누구도 처벌받지 않았다. 사이버 자경단의 사적 제재. 다르게 읽기. “최태원은 일부일처제를 깬 게 아니다.” 저출산과...
The post 이재명의 우향우? “민주당이 무섭다”는 말이 나오는 이유: 슬로우레터 6월7일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[C++ programmer's guide to undefined behavior: part 1 of 11]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1129/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/cpp/1129/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Your attention is invited to the first part of an e-book on undefined behavior. This is not a textbook, as it's intended for those who are already familiar with C++ programming. It's a kind of C...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] A generic ring buffer for the kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976836/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976836/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T16:05:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The kernel's user-space ABI does not lack for ring buffers; they have been
defined for subsystems like BPF, io_uring, perf,
and tracing, for
example.  Naturally, each of those ring buffers is unique, with no common
interface between them.  The natural response to this ABI proliferation is,
of course, to add yet another ring buffer as the generic option; that is
the intent of this
patch series from Kent Overstreet adding a new set of system calls for
ring buffers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Thursday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977442/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977442/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T16:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (cockpit, kernel, kernel-rt, libxml2, ruby:3.1, and tomcat), Debian (libarchive, pillow, and tinyproxy), Fedora (apptainer), Mageia (amavisd-new and libxml2), Oracle (edk2), Red Hat (booth, cockpit, kernel-rt, less, libxml2, nghttp2, ruby:3.1, ruby:3.3, and tomcat), Slackware (kernel), and Ubuntu (atril, bluez, frr, gdk-pixbuf, openjdk-17, openjdk-21, openjdk-8, openjdk-lts, qemu, and unixodbc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to integrate and use RStudio Server on OpenShift AI]]></title>
        <id>3bed29c8-4504-4367-8f96-46bc979c418c</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/06/how-integrate-and-use-rstudio-server-openshift-ai"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[RStudio Server is a powerful open source integrated development environment (IDE) that offers a graphical interface for the R programming language, significantly enhancing data analysis and visualization capabilities. With the rise of data-driven decision-making, having a robust tool like RStudio Server becomes crucial for data scientists and analysts. This guide will walk you through the process of setting up RStudio Server on Red Hat OpenShift AI and getting started with its extensive features.
Setting Up RStudio Server on OpenShift AI
The integration of RStudio Server with OpenShift AI provides a scalable and secure environment for data analysis.
Here’s a step-by-step guide to get you started.

Log in to the cluster. First, access your OpenShift cluster by logging in through the termina…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andriana Theodorakopoulou</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhance Kubernetes deployment efficiency with Argo CD and ApplicationSet]]></title>
        <id>a7dfda04-861d-4593-b806-f4945c3ab857</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/06/enhance-kubernetes-deployment-efficiency-argo-cd-and-applicationset"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using Argo CD to manage your Kubernetes ecosystem is an excellent GitOps approach to continuous deployment (CD). However, it can pose challenges when trying to manage multiple Kubernetes manifests for deployments, services, secrets, configurations, and other files within your Git repository.
Unlike an Argo CD Application resource that deploys resources from a single Git repository in a single cluster or namespace, ApplicationSet expands upon this use case. An ApplicationSet utilizes template-based automation to create, modify, and manage multiple Argo CD applications simultaneously, targeting multiple clusters and namespaces.
In what situations is it more convenient to use an ApplicationSet?



It is convenient to use an ApplicationSet when a user or team has too many applications to manag…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luis Falero Otiniano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[크라우드스트라이크 실적을 읽는 월가의 시선]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594863</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594863/%ed%81%ac%eb%9d%bc%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c%ec%8a%a4%ed%8a%b8%eb%9d%bc%ec%9d%b4%ed%81%ac-%ec%8b%a4%ec%a0%81-%ed%8f%89%ea%b0%80"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T06:14:20.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/6, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594859</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594859/6-6-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T06:02:35.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[홍윤희 스토리 1. 이제 회사 가서 좀 쉬어]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109322</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109322"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:23:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[홍윤희 스토리] 잘 다니던 회사 그만두고 지금은 장애인 이동권을 위한 사단법인 ‘무의’ 이사장. 지민이 엄마로, 활동가로, 자유기고가에서 이사장까지. 대체로 바쁘고 힘겹고 지겹지만 가끔씩 찬란한 ‘홍윤희의 그 길’에 관한 이야기. 홍윤희? 근데 누구세요? 장애가 ‘무의미’해지는 세상을 꿈꾸는, 아니 계획하고 실행하며 그걸 알리는 ‘무의’라는 단체가 있습니다. 처음에는 ‘진짜’ 직업 따로인 자원봉사 1인 활동가 단체였지만, 협동조합의 테두리를 갖추고,...
The post 홍윤희 스토리 1. 이제 회사 가서 좀 쉬어 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 6, 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975974/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975974/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T01:12:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The LWN.net Weekly Edition for June 6, 2024 is available.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[“내가 해봐서 아는데”, 백종원과 윤석열의 차이: 슬로우레터 6월6일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109706</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109706"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:06:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“더 이상 가망이 없다고 생각한다.” S&P도 “희망과 꿈일 뿐.” 쟁점과 현안. 헌정사상 첫 야당 단독 국회 개원. 국민의힘이 법사위에 목매는 이유. 법사위 기피증. 더 깊게 읽기. “다른 국정 운영도 이렇게 하는 것 같아 걱정.” 국가채무 비율 딜레마. “이런 사건은 범인 못 잡아요.” 언더커버를 합법 수사로. 다르게 읽기. 종부세와 재산세 통합하자는 주장 따져보니. 한국 사람들이 돈을...
The post “내가 해봐서 아는데”, 백종원과 윤석열의 차이: 슬로우레터 6월6일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[‘억만장자들만의 세상’, 이제는 대놓고 펼쳐진다]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79483</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/05/npsp_buylongerlife/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_buylongerlife"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T22:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[불로초를 찾으려 했던 진시황의 이야기는 다들 잘 아실 겁니다. 굳이 진시황이 아니라도 인류 역사에 이름을 남긴 권력자 가운데는 다시 젊어지려고 애쓴 사람이 많습니다. 오늘날 우리는 돈이 곧 권력의 중요한 원천이 되거나 아예 그 자체로 권력이 되는 자본주의 사회를 살고 있습니다. 자본주의의 첨단을 달린다는 미국의 부자들은 불로초와 비슷한 효과를 내는 비법을 독점적으로 터득했습니다. 비결이 뭘까요? 이번에도 역시 돈입니다. 전문 번역: 젊어지려고 아들 피 수혈한 백만장자…돈으로 ‘불로장생’을 사다 해설: ‘억만장자들만의 세상’, 이제는 대놓고 펼쳐진다]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Measuring and improving buffered I/O]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976856/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976856/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T20:22:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are two types of file I/O on Linux, buffered I/O, which goes through
the page cache, and direct I/O, which goes directly to the storage device.
The performance of buffered I/O was reported to be a lot worse than direct
I/O, especially for one specific test, in Luis Chamberlain's 
topic
proposal for a session at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.
The proposal resulted in a lengthy mailing-list discussion, 
which also came up in Paul McKenney's RCU session the next
day; Chamberlain led a 
combined storage and filesystem session to discuss those results with an
eye toward improving buffered I/O performance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kali Linux 2024.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977303/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977303/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T19:14:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2024.2 of the Kali Linux penetration testing distribution
has been released. This
release includes an update to GNOME
46, a high-resolution (HiDPI) mode for Xfce, as well as a number
of new packages such as the AutoRecon network
reconnaissance tool, pspy command-line utility for
snooping on Linux processes, and SploitScan tool for
fetching and displaying CVE information. Kali Linux is based on Debian
testing, and 2024.2 incorporates Debian's work to transition to 64-bit
time_t to avoid year 2038 problems. Users with existing Kali
systems should be sure to follow the documentation
when upgrading.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD 14.1 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977285/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977285/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T17:39:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 14.1 of FreeBSD has
been released. This
is the second release of the 14.x stable branch. Highlights of this
release include upgrades to OpenZFS 2.2.4, Clang/LLVM 18.1.5, and
OpenSSH 9.7p1. FreeBSD 14.1 also features cloud-init support,
sound subsystem improvements, and more. See the
what's
new blog post from the FreeBSD Foundation, 
release
notes, and errata for
more information.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Rethinking the PostgreSQL CommitFest model]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976793/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976793/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T16:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many years ago, the PostgreSQL project started holding regular CommitFests to
help tackle the work of reviewing and committing patches in a more
organized fashion. That has served the project well, but some in
the project are concerned that CommitFests are no longer meeting
the needs of PostgreSQL or its contributors. A lengthy discussion on the
pgsql-hackers mailing list turned up a number of complaints, a few
suggestions for improvement, but little consensus or momentum toward
a solution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Removing GFP_NOFS]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976355/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976355/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:48:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GFP_NOFS flag is meant for kernel memory allocations that
should not cause a call into the filesystems to reclaim memory because there are
already locks held that can potentially cause a deadlock.  The "scoped
allocation" API is a better choice for filesystems to indicate that they
are holding a lock, so GFP_NOFS has long been on the chopping block, though
progress has been slow.  In a filesystem-track session at
the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit, Matthew Wilcox wanted to
discuss how to move kernel filesystems away from the flag with the eventual
goal of removing it completely.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The state of SourceHut]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977174/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977174/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T15:09:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Drew DeVault has published
an update about the state of the SourceHut software development
platform and its plans for the coming months. This is the first update
since the January post-mortem
following a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that resulted
in a prolonged
outage:
As you can imagine, it has been a stressful time for us. However, I
wish to stress that everything we've been dealing with is planned for
in our models, both technical and financial. There is no existential
threat to SourceHut. Nevertheless, we are grateful for your patience
and support.
[...] We have been focusing on two things this year: provisioning
and managing our infrastructure and getting as much rest as
possible. Our situation has calmed down, and while we still have a lot
of loose ends to attend to I'm happy to say that we're resuming a
sense of normalcy here and preparing to resume our work on the
features you need.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Comparing BPF performance between implementations]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976317/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976317/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:50:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Alan Jowett returned for a second remote presentation at the 2024
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit to compare the performance of
different BPF runtimes. He showed the results of the MIT-licensed BPF

microbenchmark suite he has been working on.
The benchmark suite does not yet provide a good direct comparison between all
platforms, so the results should be
taken with a grain of salt. They do
seem to indicate that there is some significant variation between
implementations, especially for different types of BPF maps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Wednesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977233/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977233/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:32:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Fedora (deepin-qt5integration, deepin-qt5platform-plugins, dotnet8.0, dwayland, fcitx-qt5, fcitx5-qt, gammaray, kddockwidgets, keepassxc, kf5-akonadi-server, kf5-frameworkintegration, kf5-kwayland, plasma-integration, python-qt5, qadwaitadecorations, qgnomeplatform, qt5, qt5-qt3d, qt5-qtbase, qt5-qtcharts, qt5-qtconnectivity, qt5-qtdatavis3d, qt5-qtdeclarative, qt5-qtdoc, qt5-qtgamepad, qt5-qtgraphicaleffects, qt5-qtimageformats, qt5-qtlocation, qt5-qtmultimedia, qt5-qtnetworkauth, qt5-qtquickcontrols, qt5-qtquickcontrols2, qt5-qtremoteobjects, qt5-qtscript, qt5-qtscxml, qt5-qtsensors, qt5-qtserialbus, qt5-qtserialport, and qt5-qtspeech), Oracle (389-ds-base and ruby:3.1), Red Hat (389-ds-base, glibc, and kernel), SUSE (python-PyMySQL), and Ubuntu (libarchive).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing server calls in generated HTML]]></title>
        <id>https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Round-tripToTheServer</id>
        <link href="https://martinfowler.com/articles/tdd-html-templates.html#Round-tripToTheServer"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Matteo Vaccari completes his article on testing
         template-generated HTML, by looking at how to use TDD with pages that make
         calls to the server.
more…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Martin Fowler</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 best practices for writing interrupt service routines]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482438</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/5-best-practices-for-writing-interrupt-service-routines/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T11:40:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poorly written ISRs can result in systems with race conditions, poor responsiveness, and even excessive CPU use. Nearly every embedded system uses interrupt service routines...
The post 5 best practices for writing interrupt service routines appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jacob Beningo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Encryption at rest for Apache Kafka]]></title>
        <id>a7bd3f0f-f8f9-4b69-a4e7-b575cbcd0921</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/05/encryption-rest-apache-kafka"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past decade Apache Kafka has become a commonly deployed piece of data infrastructure. It is considered by many to be the de facto standard for low latency, high throughput, scale out message processing, and data streaming. Kafka is also a data store and therefore subject to many of the same security and compliance obligations as databases, such as encryption at rest.
Encrypting Kafka data at rest 
Apache Kafka does not provide a facility for encrypting sensitive data at rest. Infrastructure providers usually compensate for this by deploying file system or volume encryption. However, encrypting at this level has drawbacks. First, operations personnel and services with file system permissions may view data content. Secondly, file system and volume encryption is not differentiated wi…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tom Bentley</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multicluster replication in Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation S3]]></title>
        <id>660179fe-5725-4644-a799-c3783fcc6225</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/05/multicluster-replication-red-hat-openshift-data-foundation-s3"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This tutorial is designed for developers and who are managing cloud-native applications on Red Hat OpenShift. If you're looking to enhance data availability and resilience across multiple clusters, this guide will walk you through the process of setting up S3-compatible multi-cluster replication using OpenShift Data Foundation's NooBaa. By following these steps, you'll be able to ensure data is replicated across clusters, improving redundancy and fault tolerance in your infrastructure.
Red Hat OpenShift Data Foundation is a comprehensive storage solution that integrates with OpenShift to provide persistent storage for containerized applications. It supports a variety of storage types, including block, file, and object storage, and is designed to be highly scalable and resilient. OpenShift …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alberto Filice</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why your errno value isn't printing in GDB—and what to do about it]]></title>
        <id>1d7b25df-8a39-4351-bb45-47d9f9dbb91b</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/05/why-your-errno-value-isnt-printing-gdb-and-what-do-about-it"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When debugging a program using the GNU Project Debugger (GDB), printing the value of errno should be easy, but sometimes it isn't. This article explains why printing errno might not work and what to do when it doesn't.
This article will focus on systems with runtime environments which use the GNU C Library (glibc) as the C library; printing errno on other modern multi-threaded systems which use a different C library implementation should be similar, though some of the details for accessing errno (when it doesn't just work) might be different. This article with be most applicable to GNU/Linux systems running either the Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) or Fedora distributions. Much of the article should be applicable to other popular Linux distributions too, but be aware that package names ma…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kevin Buettner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[라인야후 사태, 국가주의 프레임을 넘어서]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109641</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109641"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T02:52:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[기고] 라인야후 사태를 공공성과 인권 관점에서 살펴봅니다. 오병일(진보네트워크센터 대표)은 국가주의 프레임에 빠져 라인야후 사태를 보면 타국의 보호주의를 비난하면서 자국의 보호주의를 요구하는 모순에 빠질 수 있다고 지적합니다. 라인야후 대주주인 A홀딩스의 네이버 지분을 매각하라는 일본 정부의 요구를 둘러싸고 논란이 뜨겁다. 한국의 기업과 기술을 강탈하려는 일본과 이를 수수방관하는 듯한 한국 정부에 대한 비난의 목소리가 높다. 급기야 일본 정부의...
The post 라인야후 사태, 국가주의 프레임을 넘어서 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>오병일</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사이먼 오웬스, 유튜브가 헐리우드를 계속 압도할 수 있는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594849</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594849/%ec%9c%a0%ed%8a%9c%eb%b8%8c%ea%b0%80-%ed%97%90%eb%a6%ac%ec%9a%b0%eb%93%9c-%ec%95%95%eb%8f%84-%ec%9d%b4%ec%9c%a0"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T01:33:42.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/5, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594836</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594836/6-4-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T00:43:50.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What we've been reading in May (2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/may-2024-roundup</id>
        <link href="https://interrupt.memfault.com/blog/may-2024-roundup"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here are the articles, videos, and tools that we’ve been excited about this May.
Continue reading…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Interrupt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 주가조작, “탈탈 털었는데 안 나온 것” 아니었다: 슬로우레터 6월5일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109617</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109617"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T22:19:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[김건희 서면 진술서, 소명 부족했다. 탈탈 털지 않았다. 쟁점과 현안. 산유국의 꿈? 반응이 미지근한 이유. 구멍가게 수준? 세계적인 시추 전문가? 전공의 복귀 출구 전략. 더 깊게 읽기. 국가채무 비율 줄여서 발표했나. 민주당의 감세 드라이브, “상속세 부담 줄인다.” 다르게 읽기. 쌀값이 오르는 이유. 물가 2.7%라는데 농산물은 19% 급등. 해법과 대안. 의대 증원 이후가 문제다. 4대 개혁...
The post 김건희 주가조작, “탈탈 털었는데 안 나온 것” 아니었다: 슬로우레터 6월5일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Volatile, DCL, and synchronization pitfalls in Java]]></title>
        <id>https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1128/</id>
        <link href="https://pvs-studio.com/en/blog/posts/java/1128/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if common knowledge is actually more nuanced, and old familiar things like Double-checked locking are quite controversial? Examining the code of real projects gives this kind of thought. In this...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>from pvs-studio.com</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing the Google Developer Program: Unlock New Opportunities]]></title>
        <id>https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-the-google-developer-program/</id>
        <link href="https://developers.googleblog.com/en/introducing-the-google-developer-program/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:13:44.216Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Google Developer Program gives developers access to a range of new tools and benefits,  to allow them to discover and explore all the Google sponsored communities we already offer.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Google Developers Blog</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mike Karels has passed away]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977070/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977070/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T20:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We have just received the
sad news that longtime core BSD developer Mike Karels has died; he will
certainly be missed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Incus 6.2 released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977059/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977059/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T19:31:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 6.2 of the Incus container-management system is out.  "This
release contains the second wave of changes contributed by students of the
University of Texas at Austin and a few other features and
improvements."  The features include a new incus top
command, a new API for system load information, and more.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why hardware security underlies AI progress]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482434</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/why-hardware-security-underlies-ai-progress/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T18:54:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The security of AI chips must be ironclad so models behave as expected and end users are protected from harm. Semiconductors in AI have been...
The post Why hardware security underlies AI progress appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jason Oberg</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New site feature: comment subthread hiding]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/977033/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/977033/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T18:14:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the recent discussion on commenting at
LWN, several readers asked for the ability to hide subthreads of a long
comment stream.  That feature has just been added; it is also integrated
with the three comment-display modes and with comment filtering, removing
the need for JavaScript for filtering.  Hiding is not persistent; no extra
data is stored at either end.

Give it a try; if you have comments on the new mechanism, this is the place
to put them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Handling the NFS change attribute]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975863/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975863/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T15:39:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The saga of the i_version field for inodes, which tracks the
occurrence of changes
to the data or metadata of a file, continued in a discussion at the 2024 Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit.  In a session led by
Jeff Layton, who has been doing a lot the work on changing the semantics and functioning of
i_version over the years, he updated attendees on the status of the effort since a session at last year's summit.  His summary
was that things are
"pretty much where we started last year", but the discussion this time
pointed to some possible ways forward.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Applying robot operating system drivers for motor controllers]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embedded.com/?p=4482430</id>
        <link href="https://www.embedded.com/applying-robot-operating-system-drivers-for-motor-controllers/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T14:26:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article will give an overview on how to use and integrate ROS drivers in applications, products, and systems, enabling faster technology evaluation and avoiding...
The post Applying robot operating system drivers for motor controllers appeared first on Embedded.com.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Krizelle Paulene Apostol, Jamila Macagba, and Maggie Maralit</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] An instruction-level BPF memory model]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976071/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976071/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T13:57:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are few topics as arcane as memory models, so it was a pleasant surprise
when the double-length session on the BPF memory model at the
Linux Storage,
Filesystem, Memory Management, and BPF Summit turned out to be
understandable. Paul McKenney led the session, although he was clear that the
work he was presenting was also due to Puranjay Mohan, who unfortunately could
not attend the summit.
BPF does not actually have a formalized memory model yet;
instead it has relied on a history of talks like this one and a general informal understanding.
Unfortunately, ignoring memory models does not make them go away, and this has
already caused at least one BPF-related bug on weakly-ordered architectures.
Figuring out what a formal memory model for BPF should define was the focus of
McKenney's talk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>daroc</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Tuesday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976977/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976977/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T13:35:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by Mageia (chromium-browser-stable, git, libreoffice, microcode, python-requests, webkit2, and wireshark), Oracle (container-tools:ol8, glibc, go-toolset:ol8, idm:DL1 and idm:client, less, python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9, ruby:3.0, and virt:ol and virt-devel:rhel), Red Hat (nodejs, nodejs:18, python-idna, and ruby:3.1), and SUSE (389-ds, ffmpeg, ffmpeg-4, gnutls, gstreamer-plugins-base, libhtp, mariadb104, poppler, python-python-jose, squid, and unbound).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[환자는 없었다: 정부 vs. 의료계 보도 22,224건 분석]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109592</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109592"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:23:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[사직서를 내고 진료현장을 이탈한 전공의 대부분은 전문의 자격취득을 위한 복귀 시한인 5월 20일에도 돌아오지 않았습니다. 의사 수를 늘려 의료공백을 개선하겠다는 정부 정책이 무색하게 당장 내년부터 의료인력 부족이 예고된 것이나 다름없는데요. 의료계 이탈은 정부가 2월 6일 지방의료 붕괴와 필수의료 강화 등을 위해 2025년 대입부터 의대 정원을 대폭 늘리겠다고 선포하면서 시작됐습니다. 의료계는 정부 정책에 항의하며 의료현장을 떠났고,...
The post 환자는 없었다: 정부 vs. 의료계 보도 22,224건 분석 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민주언론시민연합</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BofA 마이클 하트넷, 금리 인하 후 행동강령 : 채권 매수와 주식 매도]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594834</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594834/%ea%b8%88%eb%a6%ac%ec%9d%b8%ed%95%98-%ed%9b%84-%ec%a3%bc%ec%8b%9d-%eb%a7%a4%eb%8f%84"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T23:53:43.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[뉴페@스프] 계속 심각하니 어느새 간과하는 걸까, 저출생 문제]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79136</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/03/npsp_birthdearth/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_birthdearth"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T22:59:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[* 뉴스페퍼민트는 SBS의 콘텐츠 플랫폼 스브스프리미엄(스프)에 뉴욕타임스 칼럼을 한 편씩 선정해 번역하고, 글에 관한 해설을 쓰고 있습니다. 그 가운데 저희가 쓴 해설을 스프와 시차를 두고 소개합니다. 스브스프리미엄에서는 뉴스페퍼민트의 해설과 함께 칼럼 번역도 읽어보실 수 있습니다. **오늘 소개하는 글은 4월 15일 스프에 쓴 글입니다. 로스 더우댓(Ross Douthat)은 지난해 말 대한민국은 사라지고 있는가?라는 칼럼을 쓴 뉴욕타임스 칼럼니스트입니다. 제목만으로도 당연히 한국에서 큰 관심을 받을 수밖에 없던 글인데, 많은 선진국에서 공통으로 나타나는 저출생 경향이 유난히 두드러지는 나라가 → 더 보기]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ingppoo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[140억 배럴 산유국의 꿈? 어느 신문이 가장 흥분했나: 슬로우레터 6월4일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109542</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109542"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T21:53:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[산유국의 꿈, 어느 신문이 가장 흥분했나. 삼성전자 시가총액 5배라고? 동해 가스전의 씁쓸한 추억. 7광구는? 천공의 예언? 쟁점과 현안. VIP 격노설, 해명을 내놨는데. 9.19합의 효력 정지, 완충 구역이 사라졌다. 더 깊게 읽기. 이원석이 “성역은 없다”고 한 이유. “은밀하게 전달만 해드리고 싶어요.” 오늘 전공의 사표 받는다. 다르게 읽기. 탄핵을 정치적 반전 카드로? 1일1특검, 어제는 대북송금 수사 특검....
The post 140억 배럴 산유국의 꿈? 어느 신문이 가장 흥분했나: 슬로우레터 6월4일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LyX 2.4.0 Released]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976826/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976826/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T20:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Version 2.4.0 of the LyX
document processor has been released. LyX is a "What You See Is What You
Mean" (WYSIWYM) application that offers GUI editing of LaTeX
documents with import and export to PDF, HTML, OpenDocument, Word, and
other formats. LyX 2.4.0 is the first major release in six years, and
brings support for EPUB, DocBook 5, improved
table styles, and now uses Unicode (utf8) as its default encoding. See
the full list of new
features on the LyX wiki, and release
notes for information on known issues and caveats for those
upgrading from earlier versions of LyX.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don't Need an RTOS (Part 3)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1653.php</id>
        <link href="https://www.embeddedrelated.com/showarticle/1653.php"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T17:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least, probably not as often as you think you do. Using a preemptive RTOS can help make a system schedulable (i.e. help all of its tasks meet their deadlines) but it comes at a cost: "concurrently" running tasks can interact in unforeseen ways that cause system failures, that dreaded class of errors known as "race conditions". In part, this is because humans have difficulty thinking...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>EmbeddedRelated.com Blogs</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[[$] Debian's /tmpest in a teapot]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/975565/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/975565/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T16:16:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Debian had a major discussion
about mounting /tmp as a RAM-based tmpfs in 2012 but inertia
won out in the end. Debian systems have continued to
store temporary files on disk by default. Until now. A mere 
12 years later, the project will be switching to a RAM-based /tmp in the Debian
13 ("Trixie") release. Additionally, starting with Trixie, the
default will be to periodically clean up temporary files automatically in
/tmp and /var/tmp. Naturally, it involved a lengthy discussion first.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates for Monday]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976782/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976782/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T14:49:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security updates have been issued by AlmaLinux (python39:3.9 and python39-devel:3.9 and ruby:3.0), Debian (chromium, gst-plugins-base1.0, and kernel), Fedora (chromium, glances, glycin-loaders, gnome-tour, helix, helvum, kitty, libarchive, libipuz, librsvg2, loupe, maturin, ntpd-rs, plasma-workspace, and a huge list of Rust-based packages due to a "mini-mass-rebuild" that updated the toolchain to Rust 1.78 and picked up fixes for various pieces), Mageia (gifsicle, netatalk, openssl, python-jinja2, and unbound), Red Hat (kernel and kernel-rt), SUSE (bind, glibc, gstreamer-plugins-base, squid, and tiff), and Ubuntu (glibc).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jake</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling Backstage: A developer's guide to the CNCF project]]></title>
        <id>51e55c52-4926-439d-bb73-cefd398926b5</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/03/backstage-cncf-project"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of software development is constantly evolving. The Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF), a non-profit organization fostering open source technologies, plays a crucial role in this evolution. The CNCF acts as a hub, bringing together developers and companies to create and refine technologies specifically designed for building and running applications in the cloud. These "cloud-native" technologies emphasize scalability, resilience, and agility–essential qualities for modern software that needs to adapt to ever-changing demands.
However, the very features that make cloud-native development powerful also introduce layers of complexity. As software development teams leverage a growing ecosystem of services, APIs, and tools, developers can find themselves overwhelmed. Jugglin…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Markus Eisele</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Load testing 3scale API Management with Hyperfoil and Ansible]]></title>
        <id>9cc090d8-704b-4940-aa3c-0a4e5a30dedd</id>
        <link href="https://developers.redhat.com/articles/2024/06/03/load-testing-3scale-api-management-hyperfoil-and-ansible"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was interested in doing some load testing against Red Hat 3scale API Management. After a bit of digging around, I discovered perftest-toolkit, an open source load testing toolkit.
Figure 1 depicts an infrastructure diagram from the perftest-toolkit repository.



  
        



  

Figure 1: Infrastructure diagram showing how the the load testing tooling relates to 3scale API Management and OpenShift.

At first look I was unsure what this gave me or what it required. But after playing around with it for a while, I eventually figured it out along with a few pain points.
What do we need?
Prerequisites:

A Red Hat OpenShift Kubernetes cluster.
An instance of 3scale API Management on this cluster.
An Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instance that can connect a route on your cluster, and al…]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Austin Cunningham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[사회연대임금: 탐욕의 풍선]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=108616</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/108616"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T06:57:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[제네바 오전 8시] 이상헌(ILO 고용정책국장)의 노동과 세계 그리고 인간에 관한 이야기 인트로 & 요약 (2분) 1.스웨덴 모델인지 여부가 왜 중요한가? 스웨덴 모델인지 아닌지, 스웨덴에서 성공했는지 실패했는지는 중요하지 않다(스웨덴에서 실패했다는 지적은 대체로 사실이 아니다). 중요한 건 이제 한국은 외국 모델을 수입할 수준은 이미 넘어섰다. 우리 제도에서 어떻게 적용될 수 있을지에 관한 논의가 중요하다. 2.노조와 메커니즘의 문제....
The post 사회연대임금: 탐욕의 풍선 appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>민노씨</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6/3, 월가의 투자의견 및 주가 전망 보고서]]></title>
        <id>https://happist.com/?p=594827</id>
        <link href="https://happist.com/594827/6-3-%ec%9b%94%ea%b0%80%ec%9d%98-%ed%88%ac%ec%9e%90%ec%9d%98%ea%b2%ac"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>happist</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI와 같이 살아도 ‘외로움’을 느낄 수밖에 없는 이유]]></title>
        <id>https://newspeppermint.com/?p=79462</id>
        <link href="https://newspeppermint.com/2024/06/02/npsp_aillmloneliness/?utm_source=rss&amp;utm_medium=rss&amp;utm_campaign=npsp_aillmloneliness"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T00:05:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[인공지능이 나날이 발달하면서 인간의 외로움도 AI 챗봇이 해결해주는 날이 머지않아 오리라는 기대 섞인 말도 많이 나옵니다. 그러나 인공지능 기술이 아무리 좋아져도 다른 사람과 관계에서 오는 연결감을 해소해주는 데는 한계가 있을 수 있다는 지적도 있습니다. 제시카 그로스의 칼럼을 번역하고, 연결감과 ‘나를 필요로 하는 경험’에 대해 예일대학교 정신의학과 나종호 교수에게 해설을 청했습니다. 전문 번역: ‘그녀’라면 여친보다 나을 것이라고?… AI가 외로움까지 해결할 수 있을까 해설: AI와 같이 살아도 ‘외로움’을 느낄 수밖에 없는 이유는 이렇다]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>NewsPeppermint</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kernel prepatch 6.10-rc2]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976498/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976498/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T23:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The second 6.10 kernel prepatch is out for
testing.  "Nothing feels particularly odd, but rc2 is usually fairly small and
people are only starting to find regressions.

So please go test some more."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>corbet</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[지지율 21% 윤석열, 그날 꼭 술을 마셨어야 했나: 슬로우레터 6월3일.]]></title>
        <id>https://slownews.kr/?p=109475</id>
        <link href="https://slownews.kr/109475"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T22:09:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[윤석열 지지율 21%. 쟁점과 현안. 종합부동산세 “개편” 꺼냈더니 “폐지”. 가뜩이나 세수 줄어드는데. 종부세와 재산세를 합친다면? 한국판 ‘하우스 오브 카드’, 복수가 시작된다. 다르게 읽기. 최태원-노소영 재산 분할의 세 가지 관점. 노태우 비자금 팩트체크. “버립니다.” 더 깊게 읽기. 김정숙 특검법? 여당이 검찰 못 믿나. “이재명이 대통령처럼 보이기 시작한다.” 어떤 중산층을 말하나. 오물 풍선과 대북 확성기. 오늘의 TMI....
The post 지지율 21% 윤석열, 그날 꼭 술을 마셨어야 했나: 슬로우레터 6월3일. appeared first on 슬로우뉴스..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>이정환</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obtaining source code for training LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://shape-of-code.com/?p=8824</id>
        <link href="https://shape-of-code.com/2024/06/02/obtaining-source-code-for-training-llms/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T21:41:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Training a large language model to be a coding assistant requires huge amounts of source code. Github is a very well known publicly available repository of code, and various sites have created substantial collections of GitHub repos, e.g., GitTorrent, and Google’s BigQuery. Since 2017 the Software Heritage has been amassing the world’s source code, and […]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Derek Jones</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fedora Linux 40 election results]]></title>
        <id>https://lwn.net/Articles/976447/</id>
        <link href="https://lwn.net/Articles/976447/"/>
        <updated>2024-06-02T18:44:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Fedora Project has announced
the results of the Fedora Linux 40 election cycle. Four seats were
open on the Fedora
Engineering Steering Committee (FESCo), and the winners are Stephen
Gallagher, Neal Gompa, Michel Lind, and Fabio Valentini. The Fedora
Council had two seats open, and the winners
are Aleksandra Fedorova and Adam Samalik. One seat was open on the
Fedora Mindshare
Committee, and the winner
is Sumantro Mukherjee. Four seats were open for the first election to select
members of the EPEL
Steering Committee, which went to Troy
Dawson, Kevin Fenzi, Carl George, and Jonathan Wright.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>jzb</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space]]></title>
        <id>https://bluefruit.co.uk/?p=14079</id>
        <link href="https://bluefruit.co.uk/quality/aerospace-product-development-challenges/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-04T15:14:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The space industry is among the most innovative in the world. Propelled by communications, exploration, and R&D possibilities, it is estimated […]
The post 5 ways aerospace product development solves real-time challenges in space appeared first on Bluefruit Software.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Tristan Jago</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>